"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1394","2013-07-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164944","164944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1395","2013-07-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164945","164945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1396","2013-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164946","164946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1397","2013-07-11","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-07-09","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how much his Office spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164947","164947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1398","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164948","164948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1399","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164949","164949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1400","2013-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164950","164950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1401","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164951","164951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1402","2013-07-11","Women and Equalities","2013-07-09","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much the Government Equalities Office spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164952","164952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1403","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164953","164953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1404","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164954","164954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1405","2013-07-11","House of Commons Commission","2013-07-09","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross, representing the House of Commons Commission, how much the House of Commons Commission spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164955","164955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1406","2013-07-11","Department for International Development","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164956","164956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1407","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164957","164957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1408","2013-07-11","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164959","164959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1409","2013-07-11","Scotland Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164961","164961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1411","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many known hepatitis C victims have died in each of the last five years in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164983","164983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1412","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many known hepatitis C victims have received financial assistance via charities set up by the Government since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164984","164984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1413","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many known hepatitis C victims have been given financial assistance throughout the UK; and what the average amount of such support is.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164985","164985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1414","2013-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many reservists from Cardiff South and Penarth constituency currently attend HMS Cambria; and how many of these will be expected to relocate to the proposed new Naval Reserve base in Cardiff.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165019","165019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1415","2013-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Written Statement of 4 July 2013, Official Report, column 61WS, on reserve basing statement clarification, when he intends to write to the hon. Member for Cardiff South and Penarth on the proposed new Naval Reserve base in Cardiff and the effect of his announced changes on HMS Cambria.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165020","165020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1416","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164962","164962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1417","2013-07-11","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164963","164963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1418","2013-07-11","Wales Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164964","164964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1419","2013-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164965","164965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1420","2013-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Written Statement of 3 July 2013, Official Report, column 49WS, on army reserve (structure and basing), what discussions he has had with Cardiff County Council on the siting of any new Naval Reserve facility.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165021","165021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1421","2013-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Written Statement of 3 July 2013, Official Report, column 49WS, on army reserve (structure and basing), what plans he has for Naval Reserve facilities in (a) Cardiff County, (b) Vale of Glamorgan County and (c) Wales.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165022","165022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1422","2013-07-12","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign national criminals were deported from the UK in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165025","165025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1423","2013-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assurances Ministers of his Department will seek during meetings with President Thein Sein regarding the treatment of the Rohingya Muslim community within Burma.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165045","165045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1424","2013-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which Ministers of his Department will be present in meetings with President Thein Sein during his upcoming visit to the UK; and what the focus of each of the scheduled meetings is likely to be.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165046","165046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1425","2013-07-12","Prime Minister","2013-07-09","To ask the Prime Minister, what the Government's aim is for the upcoming visit of President Thein Sein to the UK; and what the scope of any discussions that will be held between representatives of the Burmese and British governments during that visit will be.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165053","165053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1426","2013-07-12","Prime Minister","2013-07-09","To ask the Prime Minister, what specific assurances he will be seeking from President Thein Sein regarding the treatment of the Rohingya Muslim community within Burma during his upcoming visit to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165054","165054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1427","2013-07-11","Attorney General","2013-07-09","To ask the Attorney General, on how many occasions local authorities refused requests for third party disclosure made by the Crown Prosecution Service in 2012-13.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164993","164993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1428","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in what ways the planned additional £4 million investment in his Department's operations in China will increase the UK's reach, understanding and influence in that country.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165003","165003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1429","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the UK is taking to progress international debate about cyber-security other than through participation in the UN Group of Government Experts.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165004","165004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1430","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on adoption of the UN Group of Environmental Experts report at the UN General Assembly.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165005","165005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1431","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the potential cost to the consumer of an additional two billion cubic metre UK gas storage facility.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165006","165006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1432","2013-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the revenue raised as a result of the cessation of contracted out pensions and increase in National Insurance contributions.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165001","165001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1433","2013-07-12","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on treatment given by unregulated counsellors and psychotherapists in the (a) private and (b) public sector following referrals by GPs in each of the last five years; and how many people have been referred by GPs to such counsellors and psychotherapists in the (i) private and (ii) public sector in each such year.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165029","165029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1434","2013-07-12","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints were made after raids by immigration enforcement officers in each year since 2008; and for what reasons each such complaint was made.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165032","165032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1435","2013-07-12","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the restaurants raided in 2012 by enforcement officers primarily sold (a) Indian, (b) Italian, (c) Chinese, (d) British and (e) other food.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165055","165055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1436","2013-07-12","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to received a reply to his letter of 10 June 2013 to the interim Director General, UK Visas and Immigration, on behalf of a constituent, CTS ref M8559/13.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165056","165056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1437","2013-07-12","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to received a reply to his letter of 3 June 2013 to the interim Director General, UK Visas and Immigration, on behalf of a constituent, CTS ref B15451/13.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165057","165057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1438","2013-07-12","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to received a reply to his  letter of 10 June 2013 to the interim Director General, UK Visas and Immigration, on behalf of a constituent, CTS ref B16075/13.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165058","165058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1439","2013-07-12","Cabinet Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he last published statistics on the number of (a) women, (b) ethnic minorities and (c) disabled people on public boards.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165059","165059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1440","2013-07-12","Cabinet Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) women, (b) ethnic minorities and (c) disabled people were appointed to the public boards for which he is responsible in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013 and (v) in total.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165060","165060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1441","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the efficacy of European Union Training Mission Mali.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165076","165076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1442","2013-07-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to increase participation in sports by children outside school hours.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165077","165077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14425","2013-07-11","Leader of the House","2013-07-09","To ask the Leader of the House, how much his Office spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164958","164958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1443","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to increase participation in sports by children outside school hours.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165078","165078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1444","2013-07-11","Attorney General","2013-07-09","To ask the Attorney General, how much the Serious Fraud Office has paid to Slaughter and May for the work on the defence of the damages claim brought against it by the Tchenguiz brothers to date.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165040","165040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1445","2013-07-11","Attorney General","2013-07-09","To ask the Attorney General, how much the Serious Fraud Office spent on external advocacy in (a) 2012-13 and (b) each of the seven preceding years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165041","165041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1446","2013-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether an evaluation of the incidence of TB in cattle in the badger cull pilot areas will be conducted during the pilot period.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165085","165085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1447","2013-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how humaneness will be defined in  his Department's terms of reference for the badger cull pilots.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165086","165086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1448","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of school children aged 12 to 16 years take part in at least one planned sporting activity during school hours each week.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165082","165082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1449","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many companies and organisations have signed up to the 34 pledges of his Department's Responsibility Deal.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165081","165081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1450","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of school children aged 5 to 11 years take part in at least one planned sporting activity during school hours each week.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165083","165083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1451","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many illegal workers were (a) identified, (b) arrested, (c) charged and (d) deported as a result of enforcement raids on restaurants in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165084","165084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1452","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to assist the government of Sierra Leone in tackling corruption.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165071","165071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1453","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to work with her European counterparts on tackling illicit manufacture and trafficking of ammunition.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165072","165072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1454","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the efficacy of European Union Training Mission Somalia.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165073","165073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1455","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is providing to the government of Nigeria to assist in tackling terrorist threats in that country.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165074","165074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1456","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is providing to the government of Mali to assist in fighting separatist rebels in that country.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165075","165075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1457","2013-07-12","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with (a) the Secretary of State for International Development, (b) the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs and (c) representatives of Barclays Bank on that bank's decision to suspend money transfer services; and what his policy is on that matter.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165111","165111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1458","2013-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effects of the single tier pension scheme on women born between 1951 and 1953.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165112","165112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1459","2013-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) men and (b) women born between 1951 and 1953 who will be at a financial disadvantage as a result of the implementation of the single tier pensions scheme.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165113","165113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1462","2013-07-15","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 25 April 2013, Official Report, column 1106W, on antibiotics, when the five-year antimicrobial strategy and action plan will be published; what assessment he has made of the findings reported in Science Transitional Medicine 2013, Vol. 5, Issue 192, on the effects of excessive or chronic use of antibiotics on those with mitochondrial disease; and whether concurrent use of N-Acetyl-L-Cysteine with antibiotic treatment is authorised by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence for those with mitochondrial disease.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165126","165126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156","2013-07-12","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on which occasions the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency (DVLA) has had to correct information given in response to freedom of information requests (FoIRs) related to private car parking companies; and on which occasions the Information Commissioner's Office has investigated information provided by the DVLA in response to FoIRs.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164930","164930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/202","2013-07-11","Cabinet Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much No. 10 Downing Street spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164960","164960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2031","2013-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will take steps to record the number of people referred to food banks by Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165106","165106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/415","2013-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on enforcement of the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164865","164865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421","2013-07-11","Church Commissioners","2013-07-09","To ask the Honourable Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, how much the Church Commissioners spent on contracts with (a) Deloitte, (b) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (c) KPMG and (d) Ernst and Young in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164943","164943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5442","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support maternity wards facing closure.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164794","164794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5443","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that there are sufficient trained midwives to cope with the UK's increasing birth rate.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164795","164795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5444","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that midwives are retained by the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164796","164796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5445","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that newly qualified midwives are able to find suitable positions in maternity units.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164797","164797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5531","2013-07-12","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Finance Minister about money allocated to infrastructure projects in Scotland on which work is ready to begin; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164926","164926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5532","2013-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current status of the Royal Naval buildings in Greenock is; and what future plans he has for these buildings.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165000","165000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5533","2013-07-12","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to protect blind and partially sighted pedestrians from quiet and hybrid vehicles.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164997","164997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5534","2013-07-12","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure a minimum noise level for all vehicles.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164998","164998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5535","2013-07-12","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps so that it is mandatory for car manufacturers to install an alert system in all hybrid and electric vehicles.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164999","164999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5600","2013-07-11","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2013-07-09","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, on how many occasions (a) Government Ministers and (b) Treasury officials have had meetings with the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority in each month of 2013 to date.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165128","165128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5601","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what advice she has given to officials inspecting British passports where the surnames of children differ from that of the mother.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165127","165127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5729","2013-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether and by whom the military personnel on duty in uniform at the lawn tennis championships at Wimbledon in 2013 were paid for their attendance.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165118","165118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5903","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2013, Official Report, column 659-60W, on hospitals: administration, to whom assurances following changes to the size and shape of hospital workforces and the quality and safety of patient care is maintained or improved are given; and what form they take.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164801","164801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5904","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many fully-trained paediatric nurses were employed by the NHS to serve Birmingham in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165067","165067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5905","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many fully-trained paramedics were employed by the NHS to serve Birmingham in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165068","165068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5906","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many instances of pupils being taught in temporary accommodation in (a) primary, (b) secondary and (c) sixth form colleges were recorded in Birmingham in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165089","165089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5907","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) teachers and (b) classroom assistants were employed in maintained schools in (i) the West Midlands, (ii) Birmingham and (iii) Birmingham, Selly Oak constituency in each of the last five academic years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165069","165069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5988","2013-07-12","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many applications have been made for an HM Revenue and Customs Residency Certificate in each of the last five tax years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165014","165014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5989","2013-07-12","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what comparative assessment he has made of the processing time for an HM Revenue and Customs Residency Certificate and equivalent times in other EU countries.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165015","165015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5990","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to (a) locate services from the merged Vehicle and Operator Services Agency and Driving Standards Agency in shared premises and (b) re-establish test centres instead of using private commercial properties.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165101","165101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5991","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many properties will become part of the new agency arising from the merger of the Vehicle and Operator Services Agency and the Driving Standards Agency; and what estimate he has made of the savings that will be realised from that merger.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165102","165102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5992","2013-07-12","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average waiting time was for receiving an HM Revenue and Customs Residency Certificate in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165119","165119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5993","2013-07-12","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the target waiting time was for receiving an HM Revenue and Customs Residency Certificate in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165120","165120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6328","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers employed at HMP Lincoln have been (a) made redundant and (b) given notice of redundancy between December 2012 and June 2013.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164833","164833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6329","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average ratio of prison officers to inmates in prisons in England and Wales was in June (a) 2009. (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164834","164834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6330","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidelines his Department issues to prison governors on the engagement of volunteers in prisons.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164835","164835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6331","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff were employed to perform security checks on inmates and visitors entering prisons in each prison in England and Wales, in each year from July 2008.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164836","164836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6499","2013-07-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will convene a meeting with representatives from Coventry City Football Club, the owners of the Ricoh Arena (Arena Coventry Ltd (ACL)), Coventry City Council and the Football League to negotiate an interim agreement such that Coventry can play in the Ricoh Arena in Coventry next season.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165065","165065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6500","2013-07-12","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will meet representatives from National Air Traffic Services to discuss the technical fault that occurred at the Swanwick air traffic control centre on 9 July 2013.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165121","165121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6501","2013-07-12","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will investigate the causes of the technical fault that occurred at the Swanwick air traffic control centre on 9 July 2013.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165122","165122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6502","2013-07-12","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with representatives of the (a) National Air Traffic Services and (b) Civil Aviation Authority on the reliability of the computer system at Swanwick air traffic control centre.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165123","165123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6503","2013-07-12","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received expressing concern about the computer system at Swanwick air traffic control centre.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165124","165124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6816","2013-07-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164802","164802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6817","2013-07-11","Attorney General","2013-07-09","To ask the Attorney General, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in the Law Officers' Departments used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164803","164803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6818","2013-07-11","Cabinet Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164804","164804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6819","2013-07-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164805","164805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6820","2013-07-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in her Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164806","164806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6821","2013-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164807","164807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6822","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164808","164808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6823","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164819","164819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6824","2013-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164820","164820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6825","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164821","164821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6826","2013-07-11","Women and Equalities","2013-07-09","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in the Government Equalities Office used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164822","164822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6827","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164823","164823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6828","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in her Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164824","164824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6829","2013-07-11","Department for International Development","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in her Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164825","164825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6830","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164826","164826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6831","2013-07-11","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in her Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164827","164827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6832","2013-07-11","Scotland Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164828","164828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6833","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164829","164829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6834","2013-07-11","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164830","164830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6835","2013-07-11","Wales Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164831","164831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6836","2013-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department used the facilities at Northcote House, Sunningdale Park, Berkshire  in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164832","164832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6837","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish details of the number of regional conflict Advisers employed through the Regional Pool programme in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; what estimate he has made of the likely number in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164969","164969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6838","2013-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding his Department allocated to the Conflict Pool in each year from 2010-11 to date; how much he estimates will be allocated in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164966","164966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6839","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which civil society organisations were funded through the Conflict Pool programme in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164970","164970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6840","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much funding his Department allocated to the Conflict Pool in each year from 2010-11 to date; how much he estimates will be allocated in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164967","164967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6841","2013-07-11","Department for International Development","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department allocated to the Conflict Pool in each year from 2010-11 to date; how much she estimates will be allocated in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164968","164968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6842","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the total number of staff working through Conflict Pool funding was in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164971","164971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6843","2013-07-11","Department for International Development","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment criteria her Department uses to assign projects to the Conflict Pool programme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164972","164972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6844","2013-07-12","Cabinet Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Big Society Network received assistance from his officials in completing applications for (a) Cabinet Office and (b) Big Lottery Fund funding in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165027","165027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6845","2013-07-12","Cabinet Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what complaints he has received from (a) his officials, (b) the staff, (c) charities and (d) others on working with the Big Society Network or its subsidiary charity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165028","165028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6846","2013-07-12","Cabinet Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the quality of work delivered by the Big Society Network or its subsidiary charity following receipt of funding for which his Department is responsible in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; if he will publish such assessments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165026","165026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6881","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of local authorities have reduced their expenditure on road safety since 2010.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164798","164798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6882","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has been made of the availability of lollipop people to assist children to cross roads, by local authority area; and what change there has been in the numbers of lollipop people since 2010.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165129","165129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7075","2013-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the red tape challenge on heath and safety in the agricultural sector.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164889","164889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7076","2013-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to prevent new strains of porcine epidemic diarrhoea from China and the US entering the UK.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164981","164981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7077","2013-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the UK pig sector of porcine epidemic diarrhoea from China and the US entering the UK.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164991","164991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7137","2013-07-11","Women and Equalities","2013-07-09","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will put forward amendments to the Same Sex Marriage Bill in the House of Lords to ensure that the word wife will continue to be used in statute and other official contexts to refer only to the female spouse of a heterosexual marriage and will not be redefined subsequent to the Same Sex Marriage Act to include any partner in a same sex marriage.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164799","164799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7261","2013-07-11","Department for International Development","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the humanitarian effects of the occupation of the West Bank of Palestine.","Biography information for Michael Connarty","Michael Connarty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164800","164800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7395","2013-07-11","Attorney General","2013-07-09","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of judges and magistrates on the performance of the Crown Prosecution Service.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164886","164886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7396","2013-07-11","Cabinet Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how it is decided which Ministers sit on each Cabinet Committee or Sub-Committee.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164907","164907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7397","2013-07-11","Cabinet Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what consideration is given to the respective numbers of Ministers who are members of (a) the Conservative Party and (b) the Liberal Democrat Party when deciding how many such hon. Members sit on each Cabinet Committee or Sub-Committee.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164908","164908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7579","2013-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish details of expenditure under the A respected Department programme identified in his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2011-12 in each of the last three years; and what the projected spend for each of the next three years by (a) scheme and (b) individual project is.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165016","165016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7580","2013-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish details of expenditure under the Rural Payments Agency EC funded programme identified in his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2011-12 in each of the last three years; and what the projected spend for each of the next three years by (a) scheme and (b) individual project is.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165017","165017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7581","2013-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2011-12, what amount was spent under the Strong rural communities programme in each of the last three years; and what estimate he has made of likely spend on each project and scheme under that programme in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165108","165108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7582","2013-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2011-12, what amount was spent under the A thriving farming and food sector programme in each of the last three years; and what estimate he has made of likely spend on each project and scheme under that programme in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165109","165109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7583","2013-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2011-12, what amount was spent under the A sustainable, secure and healthy food supply programme in each of the last three years; and what estimate he has made of likely spend on each project and scheme under that programme in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165110","165110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7780","2013-07-12","Prime Minister","2013-07-09","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will discuss with President Thein Sein during his visit to the UK the number of remaining political prisoners in Burma and a timetable for their release.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165047","165047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7781","2013-07-12","Prime Minister","2013-07-09","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will discuss with President Thein Sein during his visit to the UK efforts to end the conflicts in Kachin and Rakhine states and the need for full, independent and transparent investigations into the violence.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165048","165048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7782","2013-07-12","Prime Minister","2013-07-09","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will discuss the (a) role and accountability of the security forces in Burma, (b) level of sexual violence and (c) possibility of extending the Preventing Sexual Violence Initiative to Burma with President Thein Sein during his visit to the UK.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165050","165050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7783","2013-07-12","Prime Minister","2013-07-09","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will discuss with President Thein Sein the (a) treatment of the Rohingya, (b) need for unimpeded humanitarian access for all internally displaced persons, (c) reports of a two child policy imposed on the Rohingya community and (d) reviewing of the 1982 Citizenship Law; and if he will raise the Human Rights Watch report entitled, All You Can Do is Pray, with the President.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165049","165049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7784","2013-07-12","Prime Minister","2013-07-09","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will discuss with President Thein Sein during his forthcoming visit to the UK (a) the opening of an office for the UN High Commissioner for Human Rights in Burma, (b) signing the Covenant on Civil and Political Rights and (c) signing the Convention Against Torture and other Cruel, Inhuman or Degrading Treatment or Punishment.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165051","165051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7873","2013-07-11","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the number of EU Member States that tax international air travel.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164911","164911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7874","2013-07-11","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the impact on the UK economy of a reduction in air passenger duty by (a) five per cent, (b) 10 per cent, (c) 20 per cent, (d) 50 per cent and (e) 100 per cent.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164912","164912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8051","2013-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of trends in social housing rent arrears since the introduction of the under-occupancy penalty in April 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165023","165023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8052","2013-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he plans to take to improve the effectiveness of the Work Programme in helping those aged over 50 years into employment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165024","165024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8053","2013-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the trends in the number of (a) one bedroom, (b) two bedroom, (c) three bedroom and (d) four bedroom and larger void social housing properties since the introduction of the under-occupancy penalty; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164994","164994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8054","2013-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has provided to local authorities for the purpose of enforcing occupational safety and health in each of the last five years; how this amount was calculated; and how much of the funding provided was used by local authorities for this purpose.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164995","164995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8055","2013-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities in England and Wales have informed his Department that their housing rent arrears have increased following the introduction of the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164996","164996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8091","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to promote the Cycle to Work scheme.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164922","164922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8092","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Government and local authorities work together to ensure the Cycle to Work scheme helps to implement sustainable transport objectives.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164921","164921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8093","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times the cancer guarantee has been missed by hospital trusts in the last three years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164881","164881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8094","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times the cancer guarantee has been missed by Barts Health NHS Trust in the last three years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164882","164882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8095","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times the cancer guarantee has been missed by hospital trusts in London in the last three years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164883","164883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8096","2013-07-11","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the Prudential Regulation Authority will successfully oversee the continuity of the management of paying and drawing cheques.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164884","164884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8097","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the top 20 (a) best and (b) worst performing hospitals in meeting the two week cancer guarantee are.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164885","164885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8098","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish a league table of hospital trusts in London according to their performance in meeting the two-week cancer guarantee.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165066","165066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8099","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, at what point hospital trusts begin counting the length of time a patient with cancer waits to see a specialist for the purposes of the two-week cancer guarantee.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165087","165087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8113","2013-07-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will estimate the full cost to the Exchequer of restoring funding to the Arts Council to the level it would have been without the Spending Rounds of both 2010 and 2013 in the fiscal year 2015-16.","Biography information for Nadhim Zahawi","Nadhim Zahawi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165103","165103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8114","2013-07-11","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the full cost to the Exchequer of restoring funding to the Criminal Justice System, by agency, to the level it would have been without the Spending Rounds of both 2010 and 2013 in the fiscal year 2015-16.","Biography information for Nadhim Zahawi","Nadhim Zahawi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165104","165104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8115","2013-07-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the full cost to the Exchequer of restoring funding to local authorities to the level it would have been without the Spending Rounds of both 2010 and 2013 in the fiscal year 2015-16.","Biography information for Nadhim Zahawi","Nadhim Zahawi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165105","165105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8268","2013-07-12","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to improve the service provided by the Employer Checking Service.","Biography information for Simon Hughes","Simon Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164927","164927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8337","2013-07-12","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the hon. Member for West Lancashire will receive a response to her letter, CTS reference: M4151/13; and what the reasons are for the time taken to reply.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165018","165018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8550","2013-07-12","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to collect (a) data on fatal accidents caused by looped blind cords and (b) other accident and injury data.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164893","164893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8551","2013-07-12","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the proposal to create an EU-wide accident and injury database.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164894","164894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8552","2013-07-12","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department have taken to reinstate a UK-wide accident and injury database.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164895","164895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8654","2013-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the first Libyan armed forces personnel will begin basic infantry training at Bassingbourn Barracks.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165090","165090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8655","2013-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the amount that will be received from the Libyan government for training of Libyan armed forces personnel in the UK.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165091","165091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8656","2013-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what facilities Libyan armed forces personnel will visit in the UK as part of their training.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165092","165092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8657","2013-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what vetting Libyan armed forces personnel will be subject to by (a) his Department and (b) the Libyan government before they arrive in the UK for training.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165093","165093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8658","2013-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what UK assets and personnel will take part in Iceland Fighter Meet 2014.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165094","165094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8659","2013-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he last met his Icelandic counterpart; and what was discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165095","165095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8660","2013-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the combat radius of the Typhoon aircraft configured for Quick Reaction Alert Mission is.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165096","165096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8803","2013-07-12","Cabinet Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance he has issued to the Royal Parks Agency on the degree to which human rights-related matters can be taken into account when considering potential bidders for contracts.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164931","164931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8804","2013-07-12","Cabinet Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will issue guidance to non-departmental bodies and agencies on the scope for taking human rights-related matters into account when selecting contractors.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164932","164932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8938","2013-07-11","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will meet his counterpart in the Welsh Government to discuss the closure of HM Revenue and Customs enquiry centres in Wales.","Biography information for Lord Murphy of Torfaen","Paul Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164918","164918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8939","2013-07-11","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to replace HM Revenue and Customs enquiry centres in Wales.","Biography information for Lord Murphy of Torfaen","Paul Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164919","164919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8940","2013-07-11","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met his counterpart in the Welsh Government to discuss the proposed closure of HM Revenue and Customs enquiry centres in Wales.","Biography information for Lord Murphy of Torfaen","Paul Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164920","164920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9131","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the top five most expensive NHS patients have cost since May 2010.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164989","164989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9132","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people at what cost to the public purse have been fitted with gastric bands since May 2010.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164990","164990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9133","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women have been admitted to hospital for drug poisoning in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164988","164988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9134","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse of medicine use reviews has been since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165039","165039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9135","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on away days and residential training since May 2010.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165042","165042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9136","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on his Department's procurement cards since May 2010.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165043","165043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9137","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department's ministerial private offices have spent on mobile telephones  since May 2010.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165044","165044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9172","2013-07-12","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in which other EU countries those accused of criminal activities (a) need to and (b) do not need to be physically present before being charged by that country's legal authorities.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164897","164897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9176","2013-07-15","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the use of legal highs.","Biography information for Margot James","Margot James","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164851","164851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9343","2013-07-12","Home Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she plans to take to improve morale in the police.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165115","165115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9344","2013-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support is available in Barnsley Central constituency to help people with learning disabilities into work.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165116","165116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9345","2013-07-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) England received Enterprise Finance Guarantee loans from the Government between (i) May 2011 and May 2012 and (ii) May 2012 and May 2013; and what the total value of the loans guaranteed was in each case.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165117","165117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9452","2013-07-12","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library all the material prepared for officials in his Department by external consultants ahead of the Public Accounts Committee hearing on the National Programme for IT on 20 June 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164934","164934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9453","2013-07-12","Department of Health","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library all material prepared by officials of his Department for witnesses from his Department in advance of the meeting of the Public Accounts Committee on the National Programme for IT on 20 June 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165030","165030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9474","2013-07-12","HM Treasury","2013-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effects on small businesses of the decision by Barclays Bank to stop providing money transfer companies with banking services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165107","165107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9556","2013-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how his Department plans to assess the performance of the British Council's project in Sudan to train journalists working for Sudanese media and the extent to which the project has contributed towards promoting free speech in that country.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165130","165130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9557","2013-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reason his Department has reduced its Sudan unit by one member of staff; and what reports he has received about the recent upsurge of violence in Darfur, Blue Nile and South Kordofan states and continuing instability between the Republic of Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165131","165131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9722","2013-07-11","Wales Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport about road and rail infrastructure renewal in Wales.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164986","164986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9723","2013-07-11","Wales Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, when he has visited units of the armed forces based in Wales in an official capacity.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164987","164987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9724","2013-07-11","Wales Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps he is taking to promote the Big Society in Wales.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165036","165036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9725","2013-07-11","Wales Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the remit is of the Wales Office Business Advisory Group; and what has been its output to date.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165037","165037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9726","2013-07-11","Wales Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent meetings he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the Government's response to the recommendations of the Commission on Devolution in Wales.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165038","165038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9727","2013-07-11","Wales Office","2013-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps he is taking to ensure that Welsh interests are taken into consideration in the implementation of the Government's policies on employment and welfare reform.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 165100","165100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10050","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to zero rate hospices for the purposes of VAT; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164730","164730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10051","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on the value of revenue accruing to the Exchequer from VAT paid by hospices.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164731","164731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10052","2013-07-11","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2013, Official Report, column 669W, on Revenue and Customs Northern Ireland, whether he has visited Northern Ireland to discuss fuel laundering and related criminal activities.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164786","164786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10140","2013-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the case of Mohammed Roghangir, Surush Saraie, Eskandar Rezaie, Shahin Lahoodi and Massoud Rezaie who have been charged with offences arising out of their observation of their Christian faith in Iran.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164724","164724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10141","2013-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the sentence of eight years imprisonment imposed on Pastor Saeed Abedini by an Iranian court; and what recent representations he has made to Iran on this case and the need for religious toleration.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164725","164725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10277","2013-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what educational advice and support is available to mature students who wish to pursue (a) Level 2 courses, (b) Level 3 courses and (c) undergraduate degree courses.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164553","164553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10278","2013-07-10","Department for Education","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department plans to take to improve awareness of the Access to Higher Education Diploma.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164554","164554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10279","2013-07-10","Department for Education","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how frequently he meets with (a) the UK Youth Parliament and (b) young people and students to consult on his Department's policy objectives and plans.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164551","164551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10280","2013-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the murders of albino minorities in Tanzania.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164552","164552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10281","2013-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will increase links between his Department's Benefits Team and Motability to prevent claimants losing their scheme support until any benefits assessment dispute has been resolved.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164636","164636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10282","2013-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to prevent Motability from repossessing cars and other equipment from disabled claimants whose benefits assessments are currently undergoing an appeal.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164635","164635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10377","2013-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the actively seeking work criteria of the jobseeker's allowance regulations will be applied for young people aged between 18 and 24 years old enrolled on the Government's traineeships scheme.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164784","164784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10378","2013-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the 16 hour rule for study will be applied to young people aged between 18 and 24 years old enrolled on the Government's traineeship scheme and claiming jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164785","164785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10380","2013-07-12","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in (a) Wiltshire and (b) England were reported as having Lyme disease in each of the last three years; and what the incidence rate was of this disease.","Biography information for Duncan Hames","Duncan Hames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164656","164656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10618","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of new radiotherapy machines needed to allow all cancer centres in England to deliver Intensity Modulated Radiation Therapy to 24 per cent of patients as recommended by the National Radiotherapy Implementation Group by the end of 2013.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164560","164560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10619","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of HM Revenue and Customs enquiry centre customers were (a) from an ethnic minority, (b) female and (c) disabled in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164549","164549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10620","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of migrant workers used the face-to-face services provided by HM Revenue and Customs enquiry centres in (a) the East of England, (b) the East Midlands, (c) London, (d) the North East of England, (e) the North West of England, (f) Northern Ireland, (g) Scotland, (h) the South East of England, (i) the South West of England, (j) Wales and (k) the West Midlands in 2011-12.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164550","164550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10631","2013-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what improvements in human rights he will be prioritising when President Thein Sein of Burma visits the UK.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164683","164683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10778","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 6 December 2012, Official Report, columns 867-8W, on families, which relationship support programmes are being funded by the £30 million referred to in the Answer; and how many families have so far been helped by such programmes.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164574","164574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10779","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Sure Start centres offer relationship support.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164600","164600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10780","2013-07-11","Cabinet Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of people who were (a) White, (b) White British, (c) Irish, (d) Travellers of Irish heritage, (e) Gypsy/Roma, (f) any other White background, (g) White and Black Caribbean, (h) Black Caribbean, (i) White and Black African, (j) White and Asian, (k) any other mixed background, (l) Asian, (m) Pakistani, (n) Bangladeshi, (o) any other Asian background, (p) Black, (q) any other Black background, (r) Chinese and (s) any other ethnic group were married in each year since 1996.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164601","164601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10781","2013-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's publication, A study of deaths among UK Armed Forces personnel deployed to the 1982 Falklands Campaign: 1982 to 2012, how many and what proportion of (a) 3 Commando Brigade and (b) 5 Infantry Brigade who served in the Falklands campaign committed suicide in each year since 1982.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164602","164602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11072","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on exit packages for its staff in (a) 2011-12 and (b) 2012-13; and how much of this sum was spent on compulsory redundancies.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164575","164575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11073","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of violence were recorded in (a) magistrates' courts and (b) Crown courts in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011 and (iii) 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164576","164576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11074","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of those convicted of offences in relation to the disturbances in the summer of 2011 have not yet completed custodial sentences.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164577","164577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11075","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department received from the Exchequer reserve in (a) 2011-12 and (b) 2012-13; and to what use such sums were put.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164578","164578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11076","2013-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of violence involving members of families of defendants were recorded in magistrates' courts in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164514","164514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11077","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much the Prison Service spent on taxis to transport prisoners in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164609","164609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11315","2013-07-16","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the Exchequer of restoring the Future Jobs Fund in 2015-16.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164653","164653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11316","2013-07-16","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the Exchequer of extending free childcare for all three and four year olds to 17.5 hours a week in 2015-16.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164654","164654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11317","2013-07-16","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the Exchequer in 2015-16 of restoring police funding to the level it would have been without the decisions made in the 2010 Spending Review and the 2013 Spending Round.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164655","164655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11451","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's Consultation on a Draft Strategy for Achieving Officially Bovine Tuberculosis-Free Status for England published on 4 July 2013, for what reasons the UK is not following the approach used in the rest of the EU of only culling infected cattle when faced wth a herd breakdown.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164522","164522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11452","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's Consultation on a Draft Strategy for Achieving Officially Bovine Tuberculosis-Free Status for England published on 4 July 2013, for what reasons biosecurity measures will be voluntary; and what evidence was taken into account in the decision between a voluntary and mandatory approach.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164523","164523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11453","2013-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many claims to Israeli preference have been refused by HM Revenue and Customs on grounds that proof of origin accompanying the goods shows that imports have been produced in an Israeli settlement in each of the last five years for which data is available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164532","164532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11454","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposed duty to have regard to growth on the ability of Natural England to fulfil its general purpose under the Natural Environment and Rural Communities Act 2006 of ensuring that the natural environment is conserved, enhanced and managed for the benefit of present and future generations; if he will make it his policy that, in the pursuit of its advisory duties, Natural England should act with scientific integrity and impartiality in all circumstances; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164624","164624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11455","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on the conclusion of his Department's regulatory review of August 2011 in respect of the overall benefit: cost ratio of regulations implemented by his Department whose benefit to wider society has been monetised; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164746","164746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11456","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the outcome of the Triennial Review of the Environment Agency and Natural England in respect of targets for regulatory burden reduction, what consideration he has given to (a) the social, economic, environmental and health benefits of such regulation and (b) the conclusion of his Department's regulatory review of August 2011 in respect of the benefit: cost ratio of biodiversity regulations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164747","164747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11487","2013-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases of the Court of Protection were prohibited from being reported in each year since May 2005.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164562","164562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11488","2013-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many cases the Court of Protection has made an order resulting in (a) imprisonment or (b) confiscation of a defendant's possessions in each year since May 2005.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164563","164563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11489","2013-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people aged (a) 10 to 15, (b) 16 to 18 and (c) 18 to 21 years and sentenced to community orders were sentenced to (i) unpaid work for up to 300 hours, (ii) specific activities, such as developing skills or making amends to their victim, (iii) undertaking a particular programme to help change offending behaviour, (iv) prohibition from doing particular activities, (v) adherence to a curfew, requiring  the offender to be in a particular place at certain times, (vi) an exclusion requirement, prohibiting the offender from going to particular places, (vii) a residence requirement, obliging the offender to live at a particular address, (viii) mental health treatment with the offender's consent, (ix) a drug rehabilitation requirement with the offender's consent, (x) an alcohol treatment requirement with the offender's consent and (xi) supervision by the Probation Service in each year since May 2005; and how many (A) completed and (B) failed to complete their sentence in each such year.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164564","164564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11490","2013-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many decisions of the Court of Protection were appealed and how many were upheld or overturned in each year since May 2005.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164566","164566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11491","2013-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases coming before the Court of Protection were later subject to Judicial Review in each year since May 2005.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164567","164567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11492","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) longest, (b) shortest and (c) average time was for cases coming before the Court of Protection to be heard in each year since May 2005.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164571","164571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11493","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost of running the Court of Protection was in each year since May 2005.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164608","164608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11494","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost of representations on behalf of the state in cases coming before the Court of Protection was in each year since May 2005.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164610","164610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11495","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many cases the Court of Protection has made a finding of contempt of court in each year since May 2005.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164611","164611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11496","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases were considered by the Court of Protection in each year since May 2005.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164612","164612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11794","2013-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to answer Question 163024, tabled on 27 June 2013 for answer on 2 July 2013.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164717","164717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11870","2013-07-10","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make it mandatory for drivers of powerboats to wear killcords.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164541","164541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1246","2013-07-11","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he proposes it will be necessary for capital gains tax to be paid on compulsorily purchased land as a result of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164644","164644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1247","2013-07-11","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he proposes it will be necessary for inheritance tax to be paid on agricultural land which is to be compulsorily purchased as a result of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164647","164647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1248","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what aid the Government provided (a) directly and (b) via multilateral agencies to support judicial and penal reform in the Dominican Republic in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164649","164649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/125","2013-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the full cost to the Exchequer of reinstating the under-occupancy penalty in fiscal year 2015-16.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164543","164543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1268","2013-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions he has had with the Sentencing Council on sentencing guidelines for death by dangerous driving cases.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164533","164533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1269","2013-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the level of investment required to build a two billion cubic metre gas storage facility.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164537","164537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1270","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the full cost to the Exchequer of abolishing Ofgem and replacing it with a new regulator in the fiscal year 2015-16.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164538","164538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1271","2013-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of construction related jobs created by the building of a two billion cubic metre gas storage facility.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164542","164542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1272","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ban the keeping of primates as pets.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164555","164555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1273","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of flooding upon a person's mental health.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164558","164558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1274","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of flooding on insurance premiums of farmers whose (a) land, (b) livestock and (c) crops are in high risk flood areas.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164559","164559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1275","2013-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the statement of 3 July 2013, Official Report, column 923, on Reserve forces, what the effect of such changes will be in Dorset.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164561","164561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1276","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the level of subsidy per MWh to be given from the public purse to offshore wind power generation by 2020.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164573","164573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1277","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on consular assistance provided by UK embassies or consulates to people resident at addresses in Scotland in each of the last five years; what the locations of the embassies or consulates offering assistance were; and what the reasons for assistance being offered were.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164580","164580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1278","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in the Migration Refusal Pool contacted by Capita since October 2012 were subsequently found to have the right to remain in the UK.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164581","164581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1279","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with ambulance trusts on the site mapping and registration of automated external defibrillators (AED) in England and Wales; and what protocols are in place to ensure that ambulance trusts regularly replace batteries installed in public access AEDs.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164617","164617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1280","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which (a) private companies and (b) charity providers were granted Any Qualified Provider Status in England in (i) 2012 and (ii) 2013.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164618","164618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1281","2013-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage the government of the Socialist Republic of Vietnam to set a date for the visit of the UN Special Rapporteur on Freedom of Religion or Belief.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164619","164619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1282","2013-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the EU-US trade deal excludes arrangements for healthcare.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164620","164620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1283","2013-07-10","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any pinch point funding is available to assist Bournemouth Borough Council to fund a slip road from the A338.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164513","164513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1284","2013-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of (a) the performance of the Regional Growth Fund against its objectives and (b) the effect of the fund on (i) Bournemouth and (ii) Dorset; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164516","164516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1285","2013-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to the Exchequer of decreasing the universal taper rate to (a) 60 per cent and (b) 55 per cent.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164520","164520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1286","2013-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) women and (b) men were received into prison (i) for breaching a court order, (ii) for breaching bail and (iii) under sentence in (A) 2011 and (B) 2012.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164521","164521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1287","2013-07-10","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the current size of the Migration Refusal Pool is.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164524","164524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1288","2013-07-10","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many employees of the Border Force are currently under criminal investigation.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164525","164525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1289","2013-07-10","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many employees of her Department are currently under criminal investigation.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164526","164526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1290","2013-07-10","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the non-compliance notifications received in Q4 2012 were followed up with further action within that quarter.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164527","164527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1291","2013-07-10","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many immigration enforcement raids were carried out in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164528","164528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1292","2013-07-10","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) Tier 5 sponsors and (b) Tier 4 sponsors had their licences (i) revoked and (ii) suspended in Q1 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164529","164529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1293","2013-07-10","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made by Operation Nexus to date.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164530","164530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1294","2013-07-10","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Tier 2 sponsors had  their licences (a) revoked and (b) suspended in Q1 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164531","164531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1295","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the full cost to the Exchequer of restoring spending on legal aid to the level it would have been without the spending rounds of 2010 and 2013 in fiscal year 2015-16.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164544","164544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1296","2013-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of full-time permanent jobs required to support the running of a 2 billion cubic metre gas storage facility.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164545","164545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1297","2013-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the benefit to consumers that will be provided by an additional 2 billion cubic metre gas storage facility.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164548","164548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1298","2013-07-11","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will set out the expected spending profile over time of the total infrastructure plans published in investing in Britain's future disaggregating (a) roads, (b) rail, (c) energy, (d) science and innovation, (e) housing, (f) digital communications, (g) local growth measures and (h) other sectors.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164572","164572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1299","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what measures to reduce the cost of offshore wind power generation to £100 per MWh by 2020 recommended by the Offshore Wind Cost Reduction Task Force he has implemented to date.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164613","164613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1300","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, at what level per MWh the strike prices for offshore wind power generation have been set for (a) 2018, (b) 2019 and (c) 2020, expressed in 2012 prices.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164614","164614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1301","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress has been made in reducing the cost of offshore wind power generation to £100 per MWh by 2020.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164615","164615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1302","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints have been received about the Capita contract to contact persons in the Migration Refusal Pool since October 2012.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164587","164587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1303","2013-07-10","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on how many pelican crossings and puffin crossings there are on roads in England and Wales.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164621","164621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1304","2013-07-10","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for which classes of young people who are (a) UK citizens and (b) EU nationals resident temporarily in the UK are those looking after them not liable for Disclosure and Barring Service checks; and what differences there are based on the nationality of the young people concerned.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164622","164622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1305","2013-07-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to increase the representation of (a) women, (b) people with disabilities and (c) ethnic minorities on the boards of public bodies falling within his Department's area of responsibility.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164603","164603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1306","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in the Migration Refusal Pool have (a) left the UK voluntarily and (b) been removed from the UK since October 2012.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164593","164593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1307","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in the Migration Refusal Pool Capita have contacted since October 2012.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164594","164594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1308","2013-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much he expects will be saved by the closure of the Territorial Army base in Bishop Auckland.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164595","164595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1309","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many restaurants were raided by enforcement officers in 2012.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164596","164596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1310","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the operational differences between the Older Live Cases Unit and its predecessor the Case Assurance and Audit Unit are; and what the reasons are for such differences.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164599","164599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1311","2013-07-10","Cabinet Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Charities Act 2006 for the purpose of derogating provisions currently used to limit the activities of religious groups.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164643","164643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1312","2013-07-11","Cabinet Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to increase the representation of (a) women, (b) people with disabilities and (c) ethnic minorities on the boards of public bodies falling within his Department's area of responsibility.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164604","164604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1313","2013-07-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to increase the representation of (a) women, (b) people with disabilities and (c) ethnic minorities on the boards of public bodies falling within her Department's area of responsibility.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164605","164605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1314","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase the representation of (a) women, (b) people with disabilities and (c) ethnic minorities on the boards of public bodies falling within his Department's area of responsibility.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164606","164606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1315","2013-07-11","Women and Equalities","2013-07-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to increase the representation of (a) women, (b) people with disabilities and (c) ethnic minorities on the boards of public bodies falling within the Government Equalities Office's area of responsibility.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164607","164607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1316","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) his predecessors and (b) his Department received expressing concerns about Basildon and Thurrock University Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust in each year prior to May 2010, since the foundation of that trust.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164690","164690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1317","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) his predecessors and (b) his Department received expressing concerns about Blackpool Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust in each year prior to May 2010, since the foundation of that trust.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164691","164691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1318","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) his predecessors and (b) his Department received expressing concerns regarding Buckinghamshire Healthcare NHS Trust in each year prior to May 2010, since the foundation of that trust.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164692","164692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1319","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) his predecessors and (b) his Department received expressing concerns regarding Colchester Hospital University NHS Foundation Trust in each year prior to May 2010, since the foundation of that trust.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164694","164694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/132","2013-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has received reports on the discussions that the UK video on demand regulator ATVOD is having with UK financial institutions to consider whether it is possible to block payments from the UK to the operators of non-UK websites which appear to be breaking the Obscene Publications Acts by allowing children to access explicit hardcore pornography; what the Government's policy is on this matter; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164732","164732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1320","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) his predecessors and (b) his Department received expressing concerns regarding the Dudley Group NHS Foundation Trust in each year prior to May 2010, since the foundation of that trust.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164695","164695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1321","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) his predecessors and (b) his Department received expressing concerns regarding East Lancashire Hospitals NHS Trust in each year prior to May 2010, since the foundation of that trust.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164696","164696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1322","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) his predecessors and (b) his Department received expressing concerns regarding George Eliot Hospitals NHS Trust in each year prior to May 2010, since the foundation of that trust.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164697","164697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1323","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) his predecessors  and (b) his Department received expressing concerns regarding Medway NHS Foundation Trust in each year prior to May 2010, since the foundation of that trust.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164698","164698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1324","2013-07-11","Department for International Development","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what information she has on reports of cholera cases in camps for displaced Rohingya people in Burma.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164707","164707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1325","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) his predecessors and (b) his Department received expressing concerns about North Cumbria University Hospitals NHS Trust in each year prior to May 2010, since the foundation of that trust.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164699","164699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1326","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) his predecessors and (b) his Department received expressing concerns regarding North Lincolnshire and Goole Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust in each year prior to May 2010, since the foundation of that trust.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164700","164700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1327","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) his predecessors and (b) his Department received expressing concerns regarding Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust in each year prior to May 2010, since the foundation of that trust.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164701","164701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1328","2013-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, who has been appointed as a  Scotland Leadership Fellow by the Economic and Social Research Council; what funding has been made available to support their fellowships; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164681","164681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1329","2013-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of five to 16 year olds take part in at least one planned sport activity per week.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164684","164684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1330","2013-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of her Department's budget is allocated to grassroots sports in England.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164685","164685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1331","2013-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of five to 16 year olds taking part in at least one planned sport activity per week.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164686","164686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1332","2013-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons human rights lead at the Embassy in Burma has been downgraded to the third political officer position.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164687","164687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1333","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the legal obligations of the UK Government under Article 76 of the Fourth Geneva Convention with regards to investigating (a) the directors of and (b) the corporate entity of G4S plc for aiding and abetting breaches of the Convention in the transfer of Palestinian detainees from the West Bank.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164709","164709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1334","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) his predecessors and (b) his Department received expressing concerns regarding Tameside Hospital NHS Foundation Trust in each year prior to May 2010, since the foundation of that trust.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164702","164702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1335","2013-07-11","Department for International Development","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what healthcare facilities are available in each of the Rohingya internally displaced persons camps in Burma.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164710","164710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1336","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) his predecessors and (b) his Department received expressing concerns regarding United Lincolnshire Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust in each year prior to May 2010, since the foundation of that trust.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164703","164703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1337","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the cost to the public purse of the visit of Burma's President Thein Sein and his delegation to the UK will be.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164712","164712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1338","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) his predecessors and (b) his Department received expressing concerns regarding Burton Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust in each year prior to May 2010, since the foundation of that trust.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164693","164693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1339","2013-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual pay settlement for the armed forces was between 1997 and 2010.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164741","164741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1341","2013-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the annual pay settlement for local government workers has been since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164742","164742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1342","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the annual pay settlement for the Civil Service has been since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164743","164743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1343","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual pay settlement in the NHS has been since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164744","164744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1344","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual pay settlement for doctors and consultants paid from the public purse has been since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164745","164745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1346","2013-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what grants have been awarded and to whom as part of the Economic and Social Research Council research programme into pre and post referendum investment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164726","164726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1347","2013-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, to whom grants have been awarded by the Economic and Social Research Council as part of their research programme into the future of the UK and Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164727","164727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1348","2013-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what grants have been awarded by the Economic and Social Research Council to undertake research work into the future of the UK and Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164728","164728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1349","2013-07-10","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking (a) to tackle breaches of the Obscene Publications Acts by non-UK websites which provide explicit hardcore pornography equivalent to that classified R18 by the British Board of Film Classification which is downloaded in the UK and (b) to put in place suitable age verification measures to prevent children accessing such material.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164729","164729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1350","2013-07-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much Broadband Delivery UK requires in annual funding for it to carry out its responsibilities.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164752","164752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1351","2013-07-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding her Department is providing through Broadband Delivery UK to help meet her Department's objectives for change in broadband provision in the UK.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164753","164753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14424","2013-07-10","Leader of the House","2013-07-08","To ask the Leader of the House, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Office spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164673","164673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/149","2013-07-10","Cabinet Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many applicants shortlisted for the role of Director of Public Prosecutions were (a) women and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164517","164517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many properties with home insurance have (a) only buildings insurance, (b) only contents insurance and (c) have both buildings and contents insurance.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164556","164556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/20","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many domestic properties (a) have and (b) do not have home insurance.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164557","164557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2028","2013-07-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what contribution he expects the Green Investment Bank to make to green growth.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164479","164479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/21","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will provide a breakdown of the households that do not have home insurance by (a) total household income, (b) property ownership type, (c) number of people who reside in the household and (d) length of residence at the property.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164640","164640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/22","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will rank by (a) constituency, (b) local authority and (c) electoral ward the proportion of properties in each such area without home insurance.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164641","164641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment he has made of levels of investment in energy infrastructure.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164496","164496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/54","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people resident in Scotland hold a UK passport.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164579","164579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5599","2013-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it is his intention that the expansion of the Army Reserve will include the formation of new military bands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164783","164783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5670","2013-07-10","Wales Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on the effects on small and medium-sized enterprises in Wales of late payment by clients.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164623","164623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5748","2013-07-11","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on how much income is generated from online newspaper downloads to tablets and other mobile devices.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164652","164652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6122","2013-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the effects on levels of rent arrears reported by registered social landlords in (a) Wales, (b) Scotland and (c) each region of England in (i) April 2012, (ii) May 2012, (iii) June 2012, (iv) April 2013, (v) May 2013 and (vi) June 2013 of the changes made in housing benefit rules which took effect on 1 April 2013.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164565","164565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6191","2013-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the geographic extent is of the recruitment area of each reserve force base in Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164518","164518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6192","2013-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the name is of each reserve force base of each service in Wales; how many reservists attend each such base regularly; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164519","164519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6193","2013-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2013, Official Report, column 1117W, on defence support group, for what reasons agency workers were recruited from 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164546","164546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6194","2013-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2013, Official Report, column 1117W, on defence support group and the Answer of 14 May 2013, Official Report, columns 151-2W, on defence support group, how many agency workers are employed at (a) Ashchurch, (b) Bovington and (c) Donnington; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164547","164547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6195","2013-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Statement of 3 July 2013, Official Report, columns 923-5, on reserve forces, what estimate he has made of the cost of closing each of the (a) 35 Territorial Army centres and (b) three Naval Reserve centres identified for closure.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164734","164734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6196","2013-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recruits were attached to each of the (a) 35 Territorial Army centres and (b) three Naval Reserve centres identified for closure in each of the last five years; how many new recruits enlisted at each such centre in each such year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164735","164735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6362","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2013, Official Report, columns 331-2W, on the Hunting Act 2004, what proportion of the responses referred to in the Answer were (a) in favour and (b) against the repeal of the Hunting Act 2004.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164733","164733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6363","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings and discussions he and his officials have attended in the last 12 months on the potential repeal of the Hunting Act 2004.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164723","164723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6495","2013-07-15","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Public Private Partnership infrastructure projects have been assisted through the temporary lending programme announced in July 2012; and what the total value of the support provided so far is.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164720","164720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6496","2013-07-15","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which departmental capital budgets have been used to fund loans advanced through the temporary lending programme for Public Private Partnership infrastructure projects announced in June 2012.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164721","164721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6497","2013-07-15","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the administrative costs to lenders for the implementation and running of the Help to Buy mortgage guarantee scheme.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164722","164722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6498","2013-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses have received support through the Export Refinancing Facility.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164754","164754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6596","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many official photographs have been taken of (a) Ministers and (b) senior officials in his Department for use in Government publications since May 2010; how many staff of his Department are expected to undertake photography with the ministerial and senior leadership team as part of their duties; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164645","164645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6597","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pieces of correspondence his private ministerial office responded to in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164646","164646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6598","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his private ministerial office spent on access to (a) digital television and (b) internet media in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164648","164648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6599","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what contracts his Department has with mobile telephone operators for the provision of mobile telephones for (a) staff in his private office and (b) his own ministerial use.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164706","164706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6793","2013-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164657","164657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6794","2013-07-10","Attorney General","2013-07-08","To ask the Attorney General, how much (a) he and (b) officials in the Law Officers' Departments spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164658","164658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6795","2013-07-10","Cabinet Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164659","164659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6796","2013-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164660","164660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6797","2013-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much (a) she and (b) officials in her Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164661","164661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6798","2013-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164662","164662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6799","2013-07-10","Cabinet Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much (a) the Deputy Prime Minister and (b) officials in his Office spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164663","164663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6800","2013-07-10","Department for Education","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164664","164664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6801","2013-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164665","164665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6802","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164666","164666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6803","2013-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164667","164667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6804","2013-07-10","Women and Equalities","2013-07-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much (a) she and (b) officials in the Government Equalities Office spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164668","164668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6805","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164669","164669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6806","2013-07-10","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much (a) she and (b) officials in her Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164670","164670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6807","2013-07-10","Department for International Development","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much (a) she and (b) officials in her Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164671","164671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6808","2013-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164672","164672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6809","2013-07-10","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much (a) she and (b) officials in her Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164674","164674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6810","2013-07-10","Cabinet Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much (a) the Prime Minister and (b) officials in No. 10 Downing Street spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164675","164675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6811","2013-07-10","Scotland Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164676","164676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6812","2013-07-10","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164677","164677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6813","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164678","164678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6814","2013-07-10","Wales Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164679","164679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6815","2013-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much (a) he and (b) officials in his Department spent on external assistance to prepare for (i) appearances before select committees and (ii) contact with the media in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164680","164680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7011","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to record injuries to livestock caused by the residue of Chinese lanterns; and how many reports of such injuries have been recorded in each local authority area in Cheshire in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164688","164688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7012","2013-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many fires caused by Chinese lanterns have been recorded in (a) Warrington and (b) Cheshire in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164689","164689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7045","2013-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of all food procured for his Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164756","164756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7046","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2013, Official Report, column 463W, on bovine tuberculosis, under what other legislation investigations into TB-related fraudulent activity are undertaken; and how many prosecutions have resulted from investigations into TB-related fraudulent activity since 2007.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164755","164755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7047","2013-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what budget her Department set for the rollout of broadband in rural areas; what target dates were set for the rollout; how much the rollout has cost to date; what the estimated total cost of the rollout is; and what her latest estimate is of completion dates for the rollout.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164809","164809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7048","2013-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking (a) to ensure that there is sufficient competition in the process of tendering contracts for the rollout of broadband in rural areas and (b) to ensure that the contracts let to BT are securing the best value for the public purse.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164810","164810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7049","2013-07-10","Attorney General","2013-07-08","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of all food procured for the Law Officers' Departments was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164757","164757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7050","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport on the rollout of broadband in rural areas.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164811","164811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7051","2013-07-10","Cabinet Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of all food procured for his Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164758","164758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7052","2013-07-10","Church Commissioners","2013-07-08","To ask the Honourable Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what proportion of all food procured for the Church Commissioners was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164759","164759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7053","2013-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of all food procured for his Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164760","164760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7054","2013-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of all food procured for her Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164761","164761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7055","2013-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of all food procured for his Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164762","164762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7056","2013-07-10","Department for Education","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of all food procured for his Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164763","164763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7057","2013-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of all food procured for his Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164764","164764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7058","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of all food procured for his Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164765","164765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7059","2013-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken for a benefit applicant to receive written notification of the outcome of an application was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164812","164812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7060","2013-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of all food procured for his Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164766","164766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7061","2013-07-10","Women and Equalities","2013-07-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what proportion of all food procured for the Government Equalities Office was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164767","164767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7062","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of all food procured for his Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164768","164768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7063","2013-07-10","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of all food procured for her Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164769","164769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7064","2013-07-10","Department for International Development","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of all food procured for her Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164770","164770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7065","2013-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of all food procured for his Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164771","164771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7066","2013-07-10","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of all food procured for her Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164772","164772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7067","2013-07-10","Scotland Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of all food procured for his Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164773","164773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7068","2013-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has undertaken of levels of job satisfaction among staff of Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164813","164813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7069","2013-07-10","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of all food procured for their Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164774","164774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7070","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of all food procured for his Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164775","164775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7071","2013-07-10","Wales Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of all food procured for his Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164776","164776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7072","2013-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of all food procured for his Department was sourced from (a) British producers, (b) small and medium-sized enterprises and (c) producers which met British buying standards in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164777","164777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7073","2013-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken by his Department and its agencies to consider an application for benefit was (a) in 2008 and (b) in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164814","164814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7074","2013-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2013, Official Report, column 463W, on bovine tuberculosis, what the geographical distribution is of the cases which have resulted in prosecutions for TB-related fraudulent activity.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164787","164787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7240","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what payments Cross Country has made to the Exchequer in each financial year since April 2004; and what payments Cross Country has received from public funds in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164582","164582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7241","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what payments Virgin Trains has made to the Exchequer in each financial year since April 2004; and what payments Virgin Trains has received from public funds in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164583","164583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7242","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what payments the Southern train operating company has made to the Exchequer in each financial year since April 2004; and what payments Southern has received from public funds in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164584","164584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7243","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what payments South Eastern has made to the Exchequer in each financial year since April 2004; and what payments South Eastern has received from public funds in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164585","164585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7244","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what payments Northern Rail has made to the Exchequer in each financial year since April 2004; and what payments Northern Rail has received from public funds in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164586","164586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7274","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to safeguard the UK's energy security by means of shale gas and other resources.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164498","164498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7390","2013-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been given court bail after being charged with (a) murder and (b) attempted murder in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164616","164616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7391","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average charge to hospitals by the supplier for the provision of televisions to patients is.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164625","164625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7392","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people do not have a bank current account.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164626","164626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7393","2013-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people on 8 July 2013 were on bail for (a) murder and (b) attempted murder.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164627","164627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7394","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people who have been discharged from bankruptcy in the last 12 months do not have a current bank account.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164628","164628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7631","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the original estimate was of the cost of the High Speed 2/High Speed 1 link single bore tunnel from Old Oak Common to Primrose Hill; and what the most recent estimate is.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164749","164749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7632","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the original estimate was of the cost of the High Speed 2/High Speed 1 link works above ground from the Primrose Hill portal to connect with High Speed 1; and what the most recent estimate is.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164750","164750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7633","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the most recent estimate is of the cost of the January 2012 proposals for High Speed 2 at Euston.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164751","164751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7865","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much air passenger duty has been raised from passengers travelling by air from the UK to (a) Brazil, (b) Russia, (c) India, (d) China, (e) Australia and (f) South Africa, in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164534","164534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7866","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has undertaken any analysis of the economic effect of air passenger duty since 2010; and if he will publish the results of any such analysis.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164535","164535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7867","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has undertaken any analysis of the economic and fiscal effect of air passenger duty utilising dynamic scoring methodologies; and if he will publish the results of any such analysis.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164536","164536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7868","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of air passenger duty on an airline's ability to (a) start new routes and (b) maintain marginal routes.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164539","164539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7869","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which countries tax passengers travelling internationally by air at a higher level than UK air passenger duty.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164540","164540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7870","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of a reduction in air passenger duty on (a) business travel, (b) leisure travel, (c) trade and (d) economic activity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164568","164568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7871","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of air passenger duty on the competitiveness of UK airlines and airports.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164569","164569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7872","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the model used by his Department to model tax policies takes specific account of the characteristics of (a) air transport and (b) tourism sectors.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164570","164570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8049","2013-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the recent judgement OR v Secretary of State for Work and Pensions and Isle of Anglesey County Council on the operation of homeless nightshelters.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164597","164597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8050","2013-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many foodbank vouchers have been issued by jobcentres in each month in the last year.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164598","164598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8213","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2013, Official Report, column 460W, on the Green Deal Scheme, how many Green Deal apprentices in each local authority area have completed their training.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164779","164779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8214","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many Green Deal apprentices in the Liverpool city region have (a) begun and (b) completed their training to date.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164778","164778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8215","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information his Department holds on the average cost to an individual of completing PAS2030 training.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164782","164782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8216","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2013, Official Report, column 460W, on the Green Deal Scheme, what criteria Asset Skills and Construction Skills have used to allocate funding for the training of Green Deal apprentices.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164780","164780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8217","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what incentives the Government is providing for employers to take on Green Deal apprentices.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164781","164781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8335","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK Border Agency cases are outstanding; and what proportion of cases since May 2012 have taken longer than six months to process.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164650","164650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8336","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the failure of UK Border Agency contingency plans to deal with increased workloads.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164651","164651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8506","2013-07-11","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-07-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, when he intends to bring into force the  provisions on lengthened timetables for general elections enacted in the Electoral Registration and Administration Act 2013.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164588","164588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8507","2013-07-11","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-07-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, whether he plans to bring forward legislative or regulatory proposals on the use of postal votes.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164589","164589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8508","2013-07-11","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-07-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, whether he has received any representations on the commencement of provisions to lengthen the timetable for a general election to the UK Parliament contained in the Electoral Registration and Administration Act 2013 since the passage of this Act.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164590","164590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8509","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what date he expects construction of the new Serlby Park Academy School to begin.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164591","164591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8510","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date he expects construction of the Elkesley flyover on the A1 to begin.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164592","164592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8540","2013-07-10","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2013-07-08","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what estimate he has made of the total number of potential overseas nationals who are entitled to register for an overseas vote; and how many such people were registered to vote in the (a) 2005 and (b) 2010 General Elections.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164629","164629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8541","2013-07-10","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2013-07-08","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what target the Electoral Commission has to increase the number of overseas voters (a) registered and (b) voting in the next general election.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164630","164630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8542","2013-07-10","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2013-07-08","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what steps the Electoral Commission is taking to increase awareness of overseas electors of their entitlement to vote before the next election; and how such steps will differ from previous elections.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164631","164631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8543","2013-07-10","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2013-07-08","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what recommendations the Electoral Commission has made to the Government to make it easier for overseas voters to register.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164632","164632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8544","2013-07-10","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2013-07-08","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what recommendations the Electoral Commission has carried out into different overseas voting systems around the world; and what conclusions have been drawn that would be applicable to the UK.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164633","164633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8545","2013-07-10","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2013-07-08","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many overseas nationals are entitled to register to vote according to their current country of residence.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164634","164634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8546","2013-07-10","Cabinet Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 11 February 2013, Official Report, column 210W, on population, when he expects to publish the data requested.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164682","164682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8737","2013-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when a decision will be made on the regulatory licence treatment of the transmission cables of directly connected offshore renewable energy projects that are located outside of the UK; and whether such a decision will be announced in advance of an intergovernmental agreement signed by the UK and Ireland on renewable energy trading.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164637","164637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8738","2013-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether his Department has held discussions with Ofgem on whether the transmission cables for directly connected offshore renewable energy projects located outside of the UK can be treated as a generator spur; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164638","164638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8739","2013-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether his Department has held discussions with Ofgem to determine the regulatory licensing treatment of transmission cables of offshore renewable energy projects located outside of the UK; what the estimated timetable for a decision on this regulatory treatment is; when the intergovernmental agreement between Ireland and the UK is expected to be signed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164639","164639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8740","2013-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether his Department has held discussions with Ofgem on whether the transmission cables for directly connected offshore renewable energy projects located outside of the UK can be treated with a derogated interconnector licence or a derogated transmission licence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164642","164642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8800","2013-07-11","Department for Transport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) staff and (b) resources the Maritime and Coastguard Agency has allocated for work on the safety regime for the offshore oil and gas industry for each year to 2015-16.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164714","164714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8801","2013-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times in each of the last five years well operators in the UK offshore oil and gas industry reported the use of blow out prevention technology in well control operations.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164715","164715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8802","2013-07-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress has been made in implementing the recommendations of the Maitland Review of the regulatory regime for the UK offshore oil and gas industry; which recommendations are yet awaiting implementation; and when the senior oversight group expects to complete implementation of the Maitland recommendations.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164716","164716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9024","2013-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will direct HM Ambassador to Israel to draw the attention of the Israeli government to the possible breach of Article 76 of the Fourth Geneva Conventions committed by the Israeli authorities in imprisoning in Israel Palestinians charged with or convicted of offences committed in the Occupied Territories.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164708","164708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9130","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consideration he has given to reviewing primary care registration for all people in England registered with GPs as part of his review of migrant access to the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164515","164515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9339","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many drug offences relating to Class A substances have been reported in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) South Yorkshire  and (d) England since 2010; and what proportion of national offences relating to Class A substances such figures represent.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164704","164704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9340","2013-07-11","Cabinet Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of 18 to 24 year olds have been unemployed for two years or more in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) England.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164705","164705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9341","2013-07-11","Department for Education","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will review the (a) current incentives for and (b) requirements on businesses that release their staff for school governor duties.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164711","164711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9342","2013-07-11","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce shortages of consultants in (a) deprived areas, (b) geriatric medicine and (c) other areas; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164713","164713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9555","2013-07-11","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when she expects to announce her decision regarding the need for a public inquiry into the events surrounding the Omagh bombing.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164748","164748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9652","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of young people unemployed for over a year in financial year 2015-16 according to (a) official claimant count and (b) International Labour Organisation forecasts.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164816","164816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9653","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what revenue accrued to the Exchequer from VAT in 2012-13; and what estimate he has made of the likely level of revenue accruing in 2013-14 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164817","164817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9654","2013-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of businesses paying salaries between the value of the minimum wage and the living wage; and how many workers would be in receipt of such salaries.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164818","164818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9829","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse has been of undertaking the consultation into the administration of the Nursery Milk Scheme.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164736","164736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9830","2013-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to encourage appropriate models for remote eBook lending in response to the recommendations of the Sieghart Review of eBook lending in libraries.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164737","164737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9831","2013-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to implement the recommendations of the Sieghart Review of eBook lending in libraries in respect of extending public lending rights to eBooks.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164738","164738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9832","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Government response to the consultation on the future administration of the Nursery Milk Scheme, whether childcare settings providing milk under the Nursery Milk Scheme will continue to be able to have the choice to source their milk locally if they wish to.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164739","164739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9833","2013-07-10","Department of Health","2013-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Government response to the consultation on the future administration of the Nursery Milk Scheme, whether every child who is entitled to free milk under the Scheme will continue to receive their entitlement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164740","164740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10000","2013-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make a statement on Lieutenant General Benny Gantz's official engagements in the UK and their purpose.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164475","164475"
