"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455316","2016-03-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to make available to the Welsh Government funds received as a result of the application to the EU Solidarity Fund announced on 25 February 2016.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28446","28446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455317","2016-03-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received from the Welsh Government on applying to the EU Solidarity Fund as a result of flooding in Wales in late 2015 and early 2016.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28447","28447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455318","2016-03-01","Department for International Development","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what political engagement her Department had with the Afghan government on extractives governance in 2015.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28433","28433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455319","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many consultants' contracts were terminated early in each of the last six years for which figures are available; and what the cost of each such termination was in each of those years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28657","28657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455320","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) publications, (b) consultation documents and (c) circulars his Department has issued since August 2012; and what the title was of each such publication, consultation document or circular.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28673","28673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455321","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28605","28605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455322","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the compliance of the Decision of the Heads of State or Government, meeting within the European Council, on 18 and 19 February 2016 with Part 2 of the Constitutional Reform and Governance Act 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28549","28549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455323","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent from the public purse on industrial tribunals in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28625","28625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455324","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the compatibility with international law of the arrest and transfer of children from the Occupied Palestinian Territories to Israel.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28493","28493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455325","2016-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Decision of the Heads of State or Government, meeting within the European Council, on 18 and 19 February 2016, is an international Treaty to which the procedures of sections 20 and 25 of the Constitutional Reform and Governance Act 2010 will apply.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28490","28490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455326","2016-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Prime Minister's Oral Statement of 22 February 2016, Official Report, column 35, on the European Council, whether his Department is undertaking planning in the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the EU referendum.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28502","28502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455327","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many North Korean refugees have approached the British Embassy or Consulate in China for safe passage or asylum in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28546","28546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455328","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of (a) defections from North Korea and (b) unsuccessful defection attempts from that country in the last four years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28545","28545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455329","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to (a) China, (b) Laos, (c) Vietnam and (d) Myanmar on the repatriation of North Korean defectors from those countries to North Korea.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28544","28544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455330","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many civil law suits have been brought against his Department based either wholly or partially on grounds provided by the Human Rights Act 1998; how many such suits were settled out of court before a court judgment was delivered; and how much such settlements have cost the public purse since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28641","28641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455331","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Decision of the Heads of State or Government, meeting within the European Council, on 18 and 19 February 2016, meets the definition of a treaty under Article 2 of the Vienna Convention on the Law of Treaties.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28571","28571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455332","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what notification he has received on whether there are (a) constitutional requirements and (b) potential legal proceedings in other EU member states related to the Decision of the Heads of State or Government, meeting within the European Council, on 18 and 19 February 2016.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28569","28569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455333","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has paid to staff in overtime in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28689","28689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455334","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assurances or opinions has he received from the government or constitutional bodies in (a) France and (b) Germany on whether the Decision of the Heads of State or Government, meeting within the European Council, on 18 and 19 February 2016, would require a vote in the parliament of that country.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28572","28572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455335","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to extend the meningitis B vaccination programme to all infants.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28575","28575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455336","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has paid to staff in overtime in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28690","28690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455337","2016-03-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what restrictions are in place on Dr Nicole Mather in her role as Director of the Office for Life Sciences in relation to her role as Director of Deloitte's Healthcare and Life Sciences practice.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28595","28595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455338","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of rickets there were among children and young people in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28581","28581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455339","2016-03-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the salary of Dr Nicole Mather is for her role as Director of the Office for Life Sciences.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28594","28594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455340","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many civil law suits have been brought against his Department based either wholly or partially on grounds provided by the Human Rights Act 1998; how many such suits were settled out of court before a court judgment was delivered; and how much such settlements have cost the public purse since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28642","28642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455341","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adult inpatient psychiatric beds there were in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28556","28556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455342","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the report by Sir Stephen Bubb, Time for Change: the challenge ahead, published in February 2016, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of establishing a commissioner for people with learning disabilities.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28525","28525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455343","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to develop cancer clinical alliances across the country.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28555","28555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455344","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the national bed occupancy rate average was for (a) adult and (b) child and adolescent inpatient psychiatric wards in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28553","28553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455345","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which regions in England had the (a) longest and (b) shortest average waiting times for patients to access improving Access to Psychological Therapies services in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28537","28537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455346","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any national guidance has been issued relating to the use of opt in letters sent by health trusts to patients on mental health service waiting lists.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28538","28538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455347","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in England with severe mental illness are registered with a GP; and how many such people had an annual physical health check in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28539","28539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455348","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time for an ambulance was (a) nationally, (b) in London and (c) in Hornsey and Wood Green constituency in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28487","28487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455349","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans (a) his Department and (b) NICE has to reform the process for the appraisal of cancer drugs.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28488","28488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455350","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Bury Clinical Commissioning Group received in grants in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28511","28511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455351","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time for an operation in (a) Pennine Acute NHS Trust and (b) Bolton NHS Trust was in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28512","28512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455352","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of newly qualified doctors has entered (a) primary care and (b) hospitals.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28501","28501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455353","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent from the public purse on industrial tribunals in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28626","28626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455354","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28607","28607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455355","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) publications, (b) consultation documents and (c) circulars his Department has issued since August 2012; and what the title was of each such publication, consultation document or circular.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28674","28674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455356","2016-03-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been claimed in reimbursement expenses by Dr Nicole Mather in her role as Director of the Office for Life Sciences in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16 to date.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28592","28592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455357","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children aged (a) up to 12, (b) 12 to 15 and (c) 16 to 18 were prescribed (i) fluoxetine, (ii) fluvoxamine, (iii) sertraline, (iv) paroxetine, (v) escitalopram and (vi) citalopra by the NHS in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28593","28593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455358","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many emergency call handlers were employed in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28564","28564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455359","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many consultants' contracts were terminated early in each of the last six years for which figures are available; and what the cost of each such termination was in each of those years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28658","28658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455360","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been referred to mental health services in (a) London and (b) each London NHS trust for gambling addiction in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28448","28448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455361","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on the number of people employed by ambulance services who are from non-EU countries of the salary threshold increase for Tier 2 visa applications to £35,000.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28453","28453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455362","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people who were admitted for treatment by mental health trusts in London since 2010 had no previous contact with mental health services.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28450","28450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455363","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many acute beds there were in each mental health trust in London since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28451","28451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455364","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on the number of people employed as teachers who are from non-EU countries of the salary threshold increase for Tier 2 visa applications to £35,000.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28462","28462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455365","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on the number of people employed in England, excluding London, who are from non-EU countries of the salary threshold increase for Tier 2 visa applications to £35,000.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28463","28463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455366","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on the number of people employed in Northern Ireland who are from non-EU countries of the salary threshold increase for Tier 2 visa applications to £35,000.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28454","28454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455367","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on the number of people employed in Wales who are from non-EU countries of the salary threshold increase for Tier 2 visa applications to £35,000.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28455","28455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455368","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on the number of people employed in Scotland who are from non-EU countries of the salary threshold increase for Tier 2 visa applications to £35,000.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28456","28456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455369","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on the number of people employed as IT professionals who are from non-EU countries of the salary threshold increase for Tier 2 visa applications to £35,000.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28457","28457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455370","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on the number of people employed in roles classed as an essential public service who are from non-EU countries of the salary threshold increase for Tier 2 visa applications to £35,000.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28458","28458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455371","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on the number of people employed by fire and rescue services who are from non-EU countries of the salary threshold increase for Tier 2 visa applications to £35,000.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28459","28459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455372","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on the number of people employed by police services who are from non-EU countries of the salary threshold increase for Tier 2 visa applications to £35,000.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28460","28460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455373","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on the number of people employed by the NHS who are from non-EU countries of the salary threshold increase for Tier 2 visa applications to £35,000.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28461","28461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455374","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many consultants' contracts were terminated early in each of the last six years for which figures are available; and what the cost of each such termination was in each of those years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28659","28659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455375","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) publications, (b) consultation documents and (c) circulars her Department has issued since August 2012; and what the title was of each such publication, consultation document or circular.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28675","28675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455376","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in her Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28608","28608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455377","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent from the public purse on industrial tribunals in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28627","28627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455378","2016-03-01","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Prime Minister's Oral Statement of 22 February 2016, Official Report, column 35, on the European Council, whether her Department is undertaking planning in the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the EU referendum.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28506","28506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455379","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the level of violent crime in Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28509","28509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455380","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police forces in England operate a neighbourhood policing model.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28500","28500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455381","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the Government's policy is on where unsuccessful asylum applicants from North Korea are deported to.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28547","28547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455382","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to tackle cyber harassment.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28536","28536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455383","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many civil law suits have been brought against her Department based either wholly or partially on grounds provided by the Human Rights Act 1998; how many such suits were settled out of court before a court judgment was delivered; and how much such settlements have cost the public purse since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28643","28643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455384","2016-03-07","Attorney General","2016-02-25","To ask the Attorney General, what the deadline is for criminal prosecutions to be brought by the Metropolitan Police against people implicated in electoral fraud in Tower Hamlets as a result of the Election Court rulings against former mayor Lutfur Rahman.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28599","28599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455385","2016-03-01","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of applications for Disclosure and Barring Service checks (a) nationally, (b) in London and (c) in Bromley and Chislehurst constituency met the published service standards for waiting times in the last 6 months.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28591","28591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455386","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department has paid to staff in overtime in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28691","28691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455387","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications to the Disclosure and Barring Service from people living in Dulwich and West Norwood constituency have taken more than 60 days to process in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28573","28573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455388","2016-02-29","Department for International Development","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has paid to staff in overtime in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28692","28692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455389","2016-02-29","Department for International Development","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many civil law suits have been brought against her Department based either wholly or partially on grounds provided by the Human Rights Act 1998; how many such suits were settled out of court before a court judgment was delivered; and how much such settlements have cost the public purse since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28644","28644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455390","2016-02-29","Department for International Development","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of planned budget changes to her Department's Afghanistan Project on economic security in that country.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28510","28510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455391","2016-02-29","Department for International Development","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent from the public purse on industrial tribunals in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28628","28628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455392","2016-02-29","Department for International Development","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in her Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28609","28609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455393","2016-02-29","Department for International Development","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many (a) publications, (b) consultation documents and (c) circulars her Department has issued since August 2012; and what the title was of each such publication, consultation document or circular.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28676","28676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455394","2016-02-29","Department for International Development","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many consultants' contracts were terminated early in each of the last six years for which figures are available; and what the cost of each such termination was in each of those years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28660","28660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455395","2016-03-01","Department for International Development","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the UK is intending to take steps to ensure that effective benchmarks for extractive-sector governance are included on the agenda for the Brussels Conference on Afghanistan.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28435","28435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455396","2016-03-01","Department for International Development","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that the Afghan Minerals Law includes the strongest possible measures to strengthen transparency and reduce the risk of corruption in the Afghan extractive sector.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28431","28431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455397","2016-03-01","Department for International Development","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what political representations UK officials have made to the Afghan government with respect to the Afghan Minerals Law and amendments currently being considered by the Afghan government; and whether UK officials have provided technical assistance in the preparation of those amendments.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28432","28432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455398","2016-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the annual cost was of the advocacy contract at each secure training centre in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28467","28467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455399","2016-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the annual cost was of the Youth Justice Board monitoring carried out at each secure training centre in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28468","28468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455400","2016-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Written Statement by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Justice, 25 February 2016, HCWS549, on offender management, what financial penalties were incurred by his Department as a result of terminating the contract to develop a bespoke tagging product with Steatite Limited; and how much his Department spent on that contract before its termination.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28470","28470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455401","2016-02-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his Department's policy that all prison officers in youth facilities should wear body-mounted cameras.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28480","28480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455402","2016-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether Barnardo's advocates are permitted to speak to children confidentially without G4S staff in attendance at Medway Secure Training Centre.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28469","28469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455403","2016-02-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many consultants' contracts were terminated early in each of the last six years for which figures are available; and what the cost of each such termination was in each of those years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28661","28661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455404","2016-02-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of months has been between the tariff expiry date of prisoners (a) with life sentences and (b) imprisoned for public protection and the date of their first release by the Parole Board in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28566","28566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455405","2016-02-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) publications, (b) consultation documents and (c) circulars his Department has issued since August 2012; and what the title was of each such publication, consultation document or circular.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28677","28677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455406","2016-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 27179, whether the requirement in the Lisbon Treaty that the EU shall accede to the European Convention on Human Rights is legally enforceable.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28590","28590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455407","2016-02-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with (a) NOMS and (b) the Prison Officers Association on evidence submitted to the Prison Service Pay Review Body on rates of pay for prison officers.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28563","28563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455408","2016-02-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners serving life sentences have been recalled to custody in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28567","28567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455409","2016-02-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28610","28610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455410","2016-02-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent from the public purse on industrial tribunals in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28629","28629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455411","2016-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to respond to the findings of Amnesty International UK's Annual Report, published on 24 February 2016.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28489","28489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455412","2016-02-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to reduce overcrowding on the prison estate in England and Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28486","28486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455413","2016-02-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many civil law suits have been brought against his Department based either wholly or partially on grounds provided by the Human Rights Act 1998; how many such suits were settled out of court before a court judgment was delivered; and how much such settlements have cost the public purse since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28645","28645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455414","2016-02-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what average number of months life-sentenced prisoners who were recalled to custody in the last five years spent in prison before they were re-released.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28568","28568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455415","2016-02-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has paid to staff in overtime in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28693","28693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455416","2016-02-29","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in her Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28611","28611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455417","2016-03-01","Prime Minister","2016-02-25","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to his Oral Statement of 22 February 2016, Official Report, column 35, on the European Council, whether his Office is undertaking planning in the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the EU referendum.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28503","28503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455418","2016-03-01","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if the Prime Minister will make an assessment of the potential merits of each proposal on noise mitigation from aviation in the letter to him of 18 February 2016 from the Aviation Environment Federation.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28554","28554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455419","2016-02-29","Scotland Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28612","28612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455420","2016-03-07","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2016-02-25","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what recent assessment the Commission has made of the level of electoral fraud in Tower Hamlets.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28597","28597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455421","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what safeguards are in place to protect information held by the DVLA on those who use its services.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28579","28579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455422","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many civil law suits have been brought against his Department based either wholly or partially on grounds provided by the Human Rights Act 1998; how many such suits were settled out of court before a court judgment was delivered; and how much such settlements have cost the public purse since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28646","28646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455423","2016-03-01","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his future policies of the Sharm el Sheikh air crash in October 2015; and what recent reports he has received on the reasons for that crash.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28596","28596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455424","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has paid to staff in overtime in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28694","28694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455425","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if it will make it his policy to require bus operators to install audio-visual announcements of bus stops on all public buses.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28574","28574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455426","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28613","28613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455427","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent from the public purse on industrial tribunals in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28630","28630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455428","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) publications, (b) consultation documents and (c) circulars his Department has issued since August 2012; and what the title was of each such publication, consultation document or circular.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28678","28678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455429","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many consultants' contracts were terminated early in each of the last six years for which figures are available; and what the cost of each such termination was in each of those years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28662","28662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455430","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to bring forward legislative proposals to enable the construction of the Eastern Leg of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28548","28548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455431","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the walk to school programme on (a) children's health and (b) reducing traffic congestion.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28531","28531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455432","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department plans to take to increase the number of children walking to school once the Local Sustainable Transport Fund ends.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28494","28494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455433","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Department of Health to encourage more people to walk.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28495","28495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455434","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the walk to school programme on the Government's objective to increase the proportion of children aged five to 10 that usually walk to school from 46 per cent in 2013 to 55 per cent in 2025.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28496","28496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455435","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many incidents of laser pen attacks were recorded on trains in the last five years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28440","28440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455436","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many incidents of laser pen attacks were recorded on road vehicles in the last five years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28441","28441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455437","2016-02-29","Wales Office","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28615","28615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455438","2016-02-29","Department for Education","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in the Government Equalities Office.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28606","28606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455439","2016-02-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28616","28616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455440","2016-02-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent from the public purse on industrial tribunals in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28632","28632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455441","2016-02-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many consultants' contracts were terminated early in each of the last six years for which figures are available; and what the cost of each such termination was in each of those years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28664","28664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455442","2016-02-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) publications, (b) consultation documents and (c) circulars his Department has issued since August 2012; and what the title was of each such publication, consultation document or circular.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28680","28680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455444","2016-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2016 to Question 24803, whether Jobcentre work coaches are able to advise universal credit claimants of their eligibility for council tax reductions.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28542","28542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455445","2016-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many one-month reminder letters of CSA case closure have been issued in each month since November 2014 for cases in (a) segment 1, (b) segment 2, (c) segment 3 and (d) segment 4.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28437","28437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455446","2016-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many six-month notice letters of CSA case closure have been issued in each month since July 2014 for cases in (a) segment 1, (b) segment 2, (c) segment 3 and (d) segment 4.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28438","28438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455447","2016-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many final letters concerning CSA case closure have been issued in each month since January 2015 for cases in (a) segment 1, (b) segment 2, (c) segment 3 and (d) segment 4.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28439","28439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455448","2016-02-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce the prevalence of child poverty in the Greater Manchester area.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28473","28473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455449","2016-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with identified mental health needs have been (a) on the Work Programme and (b) helped into employment by that programme in each year since it began in (i) the UK and (ii) London.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28449","28449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455450","2016-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many calls were made to the Child Maintenance Options Service in each month since November 2015.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28466","28466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455451","2016-02-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many civil law suits have been brought against his Department based either wholly or partially on grounds provided by the Human Rights Act 1998; how many such suits were settled out of court before a court judgment was delivered; and how much such settlements have cost the public purse since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28648","28648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455452","2016-02-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has paid to staff in overtime in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28696","28696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455453","2016-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many long-term unemployed people have been helped back into work through the Help to Work scheme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28589","28589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454735","2016-02-26","Attorney General","2016-02-24","To ask the Attorney General, what account the CPS takes of mental health conditions when deciding whether to prosecute people under the Protection from Harassment Act 1997.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28427","28427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454736","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's spending was in Overseas Development Aid in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) the first 10 months of 2015-16; and what the recipient countries of that aid were.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28268","28268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454737","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government took to ensure that its response to its consultation, Sunday Trading, published in August 2015, took substantive account of the range of responses to that consultation.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28326","28326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454738","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many officials of his Department were employed specifically to assist with negotiations on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28328","28328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454739","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reasons the Government has not yet published its analysis of responses to its consultation, Sunday Trading, published in August 2015.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28327","28327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454740","2016-02-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will estimate (a) public and (b) private sector involvement in developing ultra-fast FTTH broadband in 2014-15.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28180","28180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454741","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what skills businesses in the retail and commercial enterprise sector are required to teach to apprentices to qualify for funding under the Government's apprenticeship programme.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28187","28187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454742","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations his Department received on the requirements to be set for businesses in the retail and commercial enterprise sector to qualify for funding under the apprenticeship programme before those requirements were determined.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28188","28188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454743","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken and what mechanisms are in place to ensure that apprentices in the retail and commercial enterprise sector are taught skills that they would not otherwise be able to learn on the job under a normal employment contract.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28189","28189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454744","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's practice in consulting manufacturers on policy of the findings by the Institution of Mechanical Engineers in its report, Engineered in Britain, on the proportion of manufacturers who consider that the Government is performing well on manufacturing policy.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28190","28190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454745","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the findings of the Institution of Mechanical Engineers on page 5 of its report, Engineered in Britain, published in December 2015, if he will take steps to increase the confidence of the public and manufacturers in Government support for the manufacturing sector.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28191","28191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454746","2016-02-26","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policies on encouraging school leavers to consider careers in science and mathematics of the conclusion of the Institution of Mechanical Engineers in its report, Engineered in Britain, published in December 2015, on the rate of change in the numbers of school leavers considering such careers.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28192","28192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454747","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policy on apprenticeships of the finding of the Institution of Mechanical Engineers in its report, Engineered in Britain, published in December 2015, on the number of manufacturers who would be encouraged to take on more apprentices if the Government provided £3,000 to any person who completed their apprenticeship.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28193","28193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454748","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reason the report commissioned by his Department from Ecofys on international electricity prices has not yet been published; when the Government plans to publish that report; and whether that report found that electricity price increases for energy intensive industries as a result of climate policies will be larger in the UK than any other country.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28214","28214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454749","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Christmas Day (Trading) Act 2014.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28229","28229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454750","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which universities have (a) introduced and (b) committed to introduce degree apprenticeships since September 2015; how many such degree apprenticeships each such university has introduced since September 2015; and in which industries those degree apprenticeships have been in.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28235","28235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454751","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the distribution of the graduate premium by each decile of graduate lifetime earnings.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28236","28236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454752","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of how much of his Department's staff expenditure was specifically related to the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28301","28301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454753","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment the Government made of the effect on (a) high streets, (b) small businesses and (c) post offices of the temporary changes to Sunday trading laws during the 2012 Olympic Games in London.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28307","28307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454754","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the likely timetable for conclusion of negotiations on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28299","28299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454755","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the implementation of the Prime Minister's commitment of April 2015 to utilise the proceeds of the £227 million fine on Deutsche Bank to create a new three-year fund to create 50,000 apprenticeships.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28350","28350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454756","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the heads of further education colleges about the implications for recruitment and retention of college staff of the Government's restrictions on public sector pay increases.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28351","28351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454757","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the expenditure of his Department which specifically related to the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28337","28337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454758","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effects on recruitment of further education staff of the Government's restrictions on public sector pay increases.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28352","28352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454759","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to answer Question 21634, tabled by the Right hon. Member for Tooting on 8 January 2016.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28376","28376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454760","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many representations he has received from (a) European and (b) American officials pertaining to the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28377","28377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454761","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent estimate his Department has made of the average cost of each official of his Department based at (a) St Paul's Place, Sheffield and (b) 1 Victoria Street, London.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28339","28339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454762","2016-02-29","Cabinet Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how the Government plans to ensure that any special advisers working part-time for Government and part-time for a campaign do not make use of departmental or government resources in their campaign work.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28378","28378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454763","2016-02-29","Cabinet Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of Senior Civil Servants were based in London in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28340","28340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454764","2016-02-29","Cabinet Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will investigate whether the reported comments of 22 February 2016 by Peter Wilkinson, director of Rail Passenger Services at the Department for Transport, are in breach of the Civil Service code.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28210","28210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454765","2016-02-29","Cabinet Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many special advisers from which departments have notified the Prime Minister's Parliamentary Private Secretary that they will be campaigning outside office hours for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28379","28379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454766","2016-02-29","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to further reform the Bank of England.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28233","28233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454767","2016-02-29","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he next plans to attend a meeting of the National Infrastructure Commission.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28234","28234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454768","2016-02-26","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the maintenance of entrepreneurial relief over the course of this Parliament.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28173","28173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454769","2016-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with (a) members of the public and (b) law professionals on proposed changes to the system of probate fees charged to activate a will.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28179","28179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454770","2016-02-26","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much and what proportion of National Infrastructure Pipeline spending has been allocated to projects in (a) Stoke-on-Trent local authority, (b) Cheshire East local authority, (c) the West Midlands region, (d) the South East region and (e) London.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28196","28196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454771","2016-02-26","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much infrastructure investment was allocated to projects in (a) Stoke-on-Trent local authority, (b) Cheshire East local authority, (c) the West Midlands region, (d) the South East region and (e) London.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28202","28202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454772","2016-02-26","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of national infrastructure investment has been allocated to projects in (a) Stoke-on-Trent local authority, (b) Cheshire East local authority, (c) the West Midlands region, (d) the South East region and (e) London in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28203","28203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454773","2016-02-29","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2016 to Question 25976, whether the proceeds from the £227 million fine imposed on Deutsche Bank will be specifically applied to a new new three-year fund to create 50,000 apprenticeships.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28353","28353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454774","2016-02-26","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to support the British gin industry.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28412","28412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454775","2016-02-29","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2016 to Question 25976, what discussions his officials have had with their counterparts in the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on the mechanisms for implementing the Prime Minister's commitment of April 2015 to use the proceeds from the £227 million fine imposed on Deutsche Bank to create a new three-year fund to create 50,000 apprenticeships.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28354","28354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454776","2016-02-29","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the net annual UK financial contribution to the EU is expected to be in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28349","28349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454777","2016-02-26","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many times Dorneywood has been redecorated in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28331","28331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454778","2016-02-29","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much public money has been spent on repairs to Dorneywood in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28251","28251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454779","2016-02-29","Church Commissioners","2016-02-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, whether the settlement the Church Commissioners made to the complainant against George Bell was made directly in relation to allegations against Bell, or on the basis that a complaint made under a subsequent Bishop, was not handled in a way which would be expected today.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28341","28341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454780","2016-02-29","Church Commissioners","2016-02-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, whether any of the Estates Commissioners saw the charge sheet on which George Bell was found guilty of child abuse on the balance of probabilities.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28342","28342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454781","2016-02-29","Church Commissioners","2016-02-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, how many people involved in investigating allegations of child abuse made against George Bell consulted his papers and diaries in Lambeth Palace Library in the last three years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28343","28343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454782","2016-02-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2016 to Question 23515, what estimate he has made of the total cost to people who pay council tax of that tax in (a) Stevenage, (b) Hertfordshire and (c) England in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28259","28259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454783","2016-02-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 26584, on housing: young people, what conditions vulnerable young people have to meet in order to qualify as being in need of support.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28241","28241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454784","2016-02-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that people who have been convicted of a child sex offence cannot serve as a local authority or parish councillor.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28306","28306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454785","2016-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent consideration he has given to amending existing non-statutory guidelines on Residential Leasehold and Recognised Tenants' Associations to ensure that those who reside in larger blocks and developments have the same opportunity to gain recognition as a recognised tenants' association as those in smaller blocks and developments.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28333","28333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454786","2016-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential contribution of community land trusts to increasing the supply of affordable housing in the UK.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28204","28204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454787","2016-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will direct local planning authorities to reassess planning permissions granted to developments on floodplains that have been affected by recent flooding events.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28182","28182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454788","2016-02-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 26614, on children in care: housing, how many young people he expects to be on the Positive Pathway Framework in 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28253","28253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454789","2016-02-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to restart work related to his Department's pre-consultation on moving the May Bank Holiday, published in 2011.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28195","28195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454790","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what guidance is issued to households on dealing with a nuclear incident.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28219","28219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454791","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government has issued iodine tablets to households in the last five years.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28220","28220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454792","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential (a) commercial and (b) other economic benefits of the expansion of HMNB Clyde to the surrounding towns and communities.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28223","28223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454793","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to accommodate the Blind Veterans Association based at the Braeholm Centre in Helensburgh when that facility closes in June 2016.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28224","28224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454794","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many military operations the UK has undertaken against (a) Daesh and (b) al-Qaeda in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28177","28177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454795","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's policy is on the provision of accommodation for naval personnel and their families visiting (a) HMNB Clyde and (b) RNAD Coulport.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28246","28246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454796","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 26801, if he will create a central register of contracts and contract information for the Successor submarine programme.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28344","28344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454797","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) scope, (b) value and (c) cost overrun from the original value are of contracts awarded to BAE Systems for the Successor submarine programme.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28345","28345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454798","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the risk provision is in the cost estimate announced in the Strategic Defence and Security Review for the Successor submarine programme.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28346","28346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454799","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the formal internal scrutiny process for the current calculations for optimism bias for the Successor submarine programme to be completed.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28347","28347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454800","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the provision for inflation is in the cost estimate for the Successor submarine programme.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28348","28348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454801","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recruits to the (a) Reserve and (b) armed forces in each local authority area of their origin in Wales and in each branch of service began their basic training in each of the last 12 months","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28420","28420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454802","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations his Department has made to the NHS England consultation on the future of mental health support for veterans of the armed forces.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28314","28314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454803","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's spending was on Overseas Development Aid in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) the first 10 months of 2015-16; and what the recipient countries of that aid were.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28267","28267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454804","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2015 to Question 11029, whether assessment of the necessary infrastructure adaptations to update the facilities at HM Naval Base Clyde and Royal Naval Armament Depot Coulport has been completed.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28271","28271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454805","2016-02-29","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on marketing for the Future Teaching Scholars programme to date.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28315","28315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454806","2016-02-29","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to encourage academies to join high-performing rather than under-performing multi-academy trusts; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28318","28318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454807","2016-02-29","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has allocated to the Future Teaching Scholars programme for the 2016-17 cohort.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28316","28316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454808","2016-02-29","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will require the OCR exam board to extend provision of GCSE and A-level Gujarati beyond 2017-18; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28325","28325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454809","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the implications of a decision to leave the EU on the higher education fees status of EU students becoming classed in the same way as that for non-EU overseas students; and whether his Department plans to assess the potential effect of any such change in classification on the number of students coming from EU member states to study in the UK.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28415","28415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454810","2016-02-29","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on (a) new IT equipment, (b) new furniture, (c) new artwork, (d) catering and events, (e) renovating its buildings and facilities, (f) new plants and shrubs and (g) special advisers' travel expenses since May 2015.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28384","28384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454811","2016-02-29","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2016 to Question 26852, what funding she expects will be provided for the Fostering Network in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19 and (d) 2019-20.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28252","28252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454812","2016-02-29","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will establish a system to permit supplementary schools and mainstream schools to bid for funding to support the professional development of staff teaching English to GCSE and A-level standard; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28260","28260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454813","2016-02-29","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will require the Oxford, Cambridge and RSA Examinations board to offer GCSE and A-level Gujarati examinations beyond September 2018; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28261","28261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454814","2016-02-26","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the new national curriculum can be taught in primary schools to mixed-age classes.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28249","28249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454815","2016-02-29","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applicants to the Future Teaching Scholars programme to date have been (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28308","28308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454816","2016-02-29","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of (a) people who will apply for 2016-17 cohort of the Future Teaching Scholars programme, (b)applicants that will join that scheme for that year and (c) such applicants that will complete that training.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28309","28309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454817","2016-02-26","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that the supply of newly-qualified teachers is not affected by imbalances in the distribution of teacher training places at a sub-regional level.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28194","28194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454818","2016-02-26","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many spaces have been set aside on initial teacher training courses for the 2016-17 cohort of the future teaching scholars programme.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28174","28174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454819","2016-02-26","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which higher education institution providers of initial teacher education have reduced their allocation for PGCE secondary training in (a) history, (b) geography, (c) English and (d) STEM subjects in 2015-16; and what that reduction is as a proportion of that provider's 2014-15 allocations in each case.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28197","28197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454820","2016-02-26","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on how many occasions a special adviser of her Department has accompanied a Minister on a foreign trip since 1 October 2015; and what the cost of that travel has been.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28198","28198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454821","2016-02-26","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the supply of newly-qualified mathematics teachers in Stoke-on-Trent.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28199","28199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454822","2016-02-26","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions (a) Ministers, (b) special advisers and (c) senior officials of her Department have had with representatives from the National Baccalaureate Trust since May 2015.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28200","28200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454823","2016-02-26","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the distribution of teacher training places in the (a) North Staffordshire sub-region and (b) West Midlands region.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28201","28201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454824","2016-02-29","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and which local authorities have notified her Department about plans to dispose of grant-funded assets through the (a) sale, (b) transfer and (c) change of use of children's centres under the requirements of the Sure Start Early Years and Childcare Grant.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28205","28205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454825","2016-02-29","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria her Department uses to assess whether a local authority should be subject to a Sure Start claw-back.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28207","28207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454826","2016-02-29","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications her Department received to the first application round for the Future Teaching Scholars programme.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28217","28217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454827","2016-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what changes have been proposed to the existing terms and conditions of the Sellafield workforce under the workforce reform initiative.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28221","28221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454828","2016-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of supporting the deployment of ultra-super critical coal fired power stations similar to those planned by China and Germany; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28242","28242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454829","2016-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will place in the Library any information her Department holds on the number of jobs imported coal supports in each of its source countries; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28243","28243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454830","2016-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will assess the suitability of the hinterland of the Port of Blyth as a location for an ultra-super critical coal fired power station; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28244","28244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454831","2016-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the Sellafield Workforce Reform programme on the Sellafield workforce.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28222","28222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454832","2016-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government has taken to encourage underground cabling connecting (a) wind farm and (b) other such installations to distribution centres in order to present visual amenity and prevent adverse environmental impacts.","Biography information for Dr James Davies","Dr James Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28416","28416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454833","2016-03-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will ensure that all standards explicitly linked to the Renewable Heat Incentive are non-commercialised and publicly available to all relevant parties who may wish to offer services related to the implementation of that initiative.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28417","28417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454834","2016-03-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department is assessing potential alternatives to the Microgeneration Certification Scheme to which the Renewable Heat Incentive is linked.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28418","28418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454835","2016-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's spending was on Overseas Development Aid in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) the first 10 months of 2015-16; and what the recipient countries of that aid were.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28264","28264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454836","2016-02-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 264385, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that EU environmental law is transposed and implemented across the whole of the UK.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28237","28237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454837","2016-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to make an assessment of the environmental effects of the disposal of imported (a) animal blood, faeces and urine and (b) other biological by-products in rural areas of the UK.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28245","28245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454838","2016-02-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will include the Food Insecurity Experience Scale survey in the next Family Food survey in order to assess households' vulnerability to hunger.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28227","28227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454839","2016-02-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to implement the findings of the Report of the Independent Farming Regulation Taskforce, published in May 2011.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28213","28213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454840","2016-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many applications for emergency authorisation for the use of neonicotinoids have been received in 2016; and how many of those applications have been granted.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28298","28298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454841","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Hungarian government on the sale of residency bonds through off-shore companies.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28335","28335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454842","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the government of Romania about the activities of (a) Central Media Enterprise, (b) Adrian Sârbu and (c) Ronald Lauder in (i) 1995 to 1999, (ii) 2000 to 2010 and (iii) 2011 to 2015.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28332","28332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454843","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Decision of the Heads of State or Government, meeting within the European Council, on 18 and 19 February 2016 will be added to his Department's Treaty Series 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28381","28381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454844","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the UN Secretary General on the supply of arms and other military equipment sales to Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28413","28413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454845","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the agreement reached at the February European Council is not amended by the European Parliament after the date of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28178","28178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454846","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's spending was on Overseas Development Aid in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) the first 10 months of 2015-16; and what the recipient countries of that aid were.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28265","28265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454847","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the commitments by the UK not to create obstacles to, but facilitate such deepening of the Eurozone, to sincere cooperation with the Eurozone, not to impede the implementation of legal acts directly linked to the functioning of the euro area to refrain from measures which could jeopardise the attainment of the objectives of economic and monetary union contained in the Decision of the Heads of State or Government, meeting within the European Council, on 18 and 19 February 2016 are legally binding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28383","28383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454848","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in which court the commitment in point 7 of Section A of the Decision of the Heads of State or Government, meeting within the European Council on 18 and 19 February 2016, to incorporate the substance of the section into the EU Treaties is enforceable.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28385","28385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454849","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions mental health trusts in London have paid for private beds since 2010; and on each such occasion (a) from which organisation the bed was purchased and (b) what the cost of that purchase was to the public purse.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28424","28424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454850","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions a Mental Health Act 1983 assessment requested on someone in custody in London took longer than 24 hours in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28425","28425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454851","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police stations in London (a) had and (b) did not have custody nurses working in them in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28426","28426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454852","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 3 on page 5 of the Five Year Forward View Mental Health Task Force report, published on 15 February 2016, if he will make it his policy to provide equal funding for mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28310","28310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454853","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of in which type of healthcare there is greatest geographical disparity of treatment (a) availability, (b) choice and (c) outcomes across England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28312","28312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454854","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of (a) all children and (b) children with mental health conditions aged five to 16 have conduct disorder.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28311","28311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454855","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people with severe and long-term mental health issues and whose care is coordinated through the Care Programme Approach in each year since 2010 had had a formal meeting to review their care in the previous 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28313","28313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454856","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's spending was on Overseas Development Aid in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) the first 10 months of 2015-16; and what the recipient countries of that aid were.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28266","28266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454857","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to support the British Heart Foundations' Wear It Beat It campaign.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28365","28365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454858","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the proposals contained in the report, Surrogacy in the UK: Myth Busting and Reform, published in November 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28366","28366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454859","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many 0 to 17 year olds have received dental treatment in (a) Nottingham North constituency, (b) Nottingham and (c) the UK in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28185","28185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454860","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the proportion of five-year olds eligible for free school meals with severe or extensive tooth decay.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28186","28186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454861","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on developing a national measure of child development at age two to two-and-a-half as part of the public health framework; and when he expects that measure to be introduced.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28206","28206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454862","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimates he has made of the additional resources needed and the cost of providing additional dialysis capacity for those patients who will no longer be suitable for a kidney transplant and for those patients whose transplant graft fails due as a result of restrictions in the range of immunosuppressant agents that will be introduced if the recommendations of the NICE review of TA 85 [ID456] are upheld at appeal.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28211","28211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454863","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to urgently consult with medical authorities on ensuring a meningitis B vaccine is provided to all young children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28230","28230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454864","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on (a) resourcing of kidney and dialysis care in Plymouth Hospitals and Royal Cornwall Hospitals NHS Trusts and (b) care for kidney patients from South East Cornwall of the recent NICE ruling on provision of immune-suppressant drugs.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28239","28239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454865","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 26546, when he expects to publish the consultation document on introducing fixed recoverable costs in clinical negligence claims.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28240","28240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454866","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department last consulted medical authorities on the potential merits of making the meningitis B vaccine available on the NHS for all children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28232","28232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454867","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to meet Mr and Mrs Timmins to discuss the death in 2013  of their son from meningitis B and the future provision of a vaccine for that disease on the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28231","28231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454868","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the £570 million referred to in paragraph 0.5 of his Department's paper, Infected blood: reform of financial and other support, published in January 2016, will be spent in each year of the programme; what the average spend per recipient will be in each such year; and in what categories of spending that funding will fall in each such year.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28374","28374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454869","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions custody nurses were not available in police stations when required in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28375","28375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454870","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 2 of Delivering the Forward View: NHS Planning Guidance, published in December 2015, how much of the £8.4 billion real terms increase in NHS funding by 2020-21 is allocated to mental health; whether that figure includes funding for children and young people's mental health announced before the 2015 General Election; and under which of his Department's budget headings that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28336","28336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454871","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) the Think Kidneys programme, (b) ongoing work relating to acute kidney injury and (c) other work programmes being led by the National Clinical Director for Renal Disease for NHS England will continue to be taken forward following the discontinuance of that director's post.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28334","28334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454872","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training staff in (a) Lancashire and (b) the North West who handle NHS 111 calls receive other that the mandatory training covered by the NHS 111 Commissioning Standards.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28247","28247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454873","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the (a) scale of the difficulty experienced by trusts in recruiting to consultant posts and (b) effect of that difficulty on numbers of occupied consultant posts in cellular pathology.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28248","28248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454874","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many lorries were (a) routinely searched and (b) searched for illegal immigrants at English ports in each of the last three years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28262","28262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454875","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional funding she plans to commit to tackling illegal immigration; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28263","28263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454876","2016-02-26","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications of the findings of the report by Europol, Migrant Smuggling in the EU, published in February 2016, for her policies on tackling smuggling through the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28297","28297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454877","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many social media accounts promoting extremist content were recommended for closure by her Department in each of the last 12 months; and what proportion of such content related to Daesh.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28422","28422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454878","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department was informed of plans by Clearsprings to expand asylum accommodation into East Cardiff.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28423","28423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454879","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was levied in respect of service credits in each key performance indicator designated met in respect of each Compass region in each year from 2012-13 to 2015-16 to date.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28212","28212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454880","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what direct funding has been provided to local authorities in Greater Manchester to manage the community impact of asylum placements in those areas.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28218","28218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454881","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 26859, if she will update her Department's response to e-petition 104867, on legalisation of medicinal cannabis, in respect of the information on availability of the drug Sativex.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28215","28215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454882","2016-02-26","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2016 to Question 23729, what the Government's policy is on the confiscation of the belongings of Syrian refugees over a certain value to help meet the cost of their stay in the UK.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28181","28181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454883","2016-02-26","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to counter people trafficking.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28270","28270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454884","2016-02-26","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what account the police takes of mental health conditions when deciding whether to prosecute people under the Protection from Harassment Act 1997.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28428","28428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454885","2016-02-26","Department for International Development","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will increase aid to Jordan in order to help that country cope with the inflow of Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28175","28175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454886","2016-02-29","Department for International Development","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will issue a response to EDM 1011, Fire at Mzuzu University, Malawi.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28216","28216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454887","2016-02-29","Department for International Development","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has made to reallocate UK aid funding from cross-EU funds and programmes in the event of the UK voting to leave the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28421","28421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454888","2016-02-26","Department for International Development","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential effect of the change in the OECD definition of foreign aid to include some military spending on the effectiveness of aid spend on reducing poverty.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28296","28296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454889","2016-02-26","Department for International Development","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if the Government will contribute emergency aid to Fiji and its surrounding islands following the recent cyclone.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28295","28295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454890","2016-02-26","Department for International Development","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February 2016 to Question 26161, how will the funds raised as result of the Supporting Syria Conference be used to create sustainable jobs in Levantine states with high youth unemployment.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28294","28294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454891","2016-02-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2016 to Question 21452, how many jobs at the Staffordshire and West Midlands Probation Trust were abolished or relocated from Stoke-on Trent between May 2010 and 1 June 2014.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28228","28228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454892","2016-02-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) disturbances and (b) riots have been recorded (i) on the prison estate and (ii) in private prisons since May 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28317","28317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454893","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to Surrogacy in the UK: Myth Busting and Reform, published in November 2015, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to reform the law governing surrogacy to better balance the rights of those involved and the welfare of children born via surrogacy.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28367","28367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454894","2016-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effects on children and families of the parental orders procedure following surrogacy arrangements.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28368","28368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454895","2016-02-26","Scotland Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the implications of a decision to leave the EU on provisions in the Scotland Act 1988 requiring compliance with EU law.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28414","28414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454896","2016-02-29","Prime Minister","2016-02-24","To ask the Prime Minister, what special advisers have (a) successfully and (b) unsuccessfully sought his permission to work on a EU referendum campaign.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28380","28380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454897","2016-02-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Prime Minister's announcement of 10 January 2016 on sink estates, with what bodies he discussed the redevelopment of 100 sink estates; and on what grounds the sum of £140 million for that redevelopment was arrived at.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28338","28338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454898","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what additional capacity for extra stations is planned for East Cardiff as a result of the electrification of the Great Western main line.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28419","28419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454899","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to implement the policy announced on 27 March 2015 by the previous Government on funding to increase the uptake for electric two-wheeled vehicles.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28300","28300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454900","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what he plans his Department's policy on industrial relations with transport unions to be over the next three years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28250","28250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454901","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total cost to Network Rail was of acquiring the ownership of freight sites under Project Mountfield; and what overall revenue received by Network Rail from those sites in 2014-15.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28302","28302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454902","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the value of EU funding was for the Great Western Main Line electrification programme on the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28303","28303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454903","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress Highways England has made on introducing Regional Road Safety Co-ordinators; and whether Highways England's Regional Incident and Casualty Reduction Plans will include targets for casualty reductions.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28304","28304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454904","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many former employees of British Rail were entitled to receive Safeguarded Travel benefits on the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28305","28305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454905","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February 2016 to Question 26407, what funding for cycling in London is included within the (a) £925 million of capital funding and (b) £659 million of resource funding paid to Transport for London.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28225","28225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454906","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2016 to Question 25199, what steps he is taking to encourage the development and implementation of improved HGV design.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28226","28226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454907","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 2 November 2010 to the Questions from the hon. Member for Denton and Reddish, Official Report, column 702W, on bus services: finance, if he will place in the Library a copy of the equalities impact assessment carried out by his Department of the decision to reduce the value of the Bus Service Operators Grant by 20 per cent.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28238","28238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454908","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will direct Highways England to give evidence to the public hearing on 18 March 2016 organised by the West Midlands Police and Crime Commissioner into closures and delays on the M6 on 4 and 5 February 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28176","28176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454909","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that transport trade unions retain confidence in his Department's Senior Civil Servants' impartiality.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28208","28208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454910","2016-02-29","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the comment by Peter Wilkinson, Director of Rail Passenger Services at his Department, of 22 February 2016, about future industrial relations between his Department and transport unions is accurate.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28209","28209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454911","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the relationship between the bus service operators grant and the cost of bus fares.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28183","28183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454912","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of whether the bus service operators grant is used by bus operators to keep fares down.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28184","28184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454913","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's spending was in Overseas Development Aid on (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) the first 10 months of 2015-16; and what the recipient countries of that aid were.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28269","28269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454914","2016-02-26","Women and Equalities","2016-02-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to encourage body confidence in young disabled people.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28172","28172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454915","2016-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what analysis his Department conducts of personal independence payment medical assessments to (a) help identify common issues which cause repeated appeals and reapplications and (b) ensure a consistent approach across such assessments.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28329","28329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454916","2016-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training and guidance is provided to medical assessors who examine claimants for personal independence payment on the implications of (a) dialysis and (b) other long-term medical treatments for such claimants.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28330","28330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454917","2016-02-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the (a) time taken to introduce and (b) cost of introduction of a system of in-work benefits for newly-arrived EU nationals as envisaged in Section D of the Decision of the Heads of State or Government, meeting within the European Council, on 18 and 19 February 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28382","28382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454918","2016-02-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many people in supported housing specifically designated for (a) disabled people, (b) victims of domestic violence, (c) people with substance misuse problems and (d) others will be affected by the change in housing benefit to the Shared Accommodation Rate.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28324","28324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454919","2016-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department provides to (a) claimants of universal credit while the benefit is assessed and dispatched and (b) people becoming unemployed from low-paid and temporary jobs who have no redundancy payments or other income.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28272","28272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454920","2016-02-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the end-dates are of his Department's contracts with Hewlett Packard Enterprise; which such contracts he plans to extend, for what reasons and to what dates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28320","28320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454921","2016-02-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's plans are for the delivery of IT and digital services after the end dates of current contracts.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28321","28321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454922","2016-02-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have made representations to his Department about the proposed change of social sector housing benefit to the level of local housing allowance.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28322","28322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454923","2016-02-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many housing providers made representations to his Department about the proposed change of social sector housing benefit to the level of local housing allowance.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28323","28323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454924","2016-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to employment and support allowance for new claimants in the work-related activity group on the mental health of those affected.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28273","28273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454925","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what (a) human resources, (b) communications, (c) grant administration, (d) building and estates management and (e) other administrative functions are shared by the seven research councils; and which such services are delivered independently by each research council.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28358","28358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454926","2016-02-26","Cabinet Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate how many (a) people and (b) organisations will be affected by the interim guidance on the new anti-lobbying clause in government grant agreements.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28255","28255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454927","2016-02-26","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Swedish government over their decision to end the production of coins containing nickel; whether he plans to further investigate the health risks posed to those who suffer from nickel allergy of the decision to switch to steel nickel-plated 5p and 10p coins in 2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28293","28293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454928","2016-02-26","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the uptake of the marriage tax allowance is; what steps he is taking to increase uptake of that allowance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28276","28276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454929","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse of the Defence Assistance Fund was in 2014-15.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28398","28398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454930","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to his Department of the Export Support Team was in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15; and whether those costs have been reimbursed by the UK Trade and Investment Defence and Security Organisation.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28396","28396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454931","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost was of maintaining the defence attaché network in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15; and what proportion of the cost of that network was attributable to support for defence and security exports.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28397","28397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454932","2016-02-26","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what official foreign visits she has undertaken since 1 October 2015; and what the cost to the public purse was of those visits.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28257","28257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454933","2016-02-26","Department for Education","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2016 to Question 27540, under whose jurisdiction objections citing provisions relating to the Armed Forces Covenant excluding those relating to service premium admission would fall.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28355","28355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454934","2016-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many organisations in receipt of grant funding awarded by her Department were found to have engaged in activity that influenced or attempted to influence Parliament, government, or the European Commission, or were found to have attempted to influence legislative or regulatory action in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28292","28292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454935","2016-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which organisations have received public grant funding from her Department in each of the last three years; and what the purposes of each grant were.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28359","28359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454936","2016-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she has taken to ensure that all renewables can compete on equal terms in the additional rounds of renewable subsidy auctions scheduled between now and 2020.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28360","28360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454937","2016-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she has taken to support the Humber region's biomass projects.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28361","28361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454938","2016-02-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will place in the Library a copy of the representations which Natural England made in response to the (a) proposal in the draft Christchurch local plan for housing development on green belt land at Marsh Lane, Christchurch, and (b) planning application by Dorset County Council for a two-form entry primary school on green belt land at Marsh Lane, Christchurch.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28405","28405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454939","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Decision of the Heads of State or Government, meeting within the European Council, on 18 and 19 February 2016 will be deposited at the United Nations.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28357","28357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454940","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2016 to Question 27033, which governments within the EU support further political integration.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28406","28406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454941","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the EU, Africa and the Middle East on addressing the refugee crisis in the Middle East.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28362","28362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454942","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Turkish counterpart on military action in the south east of Turkey and the consequences of that action for Kurdish civilians.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28254","28254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454943","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make ithis policy to assess the potential merits of the pledge by the Austrian government set out in the report by the International Campaign to Abolish Nuclear Weapons, A Pledge to Fill the Legal Gap, published in February 2015 for the work of the UN Open Ended Working Group on multilateral disarmament negotiations.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28395","28395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454944","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials of his Department undertook language classes at (a) his Department and (b) post in (i) 2001 and (ii) 2010.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28289","28289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454945","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) Arabic speakers with an operational level (C1) examination pass and (b) Mandarin Cantonese speakers were employed by his Department in (i) 2001 and (ii) 2010.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28290","28290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454946","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials of his Department had an operational level (C1) examination pass in which languages in (a) 2001 and (b) 2010.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28291","28291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454947","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were admitted to hospital as a result of NHS 111 calls made in 2015 in (a) Lancashire and (b) Burnley.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28393","28393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454948","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS 111 calls were made in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015 in (i) Lancashire and (ii) Burnley.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28394","28394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454949","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulances were called out as a result of NHS 111 calls made in 2015 in (a) Lancashire and (b) Burnley.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28392","28392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454950","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting times are for access to talking therapies in (a) the UK, (b) Yorkshire and (c) Halifax.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28274","28274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454951","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the effect on survival rates in kidney patients and on the Domain 1 outcomes of the NHS Outcomes Framework of transplants unsuccessful because of the lack of availability of immunosuppression treatments that the patient can tolerate, following the recommendation from the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (review of TA 85) [ID456] to restrict access to such agents.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28356","28356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454952","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what security arrangements are in place to protect patient data.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28279","28279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454953","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to prevent patient data being used for purposes other than direct care.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28280","28280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454954","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effects of proposed changes to the way in which drugs are assessed for inclusion in the Cancer Drugs Fund on cancer drug patients.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28363","28363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454955","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the Alzheimer's Society's Fix Dementia Care campaign.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28364","28364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454956","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the £390 million funding referred to in paragraph 0.5 of his Department's paper, Infected blood: reform of financial and other support, published in January 2016, was spent in each year to date; and what the average spend per recipient in each such year was.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28408","28408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454957","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of funding that will be required for those who may need access to the reformed scheme for providing support for people affected by hepatitis C through treatment with NHS-supplied blood or blood products but have not yet been identified.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28409","28409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454958","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library a copy of the full impact assessment of the infected blood scheme reform consultation containing the assessment of the potential financial effects of proposed reforms on recipients; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28410","28410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454959","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that approved personalised medicines are available to patients with colorectal cancer.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28411","28411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454960","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department is having with NHS England on ensuring patients continuing access established precision treatments for colorectal cancer.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28403","28403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454961","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage routine use of NHS medicines throughout the NHS.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28278","28278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454962","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department, NHS England and NICE will publish work undertaken to analyse variation between areas in treatment for patients during the transition from the current Cancer Drugs Fund (CDF) to proposed a new CDF scheme.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28283","28283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454963","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letters dated 11 December 2015, 14 January and 10 February 2016 from the Dorset Police and Crime Commissioner on port security and border controls; and if she will place a copy of her responses in the Library.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28407","28407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454964","2016-02-26","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many project licence applications under the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 were (a) granted and (b) refused on the basis of the results of the harm-benefit analysis carried out on those applications by the Animals in Science Regulation Unit.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28258","28258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454965","2016-02-29","Home Office","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what financial savings she expects to result from the transfer of processing Bangladeshi visa applications to New Delhi.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28319","28319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454966","2016-02-26","Department for International Development","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, for what reason her Department cancelled Round Six of the UK Aid Match Fund; for what reason that cancellation was not announced earlier; for what reason that cancellation was not announced earlier; and what assessment she has made of the effect of that cancellation on charities who were developing proposals.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28288","28288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454967","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure children and families created via surrogacy are treated equally.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28369","28369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454968","2016-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to respond to Question 18949, tabled by the hon. Member for Halifax on 7 December 2015.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28275","28275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454969","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 2.41 of the Government's paper, The best of both worlds: the United Kingdom's special status in a reformed European Union, published in February 2016, what contribution he expects UK environmental and energy safety regulators to make to the annual survey referred to.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28373","28373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454970","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February 2016 to Question 26406, how much is included in the Business Rate Retention Scheme funding stream to reflect the changes to the payment of Bus Service Operators Grant that were introduced in 2013.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28284","28284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454971","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to maintain a strong commercial bus market in northern regions of the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28370","28370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454972","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills about the effect of bus franchising in the vehicle manufacturing sector.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28371","28371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454973","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that bus operators have an incentive to invest in new vehicles when franchising is an option open to local authorities.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28372","28372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454974","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons Highways England have not held consultation events on the proposals for a new Lower Thames Crossing in Stanford-le-Hope, Langdon Hills, Laindon, Dunton and other areas affected by those proposals.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28402","28402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454975","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the data used to predict traffic flow at the proposed new Lower Thames Crossing - Option C was generated; and whether that data is publicly available.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28399","28399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454976","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans are in place to upgrade the existing Dartford Crossing and the A282.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28400","28400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454977","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that (a) Shropshire Council, (b) Telford and Wrekin Council and (c) Highways England put in place road safety improvements to reduce the number of road deaths and injuries on roads in (i) Shropshire and (ii) Telford and Wrekin.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28277","28277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454978","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Option A for a new Lower Thames Crossing is still (a) included in the consultation and (b) considered by his Department to be a viable option.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28401","28401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454979","2016-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many disabled people will move into work as a result of changes to the employment and allowance work-related activity group; and what research he has conducted into the effects of those changes.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28282","28282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454980","2016-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Halifax constituency will be affected by changes to employment and support allowance for new claimants in the work-related activity group.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28256","28256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454981","2016-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to support disabled people affected by the changes to employment and support allowance work-related activity group.","Biography information for Victoria Borwick","Victoria Borwick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28281","28281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454982","2016-02-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will commission an evaluation of the effectiveness of support for former Independent Living Fund recipients.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28404","28404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454983","2016-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is possible for prisoners to start their universal credit application so that it is processed and ready to be applied when they are released.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28285","28285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454984","2016-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether there are special procedures for universal credit applications for prisoners with mental health issues.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28286","28286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454985","2016-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the target timescale is for people leaving prison from application to receipt for universal credit; and how many and what proportion of applications take longer than that timescale.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28287","28287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/456291","2016-03-01","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to increase the personal allowance during this Parliament.","Biography information for Alan Mak","Mr Alan Mak","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903839","903839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/456292","2016-03-01","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to create a fiscal surplus by the end of this Parliament.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903837","903837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/456293","2016-03-01","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of successful prosecutions for tax evasion.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903830","903830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/456294","2016-03-01","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the findings of the most recent OECD Interim Economic Outlook.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903832","903832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/456295","2016-03-01","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to widen access to financial advice.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903831","903831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/456296","2016-03-01","HM Treasury","2016-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of his Department's fiscal policies on the financial position of women.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903835","903835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454007","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on the future of the Innovate UK Smart funding programme.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27864","27864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454008","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what academic research he has commissioned on the expected behavioural response of employers to the introduction of the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27865","27865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454009","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how his Department decides on allocation of funding to research councils; and what assessment he has made of the grounds for significant changes being made to the relative size of allocations to each research council compared to allocations in previous years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27862","27862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454010","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the staff costs are for (a) Crouch End Crown Post Office and (b) Muswell Hill Crown Post Office in 2015-16.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27877","27877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454011","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Post Office has spent refurbishing the premises of the Crown Post Offices in (a) Crouch End and (b) Muswell Hill since January 2010.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27878","27878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454012","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses have signed agreements with the Business Growth Service in each local authority area in the UK.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27882","27882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454013","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much central government funding has been allocated to (a) the London Local Enterprise Partnership and (b) all Local Enterprise Partnerships to support the creative industries in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27885","27885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454014","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many meetings he has held with UK Trade and Investment trade envoys since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27901","27901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454015","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what financial and other resources the Government makes available to UK Trade and Investment trade envoys.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27902","27902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454016","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many overseas visits have been carried out by UK Trade and Investment trade envoys in each year since September 2012.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27903","27903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454017","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the cost of the trade envoy programme has been since its launch in September 2012.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27904","27904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454018","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27924","27924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454019","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27945","27945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454020","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the variation in the number of teaching hours provided to and fees paid by university students.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27969","27969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454021","2016-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will instruct the National Measurement and Regulation Office to publish a list of all known heat networks in the UK.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27989","27989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454022","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether energy suppliers are obligated to report to the National Measurement and Regulation Office when a heat network is established or a lease is acquired.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27988","27988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454023","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 25652, whether people resident in Northern Ireland are able to apply for apprenticeships in England.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28014","28014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454024","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 25652, whether EU nationals are able to apply for apprenticeships in England.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28015","28015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454025","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 25652, what media outlets will be used to carry advertising as part of the national campaign for apprenticeships.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28016","28016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454026","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of members in Northern Ireland of each trade union opted to pay the political levy; and which of those trade unions' headquarters are in (a) Great Britain and (b) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28028","28028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454027","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of trade union members in (a) Great Britain and (b) Northern Ireland pay the political levy.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28029","28029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454028","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will estimate the cost to the economy of unreliable internet connectivity and speeds in 2014-15.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28087","28087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454029","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the average lifetime difference in salaries earned by graduates compared with non-graduates.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28095","28095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454030","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of his Department's UK National Contact Point in investigating complaints on private sector contract compliance with UK human rights commitments.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28076","28076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454031","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether employers named and shamed by his Department on 5 February 2016 for non-payment of the national minimum wage and found to be owing arrears to a select number of employees subsequently had their whole workforce investigated by HM Revenue and Customs to ascertain if the same practice applied to all other workers employed.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28094","28094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454032","2016-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the report, The Size and Performance of the UK Low Carbon Economy, published in March 2015, whether estimates of gross value added for electricity generation include (a) the value of renewable obligation certificates and (b) the element of the feed-in tariff and Contract for Difference prices which are above the market price of energy.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28109","28109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454033","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many responses his Department received to the devolving Sunday trading rules consultation.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28167","28167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454034","2016-02-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many responses to the Government's consultation on devolving Sunday trading rules were opposed to any relaxation of Sunday trading rules.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28168","28168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454035","2016-03-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2016 to Question 26010, when the Departmental Reading Room for access to consolidated texts related to the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership will be opened.","Biography information for John Cryer","John Cryer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28171","28171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454036","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the distribution of the average graduate premium by each decile of graduate earnings ten years after graduation.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28097","28097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454037","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the average difference in salaries earned by graduates and non-graduates ten years after graduation.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28096","28096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454038","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the apprenticeship levy on the training requirements of small and medium-sized firms unable to access the levy.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28100","28100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454039","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the apprenticeship levy on training and skills funding for people aged over 21.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28101","28101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454040","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department intends to cease any existing or planned business support mechanisms in order to implement the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28102","28102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454041","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the estimated (a) cost of establishing and (b) annual running cost of the Institute of Apprenticeships is; whether his Department has made an assessment of the effects of funding that institute on his Department's annual programme budget; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28157","28157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454042","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish his Department's impact assessment of the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28103","28103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454043","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for projects supported by State Aid agreements of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28116","28116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454044","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2016 to Question 25610, how many national minimum wage enquiries were made to (a) the Pay and Work Rights Helpline and (b) Acas between 2009-10 and 2014-15 by (i) domiciliary and (ii) residential care workers.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28163","28163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454045","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2016 to Question 25610, how many national minimum wage enquiries relating to non-payment or deductions were made to (a) the Pay and Work Rights Helpline and (b) Acas by people working in (i) domiciliary and (ii) residential care between 2009-10 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28164","28164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454046","2016-02-26","Cabinet Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance his Department issues to senior civil servants attending events organised by hon. Members of the Government party.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28063","28063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454047","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Communities and Local Government on the applicability of that Department's anti-sock puppet clause pilot scheme to other departments.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28159","28159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454048","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what representations he has received outlining concerns related to his Department's new anti-lobbying policy.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28110","28110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454049","2016-02-26","Cabinet Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance his Department provides to senior civil servants on speaking at public events.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28062","28062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454050","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for the policies of the Cabinet Office of the recommendations of the Mental Health Taskforce report, published in February 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28085","28085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454051","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what (a) guidance his Department issues and (b) regulations are in place on the provision of electoral roll data to credit reference agencies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28021","28021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454052","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what checks his Department has in place to ensure that credit reference firms do not sell-on electoral roll data.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28018","28018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454053","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many complaints his Department has received on the sale of electoral roll data by credit reference firms.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28019","28019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454054","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance his Department issues to credit reference firms on handling data on people who are on the closed electoral register.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28020","28020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454055","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27946","27946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454056","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27925","27925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454057","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Wolverhampton South West dated 11 January 2016 on the Connaught Income Fund, reference ZA2351.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27888","27888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454058","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many publicly-funded jobs relating directly to the Northern Powerhouse there are in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) Yorkshire and the Humber, (d) London and (e) other regions of England.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27880","27880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454059","2016-02-26","HM Treasury","2016-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many investigations have been opened by HM Revenue and Customs under IR35 in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27858","27858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454060","2016-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people automatically enrolled into workplace pensions between October 2012 and October 2013 have since withdrawn from that scheme.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27859","27859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454061","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the savings to the public purse of the proposed reduction of child benefits paid overseas.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27861","27861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454062","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the administration costs of the proposals in which child benefit for EU migrants would be indexed to the country where the child is resident for new claimants.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27852","27852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454063","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the reduction in the amount of child benefit spend on those EU migrants with a child resident in another country as a result of proposals to index the claims to the country where the child is resident.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27853","27853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454064","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each member of his Department's Council of Economic Advisers.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27967","27967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454065","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27963","27963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454066","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27942","27942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454067","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of businesses which are planning to pass on the increase in their National Insurance contributions from April 2016 to their employees.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27981","27981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454068","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of student loans provided by the Government are to students from other EU states; what proportion of those loans are repaid in full; and what the average amount repaid is of those loans.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28088","28088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454069","2016-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the UK paid to the EU for agricultural levies in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28082","28082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454070","2016-02-26","HM Treasury","2016-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of whether a five per cent VAT rate could continue to apply to solar PV and solar thermal within the terms of the EU's VAT directive and the judgment of the European Court of Justice on that matter.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28166","28166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454071","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the Government's policy is on funding for the Equitable Life Payment Scheme that has not been disbursed.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28146","28146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454072","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many organisations were affected by his Department's pilot of anti-sock puppet rules; how many exemptions were made under that pilot scheme; and what estimate he has made of the savings to the public purse that arose from that pilot scheme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28158","28158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454073","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions he has (a) revoked or (b) modified planning permission under Section 100 of the Town and Country Planning Act 1990 in each year since 2009-10; on how many such occasions the local planning authority paid compensation to developers in respect of that decision; and what the total value of the compensation paid to developers in those circumstances was in each of those years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28112","28112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454074","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions in each year since 2009-10 he has been asked to confirm a local planning authority's decision to revoke planning permission under Section 97 of the Town and Country Planning Act 1990; and on how many such occasions he (a) confirmed and (b) overturned that decision.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28113","28113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454075","2016-02-26","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what training is being given to members of Fire and Rescue Services who may find themselves acting as first responders as a result of collaboration between emergency services.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28074","28074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454076","2016-02-26","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Fire and Rescue Services have trained staff who can act as first responders; how many such staff have received training.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28073","28073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454077","2016-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many pupils in the North West have received funding from the European Regional Development Fund; and what the total investment from that fund in that region has been in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28127","28127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454078","2016-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2016 to Question 26305; what estimate his Department has made of the total number of licenses granted for houses of multiple occupation which are in use in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28054","28054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454079","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2015 to Question 15112, when he intends to bring forward amendments to the Town and Country Planning (General Permitted Development) (England) Order 2015; what provisions will apply to office premises that have been granted prior approval for conversion to residential use but which will not be completed before 30 May 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28026","28026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454080","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27926","27926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454081","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27947","27947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454082","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the balances held by all English local authorities.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27847","27847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454083","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Written Statement of 10 February 2016, HCWS520, when he expects the Review of the Homes and Communities Agency to be published.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27884","27884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454084","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had on introducing new duties on local authorities to assess the level of need for wheelchair accessible homes and set appropriate targets in local development plans.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27874","27874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454085","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of starter homes that will be wheelchair accessible.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27875","27875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454086","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to ensure that local authorities meet their obligation under the National Planning Policy Framework to meet the housing needs of disabled people requiring wheelchair accessible homes.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27876","27876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454087","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to increase the supply of wheelchair accessible homes in the social and affordable housing sector.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27870","27870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454088","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of people requiring wheelchair accessible homes in (a) Easington, (b) the North East and (c) England.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27871","27871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454089","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to help the social housing sector maintain and increase the provision of specialist accessible and adapted housing stock for people with disabilities.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27872","27872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454090","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to secure the adequate supply of accessible homes suitable for disabled people.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27873","27873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454091","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what powers are available to (a) parish, (b) district and (c) county councils to dispose of abandoned boats in coastal areas; and whether a disposal cost recovery scheme exists for such disposals.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27909","27909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454092","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions in each year since 2009-10 he has directed that a planning application appeal which would otherwise be determined by a person appointed by the Secretary of State will instead be determined by the Secretary of State, using his powers under Schedule 6, Paragraph 3 of the Town and Country Planning Act 1990.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27886","27886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454093","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many appeals against Local Planning Authority decisions by developers he has received under Section 78 of the Town and Country Planning Act 1990 in each year since 2009-10; in how many of those cases in each year did he exercise his powers under Section 79 of that Act to (a) allow under Section 79(1)(a), (b) dismiss under Section 79(1)(b), (c) decline to determine under Section 79(6), (d) dismiss under Section 79(6A) the appeal and (e) amend the planning authority's original decision in any way; and in how many such cases the Local Planning Authority subsequently paid compensation to the developer as a result of his decision.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27887","27887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454094","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will make assistance available to local authorities for the costs of disposing of abandoned boats, vessels and other sea-faring equipment.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27908","27908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454095","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will ring-fence housing payments for tenants in supported accommodation.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27843","27843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454096","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the capacity of Ofcom to protect the rights of internet service provider customers.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27863","27863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454097","2016-02-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what further assistance his Department plans to give the devolved legislatures for providing access to higher speed broadband services.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27855","27855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454098","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27948","27948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454099","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27927","27927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454100","2016-02-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which arts organisations have received public funding of more than £5 million in the last three years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28012","28012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454101","2016-02-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which arts organisations have been allocated capital grants of more than £5 million in the last three years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28013","28013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454102","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what criteria Arts Council England uses to allocate funding to theatre companies; and how much such funding has been disbursed to theatre companies in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28089","28089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454103","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans the Government has to commemorate the 100th anniversary of the Battle of Gallipoli.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28090","28090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454104","2016-02-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment (a) his Department and (b) Ofcom has made of the number of (a) business parks which do not have superfast broadband and (b) businesses based in business parks which do not have superfast broadband.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28131","28131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454105","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of each type of (a) combat vehicles, (b) protected patrol vehicles and (c) reconnaissance vehicles was classified as fit for service in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28122","28122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454106","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Vector protected vehicles were in operational use by the army in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28120","28120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454107","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on replacement of Vector protected patrol vehicles.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28121","28121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454108","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many equipment failure reports were filed for each type of (a) combat vehicle, (b) protected patrol vehicle and (c) reconnaissance vehicle in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28119","28119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454109","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many RAF airstrikes have taken place against Daesh targets in (a) Iraq and (b) Syria since 2 December 2015.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28134","28134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454110","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when a copy of DCDS(MilCap)/14/06/11, dated 18 June 2014, was presented to the Procurator Fiscal.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28106","28106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454111","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) date and (b) remit was of his authorisation to use RAF Lakenheath as a base to carry out airstrikes in Libya.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28098","28098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454112","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times Russian military (a) aircraft and (b) ships have entered British territory in the last 12 months; what the average response time was for the armed forces on each of those occasions; and what the type and model was of the aircraft or ship on each of those occasions.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28153","28153"
