"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227302","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what amount his Department and its agencies spent on research and development in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion such spending was of total departmental spending.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227561","227561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227303","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of a ketogenic diet in treating brain cancer patients.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227519","227519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227304","2015-03-18","Department of Health","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to reduce waiting times for urgent referrals of epilepsy patients.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227574","227574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227305","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what technologies are being developed with support from the Small Business Research Initiative programmes of (a) his Department and (b) NHS England; and what assessment he has made of the future potential uses of those technologies.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227523","227523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227306","2015-03-17","Home Office","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an estimate of potential savings from mergers of police forces.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227570","227570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227307","2015-03-17","Home Office","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what amount her Department and its agencies spent on research and development in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion such spending was of total departmental spending.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227562","227562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227308","2015-03-17","Home Office","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff in her Department and its executive agencies and associated bodies were engaged off-payroll in each of the last five years up to the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227549","227549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227310","2015-03-18","House of Commons Commission","2015-03-13","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what discussions the Commission has had with (a) Apple and (b) providers of other devices and platforms in advance of the decision to offer iPads free of charge to all hon. Members.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227500","227500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227311","2015-03-18","House of Commons Commission","2015-03-13","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what assessment the Commission has made of the suitability of the iPad for the open source, open standards and open data approach to digital services promoted by the Government Digital Service.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227499","227499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227312","2015-03-18","House of Commons Commission","2015-03-13","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what comparative assessment the Commission has made of the costs of offering iPads and equivalent Android devices free of charge to all hon. Members.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227498","227498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227313","2015-03-17","Department for International Development","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what amount her Department and its agency spent on research and development in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion such spending was of total departmental spending.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227563","227563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227314","2015-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what amount his Department and its agencies spent on research and development in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion such spending was of total departmental spending.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227564","227564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227315","2015-03-17","Department for Transport","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many off-payroll engagements there were in (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's arms-length bodies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227508","227508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227316","2015-03-17","Department for Transport","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what amount his Department and its agencies spent on research and development in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion such spending was of total departmental spending.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227565","227565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227317","2015-03-18","Department for Transport","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2015 to Question 226547, what assessment he has made of the merits of deploying civil enforcement officers rather than using cameras to enforce mandatory cycle lanes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227536","227536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227318","2015-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's 2013 Impact Assessment No. DWP0031, if he will provide a detailed breakdown of the (a) £123 million estimated cost of caseworker activity related to Child Support Agency (CSA) case arrears as part of the CSA case closure programme and (b) £20 million estimated cost of setting up areas on the Child Maintenance Service System; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227571","227571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227319","2015-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance referred to the Work Programme in 2013 or earlier (i) have and (ii) have not achieved a sustained job outcome.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227532","227532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227320","2015-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to support faith-based employment support initiatives since May 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227533","227533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227321","2015-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he plans to take to implement consistent communications by his Department on mandatory reconsideration.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227534","227534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227322","2015-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to support job clubs run by volunteers since May 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227535","227535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227323","2015-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what amount his Department and its agencies spent on research and development in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion such spending was of total departmental spending.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227567","227567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227324","2015-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff in his Department and its executive agencies and associated bodies were engaged off-payroll in each of the last five years up to the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227551","227551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227325","2015-03-18","HM Treasury","2015-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when it was decided that bailiffs could be used to recover alleged overpayment of tax credits; who took that decision; and whether it is his policy that processes to recover alleged overpayments are stayed at the request of an hon. Member for such an allegation to be investigated.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227525","227525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227326","2015-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Preston constituency (a) applied for and (b) received a Social Fund funeral payment in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227510","227510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227327","2015-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Preston constituency are in receipt of carer's allowance.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227511","227511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227077","2015-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of funding allocated to the Youth Contract programme for 2014-15 has been disbursed to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227390","227390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227078","2015-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many cases were referred to the Office of the Independent Adjudicator for each higher education institution by students of each (a) gender and (b) ethnic origin in each of the last five years; and how many of those cases concerned (i) undergraduate and (ii) postgraduate students.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227410","227410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227079","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many further education colleges there were in each of the past five years; and what estimate he has made of how many further education colleges there will be in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227447","227447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227080","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students were enrolled in further education colleges in each of the past five years; and what estimate he has made of the number of students enrolled in further education colleges in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227448","227448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227081","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many teachers and lecturers worked in the further education sector in each of the past five years; and what estimate he has made of the number of teachers and lecturers  working in that sector in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227449","227449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227082","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much and what proportion of his Department's (a) expenditure and (b) budget was allocated to the further education sector in each of the past five years; and what estimate he has made of that amount and proportion that will be allocated to that sector in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227450","227450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227083","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received from (a) schools, (b) colleges, (c) trade associations, (d) charities, (e) education experts, (f) teachers, (g) lecturers, (h) students and (i) parents on the future funding of further education colleges.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227451","227451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227084","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average number of subjects or courses offered by further education colleges was in each of the past five years; and what estimate he has made of the average number of subjects or courses that will be offered by further education colleges in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227452","227452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227085","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many small and medium-sized enterprises received money from the Funding for Lending Scheme in (a) Preston, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013 and (iii) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227463","227463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227086","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the mean class size was in further education colleges in each of the last five years; and what forecast his Department has made of the likely mean class size in such colleges in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227455","227455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227087","2015-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support the development of business and skills that will assist the UK in further developing trade links with Turkey.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227479","227479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227088","2015-03-17","Cabinet Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what arrangements are in place for Parliamentary Counsel to refer to the Law Officers proposals for legislation which appear to Parliamentary Counsel to be compliant with the European Convention on Human Rights but objectionable on fundamental grounds of fairness or legislative propriety.","Biography information for Sir Richard Shepherd","Sir Richard Shepherd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227412","227412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227089","2015-03-17","Cabinet Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what arrangements are in place to ensure that the drafting of statutory guidance, codes of practice and other forms of secondary legislation is of a consistent quality across Government and fit for purpose.","Biography information for Sir Richard Shepherd","Sir Richard Shepherd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227413","227413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227090","2015-03-17","Cabinet Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of Acts of Parliament in the present Parliament included a power for Ministers to make supplementary and incidental provision by secondary legislation for the purpose of giving full effect to the Act or for similar purposes; and if he will make arrangements to restrict instances of those powers to cases where they can be justified by urgency or other factors preventing the Bill for the Act from dealing fully with consequential and incidental matters.","Biography information for Sir Richard Shepherd","Sir Richard Shepherd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227414","227414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227091","2015-03-17","Cabinet Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what changes have been made in the structure and working arrangements of the Parliamentary Counsel Office in the present Parliament; and what steps have been taken to ensure that those changes do not adversely affect the quality of legislative drafting.","Biography information for Sir Richard Shepherd","Sir Richard Shepherd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227415","227415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227092","2015-03-17","Cabinet Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which recommendations of Lord Renton's Report on the Preparation of Legislation, Cmnd. 6053, published in 1975, have yet to be implemented; and what arrangements are proposed for the implementation of those recommendations.","Biography information for Sir Richard Shepherd","Sir Richard Shepherd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227416","227416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227093","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) couples and (b) single people living alone there were aged over (i) 65 and (ii) 80 in (A) York Central constituency and (B) City of York local authority area at the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227382","227382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227094","2015-03-17","HM Treasury","2015-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many cider and perry producers are registered as exempt from paying duty in (a) Hereford and South Herefordshire constituency, (b) Herefordshire and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227391","227391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227095","2015-03-17","HM Treasury","2015-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on the tax treatment of people living as co-workers at intentional communities run by the Camphill Village Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227495","227495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227096","2015-03-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, in how many local authorities council tax has not increased in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227496","227496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227097","2015-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much waste was recycled in City of York local authority area in 2009-10 and in each subsequent year.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227388","227388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227098","2015-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues to local government offices responsible for processing housing benefit and council tax discount scheme claims on withdrawal of pension fund money under the pension freedom rules that come into force in April 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227407","227407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227099","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with fire authorities in England and Wales on pension rights for firefighters who fail fitness tests due to illness; and how many of those authorities have indicated to him that they cannot pay those pensions.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227419","227419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227100","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent progress the Government has made on increasing competition among internet service providers.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227403","227403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227101","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps he has taken to implement EU regulations on net neutrality.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227421","227421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227102","2015-03-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations he has made to the inquiry on the proposal for the Navitus Bay offshore wind farm on the effect on the Jurassic Coast World Heritage Site of that proposal.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227432","227432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227103","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he expects all internet connection speeds to be 2Mbps or more in (a) Windsor constituency, (b) South-East England and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227435","227435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227104","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of (a) the value of and (b) the number of jobs provided by the cyber-security industry in the UK in the last five years.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227395","227395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227105","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has regular discussions with BBC management on the sources from which the BBC receives external financing.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227383","227383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227106","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department has spent on promoting or advertising (a) fibre optic and (b) satellite broadband to the public in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227476","227476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227107","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on British army pensions in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227384","227384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227108","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many suitably qualified and experienced personnel positions are (a) required and (b) vacant in (i) Type 23 and (ii) Type 45 ship crews.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227425","227425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227109","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2015 to Question 226517, if he will place a copy of the review by the Tornado Collision Service Inquiry Panel in the Library.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227404","227404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227110","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the statement by the Chief of Staff of the US Army that he was very concerned by the UK's defence budget.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227420","227420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227111","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the armed forces have been made redundant in (a) Preston, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013 and (v) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227467","227467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227112","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) regular and reserve armed forces personnel and (b) regular and reserve armed forces personnel based in Plymouth have been involved in operations to control the outbreak of Ebola in West Africa.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227458","227458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227113","2015-03-17","Department for Education","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what public consultations her Department has conducted since January 2014; and how many responses her Department has received to each of those consultations.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227442","227442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227114","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's spending was for each student in (a) Preston, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227462","227462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227115","2015-03-17","Department for Education","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she will support the proposals of her French counterpart for including specific reference to anti-Semitism in citizenship education at the meeting of EU Ministers of Education in Paris on 17 March 2015.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227422","227422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227116","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 3 February 2015 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr T Cook.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227429","227429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227117","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice and guidance his Department has provided to local authorities on the effect of the Care Act 2014 on young carers.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227490","227490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227118","2015-03-17","Department for Education","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the decision by Oxford Cambridge and RSA not to redevelop GCSE and A Level Turkish on the ability of students to acquire skills in Turkish; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227493","227493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227119","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information his Department holds on (a) how much profit each of the six largest energy companies made and (b) how much of that profit they distributed to shareholders in (i) 2010 and (ii) each subsequent year.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227381","227381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227120","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many homes in (a) York Central constituency and (b) City of York local authority area were retrofitted with cavity wall insulation, lagging or other measures to conserve energy in 2010 and each subsequent year.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227376","227376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227121","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many homes in (a) York Central constituency and (b) City of York local authority area were microgeneration energy producers using solar or wind power in 2010 and in each subsequent year.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227377","227377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227122","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many homes in (a) York Central constituency and (b) City of York local authority area have a prepayment electricity meter.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227378","227378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227123","2015-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of air quality in (a) York Central constituency and (b) City of York local authority area in 2010 and each subsequent year.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227379","227379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227124","2015-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department spent on bottled water in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227423","227423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227125","2015-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Environment Agency's flood and coastal erosion risk management investment programme 2015 to 2021, what estimate she has made of the number of properties that will be protected in the (a) Royal Borough of Windsor and Maidenhead, (b) Thames Valley and (c) UK by that programme.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227424","227424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227126","2015-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) wild animals and (b) different species of animal are licensed under the Welfare of Wild Animals in Travelling Circuses (England) Regulations 2012.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227431","227431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227127","2015-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people have been convicted of animal abuse since 2005.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227427","227427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227128","2015-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2015 to Question 226362, whether the preparation of cannon for lifting and the dusting of mobile sediments on the wreck site of HMS Victory 1744 by Odyssey Marine Exploration in the summer of 2012 was included in the Marine Management Organisation investigation into unauthorised work on the HMS Victory 1744 wreck site.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227478","227478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227129","2015-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to support businesses in developing areas  which support pollinators.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227445","227445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227130","2015-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on shortening supply chains in food production; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227494","227494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227131","2015-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish best practice guidelines for people carrying out the control agreements and orders introduced under the Infrastructure Act 2015 to ensure that animals are killed in the most humane way possible.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227483","227483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227132","2015-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of the Environment Agency budget was spent on flood defences and prevention in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227475","227475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227133","2015-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many kittens and cats entered the UK under the EU Pet Travel Scheme in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227485","227485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227134","2015-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the number of cats that have been brought into the UK illegally in the last three years.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227486","227486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227135","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that Russia remains a member of the Council of Europe.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227446","227446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227136","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that parents of abducted children can access legal aid.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227443","227443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227137","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that child abduction cases are dealt with  in a manner which takes account of the sensitivity of such cases.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227444","227444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227138","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 2 February 2015 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr M Woronycz.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227428","227428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227139","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which services the Vale of York Clinical Commissioning Group (CCG) declined to fund, in some or all cases, or restricted access to, for patients in their area, which were funded without such restriction for patients living in other CCG areas in 2013 and in each subsequent year.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227380","227380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227140","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many falls (a) at home and (b) in total were recorded by health and social care providers in (i) York Central constituency and (ii) City of York local authority area in 2010 and each subsequent year.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227385","227385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227141","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many family members looking after a relative at home were registered as carers with the local authority in (a) York Central constituency and (b) City of York local authority area in (i) April 2010 and (ii) each subsequent April.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227386","227386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227142","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Vale of York Clinical Commissioning Group spent on managing provider contracts in 2013 and in each subsequent year.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227389","227389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227143","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings of the research report Are fluoride levels in drinking water associated with hypothyroidism prevalence in England, published by the University of Kent's Centre for Health Services in February 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227426","227426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227144","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what powers he possesses to take action against abortion providers which fail to comply with his Department's interpretation of the Abortion Act 1967 as set out in the Guidance on the Requirements of the Abortion Act 1967.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227430","227430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227145","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department asked NICE to produce a clinical guideline and quality standard on adult hearing loss; and when he expects NICE to produce those documents.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227433","227433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227146","2015-03-19","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue a direction to the Chief Executive of NHS Care Services to reply to the letter of 13 February 2015 sent by the right hon. Member for Tonbridge and Malling to his company's Head of Communications, Dr Belinda Webb-Blofeld, for urgent response.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227434","227434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227147","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on the merger of Frimley Park NHS Trust and Heatherwood and Wrexham Park NHS Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227397","227397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227148","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many babies weighing (a) less than and (b) more than 1,000g and which were born at (i) 22, (ii) 23 and (iii) 24 weeks' gestation survived in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227409","227409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227149","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS patients registered for clinical trials in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227402","227402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227150","2015-03-16","Department for International Development","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many (a) NHS staff and (b) NHS staff in Plymouth have been involved in operations to control the outbreak of Ebola in West Africa.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227459","227459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227151","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of clinical consultations conducted by online pharmacies.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227460","227460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227152","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment Public Health England has made of the effect of remote prescribing of oral antibiotics through online pharmacies on resistance to antibiotics.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227461","227461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227153","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has provided to local authorities on the implementation of the Care Act 2014 and the right of carers to an assessment and support.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227488","227488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227154","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Ministers in the Department for Education on the effect of the Care Act 2014 on young carers.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227489","227489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227155","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that online pharmacies adhere to national best practice guidelines.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227466","227466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227156","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps (a) his Department and (b) Public Health England is taking to investigate the prevalence of the availability of antibiotics to treat sexually-transmitted infections via websites.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227487","227487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227157","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what regulatory powers the General Medical Council has to review online prescribing where there is evidence that patients may be being prescribed suboptimal treatment.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227477","227477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227158","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on extending beyond three months the length of time for which that GPs can prescribe medications to patients with existing conditions who are leaving the country.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227474","227474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227159","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to monitor whether care assessments carried out under the Care Act 2014 include consideration of any companion animals.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227484","227484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227160","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the evidential basis is for the limit of three months on the length of time GPs can prescribe medications to patients with existing conditions who are leaving the country.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227473","227473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227161","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons his Department's logo does not appear on any published information about care.data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227481","227481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227162","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what regulatory powers the Care Quality Commission has to review the practice of online prescribing where it is aware of evidence that patients are being prescribed suboptimal treatment.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227491","227491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227163","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Public Health England has spent on marketing campaigning in each year since it was established; and how much of that spending was on campaigns on mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227480","227480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227164","2015-03-17","Department of Health","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that national best practice guidelines are adhered to in provision of treatment of gonorrhoea through online pharmacies.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227492","227492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227165","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many pieces of unlawful terrorist material have been taken off the internet since 2010; how many hate preachers have been excluded from the UK since 2010; how many organisations have been proscribed in the UK since 2010; how many (a) British citizenships have been revoked and (b) passports have been removed for terrorism-related reasons since 2010; and how many arrests the police have made for terrorism-related offences since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227472","227472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227166","2015-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how and when the Government plans to evaluate the effectiveness of measures under the Anti-Social Behaviour, Crime and Policing Act 2014 to prevent attacks by dogs on other animals.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227482","227482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227167","2015-03-18","Home Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to review the use of detention for immigration purposes.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227497","227497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227168","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of anti-Muslim hate crime near schools have been reported to police in Lancashire and Preston since 7 January 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227465","227465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227169","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of anti-Muslim hate crime were reported to the police in Preston and Lancashire in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227468","227468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227170","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions tasers were used by the police in (a) Preston, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227464","227464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227171","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign national offenders have been removed from the UK since 2010; and how many foreign national offenders are in the process of being removed from the UK under new powers in the Immigration Act 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227471","227471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227172","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full-time equivalent neighbourhood police officers there were in March 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227469","227469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227173","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made in reducing the number of asylum cases dating to before 2007.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227470","227470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227174","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what (a) financial and (b) equality impact assessment has been undertaken of the forthcoming changes to the Immigration Rules announced on 13 January 2015 that will require further submissions by post-2007 refused asylum applicants to be made in person at her Department's office in Liverpool.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227453","227453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227175","2015-03-17","House of Commons Commission","2015-03-12","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2015 to Question 225489, if the Commission will make it its policy to collect information from contractors operating on the parliamentary estate on how many of their workers are employed on a zero-hours contract.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227405","227405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227176","2015-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training and information is given to magistrates' clerks to ensure that they operate in accordance with the Armed Forces Covenant.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227457","227457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227177","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, of which country's intelligence agencies the official arrested in Turkey in connection with the British girls who ran away from home to join ISIS is a member; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227456","227456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227178","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of noise from aircraft taking off or landing at Heathrow on productivity in (a) schools in the Thames Valley and (b) businesses in the Thames Valley.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227401","227401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227179","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to improve transport links between Windsor and (a) Reading and (b) London since 2010.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227398","227398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227180","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many letters he has received from local authorities (a) supporting and (b) opposing proposals for the expansion of Heathrow in the last five years.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227399","227399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227181","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to improve road safety in Windsor constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227400","227400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227182","2015-03-19","Department for Transport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2014 to Question 215438, and with reference to the speech of 4 February 2015 to CPRE and the Campaign for Better Transport by the Minister of State in his Department, what steps the Government is taking to work with local authorities and the private sector to improve service stations.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227417","227417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227183","2015-03-19","Department for Transport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2014 to Question 216696, what assessment he has made of the success of the European debt recovery agency in recovering outstanding charges.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227418","227418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227184","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the management of Heathrow Airport have used dispensations under section 78(4) of the Civil Aviation Act to allow night flights in the last five years.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227393","227393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227185","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government has taken to reduce motorists' driving costs.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227394","227394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227186","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to reduce traffic congestion in Berkshire.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227396","227396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227187","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many aircraft taking off or landing at Heathrow Airport breached night flight restrictions in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227392","227392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227188","2015-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were in receipt of one or more benefits for which carers are eligible in (a) York Central constituency and (b) City of York local authority area on (i) 1 April 2010 and (ii) the same date in each subsequent year.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227387","227387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227189","2015-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff directly employed by his Department at the Carer's Allowance Unit, Palatine House, Preston earn (a) more and (b) less than the national living wage.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227408","227408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227190","2015-03-17","HM Treasury","2015-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on how many occasions the Tax Credit Office instructed bailiffs to collect overpaid tax credits from people in Preston constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227406","227406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227191","2015-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many former incapacity benefit claimants found fit for work after being reassessed for employment and support allowance between October 2010 and March 2014 have found work as a result of the Work Programme in East Lothian constituency.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227411","227411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227192","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance claimants in households with dependent children in Scotland received an adverse sanction decision by (i) level of sanction and (ii) number of children in the latest 12-month period for which data is available.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227436","227436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227193","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on the number of conditionality referrals made by a Jobcentre Plus advisor being taken into account in their performance appraisal with their line manager.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227437","227437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227194","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will place in the Library a copy of all appraisal documents used to monitor the performance of Jobcentre Plus jobseeker's allowance advisors.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227438","227438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227195","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department has provided to Jobcentre Plus managers on the place of conditionality referrals in performance appraisals of jobseeker's allowance advisors.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227439","227439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227196","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2015 to Question 226527, how much of the spending identified in each year related to marketing and media communication services for the (a) Welfare Reform Act 2012 and (b) Welfare Benefits Up-rating Act 2013.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227454","227454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227197","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Scotland likely to be affected by changes to universal credit made by the Universal Credit (Surpluses and Self-employed Losses) (Digital Service) Amendment Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227441","227441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227198","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the introduction of universal credit on the level of rent arrears among claimants in the Inverness area.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227440","227440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227295","2015-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is providing to government and opposition in Bangladesh to help address the constitutional crisis in that country.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908150","908150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228017","2015-03-18","Department for International Development","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help developing countries to tackle tax avoidance and evasion.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908155","908155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228018","2015-03-18","Department for International Development","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help developing countries to tackle tax avoidance and evasion.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908149","908149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228019","2015-03-18","Department for International Development","2015-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to improve working conditions in developing countries.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908145","908145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226553","2015-03-16","Attorney General","2015-03-11","To ask the Attorney General, how much the Law Officers' Departments spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227294","227294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226554","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to increase the availability of fibre-optic broadband to businesses in (a) Woking constituency, (b) Surrey and (c) the South East.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227285","227285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226555","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress has been made on giving intellectual property rights holders an opportunity to discuss with search engine providers how to maximise the prioritisation of sites with legitimate content.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227249","227249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226556","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to increase co-ordination and accountability for intellectual property policy by establishing a cross-industry partnership between the Intellectual Property Office and the Creative Industries Council.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227252","227252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226557","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which York-based companies received financial support from (a) Yorkshire Forward in each of its last five years of operation, (b) the York, North Yorkshire and East Riding Local Education Partnership and (c) the Leeds City Region Enterprise Partnership in each year since those bodies were created; and what the financial value of that support was in each such case.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227314","227314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226558","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the value of (a) exports and (b) imports of digitally-traded goods and services was in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227231","227231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226559","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the discussion paper, Follow the Money: financial options to assist in the battle against online IP piracy, published by the hon. Member for Hove in June 2014, what steps the Government has taken to (a) ensure that initiatives to tackle intellectual property offences by cutting advertising revenue streams have an international focus and (b) promote further collaboration between the Intellectual Property Office and equivalent bodies in other countries.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227254","227254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226560","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which of his Department's projects Macquarie Bank has invested in since May 2010; and how much has it invested in each project.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227244","227244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226561","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department spent on the traineeships programme in each month from August 2013 to October 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227263","227263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226562","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227293","227293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226563","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received on LighterLife UK's business practices; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227127","227127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226564","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received from LighterLife UK franchisees on that company's business practices.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227128","227128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226565","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227146","227146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226566","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeships commenced in each sector in (a) Pendle constituency and (b) Lancashire in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227197","227197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226567","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people in (a) Pendle constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West who had jobs which primarily required working (i) during the day and (ii) at night in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227196","227196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226568","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2015 to Question 226194, how much the Government has spent on consultants in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227211","227211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226569","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many cases before the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman are awaiting allocation of an assessor.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227227","227227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226570","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what average length of time a case with the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman has taken to conclude in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227229","227229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226571","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average time was for the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman to allocate an assessor to a health case in (a) February 2015, (b) August 2014, (c) February 2014 and (d) 2010.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227140","227140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226572","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227147","227147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226573","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of full-time jobs created in (a) Woking constituency, (b) Surrey and (c) the South East since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227291","227291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226574","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential behavioural effects on managers and users of Government buildings of the repeal of regulations on display energy certificates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227259","227259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226575","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths from prescription drug overdoses there were in (a) Pendle constituency and (b) Lancashire in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227236","227236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226576","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of employees in (a) the North West and (b) England were not a member of a workplace pension scheme in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227251","227251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226577","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many new business start-ups there have been in (a) Woking constituency, (b) Surrey and (c) the South East since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227286","227286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226578","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many new business start-ups by women there were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227287","227287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226579","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227295","227295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226580","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many new part-time jobs were created in (a) Woking constituency, (b) Surrey and (c) the South East since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227322","227322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226581","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are employed by the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman; and how many people were so employed (a) 12 months and (b) five years ago.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227330","227330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226582","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227304","227304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226583","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, who the members of the Treasury Board have been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227351","227351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226584","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings his Department has had with Macquarie Bank since May 2010; and who was present at such meetings.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227239","227239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226585","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which of his Department's projects Macquarie Bank has invested in since May 2010; and how much it has invested in each project.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227243","227243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226586","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much inheritance tax was collected in each of the last five years up to the most recent period for which records are available; and what the inheritance tax gap was in each of those years in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227260","227260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226587","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have registered interest on the Pension Wise website in receiving (a) telephone or (b) face-to-face advice.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227268","227268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226588","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2015 to Question 226142, how many enquiries were opened and how much additional tax was due to be collected in total as a result of those enquiries.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227175","227175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226589","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will increase the level of funding available to the Equitable Life Payments Scheme.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227222","227222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226590","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227160","227160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226591","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people who submitted applications for child benefit to the Child Benefit Office in the last 12 months were subsequently told by that office that their application was not received.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227164","227164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226592","2015-03-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Written Statement of 23 February 2015, Official Report, column 292WS, on Protecting Public Money, which are the (a) five local enterprise partnerships and (b) local authorities which have been paying for lobbyists in potential non-compliance with the Code of Recommended Practice on Local Authority Publicity.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227168","227168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226593","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications for repowering existing onshore wind farms were (a) received and (b) recovered by the Secretary of State in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227172","227172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226594","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much onshore wind capacity for repowering farms (a) received planning approval and (b) was rejected in each year since 2009; and how many planning applications for repowering onshore wind farms were (i) approved and (ii) rejected in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227174","227174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226596","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on who authorised the distribution of publicity information for EDF Energy in communications sent to local residents by Somerset County Council and Sedgemoor District Council.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227126","227126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226597","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227148","227148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226598","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what measures that reduce energy consumption in Government buildings (a) above and (b) below 500 square metres in area he plans to remove; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227258","227258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226599","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Written Statement of 18 December 2014, HCWS 161, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of new responsibilities on local authorities relating to sustainable drainage systems.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227261","227261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226600","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Written Statement of 18 December 2014, HCWS 161, what guidance his Department has issued to local authorities on levels of fees relating to their responsibilities for sustainable drainage systems.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227262","227262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226601","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what measures he has put in place to reduce energy consumption in Government buildings (a) above and (b) below 500 square metres in area since May 2010.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227257","227257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226602","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he last reviewed whether business rates are set at an appropriate level.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227318","227318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226603","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues on consultation with the Ministry of Defence to local authorities with Ministry of Defence facilities or land within their street lighting provision which plan to turn off street lighting for periods during the night.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227277","227277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226604","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much was paid in business rates (a) nationwide, (b) in the West Midlands and (c) in Coventry in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227316","227316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226605","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average amount paid in business rates by each business was (a) nationwide, (b) in the West Midlands and (c) in Coventry in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227317","227317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226606","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of long-term empty properties in (a) England, (b) the North West, (c) Lancashire and (d) Pendle constituency.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227326","227326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226607","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many affordable housing units were built in (a) Woking constituency and (b) Surrey in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227288","227288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226608","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227339","227339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226609","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) statutory and (b) non-statutory homeless people there are in (i) England and (ii) Liverpool.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227359","227359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226611","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Written Statement of 30 April 2014, Official Report, columns 53-4WS, on betting shops and gambling, when he expects local authorities to be given additional powers to restrict the clustering of betting shops; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227367","227367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226612","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward proposals to give local authorities additional powers to restrict the clustering of betting shops in their communities and to restrict the number of fixed odds betting terminals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227368","227368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226613","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to prevent betting operators receiving licences for two betting shops which share the same premises; what discussions he has had on this issue with (a) representatives of local licensing authorities, (b) the betting industry and (c) the Gambling Commission; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227369","227369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226614","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he expects the expert working group on supporter ownership and engagement in football to publish its findings; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227370","227370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226615","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227340","227340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226616","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the Government's policy is on the digital single economy in the EU; and what further progress has been made on setting out the UK's position to the European Commission.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227250","227250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226617","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what support his Department has provided for museums in Medway.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227237","227237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226618","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the proportion of households with access to fibre-optic broadband in (a) Woking constituency and (b) Surrey in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227290","227290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226619","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227149","227149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226620","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to expedite the process for the licensing of Cannock Radio radio station in Cannock Chase constituency.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227224","227224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226621","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much arts funding (a) in total and (b) per head of population was allocated in (i) Lancashire and (ii) Pendle constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227199","227199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226622","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Navy pilots are in training to enable them to land a fast jet on the Queen Elizabeth-class aircraft carriers.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227177","227177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226623","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent on maintenance of HMS Vanguard in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227178","227178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226624","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent on refitting HMS Vanguard in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227179","227179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226625","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent on refitting HMS Victorious in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227180","227180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226626","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent on maintenance of HMS Victorious in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227181","227181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226627","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent on refitting HMS Vigilant in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227182","227182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226628","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much was spent on HM Naval Service pensions in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227187","227187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226629","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent on maintenance of HMS Vengeance in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227183","227183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226630","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent on general maintenance of Trident missiles in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227184","227184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226631","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Air Force pilots are in training to enable them to land a fast jet on the Queen Elizabeth-class aircraft carriers.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227188","227188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226632","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many days Trident submarines have not been at sea in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227189","227189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226633","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent on maintenance of HMS Vigilant in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227190","227190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226634","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent on refitting HMS Vengeance in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227191","227191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226635","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans for UK-crewed fighter jets to be stationed on the deck of a Queen-Elizabeth class aircraft carrier.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227185","227185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226636","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Trident missiles were capable of being deployed on 11 March 2015.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227192","227192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226637","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much was spent on Royal Air Force pensions in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227186","227186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226638","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent on refurbishment of Trident missiles in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227193","227193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226639","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Trident missiles are undergoing maintenance work.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227194","227194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226640","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people were in the (a) Army, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Air cadet forces in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227142","227142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226641","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Child Maintenance Service payments and Child Support Agency collections are made; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227283","227283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226642","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227296","227296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226643","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps were taken by the Service Complaints Commissioner to provide full and proper determination of a service complaint submitted by Lt Col (Retired) R. H. Jolleys.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227335","227335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226644","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to help military personnel whose employment ceased as a result of the reduction in regular troop numbers to find alternative work.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227323","227323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226645","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure that funding is available for schools to enable them to maintain the variety of A-levels they offer.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227129","227129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226646","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that funding is available to schools to enable pupils to continue at A-level subjects they took at GCSE.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227130","227130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226647","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on who authorised EDF Energy to give presentations in schools on working in the nuclear energy sector in Somerset.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227125","227125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226648","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in her Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227150","227150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226649","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2015 to Question 225826, which 12 schools within Birmingham local authority area applied for additional funding for universal infant free school meals; and in which constituencies those schools are located.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227136","227136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226650","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consideration the School Teachers Review Body has given to including salary sacrifice car schemes in the school teachers' pay and conditions document; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227225","227225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226651","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assistance her Department has made available to Lancashire County Council for expanding the number of free childcare places.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227233","227233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226652","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to introduce a salary sacrifice car scheme for teachers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227219","227219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226653","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked after children in local authority accommodation outside of their home local authority area there are for each type of placement and each local authority; and what the average distance from home is of such children for each type of placement and each local authority.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227207","227207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226654","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2015 to Question 222182, whether her Department is aware of any recorded instances of a child born outside the UK and looked-after under private fostering arrangements being referred to a local authority for care.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227202","227202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226655","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is a requirement for a local authority to be alerted if a child born outside the UK and looked-after under private fostering arrangements moves into that local authority area.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227203","227203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226656","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2015 to Question 222182, if she will make it her policy to record instances where a child born outside the UK is looked-after under a private fostering arrangement and that arrangement breaks down.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227204","227204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226657","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2015 to Question 222652, how many educational psychologists first qualified in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227205","227205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226658","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked after children were accommodated outside their home local authority area for each type of placement and for each local authority in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227208","227208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226659","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked after children were absent from their placement for more than 24 hours for each type of placement in each year from 2008; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227209","227209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226660","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many 16 to 18 year-olds in (a) Lancashire and (b) England were not in education, employment or training in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227331","227331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226661","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will discuss with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills potential steps to support teachers in raising awareness among schoolchildren of the importance of intellectual property.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227248","227248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226662","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227341","227341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226663","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in Lancashire were eligible for but did not claim free school meals in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227328","227328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226664","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which of her Department's projects Macquarie Bank has invested in since May 2010; and how much it has invested in each such project.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227246","227246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226665","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what meetings her Department has had with Macquarie Bank since May 2010; and who was present at such meetings.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227240","227240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226666","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she next plans to issue a remit to the School Teachers Review Body; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227223","227223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226667","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what meetings his Department has had with Macquarie Bank since May 2010; and who was present at such meetings.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227238","227238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226668","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the effect of (a) onshore wind, (b) offshore wind, (c) solar, (d) biomass, (e) wave and (f) tidal energy generation on the average domestic energy bill in 2014.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227255","227255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226669","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make a comparative assessment of the cost of new offshore wind capacity in Denmark and the UK.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227256","227256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226670","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to paragraph 23 of his Department's grant confirmation letter of 11 January 2010 to the MOZES community energy co-operative, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that eligible third sector organisations and local authorities will be allowed to receive grant funding from the Low Carbon Communities Challenge and feed-in tariffs.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227267","227267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226671","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which of his Department's projects Macquarie Bank has invested in since May 2010; and how much it has invested in each such project.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227245","227245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226672","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) applications have been received for licences and (b) licences have been issued for fracking in (i) York, (ii) North Yorkshire and (iii) Yorkshire and the Humber since May 2010.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227313","227313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226673","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227342","227342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226674","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on what date his Department received the report from Ray Noble on the MOZES community energy cooperative in Nottingham.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227365","227365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226675","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the options available to restructure the 2010 grant to the MOZES community energy cooperative in Nottingham in order to make it State Aid compliant.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227364","227364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226676","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will place in the Library an unredacted copy of the report commissioned by his Department from Ray Noble on the MOZES community energy pilot scheme in Nottingham.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227366","227366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226677","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much onshore wind capacity (a) received planning approval and (b) was rejected in each month in 2014; and how many planning applications for onshore wind farms were (i) approved and (ii) rejected in each such month.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227173","227173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226678","2015-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on the European Commission's decision not to proceed with the circular economy package.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227220","227220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226679","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to his Department's publication Estimated impacts of energy and climate change policy on energy prices and bills, published in November 2014, what provision has been made in that document for likely costs of (a) additional generating capacity related to the intermittency of renewables, (b) additional transmission lines to link wind and other renewable generators to centres of consumption and (c) other measures to strengthen the grid to dial with intermittency.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227176","227176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226680","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227151","227151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226681","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change of 3 February 2015, Official Report, column 22WH, on cavity wall insulation, when he plans to report progress on (a) discussions with Ofgem, (b) obtaining a summary of the number of complaints received by Ofgem and that body's views on those complaints, (c) consideration of a review of complaints, (d) consideration of the case for introducing independent oversight for all guarantees, (e) consideration of introduction of independent assessments two years after installation and (f) consideration of regulation of initial sales conversations.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227143","227143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226682","2015-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in her Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227152","227152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226683","2015-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her strategy is for tackling urban diffuse water pollution.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227200","227200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226684","2015-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she expects to publish the strategy to tackle urban diffuse water pollution referred to in her Department's Summary of responses to the consultation on Tackling water pollution from the urban environment.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227198","227198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226685","2015-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2015 to Question 224551, for what reasons no information is available on the number of pheasants and partridges imported into the UK for the purposes of game shooting.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227167","227167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226686","2015-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions officials in her Department have had with stakeholders on development of a national strategy for implementation of the European School Milk Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227333","227333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226687","2015-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to consult stakeholders on the development of a national strategy for implementation of the European School Milk Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227334","227334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226688","2015-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227297","227297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226689","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227298","227298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226690","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2015 to Questions 226471 and 226472, if he will publish by way of further written Answer the further information he has requested from NATO before the dissolution of the present Parliament.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227292","227292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226691","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the conduct of the Nigerian general election in March 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227232","227232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226692","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the efforts of the Iraqi government to engage constructively with the Sunni community; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227355","227355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226693","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Ministers in his Department have made representations to the government of Sudan on reports of human rights abuses in South Kordofan and Blue Nile states; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227353","227353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226694","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of links between ISIS and Boko Haram; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227354","227354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226695","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the security situation in Myanmar following the arrest of protestors on 10 March 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227201","227201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226696","2015-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether there is a Defence Attaché in post in the British Embassy in Ukraine.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227269","227269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226697","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on how many (a) Saharawi people and (b) Moroccan settlers live in the part of Western Sahara under Moroccan control.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227212","227212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226698","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227153","227153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226699","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Written Statement of 8 January 2015, HCWS176, when the results of the review of the Government's overseas scholarships schemes will be available; and if he will make it his policy that no changes to the governance of those schemes will be made without prior consultation of Parliament.","Biography information for Lord Haselhurst","Sir Alan Haselhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227138","227138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226700","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Written Statement of 8 January 2015, HCWS176, what provision has been made for public consultation as part of the review of the Government's overseas scholarships schemes.","Biography information for Lord Haselhurst","Sir Alan Haselhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227139","227139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226701","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2015 to Question 225987, for what reasons the Answer states that a contract for University Hospital Bristol to deliver stereotactic radiosurgery (SRS) was transferred to NHS England in April 2013 when that hospital first acquired a gamma knife to deliver SRS in October 2013.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227144","227144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226702","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of research on the efficacy and safety of e-cigarettes as a smoking cessation aid.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227133","227133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226703","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2015 to Question 225987, which refers to there being a contract for stereotactic radiosurgery and stereotactic radiotherapy services (SRS) with University Hospital Bristol, for what reasons that hospital is listed as non-contracted and non-commissioned to deliver SRS in the NHS England document Stereotactic radiosurgery and radiotherapy services needs assessment and service review, published in November 2014.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227124","227124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226704","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2015 to Question 224828, what assessment he has made of the factors contributing to the reduction in NHS-funded IVF cycles from 2013 to 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227135","227135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226705","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the costs to each clinical commissioning group of GPs and ambulance staff of attending after deaths in care homes of people subject to Deprivation of Liberty Safeguards Assessments.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227171","227171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226706","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Supreme Court judgment of 19 March 2014 in the case of P v Cheshire West and Chester Council and another, how many requests for a Deprivation of Liberty Safeguards Assessment under the Mental Capacity Act 2005 there have been in each local authority area in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227169","227169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226707","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the positive and negative effects of e-cigarettes on people with asthma.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227216","227216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226708","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many care homes with (a) a dementia service band and (b) an older people service band there were in (i) England, (ii) the North West and (iii) Lancashire in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227230","227230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226709","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will trial the HPV vaccination programme for men who have sex with men in selected sexual health clinics to assess likely take up and budgetary implications.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227163","227163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226710","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227155","227155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226711","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of treating health problems caused by alternative medicine.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227195","227195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226712","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227343","227343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226713","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the financial situation of NHS organisations in Devon.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227363","227363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226714","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish an update on its progress on the ambitions and actions in its Cardiovascular Disease Outcomes Strategy, published in March 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227372","227372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226715","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme in ensuring the availability of the most effective treatments for cancer patients.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227374","227374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226716","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to provide financial support to NHS organisations in Devon.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227361","227361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226717","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what account was taken of the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme during his Department's recent review of the financial sustainability of the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227375","227375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226718","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with NHS England on support for NHS organisations in Devon.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227362","227362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226719","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the progress made by the Cancer Drugs Fund Short Life Working Group to date.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227373","227373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226720","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of when the ambition in his Department's Cardiovascular Disease Outcomes Strategy, published in March 2013, to bring the total diagnoses of familial hypercholesterolaemia to 50 per cent, will be met.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227371","227371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226721","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) cleaners and (b) hospital porters were employed in the NHS in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227309","227309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226722","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to address local variations in the quality of care for diabetes patients.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227332","227332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226723","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England will conclude its preparations for making new hepatitis C drugs available for treating people with cirrhosis of the liver.","Biography information for Chloe Smith","Chloe Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227327","227327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226724","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people in (a) Pendle constituency, (b) East Lancashire and (c) the North West were registered as organ donors in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227324","227324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226725","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps NHS England is taking to ensure all clinical commissioning groups (CCGs) provide annual checks needed by patients with diabetes to help prevent against diabetes complications; and what action he is taking against CCGs which do not comply.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227329","227329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226726","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any of the pilots under the Prime Minister's Challenge Fund are offering patients GP appointments within 48 hours.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227308","227308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226727","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what timescales his Department has set for making decisions on appeals on the delisting of treatments from the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227321","227321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226728","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings his Department has had with Macquarie Bank since May 2010; and who was present at such meetings.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227241","227241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226729","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which of his Department's projects Macquarie Bank has invested in since May 2010; and how much it has invested in each such project.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227242","227242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226730","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2014 to Question 217335, what the causes of these incidents were; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227270","227270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226731","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2014 to Question 217335, how many patient safety incidents involving multiple pregnancies there were in each (a) hospital trust and (b) region in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227271","227271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226732","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2014 to Question 217336, what the causes of these damages were; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227272","227272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226733","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the UK's patient safety OECD ranking for patient safety incidents involving multiple pregnancies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227275","227275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226734","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2014 to Question 217334, how many multiple pregnancies received (a) the higher tariff for the antenatal phase, (b) the delivery phase tariff with complications and co-morbidities and (c) the delivery phase tariff without complications and co-morbidities in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227273","227273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226735","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2014 to Question 217334, what plans his Department has to review the costs of delivering care in multiple pregnancies antenatally, in delivery and postnatally; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227274","227274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226736","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many local winter pressure resilience plans developed for the 2014-15 winter period include reference to vaccinations.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227279","227279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226737","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding he has allocated to improving vaccination coverage as part of local winter pressure resilience plans developed for the 2014-15 winter period.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227278","227278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226738","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to support (a) research into still births and neonatal deaths and (b) the dissemination of clinical best practice in multiple pregnancies.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227281","227281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226739","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues to hospitals on the role of improved vaccination in reducing seasonal pressures.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227280","227280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226740","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what NHS spending per head of the population in Surrey was in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227289","227289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226741","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2014 to Question 217336, what (a) damages, (b) defence costs, (c) claimant costs and (d) periodic payment orders were paid in each (i) hospital trust and (ii) region in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227284","227284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226742","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2014 to Question 217331, what steps his Department is taking to support NICE and other stakeholders disseminate and implement NICE guidance for multiple pregnancies within the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227282","227282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226743","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fixed penalty notices were issued for neglect of traffic direction in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227253","227253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226744","2015-03-17","Home Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of homophobic hate crime there were in (a) Streatham constituency, (b) each London borough and (c) the UK in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227346","227346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226745","2015-03-17","Home Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of disability hate crime there were in (a) Streatham constituency, (b) each London borough and (c) the UK in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227347","227347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226746","2015-03-17","Home Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress she has made on the implementation of recommendations of the Report of the Independent Commission on Mental Health and Policing, published in May 2013.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227345","227345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226747","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227299","227299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226748","2015-03-17","Home Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the level of street prostitution in (a) Streatham constituency, (b) each London borough and (c) the UK; and what steps she is taking to protect women working in street prostitution through (i) facilitating safe exit programmes and (ii) other measures.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227348","227348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226749","2015-03-17","Home Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of people on whom tasers were used by the police in (a) each London borough, (b) each police authority and (c) in the UK were aged (i) under 12, (ii) under 14, (iii) under 16, (iv) under 18, (v) under 21, (vi) under 24, (vii) over 35, (viii) over 40, (ix) over 50, (x) over 55, (xi) over 60, (xii) over 65, (xiii) over 70, (xiv) over 75 and (xv) over 80 in the last five years; and what proportion of those people were (A) from each ethnic group and (B) estimated to have had mental health problems.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227349","227349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226750","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what counter-terrorism measures she has put in place to counter the threat of Islamic State.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227350","227350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226751","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in her Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227156","227156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226752","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many illegal firearms were seized on arrival in the UK in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227234","227234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226753","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Supreme Court judgment of 19 March 2014 in the case of P v Cheshire West and Chester Council and another, what estimate she has made of costs for each police area of attending after deaths in care homes of people subject to Deprivation of Liberty Safeguards Assessments.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227170","227170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226754","2015-03-16","Home Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether police forces have access to Government data on benefit payments in order to assist in locating wanted persons.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227137","227137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226755","2015-03-16","Department for International Development","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2015 to Question 222001, what proportion, and what value, of centrally awarded contracts were awarded to firms registered in the UK in each of the last four financial years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227210","227210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226756","2015-03-16","Department for International Development","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in her Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227157","227157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226757","2015-03-16","Department for International Development","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227300","227300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226758","2015-03-16","Department for International Development","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make it her policy that the declaration of the UNICEF Heads of Government meeting in September 2015 should prioritise the ending of abuse, exploitation, trafficking and all forms of violence and torture against children; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227276","227276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226759","2015-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227301","227301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226760","2015-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions bail decisions were challenged using powers granted under section 90 of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227235","227235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226761","2015-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to ensure the separation of sex offenders from other prisoners currently housed together at HM Prison Northumberland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227319","227319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226762","2015-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether relatives of victims of crime are compensated for the cost of attending parole boards to make victim impact statements.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227320","227320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226763","2015-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how the level of gross monthly income thresholds was determined for people applying for fee remission in employment tribunals.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227356","227356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226764","2015-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information is collected by the Employment Tribunal Service to monitor the protected characteristics of people making claims to the Employment Tribunal Service.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227352","227352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226765","2015-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227158","227158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226766","2015-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he expects section 29 of the Criminal Justice and Courts Act 2015 to be commenced.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227226","227226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226767","2015-03-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in her Department responded that they were treated fairly at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227228","227228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226768","2015-03-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227302","227302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226769","2015-03-16","Scotland Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227303","227303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226770","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will commission a strategic environmental assessment of the proposal for a High Speed 3 line between Leeds and Manchester.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227131","227131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226771","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what changes to the proposed route alignment of High Speed 2 have resulted from feedback received during the High Speed 2 Community Forum process.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227132","227132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226772","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227159","227159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226773","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will assess the potential effect on (a) jobs and (b) skills in the rail freight industry of Genesee & Wyoming's acquisition of a 95 per cent stake in Freightliner.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227166","227166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226774","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which of his Department's projects and enterprises Macquarie Bank has financed or invested in since May 2010; and how much it has invested in each such projected enterprise.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227247","227247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226775","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average cost was of a super off-peak rail return from York to Leeds in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227312","227312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226776","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227344","227344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226777","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent on cycling improvements in York Unitary Authority in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227310","227310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226778","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what arrangements are in place to correct errors of fact in the High Speed 2 Phase One Environment Statement.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227325","227325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226779","2015-03-16","Department for Transport","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) accidents and (b) fatal accidents involving cyclists there have been in (a) York Central constituency and (b) York Unitary Authority area in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227311","227311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226780","2015-03-16","Wales Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227161","227161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226781","2015-03-16","Women and Equalities","2015-03-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in the Government Equalities Office reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227154","227154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226782","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the imposition of a three-year benefit sanction on the health of people subject to such sanctions.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227141","227141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226783","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people claiming discretionary housing payments in the London Borough of Southwark have had their claim rejected because funding was unavailable in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227134","227134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226784","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) original forecast of expenditure savings and (b) actual expenditure savings were from the reassessment of incapacity benefit claims since 2010.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227145","227145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226785","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227162","227162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226786","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment the Minister has made of the performance of his Department in meeting its targets relating to claims for Remploy Employment Services.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227165","227165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226787","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of his Department's performance against targets on the processing of claims for jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227217","227217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226788","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of his Department's performance against targets on the processing of claims for employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227218","227218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226789","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial support his Department provides to 18 and 19 year olds in employment who have never attended college or university.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227221","227221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226790","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of his Department's performance in meeting targets relating to individual personal independence payment claims.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227206","227206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226791","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time was for a decision to be made on payment of the under-occupancy penalty in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227213","227213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226792","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time was for a decision to be made on a jobseeker's allowance claim in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227214","227214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226793","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time was for a decision to be made on a personal independence payment claim in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227215","227215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226794","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time was for a decision on a claim for Remploy Employment Services in each year from 2013 to date.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227336","227336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226795","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time was for a decision on a claim for employment support allowance in each year from 2013 to date.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227337","227337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226796","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people who claimed jobseeker's allowance (JSA) at some point during the year were subject to a JSA sanction in that year in (a) Stourbridge Jobcentre and (b) Stourbridge constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Margot James","Margot James","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227338","227338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226797","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will assess the merits of extending the Diffuse Mesothelioma Payment Scheme to allow compensation to be paid to non-dependent children who were under 21 years of age at the time of the diagnosis of the deceased.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227307","227307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226798","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will assess the merits of extending the Diffuse Mesothelioma Payment Scheme to allow compensation to be paid to non-dependent children in the event of there being no dependent children or spouse to receive the payment.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227306","227306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226799","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227305","227305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226800","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of employment and support allowance appeals (a) nationwide, (b) in the West Midlands and (c) in Coventry in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227358","227358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226801","2015-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2015 to Question 907921, what the average clearing time was for employment and support allowance mandatory reconsideration appeals in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227357","227357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226802","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his most recent forecast is of how many jobcentres will have universal credit available to all parents, both in and out of work, in April 2016.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227360","227360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226803","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2015 to Question 226033, when he expects migration to Universal Credit to finish, assuming no change in the labour market outlook or the pace at which claims are migrated.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227264","227264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226804","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the role and contribution is of local authorities in relation to the Work Programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227265","227265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226805","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will place in the Library a copy of the latest stocktake of Work Programme sub-contractors.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227266","227266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226806","2015-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2015 to Question 226635, how much of the £1 billion allocated to the Youth Contract has been spent to date.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227315","227315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227309","2015-03-17","Home Office","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to restrict the power of the courts to order convicted criminals awaiting deportation to relocate within the UK.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908082","908082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227601","2015-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of staffing in prisons in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908089","908089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227642","2015-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce reoffending.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908105","908105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226193","2015-03-12","Attorney General","2015-03-10","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in the Law Officers' Departments responded that they were treated fairly at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226958","226958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226194","2015-03-12","Attorney General","2015-03-10","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in the Law Officers' Departments reported experiencing bullying or harassment at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227075","227075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226195","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which businesses are providing advice and support through the Growth Voucher scheme; and how many businesses have received such assistance from each such business to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227104","227104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226196","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the 2015-16 adult social skills budget for Hyndburn is; and what the percentage change from last year's budget is.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227015","227015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226197","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the proposed timetable is for his consultation on the introduction of loans for postgraduate students.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226986","226986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226198","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been repaid to UK Export Finance by Reliance Industries of India since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226995","226995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226199","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been repaid to UK Export Finance by Petrobras since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226997","226997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226200","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been repaid to UK Export Finance by Sadara Chemical Company since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226998","226998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226201","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been repaid to UK Export Finance by Cameron GmbH since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226999","226999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226202","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been repaid to UK Export Finance by PPC Energy since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227000","227000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226203","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been repaid to UK Export Finance by ZabSibNeftekhim LLC since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226990","226990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226204","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been repaid to UK Export Finance by ABN Amro Bank since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227001","227001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226205","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been repaid to UK Export Finance by Saudi Kayan Petrochemical Company since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227002","227002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226206","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been repaid to UK Export Finance by OMV Petrom since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226991","226991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226207","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been repaid to UK Export Finance by Southern Kuzbass Coal Company OAO since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227003","227003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226208","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been repaid to UK Export Finance by Siberian Coal Energy Company since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226992","226992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226209","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been repaid to UK Export Finance by DOF Subsea AS since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226993","226993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226210","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been repaid to UK Export Finance by Gazprom since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226994","226994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226211","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been repaid to UK Export Finance by GAIL (India) Ltd since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226996","226996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226212","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his most recent assessment is of default rates under the Enterprise Finance Guarantee Scheme; and with what frequency his Department makes such an assessment.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227105","227105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226213","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many business that have applied for Growth Vouchers have not been successful in that application to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227103","227103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226214","2015-03-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many valid Growth Vouchers have been issued that have not yet been redeemed.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227102","227102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226215","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department responded that they were treated fairly at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226957","226957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226216","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of large companies' use of lengthy payment terms for suppliers on suppliers' ability to trade.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226870","226870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226217","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of UK companies requiring (i) 30 day, (ii) 60 day, (iii) 90 day, (iv) 120 day and (v) greater than 120 day payment terms from their suppliers.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226871","226871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226218","2015-03-12","Cabinet Office","2015-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department responded that they were treated fairly at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226959","226959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226219","2015-03-16","Cabinet Office","2015-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the decision to send Mark Jenner of the Special Demonstration Squad into a covert long-term surveillance operation in the 1990s was approved by (a) officials and (b) Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226977","226977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226220","2015-03-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the cost to the public purse was of the Government's advertising campaign encouraging consumers to switch energy providers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227021","227021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226221","2015-03-12","HM Treasury","2015-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when Ministers of his Department last met representatives of the oil and gas industry to discuss the fiscal implications of falling oil prices for the North Sea oil and gas industry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227020","227020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226222","2015-03-12","HM Treasury","2015-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department responded that they were treated fairly at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226973","226973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226223","2015-03-12","HM Treasury","2015-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on air passenger duty.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227088","227088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226224","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent forecast he has made of the number of parents with children who will be claiming tax credits in April 2016.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226979","226979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226225","2015-03-12","HM Treasury","2015-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to respond to the results of his Department's consultation on umbrella companies.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226951","226951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226226","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been overpaid in child tax credit and working tax credit as a result of technical and administrative errors by his Department; and how much of that overpayment has been written off in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) East Lothian constituency in each year since that scheme's inception.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226903","226903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226227","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to answer Question 224318, tabled on 11 February 2015 for Named day answer on 23 February 2015; and what the reasons are for the time taken to answer that Question.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226906","226906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226228","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that money and debt advice is available to people who do not have access to the internet.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226917","226917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226229","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2015 to Question 222025, if he will provide a breakdown of the figures in the Answer by employment sector in the most recent year or years for which that data is available.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226921","226921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226230","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to assess changes in the number of people using illegal lending sources as a result of new regulations and the annual levy on payday loan companies.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226890","226890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226231","2015-03-16","HM Treasury","2015-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the divide between the rich and the poor.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226891","226891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226233","2015-03-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with local government representatives on altering section 7 (2) and (3) of the Local Government Act 1972 relating to elections in metropolitan districts.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226910","226910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226234","2015-03-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the difference is between the amount that will be received from central Government by Sefton Metropolitan Borough Council under the (a) provisional and (b) final 2015-16 local authority settlement.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226911","226911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226235","2015-03-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department responded that they were treated fairly at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226960","226960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226236","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding has been (a) received for and (b) spent on adult social care services provided by each district authority in Lancashire.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226950","226950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226237","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people used children and young people's social care services in each district authority in Lancashire in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226947","226947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226238","2015-03-16","Department of Health","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were in receipt of adult social care services in each district authority in Lancashire in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227107","227107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226239","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total level of (a) income and (b) expenditure is for children and young people's social care in each district authority in Lancashire.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227016","227016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226240","2015-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require fire authorities to provide a full pension to fire fighters between the ages of 55 and 60 if they fail a fitness test due to no fault of their own and cannot be employed in another role within the fire service.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227101","227101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226241","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of fixed odds betting terminals on levels of gambling addiction.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227054","227054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226242","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effects of the Gaming Machine (Circumstances of Use) (Amendment) Regulations 2015 (S.I., 2015, No. 121) on (a) gambling addiction levels, (b) the total amount of money staked and (c) the profits of bookmakers and fixed odds betting terminal providers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227053","227053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226243","2015-03-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department plans to have a chair for the review process for secondary ticketing.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226933","226933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226244","2015-03-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department responded that they were treated fairly at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226961","226961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226245","2015-03-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of when average download speeds in the whole of Blaydon constituency will reach 14.7 mbps.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226912","226912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226246","2015-03-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will discuss with ministers of the Scottish Government ways to make faster progress on providing broadband to rural communities in East Lothian constituency.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226904","226904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226247","2015-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department responded that they were treated fairly at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226962","226962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226248","2015-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the future of the defence budget.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226892","226892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226249","2015-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the de Silva Report of the Patrick Finucane Review, published in December 2012, whether any Home Office guidance on the recruitment of agents was followed by his Department for the recruitment of Brian Nelson as an agent.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226886","226886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226250","2015-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 98 of the de Silva Report of the Patrick Finucane Review, published in December 2012, what the reasons were for the medical discharge of Brian Nelson from the Army.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226887","226887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226251","2015-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 99 of the de Silva Report of the Patrick Finucane Review, published in December 2012, whether his Department had a role in (a) recruiting and (b) deploying Brian Nelson as an informant; and what the seniority of the officials from his Department involved was.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226888","226888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226252","2015-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the de Silva Report of the Patrick Finucane Review, published in December 2012, what information his Department holds on where Brian Nelson served his criminal sentence.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226889","226889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226253","2015-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance the Government has given to the government of Ukraine against Russian aggression.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227084","227084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226254","2015-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 219723 and to his oral contribution of 23 February 2015, Official Report, column 11, on ISIL, if he will ensure that his Department's online record is updated to include data on each strike referred to in that contribution; and if he will provide information on the (a) date, (b) location and (c) aircraft deployed to carry out each strike.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227077","227077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226255","2015-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people from Northern Ireland applied to join the British Army in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227096","227096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226256","2015-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people from Northern Ireland applied to join the Royal Air Force in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227097","227097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226257","2015-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many military personnel are based in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227094","227094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226258","2015-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many military and aviation personnel worked in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227093","227093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226259","2015-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking in conjunction with its international partners to defeat ISIS.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227100","227100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226260","2015-03-12","Department for Education","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in her Department responded that they were treated fairly at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226963","226963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226261","2015-03-12","Department for Education","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that faith schools do not divide local communities.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226930","226930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226262","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to publish its review of asbestos management in schools; and what the reasons are for the time taken to publish that review.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226901","226901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226263","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of how many schools are teaching financial education as part of the curriculum.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226918","226918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226264","2015-03-12","Department for Education","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that teachers are fully engaged in the process of developing curriculums in schools.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226928","226928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226265","2015-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress the Government has made on ensuring that apprenticeships are recognised as having equivalent value to university degrees.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226929","226929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226266","2015-03-16","Department for Education","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what forecast she has made of the number of parents who will be eligible to claim free school meals for their children in April 2016.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227111","227111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226267","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the success of the smart meter roll-out programme to date; and how many smart meters have been installed under that programme in (a) the UK, (b) the West Midlands and (c) Birmingham, Northfield constituency.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227108","227108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226268","2015-03-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when Ministers of his Department last met representatives of the oil and gas industry; what was discussed at that meeting; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227019","227019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226269","2015-03-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2015 to Question 220887, what powers his Department plans to give Ofgem to ensure that gas suppliers cannot ask a vulnerable customer to pay a standing charge if they are not consuming gas at all.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226938","226938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226270","2015-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what processes are in place to monitor the standard of installations carried out under (a) the Energy Company Obligation and the Green Deal and (b) the Warm Front Scheme; what processes are in place to limit the use of sub-contractors in those schemes; and what right of redress householders have in the event that installations are not of a satisfactory standard.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226948","226948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226271","2015-03-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in his Department responded that they were treated fairly at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226964","226964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226272","2015-03-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether he plans that upgrading of (a) oil boilers and (b) LPG boilers will be mandated to installing energy companies as being available to qualifying householders under the revised Green Deal Home Improvement Fund.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226874","226874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226275","2015-03-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff in her Department responded that they were treated fairly at work in the most recent Civil Service People Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226965","226965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226276","2015-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the contribution of the poultry sector to the UK economy; and what discussions she has had with her counterpart in the Northern Ireland Executive on steps to support that industry in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226894","226894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226277","2015-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to publish the recommendations of the Epidemiology Report on bovine TB on the Cheshire Edge by Sue Ridout; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227073","227073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226278","2015-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will reallocate surplus funds from the current round of bids on the Badger Edge Vaccination Scheme to additional projects designed to close physical gaps in coverage along the Cheshire Edge Zone in East Cheshire and Stockport.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227074","227074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226279","2015-03-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with insurance companies on affordable insurance cover after incidents of flooding.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227117","227117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226280","2015-03-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to protect seas and fish stock quotas for (a) Northern Ireland and (b) other UK fishermen.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227119","227119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226281","2015-03-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to assist the dairy industry; and what discussions she has had with the devolved administrations on that matter.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227116","227116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226282","2015-03-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with the devolved administrations on bovine TB.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227118","227118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226284","2015-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the success of Commonwealth Day.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227120","227120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226285","2015-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to President Putin on the death of Boris Nemtsov.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227123","227123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226286","2015-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to include Bahrain as a country of concern in his Department's next Human Rights and Democracy Report.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227076","227076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226287","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last raised the issue of human rights of the Baha'i community with his counterparts in Iran.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227014","227014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226288","2015-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has raised with the Colombian government the further threats to the life of Irreal Aguilar Solano; and what steps the Colombian government has informed the Government it is taking.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 227010","227010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226289","2015-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to assist the improvement of domestic security and public protection in Libya.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226953","226953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226290","2015-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to help reduce the number of kidnappings by ISIL in Libya.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 226955","226955"
