"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45148","2014-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for how many and what proportion of employment and support allowance claimants in the Work Related Activity Group Atos has sought further medical evidence and opinion from the person's nominated professional.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193704","193704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45477","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to support young people into work.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903384","903384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45841","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the performance of the Innovation Fund to Support Separated Families.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903389","903389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45842","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what changes he plans to make to the ability of EU migrants to access benefits.","Biography information for David Rutley","David Rutley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903387","903387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45843","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants have received the personal independence payment since April 2013.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903388","903388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45844","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish an assessment of the likely effect of the change to pensions announced in the 2014 Budget on the budget for welfare payments over the next ten years.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903390","903390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45845","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what charges are incurred by those appealing against a benefit assessment ruling.","Biography information for Natascha Engel","Natascha Engel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903392","903392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45846","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to publish statistics on the number of requests for employment and support allowance decisions which are reconsidered and the number of such requests that are upheld.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903391","903391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46433","2014-04-02","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she is taking to increase the amount of government spending allocated to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903402","903402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46434","2014-04-02","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on economic development in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903406","903406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46435","2014-04-02","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress has been made on the review of so-called letters of comfort issued to on-the-runs.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903401","903401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46436","2014-04-02","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on economic development in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903407","903407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46437","2014-04-02","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the effect of reductions in the number of people employed in the public sector in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903405","903405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46438","2014-04-02","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress has been made on gaining compensation from the Libyan government for the victims of terrorist acts perpetrated by the IRA.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903399","903399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44621","2014-03-26","Attorney General","2014-03-24","To ask the Attorney General, what the Law Officers' Departments' policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193381","193381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44622","2014-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress he has made in persuading China to recognise UK export health certificates for pet foods.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193338","193338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44623","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2013, Official Report, column 643W, on foreign investments in UK, what the value of foreign direct investment was in each region of the UK in each year since 1984.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193413","193413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44624","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether additional funding allocated to the higher RAB charge will come out of non-ringfenced DEL.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193344","193344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44625","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department's total resource DEL has been increased as a result of the higher RAB charge for student loans.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193349","193349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44626","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the cost to the public purse is of the higher RAB charge for student loans.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193350","193350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44627","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the amount spent on maintenance grants for students at private colleges in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193351","193351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44628","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the RAB charge for loans issued to those on the new funding regime is for student loans issued in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2012-13.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193352","193352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44629","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193380","193380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44630","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that student entrepreneurs can access support and guidance when setting up their first businesses.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193283","193283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44631","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent progress has been made on the public register of beneficial ownership of companies operating in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193297","193297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44632","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the RAB charge is for student loans issued to those who started university before September 2012 for loans issued in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2012-13.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193368","193368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44633","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the value of Russian non-financial assets held in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193419","193419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44634","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the value of UK non-financial assets held in Russia.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193418","193418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44635","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeship places there were in Rossendale and Darwen constituency in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193299","193299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44636","2014-03-27","Cabinet Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure the accuracy of the figures for zero-hour contracts in the Labour Force Survey.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193442","193442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44637","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the policy of Barclays on the use of tax havens.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193463","193463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44638","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answers to topical question T1 of 23 January 2014, Official Report, column 434, if he will request the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate to pass to the Gangmasters Licensing Authority the details it holds on the personal accident insurance schemes operated by those employment agencies referred to in the Answers.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193465","193465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44639","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take to ensure that universities admit more students from disadvantaged backgrounds whose qualifications meet university admissions requirements.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193475","193475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44640","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people in each (a) age group and (b) parental income group resident in Islwyn constituency entered higher education in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193476","193476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44641","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what change he expects in the number of private providers of higher education in England and Wales in the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193477","193477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44642","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the annual survey of hours and earnings published on 12 December 2013, if he will estimate the number and proportion of (a) men and (b) women in (i) full-time and (ii) part-time work in each (A) local authority area and (B) parliamentary constituency earning the national minimum wage in April 2013 defined as (1) adults aged 21 years and over earning less than £6.24, (2) youths (aged 18 to 20) earning less than £5.03 and (3) 16 to 17 year olds earning less than £3.73.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193516","193516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44643","2014-03-26","Cabinet Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to incentivise departmental officials to bring old Government data sets online in accessible formats.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193287","193287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44644","2014-03-26","Cabinet Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193382","193382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44645","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason the amount allocated to the Regional Air Connectivity Fund in line 37 of Table 2.1 of Budget 2014 is £10 million per annum and the increase in funding listed at paragraph 2.42 for that Fund is £20 million per annum.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193327","193327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44646","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on how many occasions illegal fuel plants in Northern Ireland have been uncovered (a) when the fuel plant has still been operating and (b) at times when the plant had ceased being operational in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193402","193402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44647","2014-03-26","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many credit unions were operating in the UK in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193285","193285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44648","2014-03-26","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking against mortgage lenders who breach the terms of tracker-rate mortgage contracts and unilaterally increase the interest rate charged.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193279","193279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44649","2014-03-26","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of how much will be collected annually by HM Revenue and Customs through successful insolvency litigation with the use of damages-based agreements.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193369","193369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44650","2014-03-26","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to HM Revenue and Customs of the reforms to insolvency litigation under the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193370","193370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44651","2014-03-26","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much HM Revenue and Customs collected following successful insolvency litigation cases in each year since 2010.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193371","193371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44652","2014-03-26","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what consultation process is being held on the new £1 coin; and what steps he is taking to ensure that such a consultation includes representation from all parts of the country, charities and other non-industry groups.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193321","193321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44653","2014-03-26","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to pensions on the level of net migration and the number of over-55s who may emigrate; and what analysis his Department has made of the effect of this policy on the likelihood of meeting the target of reducing net migration to under 100,000 by 2015.","Biography information for Mark Reckless","Mark Reckless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193322","193322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44654","2014-03-26","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what account his Department has taken of mortgage liability in its assessment of liability for levy on higher value homes as part of its work preparatory to the possible introduction of such a tax.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193510","193510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44655","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how his Department calculates that 2.5 million eligible families would benefit from tax-free childcare in the consultation on Tax-free Childcare; and how his Department calculated the revised figure of 1.26 million eligible familes in Delivering Tax-Free Childcare, the Government's response to the consultation on design and operation.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193329","193329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44656","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has held with the Guernsey Financial Services Commission on its investigation into the Channel Islands Stock Exchange over its recognised status and the recent reported allegations of wrongdoing.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193331","193331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44657","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate has been made of the number of properties in each region liable for a possible levy on higher value homes.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193359","193359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44658","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what work has been carried out by his Department's officials on the possible introduction of a levy on higher value homes; what starting points for liability in the value of properties have been considered in the course of any such work; and if he will publish that work.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193360","193360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44659","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what methods of assessing liability for a levy on higher value homes have been considered by his Department in the course of preparatory work on the introduction of such a tax; whether individual valuation of properties has been considered in such work; and what estimate has been made of the cost of implementation of such a tax.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193361","193361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44660","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what consultations have been carried out with (a) valuers and (b) other organisations on the possible introduction of a levy on higher value homes.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193362","193362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44661","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate has been made of the yield of a levy on higher value homes during the preparatory work carried out by his Department into the possible introduction of such a tax.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193358","193358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44662","2014-03-26","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to support the development of virtual currency exchanges in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193416","193416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44663","2014-03-26","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the value of UK financial assets held in Russia.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193414","193414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44664","2014-03-26","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the value of Russian financial assets held in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193415","193415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44665","2014-03-26","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the risk of virtual currencies facilitating money laundering and other financial offences.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193417","193417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44666","2014-03-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost to landlords of fitting smoke alarms in all rented properties.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193341","193341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44667","2014-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish guidance on how local authorities can keep business rates linked to green energy and carbon neutral or passive developments; and what proportion of business rates he expects local authorities to retain.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193464","193464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44668","2014-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to encourage local authority pension funds to become signatories to the Stewardship Code.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193480","193480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44669","2014-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to encourage local authority pension funds to become active owners or stewards of their assets as defined in the Financial Reporting Council's Stewardship Code.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193481","193481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44670","2014-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the need for local authority pension schemes to integrate environmental, social and governance issues into their investment decision-making.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193479","193479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44671","2014-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has for how the new development corporation at Ebbsfleet will work with existing local authorities.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193435","193435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44672","2014-03-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many proposals have been made by local authorities under the Sustainable Communities Act 2007 in each year since that Act has been in force; and how many such proposals his Department has adopted.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193399","193399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44673","2014-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of the Government's proposed Ebbsfleet development will be funded by (a) the private sector and (b) public-sector resources.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193426","193426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44674","2014-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what consultations the Government has undertaken in drawing up plans for its proposed development at Ebbsfleet.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193425","193425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44675","2014-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of the development announced in Budget 2014 at Ebbsfleet will consist of affordable homes.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193427","193427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44676","2014-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how the Government's proposed Ebbsfleet development will be funded.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193428","193428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44677","2014-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish detailed proposals for the new development corporation announced for Ebbsfleet; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193429","193429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44678","2014-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193383","193383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44679","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what principles and criteria new developments will be required to meet in areas designated as garden cities.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193457","193457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44680","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to establish garden city principles in Ebbsfleet.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193458","193458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44681","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which organisation and individuals (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have met to discuss the recently announced garden city prospectus; and how many such meetings have been held with each organisation or individual.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193459","193459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44682","2014-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what infrastructure his Department has planned and what resources it has allocated in relation to the development of housing at Ebbsfleet.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193424","193424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44683","2014-03-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what provisions are in place as part of the Government's Olympic Legacy commitments for people with learning disabilities.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193316","193316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44684","2014-03-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding Special Olympics Great Britain has received from her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193353","193353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44685","2014-03-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on her Department's reviews of regulation of fixed odds betting terminals; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193290","193290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44686","2014-03-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the BBC Trust on the BBC's exercise of its responsibilities to provide religious broadcasting.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193545","193545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44687","2014-03-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the Government plans to ratify the 2001 UNESCO Convention on the Protection of Underwater Cultural Heritage.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193466","193466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44688","2014-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the military port function of the Sea Mounting Centre at Marchwood will continue to be operated in that location after the awarding of a lease to a commercial organisation for the development of part of that site; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193440","193440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44689","2014-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many F-35s the UK is contractually obliged to purchase.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193514","193514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44690","2014-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many F-35s his Department plans to purchase under its Joint Equipment Programme.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193515","193515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44691","2014-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to retain a permanent British garrison in continental Europe in response to recent events in the Crimea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193348","193348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44692","2014-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will update the Defence Strategic Guidance to reflect the Russian annexation of the Crimea.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193347","193347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44693","2014-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193384","193384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44694","2014-03-26","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-24","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what his Office's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193385","193385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44696","2014-03-26","Department for Education","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Statement of 13 March 2014 by the Minister for Schools, Official Report, columns 927-29, how much of the £350 million announced for the fair funding proposals will be allocated from the Exchequer in addition to that already indicated in his Department's budget.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193407","193407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44697","2014-03-26","Department for Education","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193386","193386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44698","2014-03-26","Department for Education","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people with learning disabilities reported being bullied at school in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193311","193311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44699","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to make the UK a priority destination for the King Abdullah university scholarship programme.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193434","193434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44700","2014-03-26","Department for Education","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are home-schooled in (a) Lancashire and (b) Rossendale and Darwen constituency.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193308","193308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44701","2014-03-27","Department for Education","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparison he has made with other OECD countries of the effects on pedagogy of giving one to one tablets to every pupil in secondary schools.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193448","193448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44702","2014-03-27","Department for Education","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effects on pedagogy of giving pupils in secondary schools one to one tablet computers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193447","193447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44703","2014-03-27","Department for Education","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress his Department has made on the rollout of broadband for schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193446","193446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44704","2014-03-27","Department for Education","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the baseline requirements are for wi-fi provision for all secondary schools to enable the use of one-to-one tablet computers in the classroom; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193444","193444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44705","2014-03-27","Department for Education","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the baseline requirement is for wi-fi provision for all primary schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193445","193445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44706","2014-03-26","Department for Education","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what applications he received from groups in Lancashire to establish a new free school in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193300","193300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44707","2014-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of properties in (a) Rossendale and Darwen constituency and (b) the North West which do not have mains gas access and which use domestic heating oil.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193301","193301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44708","2014-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many spare (a) generator step-up transformers and (b) transmission transformers are held in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193422","193422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44709","2014-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which companies manufacture (a) generator step-up transformers and (b) transmission transformers in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193423","193423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44710","2014-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of the UK's (a) coal, (b) gas and (c) oil requirements were met by imports from Russia in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193421","193421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44711","2014-03-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the effects on the community energy sector of removing eligibility for Enterprise Investment Scheme awards from business qualifying for renewable obligation certificates.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193453","193453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44712","2014-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the value of UK imports of (a) coal, (b) gas and (c) oil from Russia was in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193420","193420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44713","2014-03-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the use of flag brokers and flags of convenience by illegal, unreported and unregulated fishing vessels; and what representations he has made to his EU counterparts on this matter.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193471","193471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44714","2014-03-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Richmond Park, of 3 February 2011, Official Report, column 907W, on fishing vessels, what progress has been made on the creation of a global record of fishing vessels by the United Nations Food and Agriculture Organisation and what work is being undertaken by his Department on the mandatory use of International Maritime Organisation numbers for fishing vessels for the purposes of improving transparency in the global fishing industry.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193468","193468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44715","2014-03-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will seek to involve all the regions and constituent parts of the UK in developing a UK-wide strategy to tackle coastal erosion.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193538","193538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44716","2014-03-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he expects his Department's consultation on pest control to be concluded; and what the outcome has been of his Department's discussions on this matter with representatives of shooting organisations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193539","193539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44717","2014-03-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2014, Official Report, column 694W, on forests, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for International Development over the lessons to be learnt from her Department's contour afforestation schemes in developing countries.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193377","193377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44718","2014-03-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 552W, on forests, if he will make it the Environment Agency's policy to record this information in future.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193372","193372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44719","2014-03-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether changes in the number of puppies and dogs imported from EU member states since January 2012 are consistent with AHLVA risk assessment in 2010.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193356","193356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44720","2014-03-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations he has received on sheep rustling.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193319","193319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44721","2014-03-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much was spent on flood defences per head of population in (a) England and (b) each region of England in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193403","193403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44722","2014-03-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that UK companies involved with construction around the Qatari World Cup 2022 provide good conditions of work.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193282","193282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44723","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how the International Court of Justice's judgment on 5 December 2011 in the case concerning the Application of the Interim Accord of 13 September 1995 (the former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia v. Greece) will affect the Republic of Macedonia's membership entry into the North Atlantic Treaty Organisation.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193391","193391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44724","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's policy is on (a) the Republic of Macedonia and (b) the Republic of Montenegro joining the North Atlantic Treaty Organisation discussions during the 2014 Summit in Wales.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193392","193392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44725","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Greek counterpart on the Republic of Macedonia's entry into the North Atlantic Treaty Organisation.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193393","193393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44726","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether it is his Department's policy to formally classify the presence of Russian troops in (a) South Ossetia, (b) Abkhazia, (c) the Autonomous Republic of Crimea and (d) the City of Sevastopol as an occupation.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193394","193394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44727","2014-03-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in which G8 sub-groups Russia has been a participant in the last 10 years; and what assessment he has made of the effect on the work of such sub-groups arising from the suspension of Russia from the G8.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193291","193291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44728","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to Israel on the building of 839 new housing units in the Settlement of Ariel announced in March 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193397","193397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44729","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Indian counterpart on access to tourist visas for UK nationals with Pakistani heritage.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193335","193335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44730","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with ministerial colleagues on the potential role of the UK's sovereign bases in Cyprus in reaching a comprehensive settlement in Cyrpus.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193499","193499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44731","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential economic benefits of reaching a comprehensive settlement in Cyprus in respect of resolving the issues relating to the port of Famagusta.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193500","193500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44732","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions (a) he and (b) his ministerial colleagues have had with their EU counterparts on efforts to reach a comprehensive settlement in Cyprus in respect of issues relating to the port of Famagusta.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193502","193502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44733","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions (a) he and (b) his ministerial colleagues have had with their Turkish counterparts on efforts to reach a comprehensive settlement in Cyprus in respect of issues relating to the port of Famagusta.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193501","193501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44734","2014-03-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the South Korean government on monitoring and controlling the South Korean distant water fishing fleet following the formal warning issued to South Korea by the EU about frequent illegal, unreported and unregulated fishing violations in west Africa.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193472","193472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44735","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to strengthen the language of the draft Human Rights Council Resolution on Promoting Reconciliation, Accountability and Human Rights in Sri Lanka and to build support from Human Rights Council members for an international inquiry into Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193332","193332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44736","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the risk of expropriation of UK assets in Russia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193363","193363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44737","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the risk of a Russian invasion of the Transnistria region of Moldova; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193364","193364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44738","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the arrest and interrogation of eight Christians in Iran on 5 March 2014 and the issuing of arrest warrants for Amin Khuki, Hossein Bamuzadah and Rahman Buhman; and what recent representations he has made to Iran on religious toleration.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193367","193367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44739","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will seek an estimate from all British Overseas Territory governments of the value of Russian (a) financial and (b) non-financial assets held in their territories.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193366","193366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44740","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to extend the requirement to apply sanctions set out in Council Regulation (EU) 269/2014 to all British Overseas Territory governments.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193365","193365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44741","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that patients' views and feedback are taken into account in the delivery of mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193449","193449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44742","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish all representations made to him by NHS England on the care.data scheme.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193450","193450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44743","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the health risks associated with krokodil.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193451","193451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44744","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the proportion of children aged 4 and 5 years who have received screening for visual defects since 1 April 2013; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure such screening is provided universally across England in line with the recommendations of the UK National Screening Committee.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193330","193330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44745","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what disciplinary action he plans to take against hospital managers and workers who have incinerated foetal remains against the wishes of the parents.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193307","193307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44746","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will establish a strategic small surgeries fund to help small rural GPs affected by the new funding formulae.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193503","193503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44747","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer to Lord Beecham of 20 March 2014, Official Report, House of Lords, column 269, how much the Government has spent on (a) Healthy Start, (b) Change4Life and (c) the School Fruit and Vegetable Scheme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193496","193496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44748","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many managers and administrators were employed in the NHS in the (a) latest period for which figures are available and (b) 12 months prior to that period.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193509","193509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44749","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff at each grade were employed in each of the private offices of the directors of the Health Protection Agency in the 12 months prior to April 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193497","193497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44750","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS England on the time taken to roll-out the care.data scheme.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193498","193498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44751","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what safeguards are in place to protect people against health problems arising from operations involving the use of botulism toxin.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193542","193542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44752","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of necrotising fasciitis have been recorded in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193541","193541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44753","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of recent progress in the diagnosis of dementia and in the availability to the public of improved methods of diagnosis.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193540","193540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44754","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of cases of concussion in (a) football and (b) other contact sports.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193544","193544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44755","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on disposal of foetal remains through incineration to heat hospitals.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193326","193326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44756","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implementation across the NHS in England of the National Institute for Care Excellence quality standard on psoriasis.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193433","193433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44757","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the costs to the NHS of krokodil.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193430","193430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44758","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that women diagnosed with ovarian cancer should be tested for the BRCA 1/2 gene on diagnosis.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193339","193339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44759","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department will incentivise the NHS to meet the National Institute for Care Excellence quality standard on psoriasis.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193431","193431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44760","2014-03-27","Cabinet Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women in Warrington were (a) diagnosed with ovarian cancer and (b) had ovarian cancer listed as a cause of death in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193340","193340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44761","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with NHS England on the implementation of the National Institute for Care Excellence quality standard on psoriasis.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193432","193432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44762","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women and girls received NHS treatment in each foundation trust area after having undergone a female genital mutilation procedure in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193323","193323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44763","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the impartiality of abortion counselling advice provided by Marie Stopes and the British Pregnancy Advisory Service.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193314","193314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44764","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that information sourced by GPs is reliable and safe to pass to patients.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193439","193439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44765","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the British Pregnancy Advisory Service is not undertaking abortions based on gender.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193312","193312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44766","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2014, Official Report, columns 724-5W, on medical records: databases, if he will list the holders of a commercial re-use licence granted by the Health and Social Care Information Centre (HSCIC); and for each such licence for what purpose the use of HSCIC data was approved.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193405","193405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44767","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2013, Official Report, column 718W, what the additional funding for radiotherapy was spent on in each year since April 2011; and if he will publish NHS England's expenditure plans for the additional £42 million allocated for improving radiotherapy services in 2014-15.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193376","193376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44768","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England has begun the process of considering the recommendation of the Cancer Drugs Fund Panel's decision in January 2014 that ipilimumab should be commissioned directly by NHS England through baseline commissioning as a first-line treatment for advanced melanoma.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193437","193437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44769","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the draft European General Data Protection Regulation on medical research.","Biography information for Rebecca Harris","Rebecca Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193436","193436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44770","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the quality of psychological support available to individuals with cystic fibrosis who receive a lung transplantation.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193292","193292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44771","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which treatments have been appraised through a technology appraisal by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence or its predecessor bodies; in which indication each treatment was appraised; on which date each appraisal was (a) initiated and (b) concluded; what the estimated eligible patient population for the treatment in each appraised indication was; whether the end-of-life criteria were applied in each final appraisal determination; whether the additional healthcare costs associated with prolonged survival were captured in each final appraisal determination; what the (i) lowest, (ii) highest and (iii) base case estimate of the cost-per-quality adjusted life year of the treatment in each appraised indication was; and what the recommendation resulting from each appraisal was.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193294","193294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44772","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Congleton of 25 February 2014, Official Report, column 156W, on sex-selective abortion, if he will ensure that the Government's forthcoming guidance on compliance with the Abortion Act 1967 addresses the question of whether or not it is necessary for registered medical practitioners to see a woman in order to form an opinion in good faith that the continuance of the pregnancy would adversely affect her mental or physical health; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193295","193295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44773","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what evidence his Department has assessed on whether giving birth to a baby of a particular gender constitutes a greater risk to the mother's physical or mental health than termination of the pregnancy.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193284","193284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44774","2014-03-27","Cabinet Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of women in (a) the UK and (b) the North West were diagnosed with ovarian cancer in the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193396","193396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44775","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to his Answer of 20 March 2014, Official Report, columns 725-6W, on mental health services, what critical steps were set out at the third Choice in the Mental Health Workshop on 12 March 2014; and if he will publish the minutes of that workshop and the programme that emerged from it.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193411","193411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44776","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects to (a) receive and (b) publish his response to Sir Cyril Chantler's independent review of the public health impact of standardised tobacco packaging.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193409","193409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44777","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff of what grades there are in each of the private offices of the directors of Public Health England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193410","193410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44778","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people with learning disabilities received annual health checks in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193343","193343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44779","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the (a) name, (b) job title, (c) salary level and (d) professional qualifications of each director who has worked at Public Health England since that body's formation; and if he will state whether each such position was advertised publicly.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193389","193389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44780","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure all people with learning difficulties receive annual health checks.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193354","193354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44781","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what targets his Department has set for the number of people with learning difficulties who will receive annual health checks in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193355","193355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44782","2014-03-26","Home Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations she has received on sheep rustling.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193320","193320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44783","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2014, Official Report, column 604W, on EU Justice and Home Affairs, with which countries the EU as a legal personality has concluded co-operation agreements in the field of justice and home affairs.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193408","193408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44784","2014-03-26","Home Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the contribution of the (a) Tier 1 (Entrepreneur) visa route and (b) Tier 1 (Investor) visa route on economic growth.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193286","193286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44785","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department has paid for the use of Interpol's SLTD database in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193398","193398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44786","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking on the decision to allow the sale and consumption of alcohol in a motorway service area.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193334","193334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44787","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied asylum-seeking children there were in the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193337","193337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44788","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied asylum-seeking children were placed in local authority care in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193336","193336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44789","2014-03-26","Home Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with representatives of the retail sector about measures that could be taken by shops selling alcohol to reduce the incidence of binge-drinking.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193543","193543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44790","2014-03-26","Home Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many serious misconduct complaints related to the use of control and restraint during enforced removal were referred to the Professional Standards Unit in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193473","193473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44791","2014-03-26","Home Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests were made for immigration offences as a result of information received from the public in each week in 2013; and how many resulted in (a) prosecution and (b) deportation.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193469","193469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44792","2014-03-26","Home Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the report by the Refugee Council, When Maternity Doesn't Matter, what steps her Department has taken to reform the dispersal policy of the former UK Border Agency.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193461","193461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44793","2014-03-26","Home Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time was between a deportation order being made on a foreign national offender and their deportation in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193470","193470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44794","2014-03-26","Home Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many failed removals of foreign national offenders there were in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193474","193474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44795","2014-03-26","House of Commons Commission","2014-03-24","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, how many fire alarms have sounded in Portcullis House in the last 12 months; on how many of these occasions the London Fire Brigade arrived to attend a fire; and on how many of these occasions the London Fire Brigade discovered a fire.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193305","193305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44796","2014-03-26","Department for International Development","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has made an assessment of the level of risk experienced by female human rights defenders in Afghanistan; and what arrangements are in place to support their work and create a safer environment.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193460","193460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44797","2014-03-26","Department for International Development","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the policy of Barclays on the use of tax havens.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193462","193462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44798","2014-03-27","Department for International Development","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her speech of 27 January 2014 on smart aid, with which key industries and professions her Department is partnering.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193452","193452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44799","2014-03-26","Department for International Development","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to improve the capacity of governments and civil society in the west African coastal region to reduce illegal, unreported and unregulated fishing and protect local artisanal fishing.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193478","193478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44800","2014-03-27","Department for International Development","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her speech given at the London Stock Exchange on 27 January 2014, what the role will be of the dedicated contact points referred to in that speech; and whether organisations from civil society will have access to those contact points.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193513","193513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44801","2014-03-27","Department for International Development","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that its private sector strategy adheres to the Busan principles on aid effectiveness.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193511","193511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44802","2014-03-27","Department for International Development","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her speech given at the London Stock Exchange on 27 January 2014, which the major partner companies are that she referred to in the section of the speech dealing with greater engagement with businesses.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193512","193512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44803","2014-03-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic efforts his Department is making to support the Intergovernmental Authority on Development in bringing both sides of the South Sudanese conflict to the negotiating table and securing a deal for political reform.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193313","193313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44804","2014-03-26","Department for International Development","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Jonglei and the Upper Nile in South Sudan; and what steps she is taking to support those who are being displaced or affected by the conflict.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193318","193318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44805","2014-03-26","Department for International Development","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department has given to Special Olympic projects in the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193315","193315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44806","2014-03-26","Department for International Development","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the contribution of the Prime Minister of 19 March 2014, Official Report, column 781, what steps her Department (a) has taken and (b) plans to take in the next six months to ensure that UK aid is not used to facilitate or procure gender-based abortions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193296","193296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44807","2014-03-26","Department for International Development","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2014, Official Report, columns 187-8W on developing countries: forest, in which  of her Department's sponsored projects afforestation is used to minimise the risk of flooding.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193374","193374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44808","2014-03-26","Department for International Development","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what commitments the UK has to support people with learning disabilities in Africa.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193406","193406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44809","2014-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who the current bidders for the Transforming Rehabilitation prime provider contracts are in each of the 21 geographic areas; and which bidders for these contracts have indicated but then withdrawn an interest.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193390","193390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44810","2014-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in which instances Probation Trust staff have been co-located with other public or private organisations in (a) Probation Trust premises and (b) other organisation premises; and what the annual cost to the Probation Trust is of sub-letting space shared with another organisation for the purpose of staff co-location.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193387","193387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44811","2014-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people given custodial sentences for non-payment of (a) a television licence, (b) vehicle excise duty and (c) council tax in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013 were sentenced to (A) up to three months, (B) up to six months, (C) up to 12 months and (D) over 12 months.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193388","193388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44812","2014-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2013, Official Report, column 772W, on Judicial Review, what further assessment has been made of the reasons for the increase in the number of applications for judicial review.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193293","193293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44813","2014-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons Worksop Courthouse is planned to close.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193281","193281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44814","2014-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in Northern Ireland per 10,000 of the population were prosecuted for non-payment of the television licence fee in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193401","193401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44815","2014-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people appearing in court for non-payment of (a) a television licence, (b) vehicle excise duty and (c) council tax in each year since 2010 were found (i) guilty and (ii) not guilty.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193400","193400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44816","2014-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will seek an estimate from the (a) Bailiwick of Jersey and (b) Bailiwick of Guernsey of the value of Russian (a) financial and (b) non-financial assets held in each such territory.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193345","193345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44817","2014-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he take steps to extend the requirement to apply sanctions set out in Council Regulation (EU) 269/2014 to the (a) Bailiwick of Jersey and (b) Bailiwick of Guernsey.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193346","193346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44818","2014-03-27","Attorney General","2014-03-24","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2014, Official Report, columns 705-6W, on domestic violence: prosecutions, if he will estimate the number of victimless prosecutions for domestic violence-related offences in 2013.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193325","193325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44819","2014-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on the introduction of legally binding pre-nuptial agreements.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193537","193537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44820","2014-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with which countries the EU as a legal personality is currently negotiating co-operation agreements in the field of justice and home affairs.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193454","193454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44821","2014-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with which countries the EU as a legal personality has concluded co-operation agreements in the field of justice and home affairs.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193455","193455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44822","2014-03-27","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many people on remand or on bail in connection with terrorism-related charges are recipients of letters as part of the On the Run scheme.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193412","193412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44823","2014-03-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2014, Official Report, columns 654-5, on electoral register, if the Electoral Commission will publish the results of all research it has conducted into the size of the electorate.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193378","193378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44824","2014-03-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what research the Electoral Commission has commissioned into online voting.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193288","193288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44825","2014-03-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the introduction of online voting in (a) Australia and (b) South Africa and its relevance to the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193289","193289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44826","2014-03-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2014, Official Report, column 655W, on electoral register, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the reasons for the increase between December 2000 and April 2011 in the proportion of eligible people not registered at their current address.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193404","193404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44827","2014-04-02","Department for Transport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2014, Official Report, column 693W, on bus services: disability, how many public service vehicles (a) in each region and (b) operated by each operator have been issued with PSVAR certificates.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193342","193342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44828","2014-03-26","Department for Transport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the benefits to children's safety of road crossing patrollers.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193298","193298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44829","2014-03-27","Department for Transport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with train operating companies and rolling stock companies on the availability of rolling stock to train operating companies during the periods of franchise extension.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193333","193333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44830","2014-03-27","Department for Transport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy that the remuneration of Network Rail executives should be reduced in response to the incidence of deaths on level crossings.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193324","193324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44831","2014-03-26","Department for Transport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that houses purchased by HS2 Limited under the Exceptional Hardship Scheme are not sold on at less than market value.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193438","193438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44832","2014-03-26","Department for Transport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been allocated to Lancashire County Council to repair potholes in (a) Lancashire and (b) Rossendale.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193302","193302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44833","2014-03-26","Department for Transport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent on road crossing patrollers in (a) Essex and (b) Harlow constituency in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193303","193303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44834","2014-03-26","Department for Transport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been allocated from the £200 million fund to repair potholes to Blackburn with Darwen Borough Council to repair potholes in Darwen.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193304","193304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44835","2014-03-27","Department for Transport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2014, Official Report, column 692W, on rural bus services, to which projects the £300 million funding for major bus projects has been allocated; and how much has been allocated to each.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193328","193328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44836","2014-03-26","Department for Transport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to ratify the International Labour Organisation amendment C188 on the Work in Fishing Convention, in respect of a minimum age for work on a fishing vessel, minimum medical standards, basic work agreements, occupational health and safety, and social security.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193467","193467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44837","2014-03-27","Department for Transport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to appoint the working group to assess the impact of the Equality Act 2010 (Work on Ships and Hovercraft) Regulations 2011 in the shipping industry; what the terms of reference will be for that group; and what the expected timeframe will be within which it will report its findings to Ministers.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193494","193494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44838","2014-03-27","Department for Transport","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to enforce the Equality Act 2010 (Work on Ships and Hovercraft) Regulations 2011 in the shipping industry; and which regulatory body is responsible for such enforcement on (a) UK and (b) overseas-flagged vessels in UK ports.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193495","193495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44839","2014-03-26","Women and Equalities","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many meetings of the Ministerial Taskforce established to implement the recommendations of the Women's Business Council have been held; on what date each such meeting was held; who attended each such meeting; and how many further meetings she expects will be held in 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193482","193482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44840","2014-03-26","Women and Equalities","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many full-time equivalent members of staff she has allocated to support the work of the Ministerial Taskforce established to implement the recommendations of the Women's Business Council.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193483","193483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44841","2014-03-26","Women and Equalities","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the achievements to date of the Ministerial Taskforce established to implement the recommendations of the Women's Business Council.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193484","193484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44842","2014-03-26","Women and Equalities","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what meetings (a) she, (b) Ministers in her Department and (c) officials in her Department have held with external organisations or individuals to discuss the work programme of the Ministerial Taskforce established to implement the recommendations of the Women's Business Council.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193485","193485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44843","2014-03-26","Women and Equalities","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what meetings (a) she, (b) Ministers in her Department and (c) officials in her Department have held with (i) Age UK and (ii) the National Institute of Adult Continuing Education to discuss the trialling of new approaches to supporting the skills development of older workers.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193487","193487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44844","2014-03-26","Women and Equalities","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what progress her Department has made in developing guidance and toolkits for employers on retention practices for older workers.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193488","193488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44845","2014-03-26","Women and Equalities","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what progress she has made on appointing a business champion for older workers.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193486","193486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44846","2014-03-26","Women and Equalities","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with which organisations and individuals her Department has co-operated on the development of guidance and toolkits for employers on retention practices for older workers.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193489","193489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44847","2014-03-26","Women and Equalities","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will publish guidance and make available resources for parents to enable them to help their children make well-informed career and subject choices.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193493","193493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44848","2014-03-26","Women and Equalities","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what progress her Department has made on the establishment of regional pilots to test different ways to support carers to remain in work; which regions have been selected to run such pilots; what funding is being made available for such pilots; and when she expects such pilots to begin.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193490","193490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44849","2014-03-26","Women and Equalities","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to assist people with caring responsibilities to set up their own small business.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193491","193491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44850","2014-03-26","Women and Equalities","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what meetings (a) she, (b) Ministers in her Department and (c) officials in her Department have held with (i) the British Banking Association and (ii) other relevant organisations to discuss access to finance for female entrepreneurs.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193492","193492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44851","2014-03-26","HM Treasury","2014-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what regulatory standards he plans to put in place to ensure people have access to high quality financial advice.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193280","193280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44852","2014-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's policy is on whether receiving parents should be responsible for estimating the weekly expenses of the paying parent in the calculation of child maintenance entitlement.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193357","193357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44853","2014-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the suitability of the medical assessment undertaken for personal independence payment claims.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193375","193375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44854","2014-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the performance of Atos in carrying out medical assessments for personal independence payments; and if he will review this contract following the recent announcement on the Employment and Support Allowance Work Capability Assessment contract.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193373","193373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44855","2014-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people paying the under-occupancy penalty who have fallen into rent arrears.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193395","193395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44856","2014-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will amend the benefits rules on the habitual residency test to exempt family members in the services returning from an overseas posting; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193379","193379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44857","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with INEOS on its refusal to recognise a trade union at the Grangemouth refinery.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193317","193317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44858","2014-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to increase the number of people with learning disabilities in both part-time and full-time employment.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193310","193310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44859","2014-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people registered with a learning disability were in (a) part-time and (b) full-time employment in (i) 2009, (ii) 2010, (iii) 2011, (iv) 2012 and (v) 2013.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193309","193309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44860","2014-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many press officers his Department employed in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193508","193508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44861","2014-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people on the Work Programme with (a) no qualification, (b) a qualification below Level 2, (c) a qualification at Level 2 and (d) a qualification at Level 3, 4 or above secured a sustained job outcome within two years of starting on the programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193506","193506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44862","2014-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on tackling worklessness among social housing tenants.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193507","193507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44863","2014-03-27","Cabinet Office","2014-03-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) 18 year olds and (b) people under 25 have been out of work for over a year; and what the equivalent figures were in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193505","193505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44864","2014-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proposals he has to tackle worklessness among social housing tenants.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193504","193504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44865","2014-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of zero-hours contract positions advertised in Jobcentre Plus in England in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193443","193443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44866","2014-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much additional funding each local authority will receive to enable it to investigate whether claimants are eligible for refund of under-occupancy penalty payments in 2014-15.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193441","193441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44867","2014-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what powers the Child Support Agency has to investigate the weekly expenses of parents who are paying child maintenance.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193306","193306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44868","2014-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria will be used by his Department to determine how much funding each local authority will receive to investigate those eligible to receive a refund of under-occupancy payments.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193456","193456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44973","2014-03-27","Church Commissioners","2014-03-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what estimate he has made of when it will be possible for women to be bishops in the Church of England.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903288","903288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45018","2014-03-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to reduce the effect of rises in rural and off-grid energy bills on the cost of living.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903328","903328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45019","2014-03-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress he has made in negotiations with the European Commission on a derogation from the ban on the import or manufacture of incandescent bulbs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903331","903331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45032","2014-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the outcomes were of the London Conference on the Illegal Wildlife Trade 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903339","903339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45033","2014-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of progress on the water pricing review led by Ofwat; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903340","903340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44490","2014-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on maintaining the requirement for quoted companies to report on their greenhouse gas emissions.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193215","193215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44491","2014-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the resource, accounting and budgeting charge is for student loans issued (a) to those on the new funding regime, (b) in 2013-14 and (c) in 2012-13.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193225","193225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44492","2014-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what revisions have been made to the fair value of student loans issued under the previous funding regime.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193230","193230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44493","2014-03-26","HM Treasury","2014-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the reasons are for the difference between paragraph 1.5 of Tax-Free Childcare: consultation on design and operation, which states that tax-free childcare will ultimately be available to up to around 2.5 million working families in the UK and paragraph B.4 of the Government's response to that consultation, which states that around 1.9 million families will be eligible for tax-free childcare; and what the difference is between being eligible for the scheme and having qualifying childcare costs.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193217","193217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44494","2014-03-26","Department for Transport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 2.42 of Budget 2014, whether the Regional Air Connectivity Fund will only be available to new domestic routes; which regional airports will be eligible; when funding is likely to become available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193243","193243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44495","2014-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to discounted local authority leisure services to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193246","193246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44496","2014-03-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she plans to take to promote tourism in (a) North Yorkshire and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193211","193211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44497","2014-03-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent representations he has received on the work of military personnel in flood recovery operations.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193213","193213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44498","2014-03-25","Department for Education","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how the 60 mathematics teachers brought to the UK from Shanghai for an exchange organised by his Department were chosen.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193216","193216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44499","2014-03-25","Department for Education","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who owns the freehold of schools which have converted to academies; and what restrictions there are on the use of such freeholds.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193219","193219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44500","2014-03-26","Department for Education","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to free school meals to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193248","193248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44501","2014-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to assistance with utility costs to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193247","193247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44502","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on research into chronic obstructive pulmonary disease in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193220","193220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44503","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) partial and (b) whole lung transplants have been performed in the last five years; and which conditions patients had that made them eligible for a lung transplant.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193221","193221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44504","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP practices in England have access to spirometry equipment; and what proportion of that equipment is quality-assured diagnostic level spirometry.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193222","193222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44505","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of pulmonary rehabilitation services that were at full provision in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193223","193223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44506","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spends on provision of pulmonary rehabilitation services in England; and how much the NHS spends on provision of cardiac rehabilitation services in England.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193224","193224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44507","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to free prescriptions to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193244","193244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44508","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on nationally commissioned NHS services (a) at each hospital trust and (b) for each medical specialty in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2010-11, (iii) 2009-10, (iv) 2008-09, (v) 2007-08, (vi) 2006-07, (vii) 2005-06 and (viii) 2004-05.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193226","193226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44509","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings his Department had with representatives of (a) the Wine and Spirits Trade Association, (b) the Scotch Whisky Association, (c) the British Beer and Pub Association, (d) Diageo, (e) SAB Miller and (f) The Portman Group between 1 November 2013 and 19 March 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193240","193240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44510","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on nationally-commissioned NHS services (a) at each hospital trust and (b) for each medical specialty in 2012-13.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193228","193228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44511","2014-03-26","Department for International Development","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to provide support to the Gaza aquifer to enable it to recover from pollution and damage caused by over-pumping.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193241","193241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44512","2014-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to (a) assistance with civil and criminal legal aid, (b) remission for court fees and (c) access to the assisted prison visits programme to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193245","193245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44513","2014-03-25","Department for Transport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the number of bus services that have closed in the last 12 months; and what assessment he has made of the effects of changes to the concessionary travel scheme on the viability of local bus services.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193214","193214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44514","2014-03-26","Department for Transport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the £183.5 million funding commitment to help repair local roads damaged by severe weather announced by him on 20 March 2014 is the same allocation as the £140 million of spending for pothole repair announced by him on 9 March 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193242","193242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44515","2014-03-25","Department for Transport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects new trains to run on the electrified Liverpool to Manchester line.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193227","193227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44516","2014-03-25","Department for Transport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date orders were placed for rolling stock to operate on the electrified Liverpool to Manchester line.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193229","193229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44517","2014-03-25","Women and Equalities","2014-03-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she expects to meet each of the recommendations in the concluding observations of the UN Committee on the Elimination of Discrimination Against Women on the Seventh Periodic Report of the UK Government.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193218","193218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44518","2014-03-25","Women and Equalities","2014-03-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of trends in the number of women in public life.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193212","193212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44519","2014-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent estimate he has made of the (a) face and (b) fair value of existing student loans.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193231","193231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44520","2014-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the resource, accounting and budgeting charge is for student loans issued (a) those who started study before September 2012, (b) in 2013-14 and (c) in 2012-13.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193232","193232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44521","2014-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what consideration he has given to amending the Unfair Contract Terms Act 1977 to remove section 1(c) of schedule 1 on intellectual property contracts.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193238","193238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44522","2014-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received in favour of the inclusion of intellectual property contracts in the Consumer Rights Bill.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193239","193239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44523","2014-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what consideration he has given to amending the Consumer Rights Bill to provide greater protection for creators against unfair contracts.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193249","193249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44524","2014-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Intellectual Property Office has taken to promote existing protected but underused intellectual property to companies that may be interested in taking it up.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193267","193267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44525","2014-03-25","HM Treasury","2014-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the interest incurred on the debt needed to finance High Speed 2.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193261","193261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44526","2014-03-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps are being taken to ensure that the legal costs accrued over the closure of the Traveller site in Fylde are recovered from the travellers.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193259","193259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44527","2014-03-25","Department for Education","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria were used to calculate the uplift of (a) primary and (b) secondary students grant per pupil in each local education authority; and for what reasons Staffordshire received no special uplift.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193237","193237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44528","2014-03-26","Department for Education","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to designate the New Schools Network as a public authority for the purposes of the Freedom of Information Act 2000; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193278","193278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44529","2014-03-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his Written Statement of 11 March 2014, Official Report, columns 14-5WS, on EU Energy Council, what the evidential basis is for his statement that climate policy had had little impact on energy prices across Europe.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193273","193273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44530","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of gaming of 18 and 52 week waiting list thresholds by NHS secondary care providers in Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193266","193266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44531","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding his Department provided for awareness-raising work for chronic obstructive pulmonary disease in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193235","193235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44532","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of patient satisfaction (a) during and (b) after the delivery of mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193252","193252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44533","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he plans to provide services to support midwives reporting cases of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193253","193253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44534","2014-03-26","Department of Health","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the services available to support the transition of mental health patients from an early intervention team to a community mental health team.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193251","193251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44535","2014-03-26","Home Office","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons the expert panel for the review into new psychoactive substances does not include representation from the public health sector.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193255","193255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44536","2014-03-25","Home Office","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to implement the commitments made in the outcome document for UN Commission on the Status of Women 2013; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193275","193275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44537","2014-03-25","Home Office","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from civil society organisations on the UN Commission on the Status of Women 2014.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193276","193276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44538","2014-03-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were sentenced in the North Wales Police Force area to immediate custody for (a) less than six months and (b) six months or longer in each of the last six years, broken down by sex; and for which offences they were sentenced.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193272","193272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44539","2014-03-26","Department for Transport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 139W on driver: licensing, how many cases handled by the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency that required medical decisions were returned within the 90 working days target in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193254","193254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44540","2014-03-25","Department for Transport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2014, Official Report, columns 511-2W, on High Speed 2 railway line, at what URL the March 2012 reports of HS2 Ltd are published; and on what pages of those reports the evidence that led to the decision to route via Crewe rather than Stoke-on-Trent is set out.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193269","193269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44541","2014-03-25","Department for Transport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2014, Official Report, columns 511-2W, on High Speed 2 railway line, what calculations were done to demonstrate that alternative schemes would fail to deliver sufficient additional capacity; and what the passenger load factor of High Speed 2 will be as against the passenger load factor of longer trains.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193270","193270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44542","2014-03-25","Department for Transport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2014, Official Report, column 455W, on High Speed 2 railway line, on what basis it has been calculated that the (a) expense of and (b) disruption caused by adopting double-decker carriages on the West Coast Main Line would be greater than that of the construction of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193271","193271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44543","2014-03-25","Department for Transport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to HS2 Plus published on 17 March 2014, on what basis he has decided that the North's integrated station should be Crewe; and what alternative locations were considered.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193260","193260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44544","2014-03-25","Department for Transport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will consider rerouting High Speed 2 phase 2 through Stoke-on-Trent rather than Crewe as part of his consideration of the public responses to his Department's consultation.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193262","193262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44545","2014-03-25","Department for Transport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether there will be a review of the cost-benefit analysis of High Speed 2 following the decision to revise the High Speed 2 and High Speed 1 link.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193263","193263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44546","2014-03-25","Department for Transport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of how much more tickets for journeys on High Speed 2 will cost than for journeys on conventional trains; and how the cost of tickets for journeys on High Speed 2 will be calculated.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193264","193264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44547","2014-03-26","Home Office","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2014, Official Report, column 238W, on driving: licensing, how many new drivers who received driving convictions undertook speed awareness courses in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193256","193256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44548","2014-03-25","Department for Transport","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects training for train drivers to operate rolling stock on the electrified Liverpool to Manchester line to begin.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193234","193234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44549","2014-03-25","Women and Equalities","2014-03-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government has taken to meet each of the recommendations in the concluding observations of the UN Committee on the Elimination of Discrimination against Women on the Seventh Periodic Report of the UK Government; and what progress has been made on each recommendation.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193233","193233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44550","2014-03-25","Women and Equalities","2014-03-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the programme budget of the Government Equalities Office was in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-14; and what the real terms proportional change was between 2009-10 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193257","193257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44551","2014-03-25","Women and Equalities","2014-03-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the staffing budget for the Government Equalities Office is for (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16 years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193265","193265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44552","2014-03-25","Women and Equalities","2014-03-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the staffing budget of the Government Equalities Office was in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-14; and what the real terms proportional change was between 2009-10 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193258","193258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44553","2014-03-25","Women and Equalities","2014-03-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the Government Equalities Office programme budget is for (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193268","193268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44554","2014-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects to publish the audited figures for the Child Support Agency's client funds account for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Richard Bacon","Mr Richard Bacon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193274","193274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44555","2014-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of female-headed households which have had to relocate as a result of the benefit cap.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193250","193250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44556","2014-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of female-headed households which have had to relocate as a result of the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193236","193236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44557","2014-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Minister for Women and Equalities about highlighting the importance of women in the workplace in discussions on decent work at the UN Commission on the Status of Women 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193277","193277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44266","2014-03-25","Attorney General","2014-03-20","To ask the Attorney General, if he will place in the Library a copy of evidence submitted by the Law Officers' departments to the independent review of the RSCPA's prosecutions activity being carried out by Mr Stephen Wooler.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193040","193040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44267","2014-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to make access to BSI British Standards free to all UK businesses.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193004","193004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44268","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to combat the sale of fake drugs in the UK.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193070","193070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44269","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the effect of reductions in the budget of Trading Standards on its monitoring of food safety in the UK.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193009","193009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44270","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many small and medium-sized businesses were assisted by UK Trade & Investment in 2012-13.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193086","193086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44271","2014-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of businesses using UK Trade & Investment's services are either fairly satisfied or very satisfied with the service they have received in 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193031","193031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44272","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) small and medium-sized and (b) other businesses received direct financial assistance through UK Export Finance in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193051","193051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44273","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many firms have received support under the UK Export Finance Direct Lending Scheme to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193052","193052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44274","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his most recent assessment is of awareness among (a) small and (b) other businesses of the services offered by (i) UK Trade & Investment and (b) UK Export Finance; and what data his Department uses to monitor this awareness.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193053","193053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44275","2014-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) small and medium-sized and (b) other businesses have been assisted by UK Trade & Investment in 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193054","193054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44276","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish, using the 2011-12 data for higher rate taxpayers, how many and what proportion of the taxpaying population were in each taxpaying category in each region and nation of the UK; and what tax receipts accrued to the Exchequer from each such group in the last year for which data are available.","Biography information for Mr Gordon Brown","Mr Gordon Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193030","193030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44277","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the cost to the retail sector of converting all shopping trolley anti-theft guards to accept the new £1 coin.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193025","193025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44278","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the cost to (a) local authorities and (b) other parking operators of converting all ticket machines and meters to accept the new £1 coin; and if he will make funding available to help meet such costs.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193026","193026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44279","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the cost to the telecommunications industry of converting all telephone boxes to accept the new £1 coin; and if he will make funding available to this industry to help meet such costs.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193027","193027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44280","2014-03-25","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are currently employed by HM Revenue and Customs in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) each Scottish parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193010","193010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44281","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what provision he has made in funding for the tax-free childcare scheme beyond 2015 for increased take up from childcare resulting from maternal employment.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192992","192992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44282","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the annual amount of tax evasion attributable to gypsies and travellers.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193018","193018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44283","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of tax changes to fixed-odds betting terminals on (a) the number of betting shops and (b) the number of people employed in betting shops. [R]","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193019","193019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44284","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what evaluation he has made of the increase in greenhouse gas emissions resulting from the measures announced in paragraph 1.107 of the Budget 2014 to tackle the energy costs faced by the most energy intensive industries.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193065","193065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44285","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the change of use measures in paragraph 1.147 of the Budget 2014 will include a requirement on businesses extending parking areas to introduce sustainable urban drainage systems and permeable paving.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193066","193066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44286","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the impact on (a) UK employment levels and (b) Gross Domestic Product of a cut in fuel duty of (i) thre pence and (ii) one pence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193067","193067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44287","2014-03-25","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the proportion of families that will directly benefit from the tax-free childcare scheme that will be (a) couples and (b) lone parents.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193089","193089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44288","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings have taken place between (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department with FairFuelUK in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193068","193068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44289","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many evasion referrals were made to the HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) Evasion Referral Team in each tax year since 2011-12; and how many of those referrals were adopted as working cases by HMRC's (a) Criminal Investigation, (b) Specialist Investigation and (c) Local Compliance Fraud business units in each such year.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193124","193124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44290","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax refunds were withheld for enquiry to be made in the tax years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13 for (i) income tax, (ii) value added tax, (iii) corporation tax and (iv) national insurance.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193120","193120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44291","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what part by value of the tax refunds paid without being held for enquiry subsequently were reclaimed from the taxpayer to whom they were paid in the tax years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13 for (i) income tax, (ii) value added tax, (iii) corporation tax and (iv) national insurance.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193121","193121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44292","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many evasion referrals were made by the taskforces established by HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) to crack down on tax evasion and tax avoidance to the HMRC Evasion Referral Team in each tax year from 2011-12; and how many of those referrals were adopted as working cases by the HMRC's (i) Criminal Investigation, (ii) Specialist Investigation and (iii) Local Compliance Fraud business units.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193119","193119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44293","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value of tax refunds withheld for enquiry to be made was in the tax years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13 for (i) income tax, (ii) value added tax, (iii) corporation tax and (iv) national insurance; and what part by value was subsequently remitted to the taxpayer making the claim.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193122","193122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44294","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax refunds were made in the tax years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13 for (i) income tax, (ii) value added tax, (iii) corporation tax and (iv) national insurance; and what the total value of refunds was in each such category in each such year.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193123","193123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44295","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make funding available to help the (a) retail sector, (b) gaming industry and (c) vending machine operators meet the cost of the introduction of the new £1 coin.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193128","193128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44296","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the cost to the gaming industry of converting all video games machines, slot machines and other arcade machines to accept the new £1 coin.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193129","193129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44297","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the cost to the vending sector of converting all vending machines to accept the new £1 coin.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193130","193130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44298","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment has made of the overall cost to the economy of conversion to the new £1 coin.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193131","193131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44299","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential effects of the provisions of the Consumer Rights Bill on the administration and provision of childcare vouchers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193161","193161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44300","2014-03-24","HM Treasury","2014-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what value of loans have been issued under the Help to Buy equity loan scheme; how many loans have been issued to date; and what proportion of recipients are first-time buyers in each (a) region and (b) local authority area.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193179","193179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44301","2014-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential effects of the provisions of the Consumer Rights Bill on the provision and management by local authorities of controlled parking zones.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193160","193160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44302","2014-03-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of the use of sheltered housing to house families in temporary accommodation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193143","193143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44303","2014-03-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether there is a requirement for local authorities to remove apostrophes from street names and street signs.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193156","193156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44304","2014-03-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many onshore wind farm applications for what wind capacity were received by the Secretary of State in each month in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013; and how many of those applications of what capacity had been recommended for consent by the Planning Inspectorate.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193073","193073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44306","2014-03-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what information her Department holds on the comparative risks of (a) death, (b) concussion and (c) other medical problems and injuries resulting from taking part in major sports.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193006","193006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44307","2014-03-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of funding was allocated to (a) London and (b) Greater Manchester in each of the last three years to support creative industries from Arts Council England.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193011","193011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44308","2014-04-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to reform the Electronic Communications Code.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193135","193135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44309","2014-03-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will place in the Library all her correspondence on press regulation sent to or received from (a) the Press Complaints Commission, (b) the Independent Press Standards Organisation, (c) the Press Standards Board of Finance, (d) the Press Industry Working Group, (e) Peter Wright, (f) Paul Vickers, (g) Guy Black and (h) David Hunt between 1 November 2013 and 18 March 2014.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193095","193095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44310","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much the Start Thinking Soldier recruitment campaign cost; and if he will place in the Library copies of the written brief for the campaign and its subsequent evaluation.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193000","193000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44311","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much the Step Up recruitment campaign cost; and if he will place in the Library copies of the written brief for the campaign and any evaluation that has been made so far.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192999","192999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44312","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much the More Than Meets The Eye recruitment campaign has cost; and if he will place in the Library copies of the written brief for the campaign and any evaluation that has been made so far.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192998","192998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44313","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with DIO and English Heritage about the redevelopment of RAF Hullavington.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192996","192996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44314","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment has been made of the historic features of DSG Ashchurch.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192997","192997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44315","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2014, Official Report, column 504W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, in relation to training what identified the period during which the training of UK UAS operators took place in each host country; where such training took place; and which unmanned systems were used. [R]","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193064","193064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44316","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service complaints at each level are still open and unresolved since (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193107","193107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44317","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many vehicles have returned from (a) Afghanistan and (b) Germany in 2013 and 2014 to date; where each vehicle is currently located; how many vehicles will return by the end of 2014; what spare capacity is to locate vehicles on each Defence Infrastructure Organisation site; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193096","193096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44318","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many complaints have been made in each year of operation of the Service Complaints Commission at each level of representation from (a) women and (b) minority ethnic personnel in each branch of the armed forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193108","193108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44319","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many visits have been made by a Minister in his Department to individual Defence Infrastructure Organisation sites in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193097","193097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44320","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will detail the number of complaints in each year of operation of the Service Complaints Commission by members of each branch of the armed forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193109","193109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44321","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service complaints have been appealed to Level 2 where mid-year annual reports have not been completed in the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193103","193103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44322","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service complaints have been handled in each branch of the armed forces in each year since 2008; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193104","193104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44323","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the Territorial Army were subjected to summary hearings in each year since 2008; how many such people were imprisoned; what the average number of days imprisonment served was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193105","193105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44324","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many complaints have been registered relating to prescribed behaviours from each branch of the armed forces in each year of operation of the Service Complaints Commission; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193106","193106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44325","2014-03-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the contribution to the hon. Member for South West Wiltshire of 17 March 2014, Official Report, column 549W, whether there are plans to commemorate the 70th anniversary of D-Day beyond those he outlined.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193148","193148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44326","2014-03-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2014, Official Report, column 652W, on D-Day landings: anniversaries, how many (a) veterans, (b) widows, (c) spouses and (d) carers of veterans have registered their interest with the Royal British Legion regarding their attendance of the 70th anniversary of D-Day commemorations in Normandy.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193144","193144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44327","2014-03-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2014, Official Report, column 652W, on D-Day landings: anniversaries, how many (a) veterans, (b) widows, (c) spouses and (d) carers of veterans of the D-Day operations currently reside in the UK.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193145","193145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44328","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether a Defence Instruction Notice has been circulated detailing the impact of a summary hearing on the Police National Computer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193113","193113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44329","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether a value for money survey of Defence Infrastructure Organisation Ashchurch has commenced; when such a survey will conclude; how many people are allocated to work on the survey; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193098","193098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44330","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the budget of the Service Complaints Commission has been in each year of its operation; how many staff have been employed by that Commission; how such figures will change after April 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193110","193110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44331","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether (a) a bat, (d) a dormice, (c) a crested newt and (d) an owl survey has been carried out on any Defence Infrastructure Organisation site; what the result of each such survey was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193101","193101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44332","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of all Employment Tribunal judgements made against his Department since 2008 to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193112","193112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44333","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any covenants exist on the use of any of the Defence Infrastructure Organisation sites; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193102","193102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44334","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the planned timetable for the sale of the Defence Infrastructure Organisation is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193099","193099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44335","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any statutory conservation status has been assigned to any Defence Infrastructure Organisation site; what the nature is of each such status; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193100","193100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44336","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many administrative actions under AGAI67 have been considered to have been illegal punishments in each year since 2008 in each branch of the armed forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193111","193111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44337","2014-03-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2014, Official Report, column 652W, on D-Day landings: anniversaries, how much financial support from the Big Lottery Fund for the Heroes Return 2 programme will be given to (a) veterans, (b) widows, (c) spouses and (d) carers wishing to travel to Normandy for the 70th anniversary commemorations of D-Day.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193147","193147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44338","2014-03-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2014, Official Report, column 652W, on D-Day landings: anniversaries, how many (a) veterans, (b) widows, (c) spouses and (d) carers are expected to receive financial support from the Big Lottery Fund for the Heroes Return 2 programme.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193146","193146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44339","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish all contacts between his Department and Mr Dmitry Firtash since May 2010.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193181","193181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44340","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 171W, on military aircraft, how many Aircrew Moving Map Wire Alerting System units have now been released to service; on what dates such units were released to service; and when he expects further such units to be released to service.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193192","193192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44341","2014-03-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what savings have accrued to the Exchequer through the linking of the value of armed forces pensions to the Consumer Prices Index rather than the Retail Prices Index.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193206","193206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44342","2014-03-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which RAF personnel of each (a) rank, (b) duty and (c) location are currently serving overseas.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193207","193207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44343","2014-03-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what courses are currently taught at the Defence Academy.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193208","193208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44344","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many animals of what species are currently held in the Defence Animal Centre in Melton Mowbray.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193061","193061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44345","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual running cost of the Defence Animal Centre in Melton Mowbray was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193062","193062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44346","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what capital investment there has been in the Defence Animal Centre in Melton Mowbray in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193059","193059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44347","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff were employed at the Defence Animal Centre at Melton Mowbray in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193060","193060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44348","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how his Department is consulted, informed or otherwise involved in the procurement of communications systems and services at US bases in the UK. [R]","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193037","193037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44349","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2014, Official Report, column 504W, on unmanned air vehicles, in relation to training what the type of training of UK UAS operators carried out in each country was; and what the cost of such training was. [R]","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193034","193034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44350","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2014, Official Report, column 504W, on unmanned air vehicles, in which countries Royal Air Force operators have been trained. [R]","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193035","193035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44351","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any RAF officers are embedded in host forces or otherwise stationed in Niamey, Nigeria or the Seychelles. [R]","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193038","193038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44352","2014-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on where the UK ranks worldwide in terms of its number of deployable forces.","Biography information for Rory Stewart","Rory Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192990","192990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44354","2014-03-24","Department for Education","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to ensure that the contracts for the Building Schools for the Future programme include provisions to ensure prompt payment to small and medium-sized businesses.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193063","193063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44355","2014-03-25","Department for Education","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many graduates from each Russell Group university applied to the Teach First programme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193047","193047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44356","2014-03-24","Department for Education","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to improve opportunities for children in primary school to learn computer programming.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193003","193003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44358","2014-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the potential effects of the provisions of the Consumer Rights Bill on access to, quality of and cost of childcare provision; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193158","193158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44359","2014-03-24","Department for Education","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to introduce his new national school funding formula.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193118","193118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44360","2014-03-24","Department for Education","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has any plans to increase the amount of funding allocated to schools in South Staffordshire constituency.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193117","193117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44361","2014-03-24","Department for Education","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made for the number of three and four year olds who will benefit from his new early years premium; what the eligibility criteria is for those children; how those three and four year olds will be identified; what amount will be attached to each child; how the premium will be administered; whether all early years settings will be eligible to receive the premium for children in their care; and how many years that funding is guaranteed for.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192995","192995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44362","2014-03-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on what basis the assumed outputs from certified heat pumps installed in domestic premises will be used in calculations of progress towards achieving EU renewable energy targets.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193151","193151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44363","2014-03-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much onshore wind capacity (a) received planning approval and (b) was rejected in each month in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013; and how many planning applications for onshore wind farms were (i) approved and (ii) rejected in each of those months.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193072","193072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44364","2014-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 3 December 2012, Official Report, column 590W, on wind power, what progress he has made on addressing the issue of manufacturers selling turbines which have been derated to allow them to benefit from higher tariffs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192994","192994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44365","2014-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the health effects of infrasound from wind turbine generators.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192989","192989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44366","2014-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the sustainability of the use of wreck netting by trawlers.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193077","193077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44367","2014-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the rod and line fishing industry.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193078","193078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44368","2014-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of fish stocks in the English Channel over the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193079","193079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44369","2014-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to preserve and increase fish stocks in UK waters.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193080","193080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44370","2014-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings his Department has had with external bodies about the use of wild animals in circuses since the publication of the Government's response to the Fourth Report of the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs Committee of Session 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193081","193081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44371","2014-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward proposals to improve information available to consumers of fish on the method of fishing used.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193076","193076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44372","2014-03-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will place in the Library a copy of the evidence submitted by his Department to the independent review of the RSCPA's prosecutions activity being carried out by Mr Stephen Wooler.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193041","193041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44373","2014-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 7 February 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr J Rossi-Stephenson.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193032","193032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44374","2014-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the directives of the Lionfish response strategy implemented in the Overseas Territories are.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193141","193141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44375","2014-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the objectives of the Green economy projects implemented in the Overseas Territories are.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193142","193142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44376","2014-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps have been taken as part of the initiative to address threats to marine ecosystems in the Overseas Territories in the Caribbean.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193172","193172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44377","2014-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the UK meets its obligations on tackling the illegal wildlife trade under the 2014 London Declaration; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193170","193170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44378","2014-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the report of the Global Initiative against Transnational Organised Crime and llicit Trafficking in Mali; and what assessment he has made of the effect of the drugs trade and illicit economic activity on good governance, democracy and sustainable development in Mali.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193069","193069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44379","2014-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last raised (a) Palestinian refugees and (b) Israeli refugees in talks concerning the Middle East peace process.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193139","193139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44380","2014-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on a potential new Israeli settlement in the city of Hebron.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193140","193140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44381","2014-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the establishment of a UN Compensation Commission to compensate Jewish and Palestinian refugees affected by the Middle East conflict; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of such a fund on the peace process.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193136","193136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44382","2014-03-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of human rights in Kashmir.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193044","193044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44383","2014-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support initiatives to (a) combat illicit trafficking across Mali's borders, (b) strengthen the investigative and judicial capacity and capabilities of the Malian government, (c) reduce inequality and corruption in Mali and (d) reduce military intervention in Mali's politics; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193029","193029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44384","2014-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many rockets were fired from Gaza into Israel in 2013.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193028","193028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44385","2014-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the arrest of the lawyer Abdulmonim Adam in Sudan; and what representations he is making to ensure that Mr Abdulmonim Adam receives access to legal advice and representation.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193020","193020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44386","2014-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many of the staff of the British Embasssy in Kiev in 2013 were UK-based rather than locally recruited.","Biography information for Rory Stewart","Rory Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192991","192991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44387","2014-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2014, Official Report, column 417W, on unmanned air vehicles, what steps his Department has taken to respond to the UN Special Rapporteur's recommendation on the urgent and imperative need to reach a consensus on reapplicable legal principles between states. [R]","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193039","193039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44388","2014-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the recent Peace Now report entitled A Disaster-in-the-Making: The (Potential) New Settlements in Hebron.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193074","193074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44389","2014-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many requests for consular assistance as a result of public disturbances have been made by UK citizens at the UK embassy in Kiev since February 2013.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193002","193002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44390","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on Serbia's EU accession.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193055","193055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44391","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the business and inward investment environment in Serbia.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193056","193056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44392","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Serbian counterpart on (a) rule of law, (b) business and economic reforms, (c) trade and investment, (d) organised crime and (e) corruption in that country.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193057","193057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44393","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of misuse of Article 234 of the Serbian Criminal Code against the Serbian business community.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193058","193058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44394","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to collect information on the number of (a) approved and (b) rejected applications to the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193075","193075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44395","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS England on ensuring that future iterations of the Cancer Patient Experience Survey include questions targeted at those with secondary breast cancer.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193014","193014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44396","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of children in (a) Harlow constituency, (b) Essex and (c) England were classed as overweight each year since 1997.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193023","193023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44397","2014-03-24","Cabinet Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the mortality rate for deaths caused by cancer has been in (a) Harlow constituency, (b) Essex and (c) England in the last 15 years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193024","193024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44398","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the UK of the planned EU ban on e-cigarettes with over 20mg/ml of nicotine.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193005","193005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44399","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information Public Health England collects from health and wellbeing boards about their current and future spending on drugs and alcohol treatment services.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193084","193084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44400","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the level of mental illness has been in (a) Harlow constituency, (b) Essex and (c) England in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193021","193021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44401","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions were issued in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013 for medical conditions that (i) qualified for and (ii) did not qualify for prescription charge exemptions.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193127","193127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44402","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the performance of the Perinatal Institute's Growth Assessment Protocol Programme in the three pilot regions in reducing the number of stillbirths; if he will make this policy to introduce a wider roll-out of this scheme across the whole NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193153","193153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44403","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the potential benefits of pre-term at-risk profiling to (a) identify women at risk of stillbirth, (b) ensure those at risk receive increased monitoring and preventative measures and (c) reduce potentially damaging stress on those who are in an at-risk group but are not themselves at risk.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193138","193138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44404","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the potential benefits of increasing access to healthy start vitamins available to pregnant women (a) from all chemists and (b) without not means-testing.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193132","193132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44405","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had on (a) the number of treatment options available as a first line to patients with advanced melanoma and (b) the clinical effectiveness of the treatment options available as a first line to patients with advanced melanoma; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193114","193114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44406","2014-03-25","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will arrange for a reply to be sent to the Member for Walsall North to the letter that he wrote to the Chief Executive, University Hospitals Birmingham NHS Foundation Trust on 18 February 2014 concerning the father of a constituent.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193093","193093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44407","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Enfield, Southgate, of 8 January 2014, Official Report, columns 267-8W, on in vitro fertilisation, whether Klaus Reinhardt, Damian Dowling, or Edward Morrow were invited to contribute evidence pursuant to their paper in response to the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority's recent call for scientific evidence from experts in any relevant field on the safety or efficacy of pro-nuclear transfer and maternal spindle transfer techniques; whether Paul Knoepfler was invited to contribute evidence to this inquiry; which other individual scientists, research groups or learned societies were notified about this new call for evidence; and how much advance notice each such person was given of the deadline for written submissions.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193180","193180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44408","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effects of the provisions of the Consumer Rights Bill on the provision of social care services to users commissioning such services through direct payments.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193157","193157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44409","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which private sector clinics and hospitals provide abortions; how many beds there are in each facility; whether each facility is approved for (a) surgical day care abortions with or without general anaesthetic and (b) late abortions; and what the name is of the proprietor of each such facility.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193183","193183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44410","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many abortions there were at (a) 26 weeks and (b) each week after the 26th in each category of grounds for termination in 2012.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193184","193184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44411","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Enfield, Southgate of 8 January 2014, Official Report, columns 267-8, on in vitro fertilisation, in which scientific periodicals were notices placed to advertise the recent call from the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority (HFEA) for scientific evidence from experts in any relevant field on the safety or efficacy of pro-nuclear transfer and maternal spindle transfer techniques; where else the call for evidence was publicly advertised; and when the report to be published on the HFEA website will be available to members of the public.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193201","193201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44412","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to reduce the availability of energy drinks at schools.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193196","193196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44413","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2014, Official Report, column 268W, on Computer Misuse Act 1990, and with reference to action 7 under objective 1 on page 36 of the UK Cyber Security Strategy, when the Government plans to publish its review of the Computer Misuse Act 1990.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193210","193210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44414","2014-03-24","Home Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the UK meets its obligations on tackling the illegal wildlife trade under the 2014 London Declaration; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193168","193168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44415","2014-03-24","Home Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons there are differential rates for visas for dependents of British citizens coming from non-EU countries and visas for dependents of EU non-British citizens domiciled in Britain.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193115","193115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44416","2014-03-24","Home Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will abolish the differential rates for visas paid by British and EU non-British citizens living in the UK for dependents outside the EU and make the cost of all such visas the same as the EU rate.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193116","193116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44417","2014-03-25","Home Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her international counterparts on the control of legal highs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193090","193090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44418","2014-03-26","Home Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how her Department assesses the effectiveness of the Cyber Crime Reduction Partnership and progress against commitments made under the UK Cyber Security Strategy, page 36, Objective One.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193134","193134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44419","2014-03-25","Home Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to appoint an anti-slavery commissioner; and whether such an appointment will be a full-time post.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193045","193045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44420","2014-03-24","Home Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 13 February  2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Momin Khan.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193033","193033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44421","2014-03-24","Home Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library a record of those institutions which have made a conditional offer to overseas students whose application for a visa is subsequently refused.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193015","193015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44422","2014-03-24","Home Office","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the purpose and scope of the current trials of the Aeryon Skyranger unmanned system based in Gatwick are; if she will publish policy on the storage and use of data obtained in the course of such trials; and if she will make a statement. [R]","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193036","193036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44423","2014-03-25","Department for International Development","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what projects the Gurkha Welfare Trust have delivered since June 2010; and how often the Trust reports on its work.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193149","193149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44424","2014-03-25","Department for International Development","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what resources her Department has given to the Gurkha Welfare Trust since June 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193150","193150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44425","2014-03-25","Department for International Development","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her Jordanian counterpart on access of Syrian refugees to work permits in Jordan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193154","193154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44426","2014-03-24","Department for International Development","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessments she has made of the humanitarian situation in Jonglei and the Upper Nile in South Sudan; and what steps she is taking to support those who are being displaced or affected by the conflict in that region.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193126","193126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44427","2014-03-24","Department for International Development","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the UK meets its obligations on tackling the illegal wildlife trade under the 2014 London Declaration; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193169","193169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44428","2014-03-25","Department for International Development","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she had with her Sri Lankan counterpart on the resettling of the population of Myliddy village.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193152","193152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44429","2014-03-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the contribution of the hon. Member for Ashford, of 4 March 2014, Official Report, columns 317-20WH, on fatal domestic violence, if he will make it his policy that the New Homicide Scheme supports victims involved in a homicide prior to April 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193174","193174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44430","2014-03-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many written statements his Department has published since 1 January 2013 in total; how many such statements were published after the start of the day's business; and how many such statements were published after that day's deadline for requesting Urgent Questions.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193173","193173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44431","2014-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have had with Essex Probation Service since November 2013; what issues were raised in each such discussion; what steps his Department took following each such discussion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193162","193162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44432","2014-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the salary was of the (a) Chief Executive and (b) Chairman of the Essex Probation Trust in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193163","193163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44433","2014-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent representations he has received from Essex Probation Trust on the retention of the current board; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193164","193164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44434","2014-03-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department's new national homicide service will provide support to victims involved in a homicide that took place abroad prior to November 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193171","193171"
