"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943106","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July to Question 161562, what assessment he has made of the regional disparity in Local Authorities eligible to bid for the Additional Housing Revenue Account Borrowing Programme.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165157","165157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943107","2018-07-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that recreational boaters whose craft have Union Goods status retain that status after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164833","164833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943108","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what consideration was given to the Homeless Household Acceptance rates of local authorities when determining the methodology used to determine their eligibility to bid for the Additional Housing Revenue Account Borrowing Programme.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165158","165158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943109","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the UK’s continued adherence to (a) EU rail standards and (b) the provisions of the EU rail packages notwithstanding the terms of the future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165038","165038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943110","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what consideration was given to the number of right to buy sales in local authorities when determining the methodology used to determine their eligibility to bid for the Additional Housing Revenue Account Borrowing Programme.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165159","165159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943111","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings (a) Ministers in his Department and (b) officials of his Department have had with their counterparts in other European countries to discuss bilateral rail agreements.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165039","165039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943112","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to pursue bilateral rail agreements with (a) other European countries and (b) the Republic of Ireland in addition to those already under development with France, Belgium and the Netherlands.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165040","165040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943113","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) establish a national network of brain tumour centres and (b) encourage more researchers to enter the brain tumour research field.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164871","164871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943114","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to reduce noise emissions from motorcycles.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164905","164905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943115","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding his Department plans to allocate for the development of new drugs to treat brain tumours in each of the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164872","164872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943116","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what strategies the Government has put in place to tackle in-work poverty.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165151","165151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943118","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what laws govern permissive noise of motorbikes and their exhaust systems.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164906","164906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943119","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will meet with the relevant motorbiking manufacturers and associated bodies to help reduce noise generated by motorbikes.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164907","164907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943120","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions in each of the last five years NATO countries had to provide maritime patrol aircraft for use in UK airspace; and from which countries those aircraft came.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164953","164953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943121","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the answer of 16 April 2018 to Question 134539 on Incinerators: Health Hazards, whether those papers been submitted for peer review; and when the results are planned to be published.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164870","164870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943122","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many former hon. Members hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within his Department as of 17 July 2018.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164943","164943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943123","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people with mental health problems receive adequate practical support with (a) housing, (b) debt and (c) employment.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164999","164999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943124","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the General Data Protection Regulation on the income of GPs who are no longer able to charge private sector companies for the provision of patient records made at the request of patients.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165000","165000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943125","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many former hon. Members hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within his Department as of 17 July 2018.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164944","164944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943126","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has been made of the potential merits of social prescribing as a form of secondary care for mental health patients.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165001","165001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943127","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 26 of the Government's Green Paper of December 2017, Transforming Children and Young People’s Mental Health, Cm 9523, what progress has been made on recruiting 1,700 more therapists and supervisors and training 3,400 existing staff to deliver evidence-based treatments.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165002","165002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943128","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2018 to Question 158740, on Students: Occupational Therapy, what plans he has to include occupational therapists in the (a) development and (b) introduction of a University Mental Health Charter.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165003","165003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943129","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many former hon. Members hold  (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within his Department as of 17 July 2018.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164945","164945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943130","2018-07-19","Department for International Development","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many former hon. Members hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within her Department as of 17 July 2018.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164946","164946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943131","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many former hon. Members hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within his Department as of 17 July 2018.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164947","164947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943132","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many former hon. Members hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within his Department as of 17 July 2018.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164948","164948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943133","2018-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many former hon. Members hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within his Department as of 17 July 2018.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164949","164949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943134","2018-07-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many former hon. Members hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within his Department as of 17 July 2018.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164950","164950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943135","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many former hon. Members hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within his Department as of 17 July 2018.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164951","164951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943136","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many former hon. Members hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within his Department as of 17 July 2018.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164952","164952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943137","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the (a) societal and (b) economic effect of the Northern rail timetable changes made in May.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165068","165068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943138","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to abolish the minimum age of eligibility for the mobility component of disability living allowance.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165069","165069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943139","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse has been of the Go Ultra Low City Scheme since the launch of that scheme.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164852","164852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943140","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Prime Minister's oral contribution of 16 July 2018, Official Report, column 25, what role the UK plans to play in the NATO Readiness Initiative.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164954","164954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943141","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Prime Minister's oral contribution of 16 July 2018, Official Report, column 23, how many additional UK fighter jets are planned to be deployed in support of NATO air policing; which aircraft will be so deployed; and to which country they will be deployed.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164955","164955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943142","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of reinforcing the electricity National Grid to cater for the demands created by the Road to Zero policy.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164853","164853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943143","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Prime Minister's oral contribution of 16 July 2018, Official Report, column 24, what support the Government is offering to the Government of Ukraine in relation to the situation in the Crimea.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164956","164956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943144","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Thames Valley Police and Crime Commissioner has submitted an application to his Department for Special Grant funding for additional costs associated with policing the visit of Donald Trump to Oxfordshire.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165162","165162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943145","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Prime Minister's oral contribution of 16 July 2018, Official Report, column 24, what roles UK personnel will be allocated to permit the release of US personnel for other work in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164957","164957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943146","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of reports received on the alleged massacre of women and children by Cameroonian special forces.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165008","165008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943147","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the preparation of the Road to Zero policy, what estimate he has made of the number of dwellings that (a) do and (b) do not have parking on their own drive or parking area.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164854","164854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943148","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the human rights implications of the (a) activities of the Cameroonian armed forces and (b) relationship between those activities and Boko Haram.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165009","165009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943149","2018-07-23","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of (a) controls and (b) transparency regulations on donations from outside the United Kingdom to political parties in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165163","165163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943150","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to mitigate market volatility in the agriculture sector.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164877","164877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943151","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to increase the UK's level of self-sufficiency in food; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164878","164878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943152","2018-07-19","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many applications for funding for money associated with the Fresh Start Agreement have been (a) accepted and (b) rejected in each year since that funding has been made available; and for what reasons applications were rejected.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165164","165164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943153","2018-07-19","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful applications for funding from money associated with the Fresh Start Agreement have been for (i) shared education projects and (ii) integrated education projects in each year since that funding has been made available.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165165","165165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943154","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the environmental advantages of introducing off-peak flashing Amber traffic lights.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164855","164855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943155","2018-07-19","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will hold discussions with the Electoral Commission on the adequacy of regulations governing donations to political parties in Northern Ireland in light of BBC Northern Ireland’s Spotlight programme broadcast on 26 June 2018; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165166","165166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943156","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how he plans to ensure that the UK tobacco product track and trace system as required by Article 8 of the WHO FCTC Protocol to Eliminate the Illicit Trade in Tobacco Products will be fully independent from the tobacco industry.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165106","165106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943157","2018-07-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 34 of Chapter 4 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9653, published on 12 July 2018, what actions the Joint Committee will be empowered to take in the event of significant divergences between the interpretation of agreements by the courts of the UK and the EU.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164930","164930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943158","2018-07-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Transport on that Department's proposal that all new streetlights should incorporate vehicle charging capability; and what financial provision will be made available to local authorities to cover the additional cost of such capability.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164856","164856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943159","2018-07-19","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many (a) discussions her Department has held with and (b) representations her Department has received from the Electoral Commission about the adequacy of regulations governing donations to political parties in Northern Ireland since the the approval of the Transparency of Donations and Loans etc. (Northern Ireland Political Parties) Order 2018 on 7 March 2018.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165167","165167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943160","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeship standards have been submitted for approval in the past 18 months; and how many of those submissions have been approved.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164873","164873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943161","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will review the 10 per cent co-investment fee for non-apprenticeship levy paying SMEs.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164874","164874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943162","2018-07-19","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will make it her policy to launch a public consultation on amending the Transparency of Donations and Loans etc. (Northern Ireland Political Parties) Order 2018 to backdate these provisions to 2014.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165168","165168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943163","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to tackle reductions in level 2 apprenticeship starts since May 2017.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164875","164875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943164","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the annual cost to the Exchequer is of revenue foregone through the Red Diesel scheme.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164857","164857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943165","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the outcome has been of the activities of the working group on roadside litter referred to on page 56 of the 2017 Litter Strategy for England.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164931","164931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943166","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding was provided by the European Investment Bank to UK businesses in each year for which records are available since 1998; and what assessment he has made of the contribution of funding by that bank to the UK economy over that period.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165010","165010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943167","2018-07-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which the EU rules are which are referred to in paragraph 42 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, which would be interpreted by the Court of Justice of the European Union under the proposals contained in that paragraph.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164932","164932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943168","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions the Minister of State for Apprenticeships and Skills has had with ESFA officials on the position of continued transitional funding for the WEA in areas of England affected by the devolution of the adult education budget from 2019-20.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164876","164876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943169","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of remaining a member of the European Investment Bank after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165011","165011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943170","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with (a) political parties and (b) civil society in Northern Ireland on (i) repealing and (ii) amending sections 58 and 59 of the Offences Against the Person Act 1861.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165169","165169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943171","2018-07-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 47 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the financial penalties will be.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164933","164933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943172","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to prepare the pharmacy sector for (a) digital first pharmacy services and (b) other technological change.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165012","165012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943173","2018-07-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 47 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the obligations are which could be suspended.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164934","164934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943174","2018-07-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many plants in the UK produce batteries for ultra low emission vehicles; and how many new such factories he estimates will be established in the next two years.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164858","164858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943176","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what changes have been made to the performance specification for Highways England to reflect the goal of improving litter cleaning set out on page 58 of the 2017 Litter Strategy for England.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164935","164935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943179","2018-07-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will publish his proposal for the mechanism for parliamentary scrutiny referenced in paragraph 55 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164936","164936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943181","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 58 of the 2017 Litter Strategy for England, whether a revised Key Performance Indicator has been introduced for Highways England relating to litter cleaning.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164937","164937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943182","2018-07-19","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans she has to amend the powers of the Northern Ireland Human Rights Commission relating to legal proceedings as a result of Supreme Court case [2018] UKSC 27; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165170","165170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943183","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 60 of the 2017 Litter Strategy for England, what progress the Government has made in reviewing the mechanism by which councils and other land-managers are held to account for maintaining their land to the standards set out in the Code of Practice on Litter and Refuse.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164938","164938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943184","2018-07-19","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will appoint an independent facilitator to reconvene all-party talks on restoring the Northern Ireland Assembly.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165171","165171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943185","2018-07-19","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of allowing the Northern Ireland Assembly to sit in committee format, in parallel with all-party talks, to scrutinise and advise Northern Ireland Government Departments on decision making in the absence of ministers.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165172","165172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943186","2018-07-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the proportion of drugs smuggled into prisons by drones.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164970","164970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943187","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the performance of the Individual Funding Request process.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165132","165132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943188","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for confirming the salary of the Senior Traffic Commissioner; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165185","165185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943189","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the salaries are for Traffic Commissioners in each region.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165186","165186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943190","2018-07-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will set out the mechanism for parliamentary scrutiny envisaged in paragraph 55 of chapter four of the White Paper on the Future Relationship between the UK and the EU, cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164939","164939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943191","2018-07-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy to publishing in full the report into the pilot scheme which put phones into prison cells in a number of prisons.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164971","164971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943192","2018-07-19","Prime Minister","2018-07-17","To ask the Prime Minister, for what reason she did not represent the Government at the 30th Summit of the British Irish Council in Guernsey in June 2018.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165173","165173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943193","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2018 to Question 127570, on Courts: Video Conferencing, what proportion of defendants have appeared in court proceedings via video link from (a) police stations and (b) prisons in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164972","164972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943194","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2018 to Question 127570, on Courts: Video Conferencing, what proportion of witnesses have appeared in court proceedings via video link in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164973","164973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943195","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many extraditions were successfully completed from each of the other EU countries in each of the five years prior to the introduction of the European Arrest Warrant to (a) England and Wales, (b) Scotland and (c) Northern Ireland; and if he will publish a list of those extraditions by the category of crime committed.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164831","164831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943196","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many extraditions were successfully completed from each of the other EU countries in each of the last five years following the introduction of the European Arrest Warrant to (a) England and Wales, (b) Scotland, (c) Northern Ireland; and if he will publish a list of those extraditions by the category of crime committed.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164832","164832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943197","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has undertaken an impact assessment of the proposed entry level exception site policy on rural occupation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164823","164823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943198","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proposals he has to limit the ability of (a) freeholders to appoint managing agents and (b) freeholder managing agents to levy fees on leaseholders; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164822","164822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943199","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the publication of the results of the Blue Badge (disabled parking) scheme eligibility review consultation on the Gov.uk website.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164977","164977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943200","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason the results of the Blue Badge disabled parking scheme eligibility review consultation were not published within three months of the consultation closing on 18 March 2018.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164978","164978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943201","2018-07-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recruits were enlisted into the regular army in 2017-18.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164908","164908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943202","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an estimate of the cost to the public purse of uprating the state pension, for UK pensioners residing overseas, in line with the state pension in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165094","165094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943203","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans her Department has to update the state pension for UK pensioners residing overseas; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165095","165095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943204","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations her Department has received from Commonwealth countries on the uprating of UK state pensions for pensioners residing in those countries.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165096","165096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/941993","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-16","Whether his Department plans to support the arming of rural police officers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906468","906468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/941994","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-16","What steps his Department is taking to encourage greater collaboration between the police and fire services.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906469","906469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/941995","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-16","What steps he is taking to ensure that illegal migrants cannot profit from working in the UK.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906470","906470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/941996","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-16","What steps he is taking to ensure that illegal migrants cannot profit from working in the UK.","Biography information for James Morris","James Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906471","906471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/941997","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-16","What steps he is taking to ensure that the UK's security services have the resources required to counter terrorism.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906473","906473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/941998","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-16","What steps he is taking to reduce shop theft.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906474","906474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942427","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding his Department has allocated for the provision of accommodation for armed forces families in the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164395","164395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942428","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on bilateral relationships with European partners in relation to the Eurofighter Typhoon after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164396","164396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942429","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress has been made on (a) bringing the defence recruiting system up to full operating capability and (b) meeting recruitment targets.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164397","164397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942430","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to provide military veterans with an identity card to enable them to access discounts on services offered by the private sector.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164398","164398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942431","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for the next steps in his Department's veterans strategy; and what progress he has made in assisting those who (a) become homeless, (b) develop mental illness and (c) experience other personal crises.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164399","164399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942432","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department is taking steps to recognise the long-term effects on military personnel of exposure to radiation as a result of nuclear testing on Christmas Island in the 1950s; and if the Government will provide financial support and health care to personnel affected.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164400","164400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942433","2018-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on letting agencies in Scotland of the Scottish Parliament's legislating to make letting agent fees illegal.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164401","164401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942434","2018-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on private sector rents in Scotland of banning letting agent fees.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164402","164402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942435","2018-07-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with representatives of Jaguar Land Rover on the effect of the UK leaving the EU on (a) current plans to build electric cars in Coventry and (b) plans to create 6,000 new jobs on land south of the A45 by Coventry Airport as part of the Whitley South scheme.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164268","164268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942436","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the amount of plastic waste from Coventry that is sent abroad for recycling in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164269","164269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942437","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to increase access to veterinary care for animal owners in Coventry on low incomes.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164270","164270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942438","2018-07-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of proposed changes to the National Planning Policy Framework on the natural environment in Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164271","164271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942439","2018-07-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the shortage of CO2 on businesses in Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164272","164272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942440","2018-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of violence in Israel and the West Bank.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164431","164431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942441","2018-07-18","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether medical evidence of non-accidental injuries must be provided before children's services departments place children in the care of a local authority on the grounds of such injuries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164393","164393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942442","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the guidance issued by NICE on Spondyloarthritis QS170, in June 2018 is implemented effectively throughout the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164432","164432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942443","2018-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with representatives of social media providers on (a) misogynistic, (b) racist, (c) homophobic and (d) transphobic online abuse; and what steps he is taking to tackle that abuse.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164433","164433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942444","2018-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that social media companies (a) tackle the activities of online trolls  and (b) facilitate the reporting of online abuse by victims.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164434","164434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942445","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish how the Government allocates new funding for (a) the Tessa Jowell Brain Cancer Research Mission and (b) other brain tumour research.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164435","164435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942446","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many ongoing visa applications received in the last month have not been processed within the time set by his Department in its service standards.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164439","164439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942447","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to page 8 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, which items of EU law will be included in the common rulebook for goods including agri-food.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164317","164317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942448","2018-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assurances Burmese State Counsellor Aung San Suu Kyi has given to the Government on the status of Rohingya in Burma.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164452","164452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942449","2018-07-18","Department for International Trade","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what information his Department holds on UK companies exporting (a) goods or (b) services to the (i) Burmese military or (ii) Burmese military-owned or controlled companies.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164453","164453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942450","2018-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to encourage UK citizens to take holidays in UK seaside towns.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164532","164532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942451","2018-07-18","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure the availability of support for children's mental health in the run-up to examinations.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164533","164533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942452","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what  assessment he has made of the effect of negotiations on regulatory alignment for goods with the EU on the ability of the UK to agree new international trade deals.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164534","164534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942453","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to assist armed forces personnel onto the housing ladder.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164535","164535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942454","2018-07-18","Department for International Trade","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the UK increases levels of trade with the BRIC countries.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164536","164536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942455","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time was for telephone callers kept on hold before speaking to a Job Centre Plus adviser in each of the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164515","164515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942456","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will respond to the recommendations in the report, The current landscape of obesity services, published by the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Obesity in May 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164303","164303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942457","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will commission a cost-benefit analysis of allocating additional funding for the (a) prevention and (b) treatment of obesity.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164304","164304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942458","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will respond to EDM 1494, Unrest and Violence in Nicaragua.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164465","164465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942459","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Nicaraguan Ambassador to the UK on the human rights situation in Nicaragua.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164466","164466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942460","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Nicaragua on the (a) human rights situation and (b) political violence in that country.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164467","164467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942461","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of claims for compensation for delayed rail services made to Govia Thameslink Railway were successful in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164249","164249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942462","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average length of time was for compensation to be paid to a claimant for delayed rail services by Govia Thameslink Railway in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164250","164250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942463","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to extend the compensation scheme announced on 6 July 2018 to Govia Thameslink Railway passengers who are non-season ticket holders.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164251","164251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942464","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many claims of compensation for wrongful immigration detention were (a) received by his Department and (b) successful in each of the last five years; and what the cost to the public purse was of the compensation paid by his Department in that period.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164252","164252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942465","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the nationalities were of people held in immigration detention centres in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164253","164253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942466","2018-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many households affected by the Grenfell Tower fire require rehousing; and how many of those households are in (a) emergency, (b) temporary and (c) permanent accommodation.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164275","164275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942467","2018-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many households in (a) Barandon Walk, (b) Testerton Walk, (c) Hurstway Walk, (d) Treadgold House and (e) Bramley House require rehousing as a result of the Grenfell Tower fire; and how many of those households have been rehoused in (i) emergency accommodation, (ii) temporary accommodation and (iii) permanent accommodation.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164276","164276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942468","2018-07-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has plans to undertake a review of the adequacy of the guidance given to the Office of the Official Receiver in relation to the separation of non-married couples with shared assets and shared debts.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164440","164440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942469","2018-07-19","Department for International Trade","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to protect consumers from the economic effect of the introduction of reciprocal tariffs imposed by the EU in response to the tariffs imposed by the US Administration.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164441","164441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942470","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the status of the Post Implementation Review of the Non-Commercial Movement of Pet Animals Order 2011 is.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164477","164477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942471","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of increasing traffic congestion on the viability of the cab trade in London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164379","164379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942472","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how UK Border Force has performed against its target of processing non-EEA passengers at UK airports within 45 minutes in each month since January 2018.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164380","164380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942473","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of on-duty UK Border Force officers deployed at airports in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164381","164381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942474","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much she allocated to Durham County Council for Discretionary Housing Payments in each of the last five years; and what information she holds on how much of that allocation is unspent.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164391","164391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942475","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential increased cost of hiring contractors as a result of the extension of IR35 off-payroll tax into the private sector.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164537","164537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942476","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the validity of the concerns of the CEO of Contract Calculator on the extension of the IR35 off-payroll tax rules to the private sector.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164538","164538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942477","2018-07-18","Treasury","2018-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the compatibility of the proposed extension of IR35 off-payroll tax rules to the private sector with the recommendations of the 2017 Good Work: Taylor review of modern working practices.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164539","164539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942478","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how long on average her Department took to respond to correspondence from an hon. Member in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164392","164392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942479","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the average time that patients waited to receive cervical screening results in Lincolnshire in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164526","164526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942480","2018-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information he holds on how much steel is required on average to build a family car in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164376","164376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942481","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 140 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, which EU laws are included in the common rulebook with the EU on technical rules for electricity trading.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164318","164318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942482","2018-07-18","Treasury","2018-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 161 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the evidential basis is for the statement that only 4 per cent of the UK goods trade would be likely to use the tariff repayment mechanism.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164319","164319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942483","2018-07-18","Treasury","2018-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 161 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the types of goods are which are likely to be included in the 4 per cent of the UK goods trade which will need to use the tariff repayment mechanism.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164320","164320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942484","2018-07-18","Treasury","2018-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 161 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the timetable is for setting up the systems needed to run the tariff repayment mechanism.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164321","164321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942485","2018-07-18","Treasury","2018-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 162 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what are the risk and intelligence-based checks.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164322","164322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942486","2018-07-18","Department for International Trade","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to paragraph 169 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, in what way UK trade policy will promote the economic empowerment of women.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164323","164323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942487","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 13 of Chapter Two of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what measures are to be covered by sub-paragraphs (a) to (c) of that paragraph.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164324","164324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942488","2018-07-18","Department for International Development","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to paragraph 88 of Chapter Two of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, which resources the Government is planning to pool with EU institutions in accordance with the proposals there set out.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164325","164325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942489","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 5 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the proposed agreements with the EU are which are there referred to; and which of those agreements are expected to be legally binding.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164326","164326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942490","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 7 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the mechanism will be which allows the provisions of agreements with the EU to be reviewed.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164327","164327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942491","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 7 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the mechanisms are that will be adopted for future termination of agreements with the EU.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164328","164328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942492","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 7 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the arrangements are for ensuring that the UK's future relationship with the EU is adaptable and can change over time.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164329","164329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942493","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to sub-paragraph 25(a) of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, by what means he plans to achieve the goal of consistent interpretation of the common rulebook.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164330","164330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942494","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to sub-paragraph 30(a)(ii) of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what those rebalancing measures are.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164331","164331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942495","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to sub-paragraph 30(b)(iii) of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the independent arbitration mechanism will be.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164332","164332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942496","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to sub-paragraph 30(b)(iv) of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what those rebalancing measures are.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164333","164333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942497","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 31 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018,  whether the parliamentary procedure there envisaged involves primary legislation or secondary legislation.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164334","164334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942498","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 34 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the non-compliance measures there referred to are.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164335","164335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942499","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 32 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the factors there referred to are.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164336","164336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942500","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 33 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the differences are between the current prevailing legal principles relating to the CJEU and the approach to the case law of the EU there envisaged.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164337","164337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942501","2018-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will ask the Local Government Boundary Commission for England to review the boundary between Lewes District and East Sussex County Councils and Brighton and Hove City Council in order to re-unify Saltdean for the purposes of local government administration.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164512","164512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942502","2018-07-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will assess the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to permit a parish or community council to be established covering an area that is continuous over two primary local authority areas.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164513","164513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942503","2018-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 185 of the Localism Act 2011, whether his Department has issued guidance to local authorities on the (a) exemptions and (a) application of selective licensing on fully mutual housing co-operatives.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164514","164514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942504","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government has commissioned a review of research relating to the health implications of shale gas extraction by any organisation since the 2015 general election.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164421","164421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942505","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps his Department has taken to tackle alcohol abuse.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164316","164316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942506","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many specialist leaders of education in England are specialists in (a) English and (b) special educational needs and disability.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164487","164487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942507","2018-07-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the Government's proposed trade deal with the EU on the number of exports from Yorkshire after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164442","164442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942508","2018-07-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps he is taking as part of his negotiations with the EU to ensure that the effects of leaving the EU are felt equally by those living in the north and the south.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164443","164443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942509","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children have been taken into social care in each of the last five years; and what assessment he had made of reasons for the trends in those numbers.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164444","164444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942510","2018-07-18","Department for International Development","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 15 May 2018 to Question 141795, what are the terms of engagement for the independent financial audit into DFID's project spending in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164436","164436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942511","2018-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on the role of carbon capture and storage in (a) the Cadent’s HyNet project and (b) other large-scale hydrogen projects.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164423","164423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942512","2018-07-18","Treasury","2018-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to include hydrogen refuelling stations within the scope of the Charging Infrastructure Investment Fund.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164424","164424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942513","2018-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the Government’s plans are for the roll-out of hydrogen vehicle refuelling infrastructure.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164425","164425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942514","2018-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to allocate funds to replace EU funding of (a) the Orkney Surf n Turf project and (b) other such hydrogen power schemes after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164426","164426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942515","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to hold discussions with the newly appointed Deputy Mayor for Transport in London on the effect on traffic congestion of the cycle superhighways.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164454","164454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942516","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on trends in the level of traffic congestion in London as a result of the roll-out of cycle superhighways; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164455","164455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942517","2018-07-18","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what supplementary funding is available for maintained nursery schools to apply for.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164356","164356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942518","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding the Government has provided to maintained nursery schools in each of the least eight years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164357","164357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942519","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding the Government has provided to maintained nursery schools in Hull in each of the least eight years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164358","164358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942520","2018-07-18","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether maintained nursery schools will continue to be eligible to apply for supplementary funding beyond 2020.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164359","164359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942521","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many nursery schools currently receive supplementary funding.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164360","164360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942522","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many nursery schools in Hull currently receive supplementary funding.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164361","164361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942523","2018-07-18","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with nursery school operators on providing them with supplementary funding.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164362","164362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942524","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of removing supplementary funding from nurseries on the number of nurseries closing down.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164363","164363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942525","2018-07-18","Department for International Development","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with international counterparts on the (a) Gaza Reconstruction Mechanism and (b) planned review of that programme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164264","164264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942526","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department holds information on the rate of delay repay claims submitted since the introduction of the revised train timetable for (a) Great Northern Rail and (b) Govia Thameslink Services.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164497","164497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942527","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when after receiving refugee status people can expect to have their passports returned.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164294","164294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942528","2018-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on instances of Israeli authorities using equipment from UK-based companies in demolishing or assisting with demolishing structures in the West Bank.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164265","164265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942529","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what processes his Department has in place to ensure the timely return of passports and official documentation to people after their immigration status has been decided.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164295","164295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942530","2018-07-18","Department for International Development","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to (a) victims of forcible transfer and (b) people at risk of forcible transfer in the West Bank.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164266","164266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942531","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the speed of his Department's processes for (a) collecting and (b) reissuing passports.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164296","164296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942532","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times (a) he and (b) the Minister with responsibility for rail have met the chief executive of Govia Thameslink Railway since the introduction of the new national rail timetable.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164498","164498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942533","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to secure the immediate release of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164521","164521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942534","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will place in the Library a copy of his Department's contract with Iron Mountain.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164297","164297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942535","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to meet his Iranian counterpart to discuss the case of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164522","164522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942536","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent update he has received on a potential release date for Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164523","164523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942537","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many public complaints in respect of train delays his Department received in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164499","164499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942538","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care what plans he has to ensure his Department continues to engage and meet with NHS England and Vertex to discuss access to Orkambi.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164468","164468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942539","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether ensuring access to Orkambi for people with cystic fibrosis is a priority for his Department.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164469","164469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942540","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether a date has been set for the next meeting between NHS England and Vertex to discuss access to the drug Orkambi.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164470","164470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942541","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department's policy is on Vertex (a) waiving its confidentiality clause on the negotiations around NHS access to the drug Orkambi and (b) disclosing details of its offer to NHS England.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164471","164471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942542","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of increasing traffic congestion on the viability of the cab trade in London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164456","164456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942543","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the answer of 12 July 2018 to Question 162133 on Hospices: Children, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for the Children’s Hospice Grant; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164516","164516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942544","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the (a) mean, (b) median and (c) modal time taken is for NHS Digital to process a request for data from universities and other healthcare research organisations.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164387","164387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942545","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what NHS Digital does to ensure that requests for access to survey data are treated differently from requests to access patient and service use data.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164388","164388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942546","2018-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department (a) requested and (b) received presentations in person from bidders for the tender for Approved Enforcement Agency services, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164351","164351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942547","2018-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has made site visits to the bidders for the tender for Approved Enforcement Agency services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164352","164352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942548","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of applications to use APMS 2014 data received a decision more than three months after being submitted in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164389","164389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942549","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much resource NHS Digital is using to process applications by researchers to access survey data.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164390","164390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942550","2018-07-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of women who took unpaid maternity leave in 2017.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164310","164310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942551","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many immigration cases are outstanding for his Department that have not been resolved within the target time.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164273","164273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942552","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applicants have waited for over a year for their visas applications to be resolved in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164274","164274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942553","2018-07-18","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Government response to the  review of the experiences and outcomes of children in residential special schools and colleges, published in November 2017, what plans he has to ensure that the national leadership board will include people with expertise in speech, language and communication needs.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164496","164496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942554","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress has been made on Crossrail 2; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164500","164500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942555","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the Mayor of London and (b) Deputy Mayor for Transport on the construction of Crossrail 2.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164501","164501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942556","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the quantum of change in Crossrail 2 costings since the Crossrail Update report of May 2018.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164502","164502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942557","2018-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have had discussions with representatives of Corruption Watch UK on restrictions to public reporting on court cases.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164503","164503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942558","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people who have a diagnosis of autism have been in hospital for more than two years by ethnicity.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164490","164490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942559","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many instances of misdiagnosis which were corrected to a diagnosis of autism have occurred in each of the last five years by gender.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164491","164491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942560","2018-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the criteria are for the imposition of restrictions on media reporting applied to cases of economic crime.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164504","164504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942561","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many instances of misdiagnosis were corrected to a diagnosis of autism in each ethnic group, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164492","164492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942562","2018-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of foreign bribery cases have been subject to reporting restrictions in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164505","164505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942563","2018-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2018 to Question 160146 on Ticketmaster, what discussions his Department has had with the (a) National Crime Agency and (b) National Cyber Security Centre on Ticketmaster's recent data breach.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164353","164353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942564","2018-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2018 to Question 160146 on Ticketmaster, what progress has been made on the investigation into Ticketmaster's recent data breach.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164354","164354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942565","2018-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to Answer of 10 July 2018 to Question 160146 on Ticketmaster, how many consumers were affected by Ticketmaster's recent data breach.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164355","164355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942566","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many autistic females under the age of 18 have been diagnosed (a) with co-morbid mental illness and (b) with a mental illness prior to their autism diagnosis.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164493","164493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942567","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the proportion of cases involving unexplained wealth orders that have had reporting restrictions applied to them.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164506","164506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942568","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will support the research into whether obesity should be classified as a disease including the possible consequences of such a classification on NHS commissioning and other services.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164437","164437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942569","2018-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) capacity and (b) occupancy is for each open prison for men in England and Wales.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164507","164507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942570","2018-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) capacity and (b) occupancy is for each open prison for women in England and Wales.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164508","164508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942571","2018-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Iranian counterpart on the protection of (a) religious minorities and (b) the Baha'i religious community in that country.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164509","164509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942572","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his policy is on implementation of Chapter 2 of the Government's childhood obesity plan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164438","164438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942573","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of drug addiction on the economy of (a) Sheffield and (b) UK.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164511","164511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942574","2018-07-19","Cabinet Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Government's Estate Strategy of July 2018, whether a decision has been made on the location of the 1,000 public sector jobs to be located outside London in the next twelve years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164277","164277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942575","2018-07-19","Cabinet Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Government's Estate Strategy of July 2018, where the 20 Government Hubs are planned to be established by the end of the 2017 Parliament.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164278","164278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942576","2018-07-19","Cabinet Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Government's Estate Strategy of July 2018, how many of the 600 Government-operated office buildings which the Government is seeking to sell are in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164279","164279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942577","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representation he has received on his Department's participation in the 8th Conference of the Parties to the World Health Organisation framework convention on Tobacco Control in October 2018.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164377","164377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942578","2018-07-19","Cabinet Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government plans to consult with Civil Service unions on the proposed reduction and relocation of Government-operated office space set out in the Government's Estate Strategy of July 2018.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164280","164280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942579","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department's priorities are for the 8th Conference of the Parties to the World Health Organisation Framework convention on Tobacco Control to be held in October 2018.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164378","164378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942580","2018-07-18","Cabinet Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department plans to establish a strategy for other cities similar to that for enhancing the heart of London set out in the Government's Estate Strategy of July 2018.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164281","164281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942581","2018-07-18","Cabinet Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many new jobs in the north of England his Department estimates will to be created by 2020 as part of the One Public Estate programme.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164282","164282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942582","2018-07-18","Cabinet Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the size of the Civil Service's alumni networks.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164283","164283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942583","2018-07-18","Cabinet Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the number of members of Civil Service alumni networks who work for political lobbying or consultancy firms.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164284","164284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942584","2018-07-19","Cabinet Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2018 to Question 157646, whether the Rapid Response Unit stores the details of those social media accounts which have shared misinformation and disinformation.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164285","164285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942585","2018-07-18","Cabinet Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the purpose and remit are of the National Security Communications Team.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164286","164286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942586","2018-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much his Department has spent with the Big Four accountancy firms in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164287","164287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942587","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much his Department has spent with the Big Four accountancy firms in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164288","164288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942588","2018-07-18","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in (a) Lewisham Deptford constituency, (b) Lewisham borough and (c) England  were referred to children's social services on more than one occasion in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164479","164479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942589","2018-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has spent with the Big Four accountancy firms in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164289","164289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942590","2018-07-18","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussion she has had with the Department of Health in Northern Ireland the conditions of the licence for Billy Caldwell to ensure the availability of medicinal cannabis without the need to travel to Belfast.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164518","164518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942591","2018-07-18","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were referred to children's social services on more than one occasion in the same reporting year in each of the last five years in (a) Lewisham Deptford constituency, (b) Lewisham borough and (c) England.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164480","164480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942592","2018-07-18","Treasury","2018-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2018 to Question 161102, what services have been provided to his Department by the Big Four accountancy firms over the last twelve months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164290","164290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942593","2018-07-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the recommendations of the National Infrastructure Commission in the National Infrastructure Assessment, published on 10 July 2018, whether his Department has plans to (a) move offshore wind into pot 1 and (b) provide greater clarity on auction plans.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164267","164267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942594","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish the 28th report of the School Teachers’ Review Body.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164525","164525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942595","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people who are at risk of developing a gambling addiction.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164305","164305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942596","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people under the age of 18 who have a gambling addiction.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164306","164306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942597","2018-07-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department made of the effectiveness of responsible gambling messages in tackling problem gambling.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164307","164307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942598","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to recognise gambling disorder and addiction as a distinct mental health condition; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164308","164308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942599","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the provision of social care in St Helens in each year up to 2025.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164473","164473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942600","2018-07-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness (a) voluntary and (b) compulsory contributions for the (i) research, (ii) education and (iii) treatment of gambling disorders.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164309","164309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942601","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the methodology is for allocating Army Reserve applicants to Reserve units.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164311","164311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942602","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what role Capita has in allocating an Army Reserve applicant to a Reserve unit.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164312","164312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942603","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Army Reserve Units are awarded the highest priority for recruitment by Capita.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164313","164313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942604","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which body is responsible for managing communication between Capita and the Army Reserve on recruitment.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164314","164314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942605","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether contact between Capita and the Army Reserve during a recruitment process is conducted at (a) company/squadron, (b) battalion and (c) regimental level.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164315","164315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942606","2018-07-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress has been made in discussions between the Government, the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme Trustees, Trade Union representatives and others on the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme surplus.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164474","164474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942607","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2018 to Question 161175, if will estimate in monetary terms the economic cost of the disruption caused by the rail timetable changes introduced on (a) Northern Rail and (b) Govia Thameslink Railway from 20 May 2018.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164445","164445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942608","2018-07-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will include provisions for minimum alcohol pricing in his forthcoming homelessness strategy.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164449","164449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942609","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will review the language used in his Department's press releases to ensure that such releases are measured and reasonable.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164446","164446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942610","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the value is of his Department's contract with EY consultants; and what steps his Department is taking to measure the value for money of that contract.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164457","164457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942611","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding his Department has allocated to external consultants in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164458","164458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942612","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which body had ultimate decision-making responsibility for awarding the (a) Northern and (b) TransPennine Express rail franchises in 2015.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164447","164447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942613","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made on the award of contracts for genomics laboratory services.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164459","164459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942614","2018-07-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the lifetime cost of the building of HMP Wellingborough.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164481","164481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942615","2018-07-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what model of private finance his Department plans to use in the contract to build HMP Wellingborough.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164482","164482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942616","2018-07-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timeline is for the contract to build HMP Wellingborough to be put out to tender, and what the timeline for the tender process will be.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164483","164483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942617","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to encourage the purchase of electric and hybrid vans.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164448","164448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942618","2018-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department plans to issue a public consultation on the legal rights of grandparents to access to their grandchildren after estrangement between grandparents and parents.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164517","164517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942619","2018-07-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, by what date his Department plans for HMP Wellingborough to be built.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164484","164484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942620","2018-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to review the rules governing the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164485","164485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942621","2018-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what requirements his Department plans to place on the design and building of new prisons relating to the number of occupants in each room.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164486","164486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942622","2018-07-18","Cabinet Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the gold reserves of the Bank of England were on 30 June (a) 1998, (b) 2008 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164422","164422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942623","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to implement the Birds and Habitats Directive in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164403","164403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942624","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employers in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottingham South, and (c) Nottinghamshire pay the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164382","164382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942625","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to replicate the EU Alien Species Regulation after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164404","164404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942626","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of apprenticeships in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) the UK achieve NVQ level 3.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164383","164383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942627","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people in Ashfield constituency have started apprenticeships with (a) levy paying and (b) non-levy paying employers in each of the last three academic years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164384","164384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942628","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to compile a list of priority species of concern of invasive species.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164405","164405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942629","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional support his Department offers to areas with low university attendance to encourage young people to take apprenticeships of NVQ level 3 or above.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164385","164385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942630","2018-07-18","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2018 to Question HL8817, how many pupils attend (a) academy sponsor-led and (b) local authority maintained schools.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164291","164291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942631","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to transpose EU Wildlife Trade Regulations into UK law.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164406","164406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942632","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to respond to the letter of the hon. Member for Ashfield of 8 June 2018 on a safeguarding concern at an Ashfield school of a constituent.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164386","164386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942633","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to restrict the importation of wild-caught birds for the pet trade.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164407","164407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942634","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to transpose the EU Action Plan against Wildlife Trafficking into UK law.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164408","164408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942635","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has plans to maintain engagement with the EU-Trade in Wildlife Information Exchange after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164409","164409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942636","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to transpose the EU Seal Products Regulation into UK law after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164410","164410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942637","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to extend the prohibition on fur imports to all species (a) farmed and (b) trapped commercially for fur after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164411","164411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942638","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to transpose the EU ban on leg-hold traps into UK law when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164412","164412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942639","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to develop a strategy for wild-caught fish to (a) reduce stress during capture and handling and (b) improve the humane slaughter of those fish.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164413","164413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942640","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will develop a strategy to phase out the shooting of seals in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164414","164414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942641","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what projection her Department has made of the amount it will pay in universal credit in the 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164254","164254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942642","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to ban the (a) import and (b) export of live animals after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164415","164415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942643","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, by how much her Department's projected spend on universal credit in the 2018-19 financial year has changed as a result of the reduction of the minimum waiting time for payment of claims from six weeks to five.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164255","164255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942644","2018-07-19","Cabinet Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths from malnutrition there have been in the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164256","164256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942645","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cases of malnutrition there have been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164257","164257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942646","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require pig farmers use free farrowing systems.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164416","164416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942647","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the upcoming NHS 10-year plan is planned to include a respiratory programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164258","164258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942648","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance his Department has given to the respective health departments in the devolved nations on access to medical cannabis under licence.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164519","164519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942649","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to safeguard the welfare of (a) dairy cows, (b) beef cattle, (c) sheep, (d) ducks, (e) turkeys, (f) farmed fish, (g) decapod crustaceans and (h) cephalopods after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164417","164417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942650","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to reduce the maximum permitted broiler stocking density after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164418","164418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942651","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he is having with NHS England to ensure that consultants are aware of the licencing process for access to medical cannabis.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164520","164520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942652","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ban the use of enriched hen cages after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164419","164419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942653","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will consider the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to phase out the use of CO2 gas for the stunning of pigs before slaughter.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164420","164420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942654","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to complete the electrification of the mainline between Cardiff and London.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164460","164460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942655","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the  Office for Life Sciences Competitiveness Indicators, published in May 2018, what assessment his Department has made of the fall in the uptake of NICE-approved medicines.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164450","164450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942656","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Office for Life Sciences Competitiveness Indicators published in May 2018, what the reasons are for the reduction in the basic pharmaceuticals and pharmaceuticals products workforce between 2012 and 2016.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164451","164451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942657","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the reasons are for the delay to the electrification of the mainline between Cardiff and London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164461","164461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942658","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much rail track in Wales has been electrified since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164462","164462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942659","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many unfilled vacancies there are for learning disability nurses.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164427","164427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942660","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many learning disability nurses were employed in the North East in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164428","164428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942661","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the savings accrued to the public purse as a result of the cancellation of rail electrification projects since 2015.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164463","164463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942662","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent from the public purse on improving Welsh rail stations since 2015.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164464","164464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942663","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to intervene in negotiations between NHS England and pharmaceutical company Vertex on the provision of Orkambi to Cystic Fibrosis patients on the NHS.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164472","164472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942664","2018-07-18","Prime Minister","2018-07-16","To ask the Prime Minister, who she has appointed as the acting National Security Advisor while Sir Mark Sedwill is acting as her Permanent Secretary.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164489","164489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942665","2018-07-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of delays to the funding scheme for owners and operators of Programme Making and Special Events equipment as a result of the 700 MHz clearance; and when he plans to publish that scheme.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164394","164394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942666","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the target time is for the Disclosure and Barring Service to make decisions on DBS checks; and what he average time taken is to process a DBS application.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164372","164372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942667","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 15 December 2014 to Written Question 217624 on NHS: Complaints, whether his Department plans to make publicly available the reviews of the Patient Advice and Liaison Service and NHS Complaints Advocacy arrangements which were envisaged to be completed by spring 2015.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164488","164488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942668","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of including the reporting of work-related mental health problems as part of the Reporting of Injuries, Diseases and Dangerous Occurrences Regulations 2013.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164373","164373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942669","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many DS1500 applications there have been in each (a) nation and (b) region of the UK in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164292","164292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942670","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number and proportion of DS1500 forms that have been submitted without an accompanying claim form in (a) England and (b) Scotland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164293","164293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942671","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests the UK made to EU partners using the European Arrest Warrant in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164475","164475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942672","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests were submitted to the UK by EU partners using the European Arrest Warrant in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164476","164476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942673","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of face-to-face appointments have been conducted to verify a claimant's identity; and what the average waiting time was from the point of claiming Universal Credit to receiving a face-to-face assessment in order to verify a claimants identity since the introduction of universal credit.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164374","164374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942674","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many successful spousal visa applications there have been for the (a) spouses and (b) children of Afghan interpreters who relocated to the UK under the Government's Redundancy Scheme.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164375","164375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942675","2018-07-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to sub-paragraph 7(a) on page 14 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm. 9353, published on 12 July 2018, which items of EU legislation adopted over the last 30 years have made changes to the rules included in the definition of the common rulebook for goods, including agri-food, covering only those rules necessary to provide for frictionless trade at the border.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164338","164338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942676","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 136545 on Pupils: Disadvantaged, and the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Education of 14 May 2018, Official Report, column 8, what his Department's policy is on the review of the educational outcomes of children in need of help or support aged 16 and 17.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164429","164429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942677","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to reduce VAT on digital editions of magazines, books and newspapers.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164430","164430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942678","2018-07-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse was of the combat aircraft concept model he unveiled at Farnborough International Air show in July 2018.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164364","164364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942679","2018-07-19","Cabinet Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Minister for Cabinet Office, whether there are standardised cross-department pay scales for the post of policy officer in each Government Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164510","164510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942680","2018-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to require the removal of combustible cladding and insulation from (a) schools, (b) care homes and (c) hospitals.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164527","164527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942681","2018-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to introduce a more robust regulatory framework for fire conditions during tests of combustibility of materials.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164528","164528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942682","2018-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timetable is for (a) the remedial work on all high-rise buildings with combustible cladding and (b) the implementation of a ban on combustible cladding.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164529","164529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942683","2018-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many officials in his and the predecessor Department worked on the Government’s national minimum wage application and enforcement policies in each year from 2010-11 to 2017-18; and what the current staffing level of that policy area is.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164302","164302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942684","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has made an assessment of the capacity of his Department's workforce to produce a new statutory fire regulatory framework.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164530","164530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942685","2018-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the cost to the public purse has been of the (a) consultation into the banning combustible cladding and (b) the Independent Review of Building Regulations and Fire Safety led by Dame Judith Hackitt Review.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164531","164531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942686","2018-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2018 to Question 157827 on Amey, what changes his Department made to the contracts with Amey after they were reset following the HMP Liverpool inspection report in January 2018.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164494","164494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942687","2018-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2018 to Question 157827 on Amey, whether additional funding was allocated to Amey after contracts with the company were reset after the HMP Liverpool inspection report in January 2018.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164495","164495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942688","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 47 on page 94 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what those financial penalties are.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164339","164339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942689","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 47 on page 94 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the obligations are which could be suspended.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164340","164340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942690","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 55 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what proposals the Government plans to bring before the House in respect of that parliamentary scrutiny.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164341","164341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942691","2018-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will arrange for a response to be sent to the email of 23 May 2018 from the hon. Member for Slough sent on behalf of a constituent to her Department's Operations Correspondence Team and subsequently forwarded by that team on 24 May 2018 to the Berkshire, Buckinghamshire and Oxfordshire Operations Correspondence Team.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164524","164524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942692","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, which the rules are which would be interpreted by the Court of Justice of the European Union under the proposals there set out.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164342","164342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942693","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 35 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, which the actions are that the Joint Committee will be empowered to take in the event of significant divergences between the interpretation of agreements by the courts of the UK and the EU.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164343","164343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942694","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report Puppy smuggling, a tragedy ignored, published by Dogs Trust in July 2017, whether his Department has made representations to the countries cited in that report.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164478","164478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942695","2018-07-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 31, paragraph 51 of the Combat Air Strategy, published in July 2018, when his Department plans to launch a Combat Air Skills Index.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164365","164365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942696","2018-07-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 31, paragraph 54 of the Combat Air Strategy, when he plans to publish the National Value Framework.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164366","164366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942697","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 46 on page 30 of the Combat Air Strategy, published on 16 July 2018. how many (a) civil servants and (b) armed forces personnel will be in the Combat Air Strategy acquisition team.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164367","164367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942698","2018-07-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 19, paragraph 27 of the Combat Air Strategy what the criteria will be for assessing the performance of Team Tempest.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164368","164368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942699","2018-07-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 19, paragraph 27 of the Combat Air Strategy, whether the name Tempest will be given to the next UK-developed combat aircraft.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164369","164369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942700","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 35 of Chapter Four of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what the difference is between the current prevailing legal principles relating to the Court of Justice of the European Union and the obligation there envisaged on paying due regard to EU case law.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164344","164344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942701","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 19, paragraph 26 of the Combat Air Strategy, whether there are any SMEs in Team Tempest.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164370","164370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942702","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 15, paragraph 13 of the Combat Air Strategy, how much investment his Department plans to provide to key UK design engineering skills and a means to generate UK Intellectual Property.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164371","164371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942703","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 7 of page 14 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what it is proposed should be included in the non-regression provisions; and what level of detail will be specified in such provisions.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164345","164345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942704","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to sub-paragraphs 108(c) and (d) on page 38 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what it is proposed should be included in the non-regression provisions; and what level of detail will be specified in such provisions.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164346","164346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942705","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraphs 118 and 123 of page 39 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what it is proposed should be included in the non-regression provisions; and what level of detail will be specified in such provisions.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164347","164347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942706","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 7 of page 14 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, whether it is proposed that the non-regression provisions cover all relevant rules on the statute book; and whether those rules could still be amended under those non-regression provisions.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164348","164348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942707","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to sub-paragraphs 108(c) and (d) on page 38 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, whether it is proposed that the non-regression provisions cover all relevant rules on the statute book; and whether those rules could still be amended under those non-regression provisions.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164349","164349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942708","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraphs 118 and 119 of page 39 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, whether it is proposed that the non-regression provisions cover all relevant rules on the statute book; and whether those rules could still be amended under those non-regression provisions.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164350","164350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942709","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the summit held on 3 May 2018 to discuss the preparation of new guidance to promote freedom of speech at universities, and the Government response to the Eighth Report of the Joint Committee on Human Rights, Freedom of Speech in Universities, HC 1279, what plans he has to ensure that representatives of University Israel Societies are involved in the discussions on freedom of speech.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164259","164259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942710","2018-07-19","Department for International Development","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority (PA), what discussions her Department has had with the PA on the erection of a billboard in April 2018, organised and sponsored by the PA funded Palestinian Prisoners' Club, honouring 17 Palestinian terrorists.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164260","164260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942711","2018-07-19","Department for International Development","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority (PA), what discussions her Department has had with the PA on the naming of a PA Ministry of Education branch volleyball championship in May 2018 after Abd Al-Jaber Abd Al-Qaeder Khaled, who attempted to carry out a suicide bombing attack in 2002.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164261","164261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942712","2018-07-19","Department for International Development","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority (PA), what discussions her Department has had with the PA on the description on official PA TV on 17 February 2018 of the Nimr Mahmoud Ahmed Al-Jamal, responsible for the murder of three Israelis, as a martyr who ascended to heaven.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164262","164262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942713","2018-07-19","Department for International Development","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority (PA), what discussions her Department has had with the PA on the broadcast on 3 February 2018 on the official PA radio station, The Voice of Palestine, of a poem featuring lyrics stating that Palestine is etched on the heart of the foetus, a proud martyr in his mother's womb.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164263","164263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942714","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress he has made with his Irish counterparts on concluding an agreement on the management of agriculture activities in (a) Lough Foylet and (b) Carlingford Lough; what the remaining matters are to be resolved; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164298","164298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942715","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many meetings he has held with his Irish counterparts to discuss a management agreement for agriculture activities for (a) Lough Foyle and (b) Carlingford Lough in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164299","164299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942716","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether a management agreement with the Republic of Ireland on agriculture activities in relation to (a) Lough Foyle and (b) Carlingford Lough will be in place when the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164300","164300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942717","2018-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Secretary of State is taking to protect the eel industry in Lough Weagh when the UK leaves the EU in March 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164301","164301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940630","2018-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to provide stability for businesses as the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906491","906491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940634","2018-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women were served by each women's centre in each year between 2010 and 2017.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163802","163802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940635","2018-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria his Department will use to assess the success of the review of current rules regarding release on temporary licence in the Female Offenders Strategy, published in June 2018.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163803","163803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940636","2018-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the £5 million of funding announced in the Female Offender Strategy for community provision for women will come from (a) additional resources or (b) the existing Departmental budget.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163804","163804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940637","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his polices of reports from the British Medical Association that self-harm among teenage girls has increased by 68 per cent in the last three years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163806","163806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940638","2018-07-17","Home Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what his policy is on the right to reside in the UK of carers with Ruiz-Zambrano status who are nationals of countries outside of the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163797","163797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940639","2018-07-17","Home Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding his Department plans to allocate to British children of carers residing in the UK under Zambrano status after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163798","163798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940640","2018-07-17","Treasury","2018-07-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on revenue to the public purse of corporations hiring workers as self-employed to circumvent their employer’s national insurance contributions and workers’ rights liabilities as a result of changes to IR35 regulations.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163769","163769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940641","2018-07-17","Department for Education","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the £200 contribution for Disabled Students’ Allowance equipment on the take-up of that allowance on students from low income families.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163822","163822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940642","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 108(c) of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm 9593, which environmental laws and rules will be included in that commitment.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163775","163775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940643","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 108(d) of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm 9593, which laws and rules on climate change will be included in the non-regression commitment.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163776","163776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940644","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union,with reference to paragraph 108(f) of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm 9593, which laws and rules on consumer protection will be included in that commitment.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163777","163777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940645","2018-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 89 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm 9593, which benefits will be included in the proposals for coordination of welfare systems.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163778","163778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940646","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 76(b) of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm 9593, what the maximum duration of a visa-free visit will be for temporary business activity.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163779","163779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940647","2018-07-17","Home Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 76(b) of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm 9593, what activities will be included in the classification temporary business activity.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163780","163780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940648","2018-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 44 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm 9593, what (a) government and (b) regulatory activities will be included in the programme of risk-based market surveillance.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163781","163781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940649","2018-07-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 7(a) of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm 9593, which rules will be included in the category of  necessary to provide frictionless trade at the border.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163782","163782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940650","2018-07-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 5 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU,  Cm 9593, what the proportionate implications will be for the operation of the future relationship.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163783","163783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940651","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding he has allocated and how he has allocated it to the (a) Big White Wall and (b) Veterans' Gateway projects in each year since their inception; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163770","163770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940652","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if the Government will commit to funding the a) Big White Wall and (b) Veterans' Gateway throughout this Parliament.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163771","163771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940653","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Capita has a register of all reservist recruitment units; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163772","163772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940654","2018-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Government's commitment to fund in full the cost of replacing dangerous cladding on local authority and housing association tower blocks includes homes leased by local authorities and housing associations.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163753","163753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940655","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many reservists were recruited in each month in each year since 2016 to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163773","163773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940656","2018-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2018 to Question 125141 on Housing: Construction, if he will publish updated figures on the (a) number, (b) type and (c) tenure of homes under construction on public land since the publication of the Public Land for Housing programme 2015-20 annual report in February 2017.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163754","163754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940657","2018-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department issues guidance to work coaches on what support they should provide to claimants.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163800","163800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940658","2018-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish the guidance her Department provides to work coaches.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163801","163801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940659","2018-07-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the common rulebook for goods proposed in the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm9593, will cover all goods (a) produced in, (b) imported to and (c) exported from the UK.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163784","163784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940660","2018-07-17","Department for Education","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were referred to children’s social services on more than one occasion in the same reporting year in each of the last five years in (a) England and (b) Brighton and Hove.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163785","163785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940661","2018-07-17","Department for Education","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were referred to children’s social services on at least one occasion in consecutive reporting years in each of the last five years in (a) England and (b) Brighton and Hove.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163786","163786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940662","2018-07-17","Department for Education","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how his Department incentivises local authorities' children’s services to provide early help services that can prevent problems reaching crisis point.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163787","163787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940663","2018-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to fulfil its role as a penholder on Darfur in the UN Security Council.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163799","163799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940664","2018-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, at what time on 12 July 2018 his Department released the White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm 9593 to (a) the media (b) parliamentarians (c) Select Committee Chairs (f) the public.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163811","163811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940665","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the withdrawal of foreign language voice-overs and interpreters for candidates taking car and motorcycle theory tests on (a) the number of applicants and (b) the pass rate.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163791","163791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940666","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the level of unlicensed drivers on UK roads of the withdrawal of foreign language voiceovers and interpreters for candidates taking the UK car and motorcycle theory tests since April 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163792","163792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940667","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with which countries the UK has a visa reciprocity agreement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163796","163796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940668","2018-07-18","Department for Transport","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the reintroduction of foreign language voiceovers and interpreters for candidates taking the UK car and motorcycle theory tests.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163793","163793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940669","2018-07-18","Prime Minister","2018-07-13","To ask the Prime Minister, how many pieces of correspondence she has received from members of the public raising concerns over the working visit of President Trump.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163812","163812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940670","2018-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many complaints have been (a) received by the Armed Forces Ombudsman about the Royal Military Police (RMP) (b) made against the RMP, (c) investigated by the Independent Office for Police Conduct (IPCC) and (d) upheld by the IPCC in each year since 2015; when the most recent inspection of the RMP took place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163774","163774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940671","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has met the National Childbirth Trust to discuss the conclusions and recommendations of that organisation's report, Hidden Half: bringing postnatal mental illness out of hiding.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163794","163794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940672","2018-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the adequacy of funding for postnatal checks for new mothers in the General Medical Services contract.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163795","163795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940673","2018-07-17","Home Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for free citizenship have been made by people of the Windrush generation in Preston.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163762","163762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940674","2018-07-17","Home Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many live applications there are for the Windrush free citizenship scheme.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163763","163763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940675","2018-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his Answer of 01 March 2018 to Question 129214 on Industrial Disputes: Ballots, what progress his Department has made since providing that answer.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163805","163805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940676","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many heat-related illnesses have been treated in Lancashire Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust due to the recent warm weather.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163764","163764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940677","2018-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential for an increase in food bank use during the school summer holidays in the North West.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163765","163765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940678","2018-07-18","Department for International Development","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what consultation the Government plans to hold with the private sector to measure progress on Sustainable Development Goal 5: achieve gender equality and empower all women and girls, for the Voluntary National Review at the High Level Political Forum on Sustainable Development  in 2019.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163818","163818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940679","2018-07-18","Department for International Development","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what consultation the Government plans to hold with local authorities to measure progress on Sustainable Development Goal 5: achieve gender equality and empower all women and girls, for the Voluntary National Review at the High Level Political Forum on Sustainable Development in 2019.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163819","163819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940680","2018-07-18","Women and Equalities","2018-07-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the outcomes were of the 62nd session of the Commission on the Status of Women which took place in New York from 12 to 23 March 2018.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163820","163820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940681","2018-07-18","Department for International Development","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to consult the devolved governments on measurement of their progress on Sustainable Development Goal 5 for the Voluntary National Review in 2019; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163821","163821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940683","2018-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the (a) gross and (b) net spending on the housing functions of his Department was by programme in 2017-18.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163755","163755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940684","2018-07-18","Department for Education","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing mandatory training on special educational needs and disability for school governors.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163807","163807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940685","2018-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish the list of invitees to the reception for the President of the United States at Blenheim Palace on 12 July 2018.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163788","163788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940686","2018-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the cost to the public purse was of the visit to the UK of the President of the United States.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163789","163789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940687","2018-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of the reception for the President of the United States at Blenheim Palace on 12 July 2018.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163790","163790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940688","2018-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when the English Housing Survey 2016-2017 microdata will be published on the UK Data Service website.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163756","163756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940689","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of heat-related illnesses treated in Blackpool Teaching Hospitals NHS Trust as a result of recent warm weather.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163767","163767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940690","2018-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to help reduce the gap between English Housing Survey data being collected and the results being published.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163757","163757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940691","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of heat-related illnesses treated in East Lancashire Teaching Hospitals Trust as a result of recent warm weather.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163768","163768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940692","2018-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Female Offender Strategy for England will incur Barnett consequentials for Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163810","163810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940693","2018-07-17","Cabinet Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with Civil Service unions on the pay remit guidance published on 25 June 2018.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163816","163816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940694","2018-07-17","Cabinet Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with which organisations he plans to hold consultations on civil service pay following the pay remit guidance published on 25 June 2018.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163817","163817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940695","2018-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect of reported (a) human rights abuses and (b) attacks on political opposition and trade unions on the fairness of the forthcoming general election in Cambodia.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163813","163813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940696","2018-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much Official Development Assistance has been allocated to (a) trade and economic development, (b) governance and (c) human rights programmes in Cambodia.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163814","163814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940697","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2018 to Question 148619, if he will set a publication date for Public Health England’s Operational Delivery Network Hepatitis C profile tool.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163760","163760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940698","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2018 to Question 148619, whether the Public Health England’s Operational Delivery Network Hepatitis C profile tool will be published before the summer recess.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163761","163761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940699","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the he is taking to ensure that people diagnosed with dementia have access to community support services that support their personal (a) interests and (b) requirements.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163815","163815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940700","2018-07-18","Department for Education","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of specialist teachers on the progress of dyslexic learners; if he will undertake a review of the provision of dyslexia specialists in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163808","163808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940701","2018-07-18","Department for Education","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Centre of Excellence for Literacy Teaching provides support for learners with dyslexia and other literacy needs.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163809","163809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940702","2018-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timetable is for the Law Commission to publish the outcome of its work on leasehold reform.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163758","163758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940703","2018-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish a rough sleeping strategy before the summer recess.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163759","163759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940704","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish his Department's targets for the processing of decisions on applications for asylum support.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163742","163742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940705","2018-07-18","Home Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will take steps to introduce a transparent system for the monitoring of his Department's performance on the time taken to make decisions on applications for asylum support; and if he will publish the results of that performance.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163743","163743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940706","2018-07-17","Department for International Development","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which three programmes in Libya receive the largest amount of funding from her Department.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163744","163744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940707","2018-07-17","Department for International Development","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which organisations her Department allocates funding to for programmes in Libya.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163745","163745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940708","2018-07-17","Home Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps the Government has taken to counter Daesh in Libya.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163746","163746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940709","2018-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the capability of (a) Al Qaeda and (b) Daesh in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163747","163747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940710","2018-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps the Government has made to counter Daesh and Al Qaeda in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163748","163748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940711","2018-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK military personnel are involved in or supporting international operations against Al Qaeda and Daesh in Eastern Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163749","163749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940712","2018-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has plans to visit (a) Riyadh and (b) Dubai to discuss with his counterparts in those countries, the current situation in Hudaydah, Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163750","163750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940713","2018-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2018 to Question 154140 on Yemen: Military Intervention, whether UK personnel have had access to the targeting rooms of the Saudi Arabian air force.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163751","163751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940714","2018-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of (a) trends in the levels of arms smuggling into Yemen from Iran and (b) the effectiveness of UNVIM in preventing arms smuggling,","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163752","163752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939878","2018-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the recommendations contained in the report from Mr Eric Ollerenshaw on Review of local council tax support schemes, published in March 2016, if he will commission research into the effect of local council tax support schemes on the budgets of other welfare programmes.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163509","163509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939879","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timeframe is for the start of the Northern Hub related Hope Valley line improvement scheme.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163510","163510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939880","2018-07-17","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to restore the journey time of East Midland Trains Master Cutler service from Sheffield to St Pancras to its 2017 journey time.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163511","163511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939881","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) objectives and (b) milestones his Department set relating to the decision to tender all justice related interpretation services to Capita Translation and Interpreting between 2012 and 2016; and what assessment he has made of the (a) value for money for the public purse, (b) effect on the conduct of criminal trials and (c) extent to which those (i) objectives and (ii) milestones were met.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163549","163549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939882","2018-07-16","Attorney General","2018-07-12","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to tables three and seven of the Crown Prosecution Service Annual Report 2016-17, what the reasons are for conviction rates in Magistrates Courts being higher than those in Crown Court; and what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for defendants having a 25 per cent greater chance of acquittal at a Crown Court than at a Magistrates Court.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163550","163550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939883","2018-07-17","Home Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons his Department charges the rate that it does for processing licence applications for medical cannabis.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163489","163489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939884","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment has he made of trend in compliance with electrical safety regulations in the social rented sector.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163513","163513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939885","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the Government has done to ensure in negotiations with the European Commission that conformity assessments on products conducted by a UK body continue to be sufficient for the product to be sold on the EU market after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163490","163490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939886","2018-07-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what dispute resolution mechanism and other means of redress will be available to businesses once the UK has left the European Union.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163491","163491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939887","2018-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions have taken place in negotiations on the UK leaving the EU on UK citizens and businesses paying mobile roaming charges in the EU after the UK has left the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163492","163492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939888","2018-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions the Government has had with the European Commission on ensuring that businesses can hold and transfer data and personal information to EU member states without interruption after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163493","163493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939889","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assurances the Government has received from the European Commission that even in a no deal situation goods and people can be flown within the EU after Article 50 expires on 29 March 2019 without any more barriers or checks than currently apply.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163494","163494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939890","2018-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of second homes in (a) each local authority and (b) England registered as holiday lets and for which small business rate relief has been claimed; what estimate he has made of the loss of revenue as a result of that relief; whether he plans to increase the minimum number of letting days to determine eligibility for that relief; whether his Department plans to review the effect of second homes and small business rate relief; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163512","163512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939891","2018-07-17","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of including as part of the driving test process more information and guidance to young drivers on the dangers of driving powerful vehicles.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163526","163526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939892","2018-07-16","Scotland Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he has received representations on the establishment of a Marine Protected Area in the Weddell Sea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163620","163620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939893","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect the EU policy of strategic autonomy on the future availability of advanced weapon systems to the UK's armed forces.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163495","163495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939894","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the UK armed forces have the essential equipment required once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163496","163496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939895","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has plans to develop a (a) UK-only unmanned combat aerial vehicle programme and (a) sixth generation successor to the Eurofighter.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163497","163497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939896","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made on the potential effect on his Department's budget initiating UK-only pogrammes for new weapon systems.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163498","163498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939897","2018-07-17","Treasury","2018-07-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the elderly of the increasing transition to online banking and accessing billing services online.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163559","163559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939898","2018-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many households in temporary accommodation were placed out of area at the end of the January to March Quarter in each year since 1998.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163514","163514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939899","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made the ability of the Government to meet its end of life care choice commitment to babies, children and young people by 2020.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163483","163483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939900","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of patients from Hemel Hempstead that he expects to use the new hospital in Harlow Hospital; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163528","163528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939901","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the recommendations contained in the Honest Crust campaign published by the Real Bread Campaign and the charity Sustain published November 2017.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163615","163615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939902","2018-07-17","Scotland Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many times he has met the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs to discuss the promotion of Scottish interests internationally; and what joint work they have agreed on such promotion.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163621","163621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939903","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the consultation document, Consultation on the use of section 19 and section 22 permits for road passenger transport in Great Britain, published in February 2018, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the new guidelines on community transport on the number of older people who will experience loneliness.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163616","163616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939904","2018-07-16","Scotland Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps he is taking to tackle food poverty in Scotland; whether he has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on trends in the use of food banks; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163622","163622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939905","2018-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions officials in his Department with responsibility for the UK leaving the EU have had with (a) port authorities, (b) major retailers, and (c) haulage firms on the volume and nature plant and animal materials imported to the UK from EU countries; and on what dates those discussions took place.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163575","163575"
