"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17056","2013-10-23","Prime Minister","2013-10-18","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he plans to convene a meeting of Cobra to discuss the close down of Grangemouth refinery; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172081","172081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17057","2013-10-23","Department for Transport","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of UK railway stations have steps but no lift access.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172082","172082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17058","2013-10-23","Department for International Development","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding is allocated to multi-faith initiatives and for preventing communal violence in Burma.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172083","172083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17059","2013-10-23","Department of Health","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the interest on the Government's deferred payment agreements will count towards the cap on social care costs introduced by the Care Bill.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172084","172084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17060","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times the UK has provided officers of another EU member state with protection and assistance as a result of Article 20 of Council Decision 2008/615/JHA in each of the last five years; and what the substance and effect of this protection and assistance was in each case.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172095","172095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17061","2013-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he last met BAe Systems to discuss production of the M777 howitzer.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172085","172085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17062","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what requirements of Council Decision 2005/671/JHA the UK (a) has and (b) has not implemented.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172105","172105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17063","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times the UK has (a) received assistance from and (b) provided assistance to one or more other EU member state as a result of Article 18 of Council Decision 2008/615/JHA in each of the last five years; and what role such assistance played in each case in preventing crime and disorder.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172096","172096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17064","2013-10-22","Department for Education","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that young people are provided with out of school services.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172086","172086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17065","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government intends to retain unchanged existing provisions of UK law and practice required by Council Decision 2005/671/JHA, if the UK ceases to be bound by that Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172106","172106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17066","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in which instances information which is currently exchanged as a result of Council Decision 2005/671/JHA would no longer be exchanged if the UK ceases to be bound by that Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172107","172107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17067","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times the UK has (a) received information from and (b) provided information to other EU member states as a result of Article 16 of Council Decision 2008/615/JHA in each of the last five years; and what importance in preventing terrorism such information had in each case.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172087","172087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17068","2013-10-22","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with Ofcom on preventing broadband, media and mobile telephone companies from charging vulnerable customers for receiving billing and statements through the post.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172108","172108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17069","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times UK officers have been provided with protection and assistance by another EU member state as a result of Article 20 of Council Decision 2008/615/JHA in each of the last five years; and what the substance and effect of this protection and assistance was in each case.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172088","172088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17070","2013-10-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if the Government will bring forward amendments to the draft Consumer Rights Bill to prevent companies from charging vulnerable consumers from being charged by companies for choosing to receive bills and statements through the post.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172109","172109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17071","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures the UK has taken to implement Article 4 of Council Decision 2005/61/JHA; how many requests in each of the last five years the UK has (a) received and (b) sent that have been dealt with under this Article; what the decision was on each such request; how much quicker she estimates each such request was dealt with compared to if this Decision had not applied; and what assessment she has made of the effect in these matters if the UK ceases to be bound by this Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172099","172099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17072","2013-10-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if the Government will make proposals to prevent vulnerable consumers from being charged by companies for choosing to receive bills and statements through the post.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172110","172110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17073","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which EU member states the Council has decided, under Article 25(2) of Council Decision 2008/615/JHA, meet the requirements of Chapter 6 of that Decision; and when other EU member states will be the subject of such a decision.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172089","172089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17074","2013-10-22","Department for Transport","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Liverpool, was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in September 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172127","172127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17075","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many joint investigation teams including the UK have been set up in each of the last five years as a result of Article 3 of Council Decision 2005/671/JHA; and what the aims, activities and achievements of each of these teams were.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172098","172098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17076","2013-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the return of Sean Emmett to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172123","172123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17077","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which EU member states have informed the Council and the European Commission that they have implemented the obligations laid down in Council Decision 2008/615/JHA; and which of those member states have indicated that they will apply that Decision immediately in their relations with other member states that have given the same indication; and what her assessment is of when (a) other EU member states and (b) the UK will inform the Council and the European Commission that they have implemented the obligations of that Decision.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172090","172090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17078","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government intends to retain without change existing provisions of UK law and practice required by Council Decisions 2008/615/JHA and 2008/616/ JHA, if the UK ceases to be bound by those Decisions pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172091","172091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17079","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times information has been provided (a) by and (b) to the UK as a result of Article 2(6) of Council Decision 2005/671/JHA in each of the last five years; and what assessment she has made of how useful this exchange has been to the UK and the other EU member states concerned.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172100","172100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17080","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times information has been provided to Europol by UK authorities as a result of Article 2 of Council Decision 2005/671/JHA in each of the last five years; and what use this information has been put to in each case.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172101","172101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17081","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been in each of the last five years of (a) all co-operation and information exchange resulting from Council Decisions 2008/615/JHA and 2008/616/JHA and (b) preparation for and initial implementation of these Decisions.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172092","172092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17082","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times information has been provided to Eurojust by UK authorities as a result of Article 2 of Council Decision 2005/671/JHA in each of the last five years; and what use this information has been put to in each case.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172102","172102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17083","2013-10-22","Department for Transport","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Belfast, was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in September 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172125","172125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17084","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which provisions of UK law and practice implement requirements of Council Decisions 2008/615/JHA and 2008/616/JHA.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172093","172093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17085","2013-10-22","Department for Transport","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Stornoway, was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in September 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172126","172126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17086","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government intends to maintain unchanged the co-operation and information exchange with other EU member states established by Council Decision 2005/671/JHA if the UK ceases to be bound by that Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; how any such co-operation and information exchange would be maintained; and what assessment she has made of whether this would be at least as efficacious as UK participation in the Decision.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172103","172103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17087","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been in each of the last five years of UK participation in Council Decision 2005/671/JHA.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172104","172104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17088","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government intends to retain unchanged the co-operation and information exchange with other EU member states established by Council Decisions 2008/615/JHA and 2008/616/JHA if the UK ceases to be bound by those Decisions pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; if so, how such co-operation and information exchange would be maintained; and what assessment she has made of whether this would be at least as efficacious as UK participation in those Decisions.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172094","172094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17089","2013-10-22","Department of Health","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will convene an expert group on commissioning fertility treatment, for the purposes of encouraging adherence to the recommendations put forward by the NICE in its guidelines on fertility.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172122","172122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17090","2013-10-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will take steps to ensure that people in food poverty with mobility limitations are made more aware of food banks and have access to food banks.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172111","172111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17091","2013-10-22","Wales Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what meetings (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have had in the last six months with Cabinet Ministers in the Welsh Government.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172132","172132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17092","2013-10-22","Wales Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the role devolution has played in increasing exports from Wales.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172133","172133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17093","2013-10-23","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in how many cases UK authorities have co-operated with the authorities of another EU member state owing to the provisions of Article 9(2) of Council Framework Decision 2002/475/JHA, as amended in each of the last five years; what the substance and outcome of such co-operation was in each case; whether the Government intends to maintain such co-operation unchanged if the UK ceases to be bound by this Framework Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; how such co-operation would be maintained; and what assessment she has made of whether this would be at least as efficacious as UK participation in the Framework Decision.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172113","172113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17094","2013-10-22","Wales Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps he has taken to meet his objective in the Wales Office Business Plan of acting as a champion of armed forces in Wales.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172134","172134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17095","2013-10-23","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what requirements of Council Framework Decision 2002/475/JHA the UK (a) has and (b) has not implemented.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172114","172114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17096","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment he has made of the number of part-time workers working part-time because they cannot find a full-time job in (a) Wales and (b) each region and nation of the UK.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172135","172135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17097","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) applications, (b) successful applications and (c) appeals against failed applications there have been for (i) work capability assessments and (ii) personal independence payments since May 2010 by (A) people in Wales and (B) people in other areas of the UK.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172136","172136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17098","2013-10-23","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many joint operations have been conducted in the UK in each of the last five years pursuant to Article 17 of Council Decision 2008/615/JHA; how many officers and officials of other EU member states, and from which member states, took part in each such operation; and what the aims and outcomes of each such operation were.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172115","172115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17099","2013-10-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what representations he has received from (a) the solar PV industry and (b) the nuclear industry on (i) the length of contract and (ii) the approximate £ per MWH subsidy required from around 2019 to bring forward investment.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172137","172137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17100","2013-10-23","HM Treasury","2013-10-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) businesses, (b) parents and (c) other groups or organisations responded to his Department's consultation on tax-free childcare; what proportion of such respondents supported a tax-free childcare scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172121","172121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17101","2013-10-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the cost trajectories of (a) solar PV and (b) nuclear power over the past decade; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172138","172138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17102","2013-10-23","HM Treasury","2013-10-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the annual cost to the Exchequer of the tax and national insurance exemption for employer-provided childcare vouchers.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172129","172129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17103","2013-10-23","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the UK currently implements all the requirements of Council Decisions 2008/615/JHA and 2008/616/JHA; and if not (a) which requirements it does not currently implement, (b) what she estimates the cost to UK public funds would be of implementing these requirements and (c) whether the Government intends to implement these requirements if the UK ceases to be bound by Council Decisions 2008/615/JHA and 2008/616/JHA pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172119","172119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17104","2013-10-23","HM Treasury","2013-10-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the cost to the Exchequer of tax relief for workplace nurseries in each year that such relief has been available.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172130","172130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17105","2013-10-23","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether security checks for further leave to remain applications are made to (a) UK authorities or (b) external authorities.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172131","172131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17106","2013-10-23","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many joint operations have been conducted in another EU member state, pursuant to Article 17 of Council Decision 2008/615/JHA involving UK officers or officials in each of the last five years; how many UK officers and officials took part in each such operation; and what the aims and outcome of each such operation were.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172120","172120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17107","2013-10-23","Department for Transport","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on which railway lines increased capacity has been observed as a result of the upgrading of track gauges and associated works; and what the increased capacity on such lines was for each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172116","172116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17108","2013-10-23","Department for Transport","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost of upgrading track gauges and associated works was on each railway line where such work has been undertaken in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172117","172117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17109","2013-10-23","HM Treasury","2013-10-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 8 October 2013, Official Report, column 147W, on children: day care, if he will publish a list of all stakeholders consulted as part of his Department's consultation on tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172118","172118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17110","2013-10-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether his Department plans to underwrite the construction costs of the power station at Hinkley Point; what the terms of the £10 billion loan guarantee for that power station announced in the Spending Review are; whether the strike price will be updated in line with the Consumer Prices Index or Retail Prices Index; whether his discussions with investors have included provision for future alterations of the strike price (a) upwards or (b) downwards; if he will make it his policy that any increase in anticipated costs for Hinkley C will not result in any further funding from (i) the public purse and (ii) bill payers to complete the project; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172139","172139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17136","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2013, Official Report, column 467W, on entry clearances: fees and charges, what discussions the Government is having with Commonwealth countries which levy substantial visa charges on UK citizens entering their territory, to seek an equalisation of such charges across different jurisdictions.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172075","172075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17137","2013-10-22","Department for Education","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2013, Official Report, columns 602-3W, on free school meals, what plans his Department has to facilitate the availability of pupil premium to Key Stage 1 children and the schools they attend in subsequent years.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172097","172097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17138","2013-10-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on companies charging consumers who choose to receive paper bills and statements by post; and what assessment he has made of the effect this has on vulnerable consumers.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172128","172128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17139","2013-10-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much Royal Mail spent on commissioning the survey published on 25 September 2013 by Ipsos-MORI.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172124","172124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17140","2013-10-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2013, Official Report, column 855W, on Sri Lanka, which UK companies will attend the Commonwealth Business Forum; and what discussions his Department has had with such companies about the UK Action Plan on Business and Human Rights.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172112","172112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17141","2013-10-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make it his policy to subsidise nuclear power on the same basis as (a) fossil fuels and (b) solar PV.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172141","172141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17142","2013-10-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Arctic Policy Framework published on 17 October 2013, of which environmental risks associated with oil, gas and mining activities in parts of the Arctic the UK is very aware; and if he will publish the details of what constitute the highest environmental and drilling standards in the Arctic advocated by the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172140","172140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17143","2013-10-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department is aware of Government or local authority sources of emergency food that can be accessed without food vouchers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172142","172142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16859","2013-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what geographic telephone number his Department advertises for use by the general public.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171892","171892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16860","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what geographic telephone number his Department advertises for use by the general public.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171893","171893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16861","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what geographic telephone number her Department advertises for use by the general public.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171894","171894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16862","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what geographic telephone number his Department advertises for use by the general public.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171895","171895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16863","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what geographic telephone number his Department advertises for use by the general public.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171896","171896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16864","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the level of repayment was for (a) crisis loans and (b) budgeting loans in each of the four years to March 2013.","Biography information for Paul Goggins","Paul Goggins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171862","171862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16865","2013-10-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the appropriate length of time within which a Green Deal package can be agreed and fully financed.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171863","171863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16866","2013-10-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he expects the initial assessment of all homes that could be eligible for the Green Deal to be completed.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171864","171864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16867","2013-10-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what contingency plans his Department is making to prepare for a prolonged cold spell this winter.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171865","171865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16868","2013-10-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many people will be lifted out of fuel poverty by the Energy Company Obligation scheme.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171866","171866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16869","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the safety of e-cigarettes; what assessment he has made of whether e-cigarettes reduce usage of conventional cigarettes; and what steps he is taking to support smokers who have decreased their dependence on conventional cigarettes by using e-cigarettes.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171867","171867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16870","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many reported cases there are each year of potential organ donors failing to donate organs due to an unavailability of (a) suitable beds and (b) specialist nurses.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171868","171868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16871","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential value of educating school age children about organ donation and transplantation.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171869","171869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16872","2013-10-21","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he estimates the fitting of the Sea Ceptor naval defence system to the Type 23 Frigates to be completed.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171870","171870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16873","2013-10-23","Department for Education","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department expects to begin consultation on the building design standard for school premises first announced in November 2011 in respect of (a) guidance on fire sprinklers in particular and (b) other matters.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171890","171890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16874","2013-10-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information he holds on whether the big six energy companies will raise prices further over the next six months.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171891","171891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16875","2013-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce pollution levels at The Air Balloon Pub and surrounding cottages.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171897","171897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16876","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the Scottish Government, (b) Transport Scotland and (c) Network Rail on the Dalmeny Chord rail link.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171899","171899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16877","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has undertaken of the plans for the Dalmeny Chord rail link.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171900","171900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16878","2013-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on which occasions the National Tactical Response Group was called out in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171876","171876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16879","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on building the Dalmeny Chord rail link.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171901","171901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16880","2013-10-22","Department of Health","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether and at what level a centrally determined interest rate on deferred payment agreements for residential care costs will be introduced in the Care Bill.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171877","171877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16881","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people's records have been mislaid by his Department in the course of moving documents between storage offices since 1990.","Biography information for Charles Hendry","Charles Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171878","171878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16882","2013-10-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people eligible for cold weather payments in East Riding.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Mr Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171905","171905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16883","2013-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Burmese counterpart on the unconditional release of (a) Naw Ohn Hla and (b) other political prisoners.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171879","171879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16884","2013-10-24","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Humber Bridge Board on the need to avoid traffic delays on and around the bridge; and when he next intends to meet the Board.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Mr Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171906","171906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16885","2013-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of changes in incidences of the practice of torture and ill treatment towards political prisoners in Burma following the report of the UN Special Rapporteur in March 2013.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171880","171880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16886","2013-10-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to announce his decision on which areas to designate as marine conservation zones.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Mr Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171908","171908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16887","2013-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have completed their minimum sentence tariff but are still imprisoned in (a) HMP Altcourse, (b) HMP Walton and (c) all prisons in England.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171882","171882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16888","2013-10-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of those individuals sleeping rough who are former members of the armed forces.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171883","171883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16889","2013-10-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he will open discussions with the US Government on the re-negotiation of the 1966 UK-US agreement on British Indian Ocean Territory; and whether such discussions will include resettlement of Chagossians in their homeland.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171929","171929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16890","2013-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the situation of Christians in Egypt.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171884","171884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16891","2013-10-21","Cabinet Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost was of (a) establishing the Number 10 Implementation Unit and (b) abolishing the Prime Minister's Delivery Unit; and what the differences are between the work of both units.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171909","171909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16892","2013-10-21","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make representations to Clarion Events Limited on the attendance of suppliers to the Syrian government at the recent Defence and Security Equipment international arms exhibition.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171910","171910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16893","2013-10-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much (a) his Department and (b) relevant local authorities spent on 1st East Urban Regeneration Company throughout that body's existence.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171911","171911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16894","2013-10-21","HM Treasury","2013-10-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of revenue lost to the Exchequer as a result of illegal trading in (a) cigarettes, (b) spirits, (c) diesel, (d) petrol and (e) other counterfeit goods in Northern Ireland in each of the last two years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171919","171919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16895","2013-10-21","Church Commissioners","2013-10-17","To ask the Honourable Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, how many food banks are currently supported by the Church of England.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171912","171912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16896","2013-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of people aged over 55 years have been assisted in learning new job skills in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171920","171920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16897","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what comparative assessment he has made of (a) delays and (b) congestion at the A417/A419 air balloon roundabout and roundabouts with similar traffic levels elsewhere in the country.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171913","171913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16898","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average (a) weekday and (b) weekend delay time is for the A317/A319 Air Balloon roundabout during peak hours.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171921","171921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16899","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will produce a cost-benefit analysis of the options to alleviate congestion problems on the A417/A419 Air Balloon roundabout.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171914","171914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16900","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the estimated current design capacity is of the A417/A419 Air Balloon roundabout.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171915","171915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16901","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many road traffic accidents have occurred between Nettleton Bottom and the bottom of Crickley Hill in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171916","171916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16902","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Highways Agency has taken to deal with congestion centred on the Air Balloon roundabout on the A419 and A417; and whether any further such action is planned.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171922","171922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16903","2013-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in each region were convicted of (a) a motoring offence that resulted in a fatality and (b) careless driving in 2012.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171917","171917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16904","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) lowest and (b) highest daily traffic flow through the A417/A419 Air Balloon roundabout has been in the last six months.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171923","171923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16905","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many accident and emergency staff in hospitals in each region were assaulted while on duty in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171918","171918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16906","2013-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, to which prisons the National Tactical Response Group has been called out in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171886","171886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16907","2013-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of Army personnel currently serving (a) as officers and (b) in other ranks were aged under 18 at enlistment.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171887","171887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16908","2013-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of Army personnel at each rank of officer and above were aged under 18 when they enlisted.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171888","171888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16909","2013-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of Army personnel promoted to each rank of officer and above in the last 10 years enlisted as junior entrant soldiers.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171889","171889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16910","2013-10-21","HM Treasury","2013-10-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many submissions were made to the Stamp Duty Land Tax: consultation on the potential effects of devolving to the National Assembly for Wales and Welsh Government; and when a response to the consultation will be published.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171930","171930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16911","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many employees there are at the National Crime Agency.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171934","171934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16912","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many National Crime Agency specials there are; and how many are planned to be recruited.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171935","171935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16913","2013-10-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what new apprenticeship frameworks or qualifications have been created as a direct result of employer demand through the Employer Ownership of Skills project.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171924","171924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16914","2013-10-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of the employer investment in (a) each of the successful bids for round one of the Employer Ownership of Skills pilot and (b) in total, has been given (i) as a cash contribution and (ii) in kind; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171925","171925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16915","2013-10-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he last met the Chief Executive of Ofgem to discuss energy prices; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171926","171926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16916","2013-10-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to increase affordable housing supply; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171927","171927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16917","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he intends to publish his response to the Independent Advisory Panel Report on Residential Training Provision, published in July 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171928","171928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16918","2013-10-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on how many local councils in England publish magazines more than six times a year.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171936","171936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16919","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will include residential training provision for the disabled in the Disability Employment Strategy Report due to be published in November 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171898","171898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16920","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an estimate of the number of firearms illegally imported to the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171937","171937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16921","2013-10-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to promote (a) invoice financing agreements and (b) other steps to encourage banks to fund small businesses more fairly.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171902","171902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16922","2013-10-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to ensure that reports commissioned by the Council for Science and Technology are not authored by those currently seeking Government support for other projects.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171904","171904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16923","2013-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether (a) low-interest loans, (b) bail-out grants or (c) any other form of funding has been provided for severe weather schemes set up by his Department.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171955","171955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16924","2013-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proposals insurers have presented to him to off-set the effects of severe weather events on farmers.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171956","171956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16925","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many letters from hon. Members to the UK Border Agency's MPs' Liaison Unit were responded to (a) within 20 working days and (b) after 20 working days in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171939","171939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16926","2013-10-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the potential cost to the public purse if management costs for management of radioactive waste from new build nuclear plants exceed the cap on costs included in the nuclear waste and decommissioning financing arrangements for new nuclear plants.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171965","171965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16927","2013-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what reports he has received from the insurance industry of difficulties in developing an economic model that would provide sufficient contingency funding for farmers in the event of severe weather.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171957","171957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16928","2013-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, under what circumstances he would use state-funding for a contingency scheme in cases where severe weather has affected UK farmers.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171958","171958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16929","2013-10-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will (a) place in the Library and (b) publish on his Department's website copies of the agreements he concluded with Chinese nuclear authorities during his recent visit to China in respect of inward investment in the UK nuclear power programme; and which private sector business executives accompanied him on this visit.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171966","171966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16930","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how he measures the distance children travel to school in rural areas.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171959","171959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16931","2013-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of human rights in China.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171968","171968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16932","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average distance travelled to school by (a) primary, (b) secondary and (c) all other pupils for whom data is available was for the last three years of recorded data.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171960","171960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16933","2013-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in Bedford have participated in the AGE 16 to 24 Scheme; and how many and what proportion of such businesses were small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171940","171940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16934","2013-10-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent steps he has taken to encourage local authorities to provide permanent sites for gypsies and travellers to prevent unauthorised encampments.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171941","171941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16935","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding to public bus services has changed in (a) cash and (b) percentage terms in each of the last three years; and what assessment he has made of the effect of such changes on rural communities.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171962","171962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16936","2013-10-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to allow the public to take complaints about Housing Associations and their tenants to the Housing Ombudsman.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171942","171942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16937","2013-10-21","Department for Education","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what measures he is taking to ensure schools maintain positive relationships with both parents of a child when the parents are separated.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171943","171943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16938","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce the amount owed in arrears in cases managed by the Child Support Agency.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171945","171945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16939","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases are being managed by the Child Support Agency; and how many such cases have payments which are in arrears.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171946","171946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16940","2013-10-23","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what has been the increase in passenger numbers on the London Liverpool Street and Chelmsford service between 2002 and 2012.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172030","172030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16941","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what proportion of the Child Support Agency cases that are in arrears (a) the arrears are being actively repaid, (b) the arrears have been temporarily suspended and (c) payments have never been received.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171947","171947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16942","2013-10-23","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to increase capacity on the London Liverpool Street to Chelmsford line.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172031","172031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16943","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications the Child Support Agency has made to court for (a) liability orders, (b) deduction orders, (c) deduction of earnings orders, (d) third party debt orders and (e) charging orders in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171948","171948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16944","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will bring forward a legislative and regulatory reform order to remove the burden whereby people whose employment and support allowance comes to an end are required to formally claim jobseeker's allowance (JSA) enabling the automatic provision of JSA to appropriate cases.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171970","171970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16945","2013-10-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many vacanies were registered with Job Centre Plus in the (a) Chelmsford parliamentary constituency and (b) Chelmsford Local Authority area in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172032","172032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16946","2013-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in China on the use of organs taken from executed prisoners.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171971","171971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16947","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the role played by police stations in meeting the policing needs of large and growing towns.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171972","171972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16948","2013-10-21","Department for Education","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the influence of poverty on a child's (a) intellectual development and (b) social mobility.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171973","171973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16949","2013-10-21","Department for Education","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the influence of genetics on a child's (a) intellectual development and (b) social mobility.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171974","171974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16950","2013-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on a two state solution in the Middle East.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171975","171975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16951","2013-10-21","Department for International Development","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, who paid for the road building programme associated with Bost Airfield and Bost Agricultural Park in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171976","171976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16952","2013-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the role of the Greyhound Board of Great Britain in monitoring and recording (a) welfare standards within greyhound racing and (b) the number of greyhounds put to sleep for economic reasons.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171964","171964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16953","2013-10-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to his Department's study, Potential Greenhouse Gas Emissions Associated with Shale Gas Extraction and Use, what assessment his Department has made of (a) the potential effects of greenhouse gas emissions associated with shale gas extraction and (b) the global warming effect of methane associated with shale gas extraction.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171967","171967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16954","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has been having with her European counterparts on the renegotiation of the non-refoulement aspect to Article 3 of the European Convention of Human Rights since May 2010.","Biography information for Patrick Mercer","Patrick Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171987","171987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16955","2013-10-21","Department for International Development","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what work has been undertaken by her Department to assess the likely number of applicants for leaseholdings before committing investment to the development of Bost Industrial Park.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171977","171977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16956","2013-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people complained about any element of the performance of the criminal justice system in 2009-10 and 2011-12.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171986","171986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16957","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he will make a decision on whether to introduce standardised packaging on tobacco products.","Biography information for Patrick Mercer","Patrick Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171988","171988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16958","2013-10-21","Department for International Development","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what return has been achieved on her Department's investment in Bost Airfield and Bost Agricultural Park in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171978","171978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16959","2013-10-22","Department of Health","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for which quarters since May 2010 has the South Tees NHS Foundation Trust failed to meet its referral treatment target.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172000","172000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16960","2013-10-21","Department for International Development","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, for what reasons her Department operated a leaseholdings rather than land purchase programme at Bost Agricultural Park.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171979","171979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16961","2013-10-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what research progammes have been supported by resources from his Department's budget on (a) nuclear waste management, (b) nuclear plant decommissioning and (c) plutonium disposition since May 2010.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171969","171969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16962","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the progress of projects established by voluntary and third-sector organisations following the award of £6.5 million from his Department's Help and Support for Separated Families Innovation Fund in April 2013.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172009","172009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16963","2013-10-21","Department for International Development","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many fluent Pashto speakers her Department hired to work with locals on the leaseholding elements of Bost Agricultural Park.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171980","171980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16964","2013-10-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, for what reasons his Department has decided not to hold stakeholder information and engagement meetings in (a) Scotland and (b) Northern Ireland in association with his Department's national public consultation on the Geological Disposal Facility siting process review.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171989","171989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16965","2013-10-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeships will be created for (a) 16 to 18 year olds and (b) people aged 19 years and over in each of the successful bids for round one of the Employer Ownership of Skills pilot.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172001","172001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16966","2013-10-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities have successfully applied for monies through the Bellwin scheme in each of the last five years; and if he will list the local authorities and the total sum of their individual grants.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172002","172002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16967","2013-10-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the proposal from the Fire Sector Federation that the Minister should appoint a Transformation Commission to implement the findings of the review of efficiencies and operations in fire and rescue authorities in England.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171981","171981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16968","2013-10-22","Department for Education","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will place copies of the Property Data Survey Programme results for schools in the Sandwell local authority area in the library.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172003","172003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16969","2013-10-22","Department of Health","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what conversations he and his Ministerial colleagues have had with (a) Monitor and (b) the South Tees NHS Foundation Trust about (i) the Trust's failure to meet its target of treating 90 per cent of patients within 18 weeks of them being referred, (ii) the increase in reported never events at the Trust and (iii) the incidence of clostridium dificile infection at the Trust.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172010","172010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16970","2013-10-21","Attorney General","2013-10-17","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to his contribution of 14 October 2013, Official Report, column 592, if he will publish the six point action plan to increase referrals of rape and domestic violence cases by the police to the Crown Prosecution Service.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171982","171982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16971","2013-10-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what representations he has received from Ineos concerning the restructuring of their UK operations at (a) Grangemouth refinery and (b) elsewhere in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172004","172004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16972","2013-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department expects to re-open the UK Embassy in Tehran; and what progress has been made on re-opening the Iranian Embassy in London.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172012","172012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16973","2013-10-21","Department for Education","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2013, Official Report, columns 746-7W, on GCSE, what those figures are for (a) 2009-10 and (b) 2010-11.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171983","171983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16974","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of Employment and Support Allowance with a prognosis of over 12 months were referred to the work programme up to June 2013; and how many of such people secured a job outcome.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172020","172020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16975","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he will publish an evaluation of the first round of funding for projects established under the Help and Support for Separated Families Innovation Fund in April 2013.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172013","172013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16976","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the number of sanctions issued by an adviser in Jobcentre Plus is included in his or her staff appraisal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172021","172021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16977","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints submitted to the Investigatory Powers Tribunal were deemed to be vexatious or without standing in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013; what definition of (i) standing and (ii) vexatious the Investigatory Powers Tribunal uses; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171984","171984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16978","2013-10-22","Department for Education","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will visit schools in the Sandwell local authority area.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172005","172005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16979","2013-10-22","HM Treasury","2013-10-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the VAT revenue accruing to the Exchequer from online advertising in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172014","172014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16980","2013-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he received the latest official estimates of the badger population in (a) Somerset and (b) Gloucester.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172022","172022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16981","2013-10-22","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many road safety auditors there were in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Northern Ireland and (d) Scotland in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172015","172015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16982","2013-10-22","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many certificates of competence in road safety audit have been issued by the HIghways Agency in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Northern Ireland and (d) Scotland since December 2011.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172016","172016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16983","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of (a) availability, (b) capacity and (c) effectiveness of provision available for parents bursary family-based arrangements for child maintenance from 2014.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172023","172023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16984","2013-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he will publish the next Victims' Code.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172017","172017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16985","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to raise awareness of domestic abuse in the UK.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172018","172018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16986","2013-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what guidance his Department provides to wounded, injured and sick service personnel and veterans about VAT exemptions for necessary home adaptations.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172024","172024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16987","2013-10-21","Wales Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2013, Official Report, column 464W, on Devolution, what progress has been made towards the publication of the draft Wales Bill.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171994","171994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16988","2013-10-22","Department of Health","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what changes in per capita funding to the (a) NHS Sunderaland Clinical Commissioning Group (CCG), (b) NHS South Tyneside CCG, (c) NHS South Tees CCG, (d) NHS South Eastern Hampshire CCG, (e) NHS Eastbourne, Hailsham and Seaford CCG and (f) NHS Fareham and Gosport CCG are being proposed in the 2013-14 working paper on CCG allocations and indicative target allocations.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172006","172006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16989","2013-10-22","HM Treasury","2013-10-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to make necessary home adaptations for wounded, injured and sick service personnel and veterans exempt from VAT.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172025","172025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16990","2013-10-21","Wales Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many official engagements he has held in the Wales Office in the last three months.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171995","171995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16991","2013-10-21","Wales Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what progress he has made on implementing the objectives of the Wales Office Business Plan in the last three months.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171996","171996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16992","2013-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether any extension of the time period for badger culls to occur will (a) alter the recommendations of the Independent Scientific Review Group, (b) affect the scientific validity of the cull and (c) be a decision to be taken by (i) Natural England and (ii) the Independent Expert Panel and (iii) another body.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172026","172026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16993","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many ECM reviews in (a) Pakistan, (b) India, (c) China, (d) Australia and (e) the US have been refused on the basis of staff shortages in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171990","171990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16994","2013-10-21","Wales Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which deadline for the objectives in the Wales Office Business Plan he expects to meet.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171997","171997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16995","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she will publish regulations associated with the draft immigration bill.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172027","172027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16996","2013-10-22","Department for International Development","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to engage parliamentarians in the Post-2015 Development Framework; and if the Prime Minister will agree to meet hon. Members to discuss their role in this process.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172007","172007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16997","2013-10-21","Wales Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what meetings he has held with third party campaigning groups regarding the effect of the provisions of the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171998","171998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16998","2013-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that any future badger cull (a) will be compliant with the Bern Convention and (b) will ensure the correct number of badgers are culled to reduce TB.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172028","172028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16999","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the proportion of ECM reviews which are not completed due to staff shortages.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171991","171991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17000","2013-10-21","Wales Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether the Wales Office move to Caspian Point was completed within budget; and what the total cost of this move was.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171999","171999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17001","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what proportion of Child Support Agency cases that are in arrears the Agency has sought an enforcement order.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171950","171950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17002","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will place in the Library details of the (a) most common illnesses and disabilities and (b) length of prognosis of people in receipt of Employment and Support Allowance who have been referred to the Work Programme since it began.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172029","172029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17003","2013-10-21","Church Commissioners","2013-10-17","To ask the Honourable Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what recent steps the Church of England has taken to promote credit unions.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171951","171951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17004","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to re-establish the Innovations Commissioning Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171952","171952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17005","2013-10-24","Department for International Development","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that gender equality and women's empowerment becomes a standalone goal in the post-2015 development framework.","Biography information for Baroness Burt of Solihull","Lorely Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172033","172033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17006","2013-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reasons he valued the Royal Mail to be worth approximately £3.3 billion for purposes of its privatisation; and what consideration he has given since the flotation of Royal Mail shares of this being an under-valuation.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171953","171953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17007","2013-10-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the cost to the public purse has been of financial contributions to (a) Euratom, (b) European Commission Joint Research Centres, (c) the ITER nuclear fusion project, (d) the International Atomic Energy Agency and (e) the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development nuclear energy agency since May 2010.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171992","171992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17008","2013-10-24","Department for International Development","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of barriers to political participation to the lives of women and girls in developing countries.","Biography information for Baroness Burt of Solihull","Lorely Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172034","172034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17009","2013-10-21","Wales Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2013, Official Report, columns 425-6W, on Domestic Fire Safety (Wales) Measures 2011, Parliamentary Question 170435, what discussions or correspondence he has had with (a) Carl Sargeant and (b) John Griffiths AM on the Domestic Fire Safety (Wales) Measure 2011.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171985","171985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17010","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department has given to local job centres on sanctioning claimants where the only work offered is on a zero hours contract.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172035","172035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17011","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the extradition of Gilbert Deya to Kenya.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171993","171993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17012","2013-10-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when his Department will publish a response to the Efficiency and Operational review of the Fire Service undertaken by Sir Ken Knight.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172036","172036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17013","2013-10-21","Department for Education","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2013, Official Report, columns 750-1W, on pupils with English as an additional language, if he will supply the equivalent figures for Year 1.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172037","172037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17014","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent progress he has made on the reconfiguration of health services in Worcestershire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172038","172038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17015","2013-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the overall number of crime levels for the West Mercia Police Force was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172039","172039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17016","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been removed from the United Kingdom following enforcement action under sections 15 to 25 of the Immigration, Asylum and Nationality Act 2006 since May 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172051","172051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17017","2013-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his latest assessment of the situation in the Maldives is.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172040","172040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17018","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to reduce the stigmas associated with mental health issues since 2010.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172041","172041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17019","2013-10-22","Cabinet Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many businesses have used the CESG cyber incident response scheme to date.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172053","172053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17020","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how he plans to ensure that the knowledge, skills and expertise developed during the building of Crossrail will feed into future construction plans regarding High Speed 2.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172042","172042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17021","2013-10-22","Cabinet Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of the accredited providers for the G-Cloud and (a) consultants and (b) application providers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172055","172055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17022","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many searches of UK vehicle registration data authorities other EU member states have carried out in each of the last five years under Article 12 of Council Decision 2008/615/JHA; how many of those searches resulted in a match; and what action the relevant foreign authority took in each such case on the basis of finding such a match.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172043","172043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17023","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many searches UK authorities have carried out on the fingerprint databases of other EU member states in each of the last five years under Article 9 of Council Decision 2008/615/JHA; how many of those searches resulted in a match; in how many of those cases the UK received further information from the relevant foreign authority following a match; and what action UK authorities took in each case on the basis of finding such a match or receiving further information.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172044","172044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17024","2013-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2013, Official Report, column 479W, on Afghanistan, whether his Department has any plans to publish or disclose the review currently being conducted by the Chief of the Defence Staff into the findings of the US report of security at Camp Bastion.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172062","172062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17025","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many searches UK authorities have carried out on the DNA databases of other EU member states under (a) Article 3 and (b) Article 4 of the Council Decision 2008/615/JHA in each of the last five years; how many of those searches resulted in a match; in how many of these cases the UK received further information from the relevant foreign authority following a match; and what action the UK authorities took in each case on the basis of finding a match or receiving further information.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172056","172056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17026","2013-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2013, Official Report, column 479W, on Afghanistan, when the Chief of Defence Staff will finish reviewing the findings of the US report on the review of security at Camp Bastion.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172063","172063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17027","2013-10-22","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many British Transport Police officers there were in post in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172064","172064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17028","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the expenditure to date on IT for Universal Credit which will be categorised as nugatory in addition to sums already published; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172019","172019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17029","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's press release of 14 October 2013, entitled jobseekers to start signing new claimant commitment; on what date the regulations under which the claimant commitment was implemented were commenced.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172057","172057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17030","2013-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on how many occasions Human Rights concerns have been raised with the government of Sri Lanka since May 2010; and on how many occasions officials in his Department have (a) visited the North and East of that country and (b) inspected Sri Lankan refugee camps in that time.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172065","172065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17031","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseekers' allowance claimants in (a) Inverness, (b) Rugby and (c) Hammersmith have been required to sign a claimant commitment since 14 October 2013.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172058","172058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17032","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been removed to Sri Lanka under immigration law in each year since 2010-11; and what her policy is on immigration and the safety of Tamil people who are returned.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172066","172066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17033","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 34 of his Department's green paper entitled 21st Century Welfare published in July 2010, what recent assessment he has made of whether universal credit constitutes a major IT project.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172059","172059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17034","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many searches authorities of other EU member states have carried out on the UK's fingerprint database in each of the last five years under Article 9 of Council Decision 2008/615/JHA; how many of these searches resulted in a match; in how many of these cases the UK provided the relevant foreign authority with further information following a match; and what action the relevant foreign authority took in each case on the basis of finding such a match or receiving such further information.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172045","172045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17035","2013-10-22","Department for International Development","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what aid has been delivered directly (a) in Syria and (b) to Syrian refugees since January 2012.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172067","172067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17036","2013-10-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of (a) the level of interconnection between the UK's energy control network and the internet and (b) the cyber security implications arising from such interconnectedness.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172060","172060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17037","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) maximum and (b) minimum sentence that the courts have imposed under sections 15 to 25 of the Immigration, Asylum and Nationality Act 2006 is since May 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172068","172068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17038","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many searches of vehicle registration data of another EU member state UK authorities have carried out in each of the last five years under Article 12 of Council Decision 2008/615/JHA; how many of those searches resulted in a match; and what action UK authorities took in each such case on the basis of finding such a match.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172046","172046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17039","2013-10-22","Department for International Development","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to promote digital technology for democratic processes around the world.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172061","172061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17040","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) emails and (b) telephone calls have been received by the help desk operated by the UK Border Agency since May 2010 on employment enforcement under sections 15 to 25 of the Immigration, Asylum and Nationality Act 2006.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172069","172069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17041","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many prosecutions of employers there have been under sections 15 to 25 of the Immigration, Asylum and Nationality Act 2006 since May 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172070","172070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17042","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many offences involving illegal firearms were committed in (a) Liverpool, (b) Merseyside and (c) England in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172071","172071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17043","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times the UK has (a) received information from and (b) provided information to other EU member states as a result of Articles 13 and 14 of Council Decision 2008/615/JHA in each of the last five years; and what assessment she has made of the role such information played in preventing crime and disorder in each case.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172047","172047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17044","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many searches authorities of other EU member states have carried out on the UK's DNA database under (a) Article 3 and (b) Article 4 of Council Decision 2008/615/JHA in each of the last five years; how many of those searches resulted in a match; in how many of those cases the UK provided the relevant foreign authority with further information following such a match; and what action the relevant foreign authority took in each case on the basis of finding such a match or receiving further information.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172048","172048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17045","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times UK authorities have collected a DNA sample and supplied it to another EU member state due to a request under Article 7 of Council Decision 2008/615/JHA; in how many cases the person whose DNA was being obtained was a British national; and what action the relevant foreign authority took in each case using the sample provided.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172049","172049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17046","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were employed in the helpline sections of the Border Agency dealing with sections 15 to 25 of the Immigration, Asylum and Nationality Act 2006 in October 2013.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172050","172050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17047","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times UK authorities have obtained a DNA sample from another EU member state using the provisions of Article 7 of Council Decision 2008/615/ JHA in each of the last five years; and what action UK authorities took in each case using the sample provided.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172052","172052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17114","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of people infected by contaminated blood through NHS blood transfusions have since died.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171861","171861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17115","2013-10-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to help people in (a) the North West and (b) Rossendale and Darwen constituency reduce their energy bills.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171871","171871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17116","2013-10-21","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what change there has been in the number of armed forces personnel in (a) Wales and (b) each other nation and region of the UK since May 2010.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171872","171872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17117","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what change there has been in the number of police officers in (a) Wales and (b) each other nation and region of the UK since May 2010.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171873","171873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17118","2013-10-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what change there has been to average (a) gas and (b) electricity bills  in (i) Wales and (ii) each other nation and region of the UK since May 2010.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171874","171874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17119","2013-10-24","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department has issued to all local authorities on constructing and operating car parking bays of sufficient size to accommodate the average family motor vehicle.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Mr Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171907","171907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17120","2013-10-22","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full-time equivalent staff at what level of seniority will work on corruption policy in her Department following the establishment of the National Crime Agency.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171881","171881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17121","2013-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support her Department provides to women who have been trafficked in order to assist their rehabilitation into civil society.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171885","171885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17122","2013-10-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the reasons for differential gas and electricity prices across the UK; and what assessment he has made of the differing effects of price increases in each nation and region of the UK.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171875","171875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17123","2013-10-21","HM Treasury","2013-10-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many of his officials are working on analysing submissions to the  Stamp Duty Land Tax: consultation on the potential effects of devolving to the National Assembly for Wales and Welsh Government.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171931","171931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17124","2013-10-21","HM Treasury","2013-10-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people in (a) Wales and (b) each other region of the UK who will receive the married tax allowance.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171932","171932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17125","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) National Crime Agency (NCA) officers and (b) NCA specials are designated with the powers of (i) constable, (ii) immigration officer and (iii) customs officer.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171933","171933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17126","2013-10-25","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the use of pre-disposition data by Royal Air Force Recruitment and Selection; what assessment he has made of the case of Ms Lowri Simner, reference RAFC 52427/1/R&S; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171938","171938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17127","2013-10-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the total cost to the public purse of the new nuclear programme including costs arising from (a) development, (b) strike price provisions and (c) future decommissioning.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171903","171903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17128","2013-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) representatives of the farming industry, (b) environmental groups, (c) banking groups, (d) insurance groups and (e) local authorities on contingency funding for extreme weather effects affecting farmers.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171954","171954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17129","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of spending changes since 2010 on bus services in rural areas.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171961","171961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17130","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much is currently owed in arrears in cases managed by the Child Support Agency.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171944","171944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17131","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many bus routes operating in rural areas are (a) in receipt of and (b) not in receipt of government subsidy; and what cumulative distance was covered by these services in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171963","171963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17132","2013-10-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what data or information he will take into account when assessing whether the training being provided as part of Round One of the Employer Ownership of Skills pilot is (a) of high quality and (b) value for money.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172011","172011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17133","2013-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of teachers working in further education colleges are currently neither qualified nor in training.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171949","171949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17134","2013-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many separating and separated parents have been assisted so far in each project in receipt of funding from the Help and Support for Seperated Families Innovation Fund; what the gender of such parents was; and what outcomes were achieved by each such project.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172008","172008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17135","2013-10-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress has been made on incorporating the EU Cybersecurity directive into UK law.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172054","172054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16601","2013-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with which individuals and bodies his Department consulted prior to the publication of the statement 'Ministers to end work experience health and safety confusion' on the gov.uk website on 21 June 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171606","171606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16602","2013-10-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of provision of lipreading classes for adults in the UK.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171607","171607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16603","2013-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to increase awareness of the needs of people who lipread amongst providers of public services for which his Department is responsible.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171609","171609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16604","2013-10-18","Department for Transport","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many accidents on roads involving motorised mobility scooters have been recorded in the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Dame Angela Watkinson","Dame Angela Watkinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171610","171610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16605","2013-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the number of accidents in pedestrianised precincts that have taken place in the last five years.","Biography information for Dame Angela Watkinson","Dame Angela Watkinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171611","171611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16606","2013-10-21","HM Treasury","2013-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to exempt people subject to transitional arrangements between incapacity benefit and employment and support allowance from income tax due on such payments.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171612","171612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16607","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to receive a reply to his letter to the interim Director General UK Visas and Immigration of 16 September 2013 on behalf of a constituent CTS ref B25111/13.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171613","171613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16608","2013-10-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many enforcement notices have been served on occupiers of private land under the Weeds Act 1959 on owners failing to prevent the spread of weeds including ragwort in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Mr Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171614","171614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16609","2013-10-24","Department for Transport","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department issues to local authorities on the selective switching-off of road lighting at night during poor weather conditions and reduced visibility; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Mr Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171615","171615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16610","2013-10-24","Department for Transport","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions (a) he and (b) his officials have had concerning the European Union proposal for legislation requiring the future fitment of an electronic in-vehicle system that automatically alerts the emergency services when an accident occurs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Mr Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171616","171616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16611","2013-10-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding her Department has granted in 2013 to help deliver or improve rural broadband in East Yorkshire.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Mr Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171617","171617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16612","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure long-term security of the neuromuscular care adviser post in the East Midlands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171618","171618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16613","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will consider standardising information regarding warning signs of foetal distress and issue national guidance on preventing infant mortality.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171620","171620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16614","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to review current practices on the monitoring of foetal growth and development in the third trimester of pregnancy.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171621","171621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16615","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce infant mortality.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171622","171622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16616","2013-10-18","Department for Transport","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of whether the current regulation for minimal fuel carry for commercial aircraft is satisfactory.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171623","171623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16617","2013-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that Hazara women are able to sustain their current level of education following the withdrawal of British troops from Afghanistan in 2014.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171624","171624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16618","2013-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the threat to the Hazara community following the withdrawal of foreign troops in Afghanistan in 2014.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171625","171625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16619","2013-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart regarding the security of the Hazara people following the withdrawal of foreign troops from Afghanistan in 2014.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171626","171626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16620","2013-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with President Karzai of Afghanistan to ensure the security of the Hazara people following the withdrawal of foreign troops from that country in 2014.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171627","171627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16621","2013-10-18","Department for Transport","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of UK air passengers are carried by Ryanair.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171628","171628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16622","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure the long-term security of the neuromuscular care adviser post in the East Midlands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171629","171629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16623","2013-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times he has met the Victims' Commissioner.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171631","171631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16624","2013-10-21","Attorney General","2013-10-16","To ask the Attorney General, how many anti-money laundering cases, originating from suspicious activity reports or from independent law enforcement investigations, were prosecuted in each year from 2008 to 2012.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171632","171632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16625","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many suspicious activity reports were (a) filed by each of the different obligated entities and (b) submitted to law enforcement authorities in each year from 2008 to 2012.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171633","171633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16626","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to review the effectiveness of current regulations governing the use of sunbeds.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171634","171634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16627","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many local authorities are currently able to license the use of sunbeds within their area; and if he will assess the scope for increasing the number of such authorities.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171635","171635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16628","2013-10-21","Department for Education","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new school buildings were built in each of the last 10 years using funds other than or in addition to local authority funding; and how much was spent by his Department on new school buildings in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171636","171636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16629","2013-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, by what date he expects his Department's investigation of food poverty and food banks to conclude; and if he will publish any subsequent report.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171638","171638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16630","2013-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many officials in his Department are currently working on its investigation into food poverty and food banks.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171639","171639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16631","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will carry out an equality impact assessment on the effects of the use of 0845 numbers within his Department.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171640","171640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16632","2013-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what budget is allocated to support the work of the Victims' Commissioner.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171641","171641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16633","2013-10-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what analysis his Department has undertaken of the potential effects of making the Energy Performance Certificate transferable between all companies supporting the Green Deal.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171642","171642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16634","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether all future providers of probation services will be required to attend those local multi-agency meetings which consider the needs of (a) female offenders, (b) female victims of domestic abuse and (c) male perpetrators of domestic violence.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171643","171643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16635","2013-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many reports he has received about UK citizens being detained whilst visiting Sri Lanka in the last year.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171656","171656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16636","2013-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many representations he has received on the Government's representation in Sri Lanka to attend the Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting in December 2013.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171657","171657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16637","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether GP practices receive a referral payment when patients are referred to the London NHS Diagnostic Service provided by InHealth.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171658","171658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16638","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of probation offices make referrals to food banks.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171659","171659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16639","2013-10-18","Department for Education","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of schools make referrals to food banks.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171660","171660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16640","2013-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of local authorities make referrals to food banks.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171661","171661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16641","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of court diversion schemes make referrals to local food banks.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171662","171662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16642","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the cost to the public purse of raising the retirement age of magistrates to 75.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171663","171663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16643","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with trades unions on the transferring of benefit fraud officers from local authorities to the new Single Fraud Investigation Service.","Biography information for Mr David Hamilton","Mr David Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171667","171667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16644","2013-10-21","Department for International Development","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she plans to hold with hon. Members on the Post-2015 Development Framework following the UN's Review Summit in September 2013; and if she will meet relevant All-Party Parliamentary Group officers to discuss their role in any such discussions.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171668","171668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16645","2013-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the likelihood of job losses at his Department's Alnwick office under the Next Generation Shared Services Programme; and what recent discussions he has held with contractors on the work carried out at that office.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171669","171669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16646","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of rent arrears on (a) local authorities in Wales, (b) Cardiff local authority and (c) Vale of Glamorgan local authority.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171670","171670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16647","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what porportion of GP surgeries make referrals to food banks.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171671","171671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16648","2013-10-18","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much has been spent by the Parades Commission on consultations in each year since its formation.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171672","171672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16649","2013-10-18","HM Treasury","2013-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representatations he has received about waiving airport tax for charities.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171645","171645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16650","2013-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many wild animals, of which species, have been licensed under the Welfare of Wild Animals in Travelling Circuses Regulations of 2012 to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171646","171646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16651","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government intends to retain without change existing provisions of UK law and practice required by Council Framework Decision 2005/212/JHA, if the UK ceases to be bound by that Framework Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171674","171674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16652","2013-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the cost to the circus industry of complying with the licensing scheme under the Welfare of Wild Animals in Travelling Circuses Regulations 2012.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171647","171647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16653","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which requirements of Council Framework Decision 2005/212/JHA the UK (a) does and (b) does not implement.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171675","171675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16654","2013-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department has spent on developing and implementing the circus licensing scheme under the Welfare of Wild Animals in Travelling Circuses Regulations 2012.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171648","171648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16655","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times UK authorities have taken part in meetings pursuant to Article 5(2) of Council Decision 2003/335/JHA in each of the last five years; what information was exchanged with UK authorities on each such occasion; and what her assessment is of how useful this information has been to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171676","171676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16656","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department takes to ensure that certification for abortion on the grounds of risk to the woman's mental health is evidence-based.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171649","171649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16657","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how the requirements of Council Framework Decision 2001/500/JHA are implemented in the UK; and whether the Government intends to retain these implementing measures unchanged if the UK ceases to be bound by the Framework Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171677","171677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16658","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications of the findings of the Academy of Medical Royal Colleges in paragraph 5.5 of its report on induced abortion and mental health, published in December 2011, that when a woman has an unwanted pregnancy, rates of mental health problems will be largely unaffected whether she has an abortion or goes on to give birth, for the interpretation by practitioners of ground C in the certification of abortions.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171650","171650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16659","2013-10-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what cost-benefit analysis his Department has made of a North-South interconnector in Wales; and if he will publish any such analysis.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171651","171651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16660","2013-10-18","HM Treasury","2013-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on implementing of a house price growth cap of five per cent annually.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171652","171652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16661","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been of UK compliance with Council Framework Decision 2001/500/JHA in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171679","171679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16662","2013-10-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the viability of (a) the future of the post office network and (b) the future of Post Offices as community hubs in rural areas following the privatisation of parts of the Royal Mail.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171653","171653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16663","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the UK implements all the requirements of Council Framework Decision 2001/500/JHA; and if not, which requirements are not implemented.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171680","171680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16664","2013-10-18","Department for International Development","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the viability of the humanitarian situation in Syria's neighbours and the flow of refugees into those countries.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171654","171654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16665","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to maintain the reciprocal arrangements provided for by Article 4 of Council Framework Decision 2001/500/JHA with some or all other EU member states if the UK ceases to be bound by that Framework Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; how the Government would do this; and what assessment she has made of whether this would be at least as efficacious as UK participation in the Framework Decision.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171681","171681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16666","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times in each of the last five years the UK has received a request from another EU member state regarding asset identification, tracing, freezing or seizing and confiscation that was processed in accordance with Article 4 of Council Framework Decision 2001/500/JHA; and on how many such occasions the UK fulfilled the request.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171682","171682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16667","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government will seek to continue the co-operation established by Council Decision 2003/170/JHA, as amended, if the UK ceases to be bound by that Council Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; what operational and legislative measures would be needed to continue this co-operation; and what assessment she has made of whether this co-operation will continue to be possible.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171683","171683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16668","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Government plans to maintain unchanged all UK measures implementing Council Framework Decision 2003/568/JHA if the UK ceases to be bound by that Framework Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171684","171684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16669","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the usefulness of co-operation involving Gibraltar undertaken as a result of Article 9(2) of the Convention on the fight against corruption involving officials of the European Communities or officials of Member States of the European Union in the fight against the offences in question; whether the Government of Gibraltar has indicated that it intends to maintain this co-operation unchanged if Gibraltar ceases to be bound by the Convention pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; and how such co-operation would be maintained.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171685","171685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16670","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many evaluation exercises have been undertaken pursuant to Council Decision 202/996/JHA.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171692","171692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16671","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the usefulness of co-operation involving Gibraltar undertaken as a result of Article 9(1) of the Convention on the fight against corruption involving officials of the European Communities or officials of Member States of the European Union in the fight against the offences in question; whether the Government of Gibraltar has indicated that it intends to maintain this co-operation unchanged if Gibraltar ceases to be bound by the Convention pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; and how such co-operation would be maintained.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171686","171686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16672","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been of compliance with Council Decision 2003/170/JHA in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171702","171702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16673","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the UK could continue to participate in decision-making of the Council under Article 8(3) of Council Decision 202/996/JHA if the UK ceases to be bound by that Council Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171693","171693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16674","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times UK liaison officers have (a) provided and (b) received information pursuant to Council Decision 2003/170/JHA in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171703","171703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16675","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times UK authorities, including the Government but not including liaison officers, have (a) provided and (b) received information pursuant to Council Decision 2003/170/JHA in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171704","171704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16676","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times UK liaison officers have (a) provided and (b) received assistance pursuant to Article 4(2) of Council Decision 2003/170/JHA in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171705","171705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16677","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Council Decision 2003/170/JHA, as amended, gave rise to the introduction of any legislative proposals; and what such changes were.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171706","171706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16678","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government will seek to contribute to the influencing and sharing of best practice across the EU on the matters covered by Council Decision 2002/996/JHA if the UK ceases to be bound by that Council Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; how the Government would do this; and what assessment she has made of whether this would be at least as efficacious as UK participation in the mechanism established by Council Decision 2002/996/JHA.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171695","171695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16679","2013-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which firms were instructed to perform valuations of the Royal Mail property portfolio prior to its privatisation; and whether a competitive bidding process preceded their appointment.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171713","171713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16680","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many foreign heavy goods vehicles committed digital tachograph offences in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013; and what action was taken in respect of each offence.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171714","171714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16681","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many cases the Gibraltarian authorities have co-operated with the authorities of one or more EU member state due to the provisions of Article 9(1) of the Convention on the fight against corruption involving officials of the European Communities or officials of member states of the European Union in each of the last five years; and what the substance and outcome of the co-operation was in each case.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171696","171696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16682","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many widows and widowers applied for a discretionary payment under the Police Survivor Support scheme.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171715","171715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16683","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many cases the Gibraltarian authorities have co-operated with the authorities of one or more EU member states due to the provisions of Article 9(2) of the Convention on the fight against corruption involving officials of the European Communities or officials of member states of the European Union in each of the last five years; and what the substance and outcome of the co-operation was in each case.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171697","171697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16684","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will provide a breakdown of successful applicants to the Police Survivor Support scheme from each region of the UK.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171716","171716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16685","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons the Police Survivor Support scheme was time-limited.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171717","171717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16686","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which requirements of the Convention on the fight against corruption involving officials of the European Communities or officials of member states of the European Union Gibraltar (a) does and (b) does not implement.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171698","171698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16687","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications were received by the Police Survivor Support scheme after the closing date; and how many such applicants received a discretionary payment.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171718","171718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16688","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applicants received the maximum amount payable under the Police Survivor Support scheme.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171719","171719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16689","2013-10-21","Department for Transport","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many drivers of foreign heavy goods vehicles were found to be breaking EC Regulations No. 1072/2009 in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013; what aspects of the regulations such drivers were in breach of; and what action was taken in respect of each offence.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171720","171720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16690","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what laws or practices implement in Gibraltar the requirements of the Convention of the fight against corruption involving officials of the European Communities or officials of member states of the European Union; and what conversations he has had with the government of Gibraltar on whether that body intends to retain these implementing measures unchanged if Gibraltar ceases to be bound by the Convention pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171699","171699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16691","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what quality and performance standards are in place for the NHS 111 Service; and whether it has met them in (a) London and (b) Brent.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171700","171700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16692","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with respect to the service specification metrics of the NHS 111 Service, how many calls have not been (a) answered, (b) referred to a clinician or trained nurse within the appropriate timescale or (c) in receipt of a call-back from an appropriate clinician within 10 minutes to date.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171701","171701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16693","2013-10-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people in (a) Crawley constituency, (b) the South-East and (c) England started an apprenticeship in (i) 2012 and (ii) 2013.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171707","171707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16694","2013-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff are employed, in what capacity, at the (a) UK embassy in Baghdad and (b) UK consulate in Erbil.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171708","171708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16695","2013-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Planning Practice Guidance for Renewable and Low Carbon Energy issued by his Department in July 2013 on (a) the number of wind turbine application appeals sent to the Inspectorate and (b) the number of refusals overturned by the Inspectorate citing the above guidance.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171710","171710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16696","2013-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will issue guidance on the application of his Department's Planning Practice Guidance for Renewable and Low Carbon Energy, clauses 39 and 40; and how the cumulative landscape and visual effect of turbines is assessed.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171712","171712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16697","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to UK public funds of UK participation in the European Network for the Protection of Public Figures, established by Council Decision 2002/956/JHA has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171688","171688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16698","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many common views have been established, and remain valid, pursuant to Article 4 of Council Decision 2002/956/JHA, as amended; what the substance of these common views is; whether these common views have entailed any changes to UK practices; and how often the relevant UK authorities have drawn on these common views in their operations in each of the five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171689","171689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16699","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to UK public funds of UK participation in Council Decision 2002/996/JHA, including the secondment of national experts to evaluation teams has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171691","171691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16700","2013-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the annual cost of all benefits paid to people classed as (a) unemployed, (b) pensioners and (c) in work in the last five years.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171732","171732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16701","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will review the retirement age for magistrates.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171721","171721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16702","2013-10-18","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many meetings Ministers in her Department have had with the Police Ombudsman for Northern Ireland since September 2012.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171734","171734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16703","2013-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on house building of his plans to transfer £400 million of New Homes Bonus funding to local enterprise partnerships.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171735","171735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16704","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been in each of the last five years of UK participation in Council Decision 2004/919/EC.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171741","171741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16705","2013-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions spatial disorientation of a pilot has resulted in (a) damage or (b) total loss of an airframe in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171723","171723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16706","2013-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the £400 million which is being transferred from local authorities' New Homes Bonus funds into local enterprise partnerships budgets will be counted as local authority budget cuts.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171736","171736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16707","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times UK authorities have received information as a result of Article 3(3) of Council Decision 2003/335/JHA in each of the last five years; and what action was taken by UK authorities on the basis of this information in each case.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171742","171742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16708","2013-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any pilots testing the Joint Strike Fighter have suffered spatial disorientation using the helmet mounted display.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171724","171724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16709","2013-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of the welfare budget was spent on (a) the unemployed, (b) pensioners and (c) those in work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171737","171737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16710","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times UK authorities applied to the authorities of another EU member state for information under Article 3(2) of Council Decision 2003/335/JHA in each of the last five years; and on how many of these occasions UK authorities received the information they sought.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171743","171743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16711","2013-10-18","Cabinet Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff of his Department worked in the Efficiency and Reform Group in (a) April 2013 and (b) the latest period in which figures are available.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171738","171738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16712","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in how many cases UK authorities co-ordinated their activities with the authorities of one or more other EU member states as a result of the provisions of Article 5(1) of Council Decision 2003/335/JHA in each of the last five years; and what the substance and outcome of the co-ordination was in each case.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171744","171744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16713","2013-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his estimate is of the cost of removing equipment installed on Warthog vehicles for use in Afghanistan; and what equipment will replace it.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171726","171726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16714","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proposals the Government would bring forward to maintain the relevant co-operation were the UK no longer bound by Council Common Position 2005/69/JHA pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171739","171739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16715","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether UK practice regarding the information exchange covered by Council Common Position 2005/69/JHA would change as a result of the UK ceasing to be bound by that Common Position pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171740","171740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16716","2013-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what live armaments have been used by the Joint Strike Fighter to date.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171728","171728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16717","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to maintain co-operation with other EU member states established by Council Decision 2003/335/JHA were the UK no longer bound by that Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; and what assessment she has made of whether this would be at least as efficacious as UK participation in the Decision.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171745","171745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16718","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been of UK participation in Council Decision 2003/335/JHA in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171746","171746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16719","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government intends to retain unchanged existing UK law and practice required by Council Decision 2004/919/EC if the UK ceases to be bound by that Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171751","171751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16720","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which of the requirements of Council Decision 2004/919/EC the UK (a) has and (b) has not implemented.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171747","171747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16721","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to retain unchanged existing UK law and practice required by Council Framework Decision 2004/757/JHA, if the UK ceases to be bound by that Framework Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171752","171752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16722","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the UK would continue to co-operate with other EU member states on issues pertaining to Council Framework Decision 2004/757/JHA were the UK no longer bound by the Framework Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171753","171753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16723","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure long-term security of the neuromuscular care advisor post in the East Midlands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171755","171755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16724","2013-10-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will publish figures for 2009, 2010, 2011 and 2012 for exploration, development and operating activities on the UK Continental Shelf, including oil sales, natural gas sales, natural gas liquids sales and other UKCS aggregate incomes including revenues from pipelines and terminals as well as other revenues from operators and production licences.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171761","171761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16725","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to retain unchanged existing provisions of UK law and practice required by Council Decision 2003/335/JHA, were the UK no longer bound by the Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171756","171756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16726","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy that all future providers of probation services will be required to attend local violence against women and girls forums.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171763","171763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16727","2013-10-18","Department for International Development","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of her Department's funding for the Syria emergency is currently being used for (a) gender-based violence prevention, (b) gender-based violence case management and (c) sexual and reproductive health in (i) Syria and (ii) neighbouring countries.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171764","171764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16728","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in how many cases UK authorities co-operated with the authorities of another EU member state due to the provisions of Article 3(1) of Council Decision 2003/335/JHA in each of the last five years; and what the substance and outcome of the co-operation was in each case.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171757","171757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16729","2013-10-18","Cabinet Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many part time workers are working less than 24 hours a week in each parliamentary constituency in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171765","171765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16730","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which of the requirements of Council Decision 2003/335/JHA the UK (a) has and (b) has not implemented.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171758","171758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16731","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to monitor the sustainment of self-employed businesses established with support from the new enterprise allowance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171774","171774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16732","2013-10-18","Department for Education","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what procedures are in place to ensure pupil premium payments follow students who move schools during an academic year.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171760","171760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16733","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken as a result of Article 3(1) of Council Decision 2004/919/EC in each of the last five years; what the frequency of these actions has been; and what assessment she has made of the usefulness of these actions in the fight against cross-border vehicle crime.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171748","171748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16734","2013-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of housing benefit were (a) unemployed and (b) employed in each region of the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171806","171806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16735","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of employment and support allowance who were referred to the Work Programme in the 104 weeks from June 2011 had a sight problem as their main impairment; and how many such people secured a Job Outcome in that period.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171775","171775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16736","2013-10-18","Department for Education","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of poverty on the early cognitive development of a child.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171807","171807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16737","2013-10-18","Department for Education","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many books were delivered by Bookstart in each constituency of the UK in each year of the scheme's existence.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171808","171808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16738","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government intends to maintain unchanged the co-operation and information exchange with other EU member states established by Council Decision 2004/919/EC if the UK ceases to be bound by that Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; how such co-operation would be maintained; and what assessment she has made of whether this would be at least as efficacious as UK participation in the Decision.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171749","171749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16739","2013-10-18","Cabinet Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the level of computer ownership among (a) the general population and (b) the unemployed.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171768","171768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16740","2013-10-18","Department for Education","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding was allocated to Bookstart by his Department in each year of its existence.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171809","171809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16741","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people on employment and support allowance receiving a sanction on the advice of a Work Programme provider were classified as belonging to an ethnic minority in (a) 2008, (b) 2009, (c) 2010, (d), 2011, (e) 2012 and (f) January to September 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171776","171776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16742","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times UK authorities provided information to Europol as a result of Article 9 of Council Decision 2004/919/EC in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171750","171750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16743","2013-10-18","Cabinet Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what was the median gross weekly earnings for employees in each constituency between April 2006 and the latest year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171810","171810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16744","2013-10-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) housing planning decisions and (b) other planning decisions his Department has overturned since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171814","171814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16745","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether every household will receive an opt-out form along with information about care.data.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171784","171784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16746","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data he has on the prognoses for people in receipt of employment and support allowance who were referred to the Work Programme in the 104 weeks from June 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171777","171777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16747","2013-10-21","Department for International Development","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make representations to the Secretary of State for the Home Department to request permission for Syrian refugees with existing connections to the UK to be assisted in entering and staying in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171817","171817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16748","2013-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish details of (a) all licensing inspections carried out on travelling circuses, (b) the licences granted and the conditions applied, (c) all licensed travelling circuses using wild animals and (d) details of all licensed wild animals within such circuses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171813","171813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16749","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the establishment of the Single Fraud Investigation Service on the ability of local authorities to investigate benefit fraud.","Biography information for Mr David Hamilton","Mr David Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171787","171787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16750","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what dates she has visited the Independent Police Complaints Commission's Hillsborough investigations headquarters.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171788","171788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16751","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of Mosquito devices in operation in (a) England and (b) each London borough.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171789","171789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16752","2013-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the findings of the recent report by a group of animal welfare charities entitled Left on the Verge: The approaching equine crisis in England and Wales; and what steps he plans to take further to safeguard horse welfare.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171795","171795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16753","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what arrangements her Department has in place for monitoring the prevalence of Mosquito devices in England.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171790","171790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16754","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what evaluation he has made of the pilot programmes of the benefit of transferring staff from local authorities to the Single Fraud Investigation Service.","Biography information for Mr David Hamilton","Mr David Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171820","171820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16755","2013-10-21","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times tasers were used on under 18s in (a) England and (b) each London borough in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171791","171791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16756","2013-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information has been supplied by the Government following the allocation of shares to those who applied for shares in Royal Mail (a) online and (b) by post.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171821","171821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16757","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission an analysis of the reasons for the increase in referrals to Improving Access to Psychological Therapy services in the last two years; and if he will ensure that sufficient resources are in place to support those services.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171796","171796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16758","2013-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of progress in promoting peace and democracy in Eastern Afghanistan following the recent murder of a provincial governor in Puli Alam.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171797","171797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16759","2013-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, by what date he expects funds to be returned to those who applied for Royal Mail shares but were unsuccessful or did not receive their full allocation; and what process he has established for this process.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171822","171822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16760","2013-10-22","Department for Transport","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made in replacing the overhead electrification cables on the line from London Liverpool Street to Ipswich; and what the cost of the project has been to date.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171800","171800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16761","2013-10-21","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the care data system will extract the records of people who have received treatment for a sexually-transmitted disease.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171798","171798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16762","2013-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what has been the total value of interest accrued to date by the Government from funds deposited from shares in Royal Mail by investors which was not used for the purchase of shares; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171823","171823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16763","2013-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on what date those applying for shares in Royal Mail (a) by post and (b) online were informed whether their application was successful.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171824","171824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16764","2013-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what advice his Department has received on the value of Royal Mail's surplus property holdings from banks or financial institutions involved in the privatisation of Royal Mail.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171799","171799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16765","2013-10-22","Department for Transport","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans there are to build a new railway station at Beaulieu Park, Chelmsford; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171801","171801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16766","2013-10-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reason his Department believes that the Land Registry Business Strategy cannot be delivered effectively under the Trading Fund status; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171827","171827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16767","2013-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the total amount of funds received by the Government on applications for Royal Mail shares option applications had closed and before shares were allocated was; and in what account these funds were held.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171825","171825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16768","2013-10-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether Land Registry cash reserves have been considered for the delivery of the Business Strategy under its current Trading Fund status.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171828","171828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16769","2013-10-22","Department for Transport","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress is being made in upgrading the track from London Liverpool Street to Ipswich; and what the cost of that project has been to date.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171802","171802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16770","2013-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of staff who will be transferred from local authorities to his Department when the Single Fraud Investigation Service is established.","Biography information for Mr David Hamilton","Mr David Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171779","171779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16771","2013-10-22","Department for Transport","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans there are to build a (a) loop and (b) third rail from Beaulieu Park to Witham; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171803","171803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16772","2013-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to refund interest lost to retail investors who applied for but did not receive Royal Mail shares.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171781","171781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16773","2013-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on maintaining the privatised Royal Mail as a body subject to Freedom of Information Act 2000 requests.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171782","171782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16774","2013-10-25","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to encourage closer working relationships between Armed Forces Family Support units and domestic violence charities.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171804","171804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16775","2013-10-18","Cabinet Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure that Government procurement supports British innovation.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171852","171852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16776","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the age profile of midwives working for the NHS in England was in each year since 2001.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171832","171832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16777","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on what happens to those who qualify as midwives at higher education institutions in England; and how many go on to practise as midwives in the NHS.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171833","171833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16778","2013-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Thales Starstreak high velocity missiles have been purchased by his Department on 11 October 2013; and what the cost to the public purse of this purchase was.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171853","171853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16779","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many places for midwifery training were commissioned in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and what the total population of student midwives in England has been in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171834","171834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16780","2013-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Thales Starstreak high velocity missiles are currently in the inventory of the armed forces.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171854","171854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16781","2013-10-18","Department for Education","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to improve engagement between schools and local employers.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171842","171842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16782","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on maternity services in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion of total NHS spending this represented in each such year.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171835","171835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16783","2013-10-18","Department for Education","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his Department is doing to promote careers in construction to young people in schools.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171843","171843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16784","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on NHS maternity services in each region in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171836","171836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16785","2013-10-18","Department for Education","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage schools to teach pupils about entrepreneurship and starting a business.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171844","171844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16786","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost was of training a midwife in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171837","171837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16787","2013-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Warthog vehicles will be operated by 32 and 47 Regiment's Royal Artillery.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171856","171856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16788","2013-10-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of new student visa regulations on UK universities.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171845","171845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16789","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many student midwives were in receipt of a bursary in each of the last three academic years for which figures are available; what the average bursary paid to a student midwife was in each of those years; and what the total cost was to his Department in each year of bursaries paid to student midwives.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171838","171838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16790","2013-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what incentives his Department makes available to encourage pet owners to microchip their animals.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171846","171846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16791","2013-10-18","Cabinet Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the age profile of women giving birth in England has been in each year since 2001.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171839","171839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16792","2013-10-18","Department of Health","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many births per full-time equivalent NHS midwife there have been in (a) England and (b) each region in each year since 2001.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171840","171840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16793","2013-10-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support his Department provides to businesses to allow them to deliver City and Guilds qualifications to their staff directly.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171848","171848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16794","2013-10-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to increase training and skills for small independent retailers.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171849","171849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16795","2013-10-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what incentives his Department provides to encourage businesses to increase staff skills.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171850","171850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16796","2013-10-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on what date (a) planning was granted for and (b) works on site commenced on the Aldbrough gas storage facility.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171829","171829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16797","2013-10-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps his Department has taken to reduce the number of functionally illiterate adults in the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171851","171851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16798","2013-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much has been distributed in pay and pensions to councillors across the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171859","171859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16799","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the minimum standards for the supervision of female offenders will be in his probation on tender documents.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171857","171857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16800","2013-10-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on what date (a) planning was granted for and (b) works on site commenced on the Halford gas storage facility.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171830","171830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16801","2013-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the range of payments for pay and pensions to councillors across the UK was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171860","171860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16802","2013-10-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on illegal file-sharing of draft regulations introducing a private copying exception which includes cloud storage.","Biography information for Michael Connarty","Michael Connarty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171858","171858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16803","2013-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to decrease the level of re-offending amongst young offenders.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171831","171831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16810","2013-10-18","HM Treasury","2013-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will reduce VAT for the tourism and hospitality sector.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171608","171608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16811","2013-10-18","Cabinet Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the mortality rates for (a) pre-term, (b) term and (c) infants by (i) local health authority and (ii) clinical commissioning group in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171619","171619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16812","2013-10-18","Wales Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the economic impact of the closure of the Severn tunnel on the Rugby League World Cup opening ceremony and the World Music Expo in Cardiff during the weekend of 26 and 27 October 2013.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171630","171630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16813","2013-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Tempora and Prism programmes are conducted under statutory authority.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171637","171637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16814","2013-10-18","HM Treasury","2013-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the cost of solar farms financed under the Enterprise Investment Scheme.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171655","171655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16815","2013-10-18","HM Treasury","2013-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many applications he has received for the financing of solar farms under the Enterprise Investment Scheme to date.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171664","171664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16816","2013-10-18","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the likely benefits to tourism in Northern Ireland as a result of the 2013 World Police and Fire Games.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171673","171673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16817","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times the UK has sent a request to another EU member state regarding asset identification, tracing, freezing or seizing and confiscation that was processed in accordance with Article 4 of Council Framework Decision 2001/500/JHA in each of the last five years; and on how many of these occasions the UK request was fulfilled.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171678","171678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16818","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many exchanges of information involving the UK have taken place in each of the last five years owing to Council Decision 2002/956/JHA, as amended; and how many of these exchanges have included operational information on the protection of a UK public figure or a public figure in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171687","171687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16819","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether other EU member states have implemented recommendations made to them as a result of the evaluation process established by Council Decision 2002/996/JHA.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171694","171694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16820","2013-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2013, Official Report, column 510W, on Richard III, with which organisations and individuals he has met, consulted or corresponded about the licence to dig for the human remains of King Richard III or on any other matter connected with the remains of King Richard III since they were discovered; when any such meeting was and any such correspondence received; and if he will place copies of all correspondence and an account of each such meeting in the Library.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171644","171644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16821","2013-10-18","Prime Minister","2013-10-16","To ask the Prime Minister, who will accompany him on the delegation to the forthcoming Commonwealth Heads of Government meeting in Colombo, Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171709","171709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16822","2013-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he will make an assessment of the effect of the Planning Practice Guidance for Renewable and Low Carbon Energy issued by his Department on (a) the number of wind turbine application appeals sent to the Inspectorate and (b) the number of refusals overturned by the Inspectorate citing the above guidance.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171711","171711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16823","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government intends to continue the co-operation with other EU Member States currently undertaken as a result of Council Decision 2002/956/JHA if the UK ceases to be bound by that Council Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; and what estimate she has made of the approximate cost to UK public funds of making arrangements for continuing such exchanges.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171690","171690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16824","2013-10-18","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many meetings Ministers in her Department have had with the Chief Constable of the Police Service of Northern Ireland since September 2012.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171731","171731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16825","2013-10-18","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many meetings she has had with (a) the Parades Commission and (b) individual members of the Parades Commission in 2013 to date.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171733","171733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16826","2013-10-18","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many meetings she has had with Richard Haass or members of his staff since his appointment as Chair of round table talks in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171722","171722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16827","2013-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the ability of the helmet mounted display for the Joint Strike Fighter to (a) match the acuity of the human eye and (b) enable the pilot to view directly behind them during flight.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171725","171725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16828","2013-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Watchkeeper unmanned aerial vehicle will receive a full release to service; and if he will estimate how much has been spent on the programme to date.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171727","171727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16829","2013-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will ensure that the UK's Mid-Term Report (Universal Periodic Review) to the UN Human Rights Council includes British Indian Ocean Territory.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171729","171729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16830","2013-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the government of the United Arab Emirates on extending the amnesty for Emirati citizens from prosecution over bounced cheques to expatriate UK citizens.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171730","171730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16831","2013-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to allow claimants to study further education courses which are designated as full-time whilst still actively seeking employment.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171754","171754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16832","2013-10-18","Home Office","2013-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times UK authorities have (a) provided information to and (b) received information from authorities of one or more other EU member states as a result of Articles 4 and 5 of Council Decision 2004/919/EC in each of the last five years; and what action (i) authorities of other EU member states and (ii) UK authorities took on the basis of information received in each case.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 171771","171771"
