"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62390","2014-06-19","Department for Transport","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the EU Roadworthiness Directive on the owners of historic vehicles in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201102","201102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62392","2014-06-19","Department for Transport","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received about deaths of young people in traffic accidents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200666","200666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62393","2014-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants for personal independence payments who require a home consultation have waited longer than (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four, (e) five and (f) six or more months for such a consultation.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201021","201021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62394","2014-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases in Bradford are awaiting mandatory reconsideration of employment and support allowance decisions.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201009","201009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62395","2014-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what additional resources his Department is making available to reduce the time taken to process requests for mandatory reconsideration of employment and support allowance decisions in West Yorkshire.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201010","201010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62396","2014-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases in Bradford are (a) pending and (b) being processed through his Department's mandatory reconsideration mechanism.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201011","201011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62397","2014-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's key performance indicators are for decisions that require mandatory reconsideration.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201012","201012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62398","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time to process a personal independence payment claim has been in each month since it was introduced.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200972","200972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62399","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to improve the personal independence claims and decision making process.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200976","200976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62400","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many refused claims for personal independence payment have (a) been appealed and (b) been successfully appealed to date.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200966","200966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62401","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims for personal independence payment have been refused to date.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200968","200968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62402","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims have been submitted for personal independence payment in each month since its introduction.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200969","200969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62403","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants in Preston constituency are being sanctioned for (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201101","201101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62404","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are enrolled in National Employment Savings Trust (NEST); how many such people enrolled in NEST are making additional payments by direct debit each month; and what the average additional contribution by direct debit each month is.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201100","201100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62405","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on external legal advice in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201098","201098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62406","2014-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he expects EU funding allocated to the Youth Guarantee to be drawn down in the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201125","201125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62407","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which jobcentres (a) do and (b) do not have wifi access for jobseekers to use.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201099","201099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62408","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been paid in consolatory payments for claimants in (a) Preston and (b) the rest of the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201097","201097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62409","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) Nottingham, have been sanctioned in the last (i) six and (ii) 12 months.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201079","201079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62410","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy that reminders should be sent by text or other telephonic means informing people of the date, time and location of their upcoming work capability assessments.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201091","201091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62411","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much is paid out in tax relief each month for savers within the National Employment Savings Trust; and what the average amount paid out in tax relief has been to a scheme member in each month.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201126","201126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62412","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are claiming (a) disability living allowance and (b) personal independence payment following an adverse effect to a medical procedure.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200656","200656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62413","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that personal independence payment applicants do not suffer financial hardship due to delays deciding their claims.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200657","200657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62414","2014-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment he has made of the average waiting time for claimants of the personal independence payment who require a home consultation in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201022","201022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62415","2014-06-19","Cabinet Office","2014-06-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many employed people worked from home in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201033","201033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62416","2014-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many officials have acted as Senior Responsible Officer for the Universal Credit project since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201073","201073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62417","2014-06-23","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) appeals and (b) successful appeals against Atos assessments in (i) Nottingham and (ii) Ashfield constituency there were in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201074","201074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62418","2014-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of employment opportunities resulting from the Commonwealth Games; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201060","201060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62419","2014-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on ensuring that people claiming benefits receive medical treatment that has been identified as enabling them to return to work; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201057","201057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62420","2014-06-23","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-17","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, with reference to the Cabinet Manual, paragraph 5.38, whether the convention that the House of Commons should have an advance opportunity to debate significant military action applies to the deployment of unmanned aerial vehicles outside Afghanistan when operated from RAF Waddington.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201155","201155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62421","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many remote sites are available and in use by child victims and witnesses in (a) each region of England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland and (d) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201140","201140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62422","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many registered intermediaries are available for use by child victims and witnesses in (a) Bolton, (b) Lancashire, (c) England, (d) Scotland and (e) Wales.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201141","201141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62423","2014-06-19","Home Office","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many sexual abuse cases involving children there have been in (a) Bolton, (b) Lancashire, (c) England, (d) Scotland and (e) Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201142","201142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62424","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many child victims and witnesses involved in sexual  abuse cases have been given access to and use of a Registered Intermediary in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201143","201143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62425","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans his Department has to increase the number of Registered Intermediaries available for use by child victims and witnesses of sexual abuse; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 201144","201144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62754","2014-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the level of youth unemployment in (a) the UK and (b) Bournemouth East constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904366","904366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62832","2014-06-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received on steps to encourage more firms to offer apprenticeships for the long term unemployed.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904373","904373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63016","2014-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made on improving the employment and support allowance appeals process.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904380","904380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61946","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the value of exports from businesses in (a) Glasgow North West constituency, (b) Glasgow and (c) Scotland to other EU member states in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200757","200757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61947","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what visits Ministers in his Department made to Australia in the last year; what the primary purpose was of those visits; and who accompanied them on those visits.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200759","200759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61948","2014-06-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of foundation degree students continued to a honours degree in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200809","200809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61949","2014-06-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of foundation degrees have been delivered by (a) further education colleges and (b) universities in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200811","200811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61950","2014-06-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students have (a) started and (b) completed a foundation degree in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200812","200812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61951","2014-06-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, (a) how many higher national diplomas and (b) higher national certificates have been completed in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200814","200814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61952","2014-06-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in Warrington North constituency received funding from the Regional Growth Fund in each year since 2011-12; and how much each such business received.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200829","200829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61953","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the written statement of 16 June 2014, Official Report, columns 70-1WS, on student support in England, how many of the students who were unable to or chose not to provide adequate evidence of residency were studying at an alternative provider with designated courses; at which provider they were studying; for what qualifications they were registered; and on what basis his Department calculated that £65 million was due to be paid to 1,333 students.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200842","200842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61954","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many meetings he has had with his Department's Chief Scientific Adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200784","200784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61955","2014-06-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the Offshore Wind Industry Council last met; and what meetings of the Council have taken place since 16 May 2013.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200863","200863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61956","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many meetings the Minister of State for (a) Business and Enterprise, (b) Universities, Science and Skills and (c) Skills and Enterprise has had with his Department's Chief Scientific Adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200796","200796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61957","2014-06-18","Department for Education","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to increase the proportion of girls taking separate science at GCSE.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200798","200798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61958","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress his Department has made on increasing the number of women in engineering roles.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200799","200799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61959","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of levels of public expenditure on science on UK economic productivity figures.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200800","200800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61960","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many complaints the Government has received on the England and Wales personal insolvency regime in relation to (a) bankruptcy, (b) individual voluntary arrangements and (c) debt relief orders in each year since 2010; and what the nature was of such complaints.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200891","200891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61961","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when his Department's review of debt relief orders will be launched.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200892","200892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61962","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will review the level of the debt threshold for a creditor bankruptcy petition.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200896","200896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61963","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward proposals to give employers the choice of (a) having either a direct Government contract for apprenticeships and (b) accessing funding support through their chosen training provider.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200877","200877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61964","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people are in receipt of disabled students' allowance in (a) the North West, (b) Warrington and (c) Warrington North constituency.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200880","200880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61965","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what (a) capital and (b) revenue funding his Department has allocated to research (i) projects and (ii) facilities, excluding quality-related research funding distributed via the funding councils and awards made by the research councils, in each financial year from 2010-11; to which organisations and for what period such allocations have been made; how the outcomes of such funding will be assessed; and which organisations will undertake those assessments.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200883","200883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61966","2014-06-19","Cabinet Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of people over 50 had been out of work for over a year in each year since 1994.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200922","200922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61967","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of jobseekers excluded from the claimant count because their benefit has been sanctioned; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200930","200930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61968","2014-06-19","Cabinet Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people from in Warrington North constituency were employed on temporary or fixed term contracts in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200918","200918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61969","2014-06-18","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-16","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what costs have been incurred under each cost heading for the production and postage of anti-Scottish independence pamphlets to be sent to every home in Scotland.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200770","200770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61970","2014-06-18","Cabinet Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of potential savings to the public purse from the Shared Services Connected Ltd venture.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200758","200758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61971","2014-06-18","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-16","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what discussions he has had with charities on implementation of the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act 2014 since that act received Royal Assent.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200761","200761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61972","2014-06-18","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-16","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how much has been spent under each cost heading by the Government in relation to the Scottish independence referendum.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200772","200772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61973","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are employed in the HM Revenue and Customs national minimum wage enforcement team based in Belfast; and how many complaints have been reeived by the Pay and Work Rights helpline relating to Northern Ireland-based employers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200738","200738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61974","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps HM Revenue and Customs has taken to to tackle the problem of employees being paid below the minimum wage in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200743","200743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61975","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 1 April 2014, Official Report, column 625W, on coinage, whether he has fixed the dates for the public consultation on the impact of the introduction of a new one pound coin.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200779","200779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61976","2014-06-19","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the average annual cost of childcare in the UK for a child aged (a) two and under, (b) three to four and (c) five and over in each year since 2009-10; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200802","200802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61977","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date the Private Finance Initiative contract between HM Revenue and Customs and Mapeley Steps Contractor Limited was entered into.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200801","200801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61978","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects Network Rail to be officially re-classified as a public sector company.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200861","200861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61979","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings he has had with his Department's Chief Scientific Adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200794","200794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61980","2014-06-19","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) HM Revenue and Customs and (b) National Savings and Investments staff will be employed administering tax-free childcare in (i) 2015-16, (ii) 2016-17, (iii) 2017-18 and (iv) 2018-19.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200822","200822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61981","2014-06-19","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what performance indicators he has agreed with National Savings and Investments (NS&I) on the delivery of tax-free childcare; how often NS&I will be benchmarked against such indicators; how often the results of this benchmarking will be made available; what penalties have been agreed for poor performance against these indicators; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200821","200821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61982","2014-06-19","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost was of the report entitled, Evaluating alternative market models for Tax-Free Childcare vouchers, prepared by Economic Insight for his Department; what assessment he made of this report's findings and recommendations; and whether these recommendations informed the operation and design of his Department's policy on tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200823","200823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61983","2014-06-19","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support his Department will give childcare provides on the introduction of tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200936","200936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61984","2014-06-19","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish any cost benefit analysis of awarding the contract for the tax-free childcare scheme to National Savings & Investments undertaken before the decision was announced.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200937","200937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61985","2014-06-19","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Glasgow North constituency have used the Help to Buy mortgage guarantee scheme to date.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200923","200923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61986","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many times HM Revenue and Customs has met with (a) the Ministry of Justice and (b) the Insolvency Service to discuss the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 reforms to insolvency litigation on creditors since 2012.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200898","200898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61987","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints have been made about HM Revenue and Customs in each of the last five years; and how many such complaints related to mistakes in calculated tax liability.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200897","200897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61988","2014-06-19","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, in what capacity he and the Secretary of State for International Development attended the recent Bilderberg Conference in Copenhagen; and whether the visits have been recorded in the register of interests.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200959","200959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61989","2014-06-19","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the next dataset of bank lending by postcode from the major UK banks will be released; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200964","200964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61990","2014-06-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to bring empty (a) residential and (b) commercial properties back into use.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200781","200781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61991","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment has been made of the likely effects of the Government's proposed Deregulation Bill on jobs in tourism.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200855","200855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61992","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many electronic workstations were made available in each public library per thousand population in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200866","200866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61993","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much lottery funding and from which year is being committed to Arts Council England's national portfolio organisations and national partner museums as part of their overall settlement for the period 2015 to 2018.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200859","200859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61994","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of public libraries replenished their full lending stock within eight and a half years in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200867","200867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61995","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much was made available for purchasing public library items in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200868","200868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61996","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many visits per thousand of the population were made to each public library's website in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200869","200869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61997","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which Arts Council England strategic programmes are designed specifically to address the National Lottery directions issued in 2007.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200884","200884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61998","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of public libraries open for more than 10 hours a week provided access to online catalogues in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200890","200890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61999","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether National Public Library user surveys are still being taken.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200889","200889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62000","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of public libraries with a catchment area of more than 40,000 resident population were open at least 45 hours per week in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200888","200888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62001","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what Arts Council England strategic funding programmes funded from the National Lottery are designed wholly or primarily to benefit national portfolio organisations and national partner museums.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200885","200885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62002","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, for what proportion of time public library service points were unavailable to visitors because of (a) emergency closures and (b) missed or cancelled mobile library stops in each of the years (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200873","200873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62003","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many public libraries were open at least five hours per week outside 9am to 5pm on weekdays in each of the years (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200872","200872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62004","2014-06-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve care for veterans suffering  with psychological injuries after their service.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200935","200935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62005","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the deviations or exemptions from the Military Air Systems Certification Process that allowed the inaugural flight of the Rivet Joint aircraft on May 27 2014 were the final form that will be used for all operations.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200906","200906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62006","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what event or risk of event led to the approval of the Collision Warning Technology Demonstrator Programme for fast jet aircraft; when that event was identified; and where that event is recorded.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200907","200907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62007","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of whether arrangements for defence nuclear co-operations which were agreed at the UK-France summit in January 2014 summit comply with the (a) Comprehensive Nuclear-Test Ban Treaty, (b) Treaty on the Non-Proliferation of Nuclear Weapons and (c) other aspects of international law; and if he will place in the Library a copy of any such assessments.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200908","200908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62008","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the value of purchasing AM-aluminium matting for landing pads for the JSF 35B.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200909","200909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62009","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total cost was of the Nimrod MR4A programme; and what payments were made to each company involved in the programme after 20 October 2012.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200910","200910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62010","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the completion date is for refurbishment of existing hydrodynamics research facilities at the Atomic Weapons Establishment Aldermaston; what the cost is of the refurbishment; and what the expected lifetime is of the new facilities.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200911","200911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62011","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which personnel aboard Queen Elizabeth Class aircraft carriers will need to wear active noise cancellation headsets; how many such headsets will be required; and what the cost of such headsets will be.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200914","200914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62012","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library copies of agreements with the French government to (a) undertake joint research at the Atomic Weapons Establishment Orion and Commissariat à l'Énergie Atomique Laser Megajoule, (b) allow use of hydrodynamics research facility at the Atomic Weapons Establishment and (c) peer review technical and scientific data underpinning nuclear warhead certification.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200912","200912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62013","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what risk assessment he has made of the safety of aircraft handlers and maintenance personnel due to the noise produced by the Joint Strike Fighter.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200915","200915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62014","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the final investment approval for Project Teutates.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200913","200913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62015","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) actual and (b) simulated flight hours pilots need to adjust from a fast jet with a heads-up-display to one with only a helmet mounted display.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200916","200916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62016","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the loudest decibel levels are that are produced by JSF 35B during operations aboard an aircraft carrier.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200899","200899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62017","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when HMS Ocean will be declared fit to deploy; and when she will depart on Exercise Cougar 14.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200900","200900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62018","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the total cost of disposal of Nimrod MR4A associated material at RAF Kinloss.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200901","200901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62019","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the near cash projected spending on the Equipment Plan and Equipment Support Plan is for each year to 2018.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200902","200902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62020","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what deviations or exemptions from the Military Air Systems Certifications Process were made for the Airseeker aircraft; when those deviations or exemptions were made; and who authorised each such deviation or exemption.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200905","200905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62021","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assets his Department has sold and leased back over the last 12 months; what the sale price was of each asset so sold; and what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of leasing back each such asset over the period of the lease.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200903","200903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62022","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) precision-guided munitions and (b) gravity bombs of each type have been dropped in Afghanistan by British (i) fixed-wing aircraft and (ii) unmanned aerial vehicles since 23 March 2011.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200904","200904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62023","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many meetings he has had with his Department's Chief Scientific Adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200785","200785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62024","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department owns any of the Filton Airfield site; and whether his Department will be entitled to any share of the site's sale.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200771","200771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62025","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what capabilities are currently being utilised to fulfil the role that would otherwise have been undertaken by Nimrod MRA4 aircraft; and what captabilities will fulfil that role in the long term.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200749","200749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62026","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place a copy of 2014DIN07-082 on 2014/2015 Defence Cyber Practitioner Courses in the Library.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200739","200739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62027","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place a copy of 2014DIN07-081 on Physical Training Policy For Army Reserve And Full Time Reserve Service in the Library.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200740","200740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62028","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place a copy of 2014DIN05-013 on The Closure of Ministry of Defence Hospital Unit Peterborough in the Library.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200741","200741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62029","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place a copy of 2014DIN05-012 on JSP 441 - The Defence Records Management Policy and Procedures: Publication of Version 4:3 in the Library.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200742","200742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62030","2014-06-18","Department for Education","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to publish the terms of reference for its review of the resolution of disagreements for people with education, health and care needs under the Children and Families Act 2014.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200755","200755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62031","2014-06-18","Department for Education","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers took early retirement in (a) Bury St Edmunds constituency, (b) Suffolk and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200744","200744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62032","2014-06-18","Department for Education","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department's review of arrangements for complaints and redress for people with education, health and care needs under the Children and Families Act 2014 will commence.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200762","200762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62033","2014-06-18","Department for Education","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to publish further details of its review of resolution of disagreements for people with education, health and care needs under the Children and Families Act 2014.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200764","200764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62034","2014-06-18","Department for Education","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many meetings he has had with his Department's Chief Scientific Adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200786","200786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62035","2014-06-18","Department for Education","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) feasibility and (b) cost to the public purse of enabling supply teachers to contribute to the teachers' pension scheme.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200849","200849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62036","2014-06-23","Department for Education","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which free schools have been approved in each local education authority area excluding London since 2010; and which such schools are (a) non-denominational and (b) of each religious denomination.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200839","200839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62037","2014-06-19","Department for Education","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of school closure for local elections on parents and children.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200820","200820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62038","2014-06-18","Department for Education","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department will publish further information on pilots testing the role of the Special Educational Needs and Disability Tribunal in making recommendations on the health and social care aspects of Education, Health and Care Plans.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200840","200840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62039","2014-06-18","Department for Education","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what research has been undertaken by or on behalf of his Department into the potential (a) benefits and (b) disbenefits to children of further delegation of children's social care functions.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200876","200876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62040","2014-06-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the timetable is for the next periodic safety review of each of the UK's nuclear power stations; whether an environmental impact assessment is required as part of the periodic safety review procedure; and what opportunities exist for public involvement in such reviews.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200777","200777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62041","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects to complete the loan guarantee arrangement for the proposed nuclear power station investments.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200778","200778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62042","2014-06-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the efficacy of the published acceptable limits for formaldehyde in the air within a domestic dwelling.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200819","200819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62043","2014-06-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many meetings he has had with his Department's Chief Scientific Adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200787","200787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62044","2014-06-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the planned further research into the use of carbon monoxide as a potential method of culling badgers will include (a) trials on living badgers, (b) trials on existing badger setts and (c) laboratory trials.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200931","200931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62045","2014-06-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the annual income from the carrier bag levy in the four years from October 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200882","200882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62046","2014-06-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to prevent illegally-harvested timber and endangered hardwoods being imported into the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200944","200944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62047","2014-06-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department issues on types of timber it discourages from being imported to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200945","200945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62048","2014-06-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress made by the President of Iran towards granting greater civil rights to religious minorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200881","200881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62049","2014-06-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent correspondence his Department has received from UK citizens living in Italy on delays in passport renewal; whether all such letters were acknowledged; and for what reasons any such letter has not yet been acknowledged.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200963","200963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62050","2014-06-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the UK has made to Israel following the Israeli parliament's consideration of legislation to allow force-feeding of Palestinian administrative detainees on hunger strike.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200934","200934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62051","2014-06-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of (a) Farshid Fathi, (b) Behnam Irani, (c) Silas Rabbani, (d) Amin Khaki, (e) Saeed Abedini and (f) other pastors and deacons imprisoned in Iran being beaten in prison.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200929","200929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62052","2014-06-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which UN peacekeeping missions established since 1990 do not have a human rights mandate.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200874","200874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62053","2014-06-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many meetings he has had with his Department's Chief Scientific Adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200788","200788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62054","2014-06-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department have had with their (i) Indian and (ii) Pakistani counterparts on the increase of trade and transit between the two countries.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200751","200751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62055","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of running and administering the (a) West Suffolk Clinical Commissioning Group and (b) East Suffolk Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200776","200776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62056","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many meetings he has had with his Department's Chief Scientific Adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200789","200789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62057","2014-06-19","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients who were referred by GPs for tests for suspected cancers at (a) Lewisham Hospital, (b) Queen Elizabeth Hospital Woolwich, (c) Guys and St Thomas' Hospital and (d) Kings College Hospital were not seen within six weeks of referral in the last six months.","Biography information for Dame Joan Ruddock","Dame Joan Ruddock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200864","200864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62058","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what responsibilities NHS England has for commissioning breast cancer services.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200870","200870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62059","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what responsibilities clinical commissioning groups have for commissioning breast cancer services.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200871","200871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62060","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost per patient was of antiretroviral therapy for HIV in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200862","200862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62061","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what payments his Department has made to the devolved administrations as a consequence of rebates paid to it under the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200803","200803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62062","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure GPs are accessible to patients.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200858","200858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62063","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what definition his Department uses of an adequate amount of weekly physical activity.","Biography information for Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200783","200783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62064","2014-06-19","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many redundancy payments have been recovered from NHS staff who have been made redundant and subsequently re-employed by an NHS organisation in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200856","200856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62065","2014-06-19","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times ambulance response times in (a) the North West and (b) each ambulance service trust in England have exceeded (i) 15, (ii) 20, (iii) 30 and (iv) 60 minutes since May 2010.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200857","200857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62066","2014-06-19","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of how many non-clinical dementia specialist professionals are currently working across the health and care sector.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200824","200824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62067","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he has given to clinical commissioning groups on their involvement with (a) strategic clinical networks and (b) breast network site-specific groups.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200886","200886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62068","2014-06-19","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps he has taken to reduce child obesity in Barnsley.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200932","200932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62069","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he has given to clinical commissioning groups on the use of the NICE breast cancer quality standard when commissioning breast cancer services.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200887","200887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62070","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of reports that scientists at the University of Wisconsin-Madison have created a virus that closely resembles the 1918 Spanish flu strain; whether he has made an assessment of the potential threat to the UK population arising from that experiment; and whether the Government has made any representation to the US administration on this matter.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200875","200875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62071","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people received funding through the Cancer Drugs Fund in (a) Coventry North East constituency, (b) Coventry, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200879","200879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62072","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the average travelling distance to a 24-hour accident and emergency department for people in (a) Bury St Edmunds constituency, (b) Suffolk and (c) England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200878","200878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62073","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues on the ratio of GPs to patients; and what that ratio is in Tendring.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200939","200939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62074","2014-06-19","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on the integrated sexual health tariff.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200940","200940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62075","2014-06-19","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of sexual health services delivered by private providers.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200941","200941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62076","2014-06-19","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the sexual health commissioning toolkit will be published.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200942","200942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62077","2014-06-19","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish an update to A Framework for Sexual Health Improvement in England first published in March 2013.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200943","200943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62078","2014-06-19","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were working in his Department on sexual health matters in each year since 2010; and how many people have worked in (a) his Department and (b) Public Health England on sexual health matters since the formation of Public Health England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200949","200949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62079","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff were employed in the Passport Office in Belfast in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200956","200956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62080","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passports were processed by the Belfast Passport Office in each of the last five years; and what proportion of those passports were processed within three weeks.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200957","200957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62081","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that hospitals do not discourage whistleblowing by staff; and if he will take steps to issue a UK NHS-wide policy on that matter.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200954","200954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62082","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that ambulance crews and dispatch staff are able to access meaningful supervision; and if he will assess the merits of introducing rapid response units similar to those operating in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200955","200955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62083","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of Albumin Bound Paclitaxel, Bevacizumab and Cabozantinib since the introduction of those drugs; and what discussions on this matter he has had with his counterparts in the devolved Assemblies.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200953","200953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62084","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to train and recruit more GPs in (a) Linton and Walton and (b) nationally.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200958","200958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62085","2014-06-19","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests in the UK have resulted from Operation Rescue; how many charges were brought following those arrests; how many open investigations remain from those identified; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200938","200938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62086","2014-06-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if she will review the effectiveness of Part 8 of the Anti-Social Behaviour Act 2003; and if she will bring forward legislative proposals to extend the scope of these provisions to include complaints on high hedges.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200895","200895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62087","2014-06-19","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the TecSOS system for high risk victims of domestic abuse; and what plans she has to rollout the programme to other areas of the country.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200933","200933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62088","2014-06-19","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs on the processing of passport applications from abroad since 1 January 2014.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200813","200813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62089","2014-06-23","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with the National Farmers' union on the details of the injunction relating to protestor activities around the  badger culls scheduled to take place in Gloucestershire and Somerset in 2014.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200838","200838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62090","2014-06-19","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the current anticipated turn-round time for passport processing is for (a) applications from UK residents making new applications, (b) new applications for a child's passport and (c) UK residents applying abroad.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200815","200815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62091","2014-06-19","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much in overtime costs has been spent in HM Passport Office in each month of 2014.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200816","200816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62092","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many drink-driving offences were recorded in (a) Bury St Edmunds, (b) Suffolk and (c) England and Wales in each of the last five years; and how many successful prosecutions for such offences there have been.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200852","200852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62093","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many meetings she has had with her Department's Chief Scientific Adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200790","200790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62094","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of (a) adult and (b) child passport renewal applications were processed within the three-week service standard in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200841","200841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62095","2014-06-19","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to receive a reply to her letter to the Director General, UK Visas and Immigration, of 1 May 2014 on behalf of a constituent, CTS ref M5845/14.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200805","200805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62096","2014-06-19","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, from which other Departments temporary additional staff at the Passport Office have been deployed; and what training costs have arisen from such redeployment.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200810","200810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62097","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with representatives of the travel insurance industry regarding cancellations of holidays or business trips due to delays in processing passport applications.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200765","200765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62098","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests for information held on the National DNA Database were received by her Department from other countries in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200768","200768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62099","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of passport renewal applications have been upgraded from a standard application to the premium service in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200748","200748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62100","2014-06-19","House of Commons Commission","2014-06-16","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, who determined the terms of the advertisement seeking applications for the post of Clerk of the House and Chief Executive.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200927","200927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62101","2014-06-19","House of Commons Commission","2014-06-16","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what the composition will be of the selection committee for the appointment of the next Clerk of the House and Chief Executive; and what the composition was of the equivalent committee when the present postholder was appointed.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200928","200928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62102","2014-06-19","House of Commons Commission","2014-06-16","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, whether the next Clerk of the House and Chief Executive will be subject to security vetting if he or she is appointed from outside the House service or Civil Service; and whether he or she will be subject to a confirmation hearing before a select committee.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200924","200924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62103","2014-06-19","House of Commons Commission","2014-06-16","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, whether a tender was issued for the use of head-hunters to find candidates for the post of Clerk of the House and Chief Executive.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200925","200925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62104","2014-06-19","House of Commons Commission","2014-06-16","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what assessment will be made, prior to the appointment of the next Clerk of the House and Chief Executive, of each candidate's knowledge of and expertise on procedural and constitutional issues.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200926","200926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62105","2014-06-19","House of Commons Commission","2014-06-16","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, if the Commission will incorporate into commemorations of the 800th Anniversary of the Magna Carta commemoration of the Peasants' Revolt of 1381 and the Putney debates in 1647 on how the country should be ruled.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200965","200965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62106","2014-06-18","Department for International Development","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the post-2015 development framework includes a sustainable development goal on water and sanitation that includes universal access to sanitation by 2030.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200860","200860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62107","2014-06-18","Department for International Development","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many meetings she has had with her Department's Chief Scientific Adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200791","200791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62108","2014-06-18","Department for International Development","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what programmes and projects her Department funds which aim to promote trade and transit between India and Pakistan.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200747","200747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62109","2014-06-18","Department for International Development","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what (a) unilateral, (b) bilateral and (c) multilateral projects her Department is sponsoring in Kashmir.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200750","200750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62110","2014-06-18","Department for International Development","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether Ministers from the devolved administrations have been invited to the Girl Summit co-hosted by the Prime Minister and UNICEF on 22 July 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200766","200766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62111","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department collects data on the number and success rate of Aarhus claims made in England and Wales since 1 April 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200769","200769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62112","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether a full range of sanitary products is provided free-of-charge to female prisoners.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200773","200773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62113","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which types and brands of sanitary products female prisoners may purchase from the National Product List; and at what cost.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200774","200774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62114","2014-06-18","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-16","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how many schools in England and Wales were closed for the local and European elections on 22 May 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200775","200775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62115","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many applications for Judicial Review in England and Wales the defendant has successfully challenged the claim as an Aarhus claim since 1 April 2013.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200808","200808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62116","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Aarhus claims in England and Wales have been successful for the claimant since 1 April 2013.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200806","200806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62117","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Aarhus claims in England and Wales have been granted permission to proceed since 1 April 2013.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200807","200807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62118","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what average length of time was taken by the Tribunals Service to administer a First-tier Tribunal Social Security and Child Support appeal in respect of (a) disability living allowance, (b) employment and support allowance, (c) income support, (d) jobseeker's allowance and (e) tax credits in (i) Coverntry, (ii) the West Midlands and (iii) England in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200752","200752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62119","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of appeals to the Tribunals Service from appellants in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England relating to (i) disability living allowance, (ii) employment and support allowance, (iii) income support, (iv) jobseeker's allowance and (v) tax credits were successful in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200753","200753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62120","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners are being held in police cells; what the daily cost is of holding such prisoners; and how many prisoners were held in police cells in (a) Bury St Edmunds constituency, (b) Suffolk and (c) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200745","200745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62121","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many meetings he has had with his Department's Chief Scientific Adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200792","200792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62122","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of prisoners are classed as unemployed in each prison in England and Wales.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200833","200833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62123","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number was of hours per week spent working by prisoners in each prison in England and Wales in (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2013-14.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200831","200831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62124","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week of purposeful activity was undertaken by offenders in each security category in (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2013-14.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200830","200830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62125","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions the Royal Prerogative of Mercy has been granted in relation to offences occurring as a result and in the course of escaping from or breaking out of prison in the last 25 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200853","200853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62126","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week were spent in cells by prisoners by (a) per week day and (b) per weekend day by security category of prisoner, in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200832","200832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62127","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what decisions he has made about the future of HMP Wellingborough.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200827","200827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62128","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for judicial review in England and Wales made since 1 April 2013 have been identified on Claim Form N461 as Aarhus Convention claims.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200817","200817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62129","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will meet the hon. Member for Wellingborough to discuss HMP Wellingborough.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200825","200825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62130","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will re-open HMP Wellingborough to increase prison capacity.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200826","200826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62131","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for employment tribunal fee remission were (a) received, (b) granted and (c) refused between 1 January and 31 March 2014; and how many such refusals were successfully appealed.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200818","200818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62132","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 13 May 2014, Official Report, column 494W, on prisons: mobile telephones, when data on mobile telephones seized in prisons in 2013 will be made available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200962","200962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62133","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what average time was left to be served on a sentence for prisoners serving (a) determinate, (b) indeterminate, (c) life and (d) all sentences moved from closed to open conditions within the prison estate in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200961","200961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62134","2014-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners serving sentences in open conditions have previously absconded for their current or previous establishments (a) once, (b) twice, (c) three times and (d) four or more times.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200960","200960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62135","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations he has had on including insolvency litigation in the scope of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200893","200893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62136","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of prisoners in each prison in England and Wales are willing and able to work but cannot do so as a result of a lack of available vacancies in their prison establishment.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200797","200797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62137","2014-06-19","Attorney General","2014-06-16","To ask the Attorney General, what recent steps his Department has taken to increase the number of rape convictions.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200919","200919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62138","2014-06-18","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps her Department has taken to ensure further opportunities for Northern Ireland's film industry are secured.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200952","200952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62139","2014-06-18","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that local colleges train the people of Northern Ireland with the appropriate skills to enable further growth in film and television production in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200950","200950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62140","2014-06-18","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps her Department is taking to promote Northern Ireland's natural beauty to boost its tourism.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200951","200951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62141","2014-06-18","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, who the beneficiaries in Northern Ireland of the Royal Prerogative of Mercy granted by means of a Warrant under the Royal Sign Manual were in the last 25 years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200854","200854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62142","2014-06-19","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many (a) permanent and (b) non-permanent staff were employed in her Department on 1 June 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200836","200836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62143","2014-06-19","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether she plans to attend the International Festival for Business in Liverpool.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200837","200837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62144","2014-06-19","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, where and for what purpose she held her meeting with the Northern Ireland Minister for Social Development on 8 May 2014; and what the duration was of that meeting.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200835","200835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62145","2014-06-19","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what topics were discussed at her meeting with the Northern Ireland Minister for Social Development on 8 May 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200834","200834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62146","2014-06-19","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when she last met the Chief Executive of UK Trade & Investment to discuss that organisation's role in attracting inward investment to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200804","200804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62147","2014-06-18","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she is taking to support the progress of the First World War legacy project in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200782","200782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62148","2014-06-18","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with her ministerial colleagues at the Foreign and Commonwealth Office on how the UK's overseas posts may be used more effectively to promote Northern Ireland trade and investment.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200760","200760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62149","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has put in place to commemorate the 600th anniversary of the Battles of Harfleur and Agincourt.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200865","200865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62150","2014-06-18","Scotland Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent estimate he has made of the level of investment in (a) Glasgow North West constituency, (b) Glasgow and (c) Scotland that resulted from EU membership in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200767","200767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62151","2014-06-18","Scotland Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent assessment he has made of the effects of membership of the EU on jobs in (a) Glasgow North West constituency, (b) Glasgow and (c) Scotland.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200756","200756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62152","2014-06-19","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-16","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what the total cost was of production and delivery of the booklet, What staying in the United Kingdom means for Scotland; and what proportion of such costs relate to (a) research, verification and co-ordination, (b) writing, editing, sub-editing and proofing of the text, (c) photography, design, artwork and licensing, (d) printing, (e) distribution and delivery and (f) related communications, administration and public affairs support.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200946","200946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62153","2014-06-19","Scotland Office","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the total costs incurred (a) in his Department and (b) in the Government of the creation and production of the booklet, What staying in the United Kingdom means for Scotland.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200947","200947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62154","2014-06-19","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-16","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what estimate he has made of the charges made by external (a) public affairs consultants, (b) creative agencies and (c) printing, logistics and delivery companies for work relating to the production of the booklet, What staying in the United Kingdom means for Scotland.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200948","200948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62155","2014-06-18","Department for Transport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of projected ticket prices for rail passengers using the High Speed 2 rail line.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200848","200848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62156","2014-06-18","Department for Transport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many meetings he has had with his Department's Chief Scientific Adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200793","200793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62157","2014-06-18","Department for Transport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to publish information on ticket pricing for High Speed 2.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200851","200851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62158","2014-06-18","Department for Transport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he expects High Speed 2 will require a separate ticket pricing structure from regular rail services.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200850","200850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62159","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency who have submitted a claim for personal independence payment have been waiting more than (a) six months and (b) three months for a medical assessment.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200828","200828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62160","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that asylum seekers are able to receive a National Insurance number without unnecessary delay.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200843","200843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62161","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of changes in the number of interpreters available at Middlesbrough Jobcentre in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200844","200844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62162","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many meetings he has had with his Department's Chief Scientific Adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200795","200795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62163","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to ensure that asylum seekers receive the benefits to which they are entitled.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200845","200845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62164","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to ensure that the centralisation in Newcastle of national insurance services for the North East does not have a negative effect on service for users.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200846","200846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62165","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason Newcastle was chosen as the National Insurance centre for residents of Middlesbrough; and what effect this choice is having on service provision.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200847","200847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62166","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with Glasgow City Council on the Glasgow Guarantee.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200754","200754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62167","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the number of (a) new national insurance numbers registered and (b) new workers in (i) Bury St Edmunds constituency, (ii) Suffolk and (iii) England and Wales in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200746","200746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62168","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to publicise information on changes to child maintenance.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200763","200763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62169","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the additional costs to claimants living in rural communities of travel to attend jobcentre interviews for (a) fortnightly signing and (b) other interviews and advisory meetings.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200780","200780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62170","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many youth contract wage incentives he estimates will be taken up by April 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200921","200921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62171","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to improve support for people over 50 provided through the Work Programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200920","200920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62172","2014-06-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people for each jobcentre plus vacancy were claiming out-of-work benefits in Warrington North constituency in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200917","200917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62173","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on the freezing of state pensions for those living overseas.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200894","200894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62268","2014-06-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the UK's security of energy supply.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904346","904346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62391","2014-06-19","Department for Transport","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will work with the Department for Communities and Local Government, the Cabinet Office, the Northamptonshire and South East Midlands LEPs and local authorities to help secure funding for a new junction 10A on the A14 which is required to facilitate the creation of a 60MW renewable energy park and low carbon business park between Burton Latimer and Kettering.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904342","904342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62633","2014-06-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households with a below-average income have received support for comprehensive insulation of their homes in the last year.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904340","904340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61852","2014-06-17","HM Treasury","2014-06-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding of the Financial Ombudsman Service came directly from the levy on the Office of Fair Trading licences on consumer credit firms in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013; how this funding will be levied in future; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200700","200700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61853","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he had on human rights during his recent visit to China.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200693","200693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61854","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the decision was taken that National Savings and Investments would be responsible for the delivery of tax-free childcare; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200714","200714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61855","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department had with representatives of National Savings and Investments in (i) August 2013, (ii) September 2013, (iii) October 2013, (iv) November 2013, (v) December 2013, (vi) January 2014, (vii) February 2014 and (viii) March 2014.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200703","200703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61856","2014-06-17","HM Treasury","2014-06-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the expected increase in the fees and levies on regulated consumer credit firms that will go towards the funding of the Money Advice Service and Financial Ombudsman Service in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017 under the new Financial Conduct Authority regulated fees and levies regime.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200701","200701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61857","2014-06-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the number of households with children in the private rented sector in England.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200690","200690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61858","2014-06-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of brownfield land in England is covered by a Local Development Order.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200691","200691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61859","2014-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2014, Official Report, column 142W, on embassies: Iran, what the estimated monetary value is of each of the works of art cited in that answer which is owned by the Government Art Collection.","Biography information for Michael Ellis","Michael Ellis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200716","200716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61860","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which charitable projects in Scotland have received funding from the Armed Forces Covenant (LIBOR) Fund to date.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200726","200726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61861","2014-06-18","Department for Education","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Phonic Screening Check.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200732","200732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61862","2014-06-18","Department for Education","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Government plans to evaluate the introduction of the Phonic Screening Check and take a decision on its continuation.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200733","200733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61863","2014-06-18","Department for Education","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the information considered by his Department ahead of making the decision to introduce the Phonic Screening Check.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200734","200734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61864","2014-06-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Scottish Government regarding environmental and economic effects of the restoration of former open cast sites in East Ayrshire.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200725","200725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61865","2014-06-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress he has made in providing funding to assist East Ayrshire Council with the restoration of former open-cast sites in East Ayrshire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200727","200727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61866","2014-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of community energy schemes that have not gone ahead due to the cost of securing a connection to the local grid; if he will make it his policy to (a) introduce standardised affordable grid connection charges for community energy schemes and (b) exempt community energy schemes from wider network upgrade costs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200681","200681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61867","2014-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding has been allocated to the Green Deal Home Improvement Fund for (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16, (c) 2016-17 and (d) all further years for which funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200682","200682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61868","2014-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding his Department has allocated to (a) solid wall insulation, (b) other energy efficiency and insulation measures from his Department's approved list and (c) refunds for Green Deal assessments under the Green Deal Home Improvement Fund in (i) 2014-15, (ii) 2015-16, (iii) 2016-17 and (iv) over the lifetime of the fund.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200684","200684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61869","2014-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding his Department has allocated to the Green Deal Home Improvement Fund for the lifetime of the programme.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200685","200685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61870","2014-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the number of households that will receive cashback under the Green Deal Home Improvement Fund in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16, (c) 2016-17 and (d) all further years for which funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200683","200683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61871","2014-06-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reason Sri Lanka has not been included as a priority country for the Preventing Sexual Violence Initiative.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200735","200735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61872","2014-06-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of prevalence of sexual violence in conflict in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200736","200736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61873","2014-06-17","Department of Health","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2014, Official Report, column 61W, on radiotherapy, what reports he has received of the reasons NHS England has paid for gamma knife treatment at University College Hospital London for a patient referred there from Plymouth Derriford Hospital by James Palmer, NHS England's Clinical Director of Specialised Commissioning.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200731","200731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61874","2014-06-17","Department of Health","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether guidance issued by Monitor is mandatory for NHS England to follow.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200737","200737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61875","2014-06-17","Department of Health","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, column 132W, on radiotherapy, what reports he has received on the reasons NHS England has paid for Gamma Knife treatment at University College Hospital London (UCHL) for a patient with an acoustic neuroma referred to UCHL from Bournemouth and Poole Hospital.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200728","200728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61876","2014-06-17","Department of Health","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the time and resources that clinicians spend on administering individual funding requests for treatments of Parkinson's disease and other progressive conditions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200677","200677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61877","2014-06-17","Department of Health","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the (a) prevalence of additional health problems experienced by people with Parkinson's Disease due to delays in receiving Duodopa and (b) costs incurred by the NHS as a result of such delays; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200678","200678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61878","2014-06-17","Department of Health","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that clinicians making individual funding requests for Parkinson's disease medication are informed of the outcome within 40 days; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200679","200679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61879","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of all UK visa applications processed by TPContact in (a) Israel, (b) Russia, (c) South Africa and (d) Ukraine have been subject to delays outside the stated service standards.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200696","200696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61880","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of all UK visa applications processed by TPContact in all its overseas service centres have been subject to delays outside the stated service standards.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200697","200697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61881","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints she has received about UK visa applications processed by TPContact in (a) Israel, (b) Russia, (c) South Africa and (d) Ukraine to date.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200698","200698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61882","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK visa applications processed by TPContact in (a) Israel, (b) Russia, (c) South Africa and (d) Ukraine have been withdrawn by the applicant after the service standard for processing time has been missed in the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200699","200699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61883","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what sanctions are available if TPContact fails to achieve and maintain high standards of customer service while providing services to her Department.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200686","200686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61884","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department takes to ensure that TPContact achieves and maintains high standards of customer service.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200687","200687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61885","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what sanctions have been levied by her Department as a result of TPContact failing to achieve and maintain high standards of customer service while providing services for her Department.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200688","200688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61886","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to compensate people who have paid for an upgrade in their passport application as a result of delays in processing their original application.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200689","200689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61887","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department took to ensure that TPContact was prepared for the required increase in capacity at its facilities worldwide to deal with the summer rush of visa applications.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200702","200702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61888","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of applicants who have upgraded to a premium service following contact with the Passport Office in each of the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200717","200717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61889","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what target she has set for the time in which applicants should receive a call back from the Passport Office when making enquiries about applications.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200723","200723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61890","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of passport applications submitted by residents of Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency in each month since June 2010; and how many such cases were processed within three weeks of receipt.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200724","200724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61891","2014-06-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications were made to the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority's Hardship Fund in 2013-14; and what proportion of such applications were successful.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200718","200718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61892","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many agency workers have been employed as cover for uniform operational support staff in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200711","200711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61893","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons operated on half regime during (a) January, (b) February, (c) March, (d) April and (e) May 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200712","200712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61894","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders under the age of 18 were held in the adult secure estate in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200713","200713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61895","2014-06-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent on agency workers to cover clerical staff in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200708","200708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61896","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent on agency workers to cover uniformed operational support staff in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200709","200709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61897","2014-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many agency workers have been employed as cover for clerical staff in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200710","200710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61898","2014-06-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, who has been invited to the UK-China business summit scheduled during the visit of the Chinese Premier, Li Keqian, to the UK.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200694","200694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61899","2014-06-18","Prime Minister","2014-06-13","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he plans to discuss (a) the abolition of the death penalty, (b) freedom of expression and (c) freedom of religion or belief and (d) Tibet with the Chinese Premier during his visit to the UK.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200692","200692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61900","2014-06-18","Prime Minister","2014-06-13","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will refer the matter of the release of correspondence between the Home Secretary and the Secretary of State for Education on preventing extremism to the Independent Adviser on Ministers' Interests.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200722","200722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61901","2014-06-17","Department for Transport","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to encourage local authorities to provide training for drivers of heavy goods vehicles to increase awareness of the dangers faced by cyclists.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200680","200680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61902","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of those who are (a) out-of-work, (b) self-employed and (c) employed in each of the last five years are tax credit claimants.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200695","200695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61903","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the recent report from Mind entitled Fulfilling Potential? ESA and the fate of the Work-Related Activity Group.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200715","200715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61904","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress he has made in developing local support services for Universal Credit claimants; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200719","200719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61905","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 16 year olds claimed jobseeker's allowance in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200720","200720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61906","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 16 year olds claimed employment and support allowance in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200721","200721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61907","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payments entitlement decisions on applications made by people not suffering with a terminal illness were made in each of the three months to June 2014.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200704","200704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61908","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payments applications made by people not suffering with a terminal illness were made in each of the three months to June 2014.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200705","200705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61909","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for personal independence payments have been made by claimants whose disability living allowance payments have been terminated; and what interim financial support his Department makes available to such claimants.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200706","200706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61910","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure claimants experiencing delays in their personal independence payments assessments are kept better informed of the status of their applications.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200707","200707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61911","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what scope there is for a Work Programme prime provider or sub-contractor to propose variations to the claimant commitment agreed with a jobseeker who subsequently embarks on the Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200729","200729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61912","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what scope there is for amending an individual's claimant commitment after it has first been drawn up.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200730","200730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61569","2014-06-16","Attorney General","2014-06-12","To ask the Attorney General, how many parliamentary questions tabled to the Law Officers' Departments in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200438","200438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61570","2014-06-16","Attorney General","2014-06-12","To ask the Attorney General, what visits each of the Ministers in the Law Officers' Departments have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200478","200478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61571","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200477","200477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61572","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps are being taken to promote UK trade with Latin America in connection with the 2014 Football World Cup taking place in Brazil.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200553","200553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61573","2014-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will bring forward proposals to make apprentices who earn below earning thresholds eligible for statutory sick pay.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200562","200562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61574","2014-06-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with Royal Mail Group, Ofcom or officials or Ministers in other departments about invoking section 44(9) and section 44(10) of the Postal Services Act 2011 to ask Ofcom to report on the sustainability of the Universal Service Obligation.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200467","200467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61575","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many parliamentary questions tabled to his Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200437","200437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61576","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many start-up loans have been granted to businesses in (a) Gillingham and Rainham constituency, (b) Medway and (c) Kent to date.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200382","200382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61577","2014-06-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps UK Trade and Investment has taken to encourage exports from the north east to Brazil, Angola and Mozambique and other emerging lusophone markets.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200358","200358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61578","2014-06-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will increase the minimum rate of pay for apprentices from £2.68 per hour to £2.96 per hour.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200564","200564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61579","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many company formations were recorded in (a) Gillingham and Rainham, (b) Medway and (c) Kent in the last year.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200510","200510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61580","2014-06-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been paid out by his Department in statutory entitlements following the collapse of Comet; how many people have been compensated to date; and what estimate he has made of the total cost to the Exchequer of meeting all arising liabilities in this case.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200565","200565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61581","2014-06-16","Cabinet Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many parliamentary questions tabled to his Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200439","200439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61582","2014-06-19","Cabinet Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department has spent on redundancy payments for special advisers since May 2010.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200473","200473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61583","2014-06-16","Cabinet Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what visits (a) each of the Ministers in his Department, (b) the Prime Minister and (c) the Deputy Prime Minister have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200498","200498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61584","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200495","200495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61585","2014-06-17","HM Treasury","2014-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are registered as self-employed in each region and constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200518","200518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61586","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimates have been made for the net financial benefit to the pub industry of the reduction in beer duty in the 2014 Budget.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200569","200569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61587","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to introduce a clause into private finance initiative contracts to limit the ability of contractors to move offshore.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200422","200422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61588","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many parliamentary questions tabled to his Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200449","200449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61589","2014-06-17","HM Treasury","2014-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 8 May 2014, Official Report, column 298W, on Highways Agency, what the (a) criteria and (b) procedures are for considering the extension of the provisions of section 41(3) of the VAT Act 1994 to a new body.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200463","200463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61590","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many income tax payers were registered with HM Revenue and Customs as self employed in (a) 2010-11 and (b) each succeeding year.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200622","200622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61591","2014-06-16","Church Commissioners","2014-06-12","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, how many parliamentary questions tabled to the Church Commissioners in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200440","200440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61592","2014-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many parliamentary questions tabled to his Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200441","200441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61593","2014-06-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what research his Department has (a) conducted or (b) commissioned on recent trends in homelessness among people under the age of 35 years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200364","200364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61594","2014-06-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department provides to music venues facing potential closure from noise abatement notices as a result of change of use of neighbouring buildings under permitted development rights.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200374","200374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61595","2014-06-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he intends to bring forward new proposals for the Firefighters' Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200517","200517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61596","2014-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200479","200479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61597","2014-06-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons his Department no longer publishes statistics for non-fire incidents with casualties attended by the Fire and Rescue Service in Great Britain.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200567","200567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61598","2014-06-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many non-fire incidents with casualties were attended by the Fire and Rescue Service in Great Britain in (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2013-14.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200568","200568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61599","2014-06-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with refence to paragraph 1.20 of the Fire Statistics Great Britain 2012-13; what the reasons are for the difference in the number of primary fires in England attended by the Fire and Rescue Service reported in each table and table 1a of the appendices to the Fire Incidents Response Times, England 2012-13.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200566","200566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61600","2014-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when his Department plans to publish draft legislation to amend the legal threshold from substantial damage and distress to nuisance, annoyance, inconvenience or anxiety for the International Commissioner's Office to take enforcement action from substantial damage or distress under the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003; and when he expects that legislation to be in force.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200590","200590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61601","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2014, Official Report, column 27W, on the Royal Air Force, whether any UK personnel other than Remotely Piloted Air System personnel are embedded in the 732nd Operations Group.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200598","200598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61602","2014-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200480","200480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61603","2014-06-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent estimate he has made of the amount of philanthropic giving to arts and heritage organisations in each region and constituent part of the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200471","200471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61604","2014-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of diversity in employment in public and private sectors of the media industry.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200431","200431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61605","2014-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department plans to take to improve equality monitoring of employment within the media industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200433","200433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61606","2014-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what advice or guidance his Department provides to employers in the media industry on equality monitoring.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200434","200434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61607","2014-06-19","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department has spent on redundancy payments for special advisers since May 2010.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200474","200474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61608","2014-06-17","HM Treasury","2014-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of (a) the total amount paid out in film tax relief and (b) the resultant benefit to the UK economy as a result of such tax relief since 2007; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200470","200470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61609","2014-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on treating gambling addiction.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200557","200557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61610","2014-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of adult gambling addicts in Britain; and what proportion of total funding on addressing gambling addiction has come from (a) the NHS, (b) local authorities and (c) the gambling industry.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200556","200556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61611","2014-06-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many local digital service licences have been awarded in Kent and Medway.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200386","200386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61612","2014-06-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to encourage local media and regional broadcasting in Kent and Medway.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200387","200387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61613","2014-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many parliamentary questions tabled to his Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200442","200442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61614","2014-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the roundtables on nuisance calls and texts met; and when the next roundtable will meet.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200416","200416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61615","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which US establishments were visited by personnel from the Atomic Weapons Establishment under the terms of the US-UK Mutual Defence Agreement in 2013; and how many staff visited each such establishment.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200408","200408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61616","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what facility rekit projects have taken place at the Atomic Weapons Establishment under the scope of the Nuclear Weapons Capability Sustainment Project; and what the cost of each such project was.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200409","200409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61617","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons a review of the scope of Project Pegasus is being undertaken at the Atomic Weapons Establishment; and what changes he expects to be made to the scope of the project as a result of the review.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200410","200410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61618","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many parliamentary questions tabled to his Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200443","200443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61619","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has for reviewing the conduct of and representation on Local Liaison Committees for defence nuclear sites.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200398","200398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61620","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate the (a) monthly and (b) total additional cost to date for paying Capita as if it was meeting quantity and quality standards for recruitments in the Recruiting Partnering Project.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200381","200381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61621","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Army 2020, HC 263, published on 11 June 2014, page eight, when Ministers in his Department first established that reserves cost around 87 per cent of the cost of regulars when mobilised.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200574","200574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61622","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether UK aircraft have flown outside Afghan airspace in support of NATO International Security Assistance Force missions in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200555","200555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61623","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Army 2020, HC 263, published on 11 June 2014, page eight, if he will provide a breakdown of the costings used to work out that reserves cost around 87 per cent of the costs of regulars when mobilised.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200573","200573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61624","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Army 2020, HC 263, published on 11 June 2014, page 30, if he will provide a breakdown of the extra £70 million in costs that will be borne by his Department for the decision to revert to a hosting environment provided by Capita as part of the Recruiting Partnering Project.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200538","200538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61625","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Army 2020, HC 263, published on 11 June 2014, page 25, if he will provide details of (a) the 167 implementation orders that his Department has already issued as part of the Army 2020 reforms and (b) any implementation orders which have yet to be issued.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200539","200539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61626","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department will issue a formal response to the National Audit Office report, Army 2020, HC 263, published on 11 June 2014.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200540","200540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61627","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will provide details of the current workforce model for the Army Reserve that his Department is using to assess how long it will take to recruit the required number of 30,000 reserves; and when under the current model that target will be met.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200585","200585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61628","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what planning data was used to devise his Department's recruitment target for the Army Reserve as part of its Army 2020 reforms.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200586","200586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61629","2014-06-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what preliminary tests his Department conducted to assess whether it was feasible to recruit and train the required number of reserves within the necessary timescale envisaged by the Army 2020 proposals.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200587","200587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61630","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Army 2020, HC 263, published on 11 June 2014, page 12, what his Department's response is to the recommendation that it should reassess its targets for recruiting reserves.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200536","200536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61631","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Army 2020, HC 263, published on 11 June 2014, page 17, if he will provide details of the eight options for force structures that his Department considered in 2011, and his Department's estimate of the savings each would have accrued.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200537","200537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61632","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons his Department did not provide supporting ICT infrastructure for Capita's new recruitment software as required under its contractual arrangements with Capita in relation to the Recruiting Partnering Project.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200575","200575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61633","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Army 2020, HC 263, published on 11 June 2014, page 10, which Minister in his Department signed off on the decision not to provide supporting ICT infrastructure for Capita's new recruitment software as part of his Department's contractual arrangements with Capita in relation to the Recruiting Partnering Project.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200576","200576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61634","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recruits of each sex commenced Phase 1 training at AFC Harrogate in each year since 2006; how many recruits of each sex enlisted in an infantry role in that time; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200601","200601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61635","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recruits of each sex dropped out of training at AFC Harrogate before completing Phase 1 in each year since 2006; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200602","200602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61636","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recruits of each sex completed training at AFC Harrogate in each year since 2006; how many recruits of each sex commenced Phase 2 training (a) elsewhere and (b) at ITC Catterick; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200603","200603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61637","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) male and (b) female recruits who completed phase two training at Catterick Infantry Training Centre in each year since 2006 went on to join the trained strength; how many such recruits in those categories were aged under 18 years when they enlisted; how many had undertaken phase one training at Harrogate Army Foundation College; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200578","200578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61638","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the full out-turn cost was of AFC Harrogate in each year since 2006, including (a) building maintenance, (b) staffing costs, (c) training costs and (d) salaries for recruits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200604","200604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61639","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the full outturn cost of (a) building maintenance, (b) staffing, (c) training, (d) salaries for recruits and (e) other costs were at Catterick Infantry Training Centre in each year since 2006; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200579","200579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61640","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Army 2020, HC 263, published on 11 June 2014, page five, if he will provide a breakdown of the £5.3 billion savings that reductions in the army would save from 2012-13 to 2021-22.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200572","200572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61641","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recruits are expected to commence Phase 1 training at AFC Harrogate in financial year 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200605","200605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61642","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) male and (b) female recruits dropped out of training at Catterick Infantry Training Centre after completing phase one but before completing phase two in each year since 2006; how many such recruits in each category were aged under 18 years when they enlisted; how many had undertaken phase one training at Harrogate Army Foundation College; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200580","200580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61643","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the anticipated out-turn cost of AFC Harrogate is for financial year 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200606","200606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61644","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) male and (b) female recruits who commenced phase two training at Catterick Infantry Training Centre had undertaken phase one training at Harrogate Army Foundation College in each year since 2006; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200581","200581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61645","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the anticipated out-turn cost of ITC Catterick is for financial year 2014-15.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200623","200623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61646","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recruits are expected to commence Phase 1 training at ITC Catterick in financial year 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200607","200607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61647","2014-06-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on redundancy payments for special advisers since May 2010.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200475","200475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61648","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200481","200481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61649","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 22 November 2011, Official Report, column 272W, on AWE, what his most recent estimate is of the (a) anticipated out-turn cost and (b) projected in-service date of each of the new build projects in the Atomic Weapons Establishment Site Development Context Plan.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200428","200428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61650","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) male and (b) female recruits dropped out of training at Catterick Infantry Training Centre before completing Phase 1 in each year since 2006; how many such recruits in each category were aged under 18 when they enlisted; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200582","200582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61651","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) male and (b) female recruits have commenced Phase 1 training at Catterick Infantry Training Centre in each year since 2006; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200583","200583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61652","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to rectify the (a) inconsistent understanding of Army staffing requirements, (b) limited use of management information and (c) unsystematic approach to improvement in relation to the Recruiting Partnering Project referred to on pages 36 and 37 of the National Audit Office report, Army 2020, HC 263, published on 11 June 2014.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200584","200584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61653","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 12 September 2013, Official Report, column 798W, on Unmanned Aerial Vehicles, whether changes to the Reaper Agreement pertaining to the UK Reaper Force Squadron have been finalised; and whether this Agreement will remain in force following the cessation of NATO International Security Force missions in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200600","200600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61654","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 25 March 2013, Official Report, column 940W, on Unmanned Aerial Vehicles, whether UK personnel at Creech Airforce base will remain embedded following the cessation of NATO International Security Force missions in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200599","200599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61655","2014-06-16","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how many parliamentary questions tabled to his Office in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200444","200444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61656","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many parliamentary questions tabled to his Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200445","200445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61657","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations he has received on funding sixth forms in rural schools.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200419","200419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61658","2014-06-17","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistant training posts have been (a) commissioned and (b) filled in in (i) Copeland and (ii) Cumbria in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200365","200365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61659","2014-06-17","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the current status is of schools placed in special measures in (a) Copeland and (b) Cumbria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200366","200366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61661","2014-06-17","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received in support of his proposals to allow further delegation of children's social care functions in order to improve outcomes for children in receipt of child protection services.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200384","200384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61662","2014-06-17","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to develop pilot projects of his proposals to allow further delegation of children's social care functions.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200385","200385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61663","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to ensure a high standard of teaching in numeracy and literacy.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200344","200344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61664","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that children at primary and secondary schools have access to a healthy and balanced dinner each day.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200348","200348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61665","2014-06-17","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the proportion of 17 year olds staying in education (a) before and (b) after the raising of the participation age.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200516","200516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61666","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the current starting age for children entering primary education on the wellbeing and attainment of those born in summer months.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200501","200501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61667","2014-06-16","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will introduce a concessionary bus fare scheme for 16 to 18 year olds to allow them to pay child fare for their school bus passes.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200502","200502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61668","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200482","200482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61669","2014-06-17","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications for free schools have been made in (a) Copeland constituency and (b) Cumbria in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200533","200533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61670","2014-06-17","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants have been employed in schools in (a) Copeland constituency and (b) Cumbria in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200524","200524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61671","2014-06-17","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 8 April 2014, Official Report, column 205W, on the London Academy of Excellence, whether the enrolment data for 2013-14 for the London Academy of Excellence is now available; and if he will publish that data.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200588","200588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61672","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to ensure that cancer awareness and awareness of cancer symptoms is covered in schools.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200543","200543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61673","2014-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policy on the need for additional gas storage in the UK of the statement on 16 May 2014 of the EU Energy Commissioner that the gas security of supply directive should be amended to increase the mimimum quantity of gas that member states are obliged to store.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200618","200618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61674","2014-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policy on the need for additional gas storage capacity in the UK of recent events involving Russia and Ukraine; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200619","200619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61675","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the proportion of the Demand Side Balancing Reserve that will comprise of active demand reduction rather than switching on generation assets.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200508","200508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61676","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200483","200483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61677","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much in public subsidy he expects to allocate to the proposed wind farm at Navitus Bay.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200455","200455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61678","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the unit mitigation cost of Navitus Bay in sterling and in US dollars per Kelvin of global warming abated will be as a result of the proposed wind farm.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200459","200459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61679","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the cost of abating all global warming projected to occur over the lifetime of Navitus Bay in sterling and in US dollars; and what intertemporal discount rate has been used in such calculations.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200460","200460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61680","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the radioactive forcing from the increase in carbon dioxide concentration will be over the lifetime of Navitus Bay (a) if the project goes ahead and (b) if the project does not go ahead.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200458","200458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61681","2014-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, for what reason householders converting to higher efficiency natural gas condensing boilers are eligible for help under the Green Deal Home Improvement Fund, but householders in rural areas converting to higher efficiency oil or liquid petroleum gas condensing boilers are not eligible.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200373","200373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61682","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, in determining the reduction in UK carbon dioxide emissions arising from Navitus Bay, what allowance his Department for UK carbon dioxide emissions from backup baseload generation to cover (a) for maintenance and repair downtime and (b) for the failure of the wind to blow in the operating range.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200453","200453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61683","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much of mean electricity generation in the UK will be represented by the proposed development at Navitus Bay over its lifetime.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200450","200450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61684","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of the carbon dioxide emissions will be represented by UK electricity generation over the lifetime of the proposed development at Navitus Bay.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200451","200451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61685","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of UK carbon dioxide emissions that would otherwise have occurred will be prevented by the proposed wind farm at Navitus Bay.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200452","200452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61686","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what fraction of global carbon dioxide emissions will be represented by UK carbon dioxide emissions over the lifetime of the proposed wind farm at Navitus Bay.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200454","200454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61687","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what fraction of mean rated output will be achieved on average throughout the lifetime of Navitus Bay.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200456","200456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61688","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the global mean carbon dioxide concentration in the atmosphere and partial pressure of carbon dioxide in the oceans will be (a) at the outset and (b) at the end of the Navitus Bay lifetime, if the project goes ahead, (c) at the end of the Navitus Bay lifetime, if the project does not go ahead.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200457","200457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61689","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many parliamentary questions tabled to his Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200446","200446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61690","2014-06-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations he has received on support for moorland farmers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200421","200421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61691","2014-06-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that the UK's sanitary and phytosanitary rules in food production are not affected by the agreement of the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200372","200372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61692","2014-06-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to reduce risks to the environment posed by the release of helium balloons.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200367","200367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61693","2014-06-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the effective implementation of regulations (a) relating to storage of slurry and (b) in general for safety in farm yards.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200345","200345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61694","2014-06-17","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many xx-positive cases have been recorded in the UK in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Dr Thérèse  Coffey","Dr Thérèse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200390","200390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61695","2014-06-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200484","200484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61696","2014-06-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 10 April 2014, Official Report, column 394W, on forests, for what reasons the Government did not announce in the Queen's Speech legislative proposals to protect the public forest estate.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200611","200611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61697","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2014, Official Report, column 212W, on USA, whether either government places restrictions on the use of data shared between the UK and the US.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200608","200608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61698","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the meeting between President Salva Kir and Riek Machar in Addis Ababa on 10 June 2014.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200552","200552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61699","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on co-ordinating efforts to secure the release from prison of Meriam Ibrahim.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200554","200554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61700","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many parliamentary questions tabled to his Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200591","200591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61701","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200485","200485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61702","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to improve support and protection for women human rights defenders in Afghanistan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200430","200430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61703","2014-06-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has spent on redundancy payments for special advisers since May 2010.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200476","200476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61704","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts and other senior figures in the United Nations and the EU on human rights abuses in Tibet.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200500","200500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61705","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Lithuanian government to secure restitution for British citizens who had assets seized by the Nazis as soon as possible.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200383","200383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61706","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what direct steps the Government has taken to ensure the safety of Christians in countries where they are being persecuted for their faith.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200349","200349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61707","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in China.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200350","200350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61708","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the issue of rape and sexual violence by the Burmese Army was raised with the Burmese colonel who received training in the UK from 10 March to April 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200354","200354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61709","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many meetings he has had with world leaders to discuss the situation in Yemen since 1 January 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200356","200356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61710","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Israeli counterpart in favour of the removal of demolition orders from all structures at the Tent of Nations farm outside Nahalin village on the West Bank.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200352","200352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61711","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether precursors of genocide exist in Burma for the Rohingya; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200353","200353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61712","2014-06-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the new Indian government in favour of increased action to tackle caste discrimination, sexual violence and other forms of discrimination and inequality.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200377","200377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61713","2014-06-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of recent territorial gains of the Islamist insurgent group Islamic State of Iraq and the Levant; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200413","200413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61714","2014-06-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what efforts his Department is making to support the Iraqi government in maintaining stability in that country.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200414","200414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61715","2014-06-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the threat ISIS and other Islamist groups in Syria pose to (a) the wider Middle East and (b) other areas.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200415","200415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61716","2014-06-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the government of Israel on the recent arrest of Mahmoud Zwahre in Al Maasara, Bethlehem.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200359","200359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61717","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the savings to the NHS from the use of mindfulness interventions to reduce the number of GP visits.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200397","200397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61718","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the relationship of the length of time of GP patient consultation and successful diagnosis.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200399","200399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61719","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the benefits of nurse-led patient health checks immediately before GP consultations.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200400","200400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61720","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the relationship between the length of time of GP patient consultation and patient satisfaction.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200401","200401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61721","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of stress on heart failure.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200404","200404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61722","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the incidence of heart attacks among workers who work (a) 40 and (b) 60 hours a week.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200405","200405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61723","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative assessment he has made of the rates of mental ill health caused by (a) working long hours and (b) being unemployed.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200406","200406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61724","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of using mobile telephone apps to use GPS to locate trained resuscitators and atrial fibrilation equipment to bring a rapid response to those who have suffered a heart attack.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200407","200407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61725","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the out-of-hospital survival rates are for patients who suffer a heart attack in each year since 1984 for which information is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200402","200402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61726","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what future plans he has for community hospitals in the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200420","200420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61727","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the review by the NHS on intellectual property, Innovation, Health and Wealth.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200424","200424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61728","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much a GP practice is paid for each patient visit to a GP.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200417","200417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61729","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of work-based stress on suicide levels.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200412","200412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61730","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of adaptive licensing or early access schemes (a) in the UK and (b) across the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200378","200378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61731","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what restrictions apply to the discretion of clinical commissioning groups to commission immunisation services.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200343","200343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61732","2014-06-17","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints his Department received from members of the public on care and treatment by Medway NHS Foundation Trust between 2005 and 2010.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200388","200388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61733","2014-06-17","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the next British Child and Adolescent Mental Health Survey will be carried out.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200389","200389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61734","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average length of a GP consultation was in each year since 1984 for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200395","200395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61735","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total cost of GP visits was in each year since 1984 in which information is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200396","200396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61736","2014-06-17","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to prevent NHS England from implementing restrictions on the use of new drugs for advanced prostate cancer, enzalutamide and abiraterone.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200514","200514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61737","2014-06-17","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to increase the transparency of NICE's decisions on the Cancer Drugs Fund to remove any restrictions on treatment use arising from budgetary pressures and increase its level of engagement with members of the public.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200515","200515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61738","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to maintain the quality of services provided by children and adolescent mental health services in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200499","200499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61739","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200487","200487"
