"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31413","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's top five children's health priorities are following the publication of the Chief Medical Officer's report, Our children deserve better - prevention pays.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182122","182122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31414","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will revise the methodology for health technology assessments of interventions in children to recognise differences between adult and child health in the light of the Chief Medical Officer's report Our children deserve better - prevention pays.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182123","182123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31415","2014-01-09","Cabinet Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Chief Medical Officer's report Prevention pays - our children deserve better, what the (a) top 20 causes of paediatric deaths in children under five years of age in England, (b) the top five causes of death from infectious diseases in children under five years of age in England were in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182127","182127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31416","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases there were of (a) meningitis C in 1998 and (b) meningitis B in 2012.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182126","182126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31417","2014-01-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her policy is on promoting competition in provision of superfast broadband infrastructure; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181677","181677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31418","2014-01-13","HM Treasury","2014-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the annual savings to the Exchequer as a result of (a) withdrawing housing benefit entitlement for young people aged under 25 and (b) evicting households with annual incomes of £60,000 from council tenancies.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181678","181678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31419","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in private rented accommodation currently claim housing support (a) below the maximum they would be entitled to according to their local housing allowance (LHA) entitlement, (b) at the maximum level of their LHA entitlement and (c) above the maximum they are entitled to according to their LHA entitlement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182057","182057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31420","2014-01-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the progress BDUK has made towards its three business aims agreed with her Department in 2011.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182068","182068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31421","2014-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with Ministerial counterparts on increasing the purchase of British food by public bodies.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182056","182056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31422","2014-01-13","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Public Health England's work on obesity; and what recent discussions he has had with that body on tackling obesity.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181653","181653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31423","2014-01-13","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time staff of Public Health England are working on obesity matters.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181654","181654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31424","2014-01-13","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps Public Health England has taken to disseminate information about anti-obesity programmes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181655","181655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31425","2014-01-13","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Public Health England on encouraging directors of public health to compile registers of appropriate community weight management options in their region.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181656","181656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31426","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the target timeframe is for processing applications for (a) disability living allowance and (b) employment and support allowance; and whether his Department is currently meeting those targets (i) nationally, (ii) in each region and (iii) in each constituency.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181657","181657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31427","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had on the potential use of proton beam therapy for treatment of eye cancer in the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182249","182249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31428","2014-01-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the extent to which the rights of Christians to religious freedom are safeguarded by employers who require Sunday working.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182250","182250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31429","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with professional bodies on the use of vitamin D as a preventative measure against breast cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182251","182251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31430","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of prescribing (a) tocilizumab and (b) other drugs for treatment of juvenile arthritis in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182252","182252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31431","2014-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to maintain water vole numbers and protect their habitat.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182237","182237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31432","2014-01-09","Home Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with (a) the Countryside Alliance and (b) the British Association of Shooting and Conservation on proposed changes to legislation on firearms.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182238","182238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31433","2014-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the responsible ministers in the Welsh Government, Scottish Government and Northern Ireland Executive on steps to address the effects of winter weather on farming.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182242","182242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31434","2014-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assistance his Department makes available to farmers for dealing with the effects of bad winter weather.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182241","182241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31435","2014-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with (a) the Countryside Alliance, (b) the British Association of Shooting and Conservation and (c) the Scottish Landowners Association on potential reintroduction programmes for the Scottish wildcat.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182239","182239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31436","2014-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department plans to take to assist the UK farming sector to introduce GM crops.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182240","182240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31437","2014-01-13","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2013, Official Report, column 353W, on health education, what percentage of the Change4Life budget is being spent on (a) alcohol, (b) obesity and physical health and (c) other areas.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182227","182227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31438","2014-01-13","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2013, Official Report, column 349W, on alcoholic drinks: misuse, how many meetings at ministerial level to discuss matters arising from the strategy have been held; and which ministers have attended each such meeting.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182228","182228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31439","2014-01-13","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many surgeons are qualified to undertake L5 S1 anterior fusion surgery in (a) Merseyside, (b) the North West and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182231","182231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31440","2014-01-13","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the target waiting time is for urgent spinal surgery; how many hospitals are in breach of waiting time targets for urgent spinal surgery; and what the average waiting time for such patients is in (a) Merseyside, (b) the North West and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182230","182230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31441","2014-01-13","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2013, Official Report, column 349W, on alcoholic drinks: misuse, on what date the Government and Partners Alcohol Working Group last met; when the next meeting is scheduled to take place; and which organisations have been invited to attend.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182229","182229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31442","2014-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many communications his Department sent to local authorities in 2013.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181652","181652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31443","2014-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his Greek counterpart.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181664","181664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31444","2014-01-13","Prime Minister","2014-01-07","To ask the Prime Minister, when he last held discussions with (a) Romanian Prime Minister Victor Ponta and (b) Bulgarian Prime Minister Plamen Oresharski.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181669","181669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31445","2014-01-13","Home Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of Romanians and Bulgarians who have entered the UK since 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181670","181670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31446","2014-01-13","Home Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times the Minister of State for Crime Prevention has met with (a) chief constables and (b) police and crime commissioners to discuss combating prescription drug abuse in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181671","181671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31447","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many national insurance numbers were issued to foreign nationals from each country of birth in 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181672","181672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31448","2014-01-13","HM Treasury","2014-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many non-UK EEA nationals had dependants eligible to receive child benefit where the dependant is (a) in the UK and (b) outside the UK on 1 January 2014; and how much has been paid in such a fashion in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181673","181673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31449","2014-01-09","Department for Education","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish details of all funds allocated by his Department and associated agencies directly to schools located within (a) West Berkshire and (b) Reading Borough in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Alok Sharma","Alok Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182164","182164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31450","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish details of all funds allocated by his Department and its associated agencies to (a) Reading Borough Council and (b) West Berkshire Council in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Alok Sharma","Alok Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182169","182169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31451","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish details of all funds allocated by his Department and its associated agencies to projects located within (a) Reading Borough Council and (b) West Berkshire Council in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Alok Sharma","Alok Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182170","182170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31452","2014-01-09","Department for Education","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish details of all funds allocated by his Department and its associated agencies to (a) Reading Borough Council and (b) West Berkshire Council in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Alok Sharma","Alok Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182167","182167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31453","2014-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish details of all funds allocated by his Department and its associated agencies to (a) Reading Borough Council and (b) West Berkshire Council in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Alok Sharma","Alok Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182168","182168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31454","2014-01-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding was allocated by his Department and its associated agencies to (a) Reading Borough Council and (b) West Berkshire Council in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Alok Sharma","Alok Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182166","182166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31455","2014-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish details of all funds allocated by his Department and associated agencies to (a) Reading Borough Council and (b) West Berkshire Council in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Alok Sharma","Alok Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182165","182165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31456","2014-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to prevent illegal migration onto the Turks and Caicos Islands and to reduce the number of potentially fatal journeys taken by such immigrants.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182176","182176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31457","2014-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent correspondence his Department has had with the European Citizens Action Service.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182174","182174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31458","2014-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress the Government has made on incorporating Gibraltar into EU aviation legislation.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182175","182175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31459","2014-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect that gathering of information on the Gibraltar border situation by the Government, in collaboration with the Gibraltar government, and the forwarding of that information to the European Commission, has had on reducing border delays.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182178","182178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31460","2014-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the effect that Gibraltar border delays have had on tourism and visitor numbers to Gibraltar over the last four months.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182171","182171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31461","2014-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the local economy of the proposed 15 per cent duty on bookmakers' online winnings in Gibraltar.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182173","182173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31462","2014-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on plans by the government of Gibraltar to establish a state-owned bank in that territory.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182172","182172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31463","2014-01-09","Department for Education","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will direct Ofsted to make a comparative assessment of the quality of training available through school-centred initial teacher training and other initial teacher training providers.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182135","182135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31465","2014-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what additional cost to the public purse was incurred as a result of the first RC 135 Airseeker being ready for delivery before the RAF could accept it.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182233","182233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31466","2014-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the Military Airworthiness Authority to give the first RC 135 Airseeker its release to service.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182232","182232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31467","2014-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to his Department was of military aviation collaboration projects (a) in the EU, (b) with non-EU countries, excluding the US and (c) with the US in the last two years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182236","182236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31468","2014-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what additional information was requested from (a) the USAF and (b) Boeing by QinetiQ in order to meet the Military Airworthiness Authority standards to release to service the first RC 135.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182234","182234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31469","2014-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the RC 135 Airseeker is equipped with single skin fuel lines.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182235","182235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31470","2014-01-13","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure an additional neuromuscular care advisory post is in place for the North East region; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182061","182061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31471","2014-01-13","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency has ever exercised discretion in revoking the licence held by a new driver who has accumulated six penalty points since the introduction of the Road Traffic (New Drivers) Act 1995.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182059","182059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31472","2014-01-13","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of new drivers that did not have their licence revoked under the provisions of the Road Traffic (New Drivers) Act 1995 following the accumulation of six penalty points in each year since that Act's introduction; and under what circumstances each such non-revocation took place.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182060","182060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31473","2014-01-13","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, at what point a new driver who has accumulated six penalty points has his or her licence revoked.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182226","182226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31474","2014-01-13","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of people in the UK who commute to work by (a) public and (b) private means of transport.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182159","182159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31475","2014-01-13","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the average (a) distance and (b) length of time it takes people in the UK to commute to work.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182160","182160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31476","2014-01-13","Department for International Development","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with the British Council about her Department's policy of improving the lives of girls and women through better education.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182161","182161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31477","2014-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have joined the Territorial Army in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182162","182162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31478","2014-01-13","Department for International Development","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the progress her Department has made towards the target of reaching 60 million people with access to water, sanitation and hygiene by 2015.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182163","182163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31479","2014-01-09","Attorney General","2014-01-07","To ask the Attorney General, for each of the past three calendar years, how many confiscation orders imposed in relation to CPS tax fraud prosecutions were for (a) £0-£1,000, (b) £1,001-£5,000, (c) £5,001-£10,000, (d) £10,001-£20,000, (e) £20,001-£50,000, (f) £50,001-£100,000, (g) £100,001-£500,000, (h) £500,001-£1 million, (i) £1 million-£5 million and (j) more than £5 million.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182184","182184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31480","2014-01-09","Attorney General","2014-01-07","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2013, Official Report, column 398W, on fraud: prosecutions, what assessment he has made of the likely causes of the 12 per cent reduction in the Crown Prosecution Service's conviction rate in contested fraud cases between 2008-09 and 2012-13.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182185","182185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31481","2014-01-09","Attorney General","2014-01-07","To ask the Attorney General, if he will place in the Library the minutes of the meeting of 26 September 2013 between the former Director of Public Prosecutions and representatives of the Home Office regarding the decline in referrals for prosecution of cases of violence against women and girls.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182183","182183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31482","2014-01-09","Attorney General","2014-01-07","To ask the Attorney General, how many Crown Prosecution Service prosecutions were delayed due to the 6 January 2014 walk out by solicitors and barristers.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182080","182080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31483","2014-01-09","Attorney General","2014-01-07","To ask the Attorney General, how many asset restraining orders the Crown Prosecution Service has applied for in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182079","182079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31484","2014-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the role played by Russia in attempts to find a non-violent solution to the conflict in Syria.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182097","182097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31485","2014-01-09","HM Treasury","2014-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the reasons are for the recent change in forecasted revenue accruing to the Treasury from the UK-Swiss tax evasion agreement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182099","182099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31486","2014-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote the protection and enhancement of civil society organisations in Syria.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182098","182098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31487","2014-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households categorised as homeless have been housed in temporary accommodation for more than six weeks in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182181","182181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31488","2014-01-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department has spent on external consultants to advise on the proposed sale of the Government's stake in Urenco.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182129","182129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31489","2014-01-09","HM Treasury","2014-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will assess the effect of fining Royal Bank of Scotland for breaching sanctions against Iran on the Government's assessment of the efficacy of (a) UK criminal law pertaining to financial crime and (b) the Financial Conduct Authority's ability to regulate the financial sector.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182130","182130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31490","2014-01-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the economic consequences of selling the Government's stake in Urenco.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182131","182131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31491","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to promote research into carbon-neutral aviation technology.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182132","182132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31492","2014-01-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to increase the safety margin of electricity supply above peak demand.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182133","182133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31493","2014-01-09","HM Treasury","2014-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the likely effect of the Liechtenstein Disclosure Facility on the recovery of UK tax liabilities from assets held in Switzerland at the time of the signing of the UK-Swiss tax agreement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182134","182134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31494","2014-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he will answer the five written questions tabled by the hon Member for Harborough on 17 December 2013 for answer on 19 December 2013.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182186","182186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31495","2014-01-09","Home Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the number of thefts of catalytic converters in (a) 2013, (b) 2012 and (c) 2011.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181680","181680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31496","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent by the NHS on drugs for cancer treatment in Bolton North East constituency in each year since 1997; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182100","182100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31497","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many investigations the Vehicle and Operator Services Agency has undertaken in each year since 2010 into passenger train journeys serving Bolton following alleged infringements of the Public Service Vehicles (Carrying Capacity) Regulations 1984.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182101","182101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31498","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2013, Official Report, column 631W, on rolling stock: North West, what volume of passengers on the Bolton corridor peak time journeys is sufficient to trigger the contingency plans drawn up by his Department and Northern Rail.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182114","182114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31499","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects his Department to announce its discretionary housing payment allocations for 2014-15.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182058","182058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31500","2014-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) average and (b) range of time it has taken the Legal Aid Agency to make a decision following an application for exceptional case funding has been since April 2013.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182224","182224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31501","2014-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the situation of Christians in Syria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182158","182158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31502","2014-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of aid to rebel factions in Syria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182128","182128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31503","2014-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential of synergetic air-breathing rocket engines for improving the speed and efficiency of travel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182152","182152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31504","2014-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential of synergetic air-breathing rocket engines for placing large-scale solar stations in geo-stationary orbit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182151","182151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31505","2014-01-13","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on doctors' surgeries using 0844 numbers.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182067","182067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31506","2014-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what effect the recent disturbance in HMP Oakwood will have on his Department's decision on whether the planned prison in Wrexham will be privately-run in part or in full; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182206","182206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31507","2014-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what Welsh language facilities will be provided for inmates and staff in the planned prison in Wrexham.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182207","182207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31508","2014-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of privately-run prisons in light of the recent disturbance in HMP Oakwood; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182209","182209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31509","2014-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the proposed prison in Wrexham will be run by the public sector.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182210","182210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31510","2014-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many jobs will be created when the new planned prison in Wrexham opens.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182208","182208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31511","2014-01-13","Department for International Development","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the recent conflict in South Sudan on the number of (a) internally-displaced persons, (b) people subject to food insecurity and (c) young people in full-time education in that country.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182243","182243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31512","2014-01-09","Attorney General","2014-01-07","To ask the Attorney General, when he last met the Secretary of State for the Home Department to discuss changes in the number of domestic violence and rape cases being referred by the police to the Crown Prosecution Service; and what action followed those meetings.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181682","181682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31513","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people currently do not pay the under-occupancy penalty because they meet the criteria of Schedule 3 to the Housing Benefit and Council Tax Benefit (Consequential Provisions) Regulations 2006.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182149","182149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31514","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to his Department is of appeals against the under-occupancy penalty based on Schedule 3 to the Housing Benefit and Council Tax Benefit (Consequential Provisions) Regulations 2006.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182147","182147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31515","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to his Department in the next financial year of appeals against the under-occupancy penalty based on Schedule 3 to the Housing Benefit and Council Tax Benefit (Consequential Provisions) Regulations 2006.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182148","182148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31516","2014-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what places in the High Speed 2 safeguarded area or within half a mile of that safeguarded area (a) have been flooded in the past two months and (b) are considered to be at risk from flooding.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182155","182155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31517","2014-01-13","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) individuals and (b) organisations have contacted HS2 Ltd or his Department to ask for an extension to the consultation period on the environmental statement on High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182154","182154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31518","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to ensure the design of the proposed HS2 route within the designated landscape of the Chilterns Area of Outstanding Natural Beauty meets all requirements under section 85 of the Countryside and Rights of Way Act 2000; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182066","182066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31519","2014-01-09","Department for Education","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with local authorities on funding allocation for schools.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181658","181658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31520","2014-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking in response to the recent assessment of HM Prison Oakwood by HM Inspector of Prisons.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182065","182065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31521","2014-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to improve performance at new prisons and implement lessons learnt from HM Prison Oakwood since that establishment's opening.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181675","181675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31522","2014-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the disturbances at HM Prison Oakwood on 5 January 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181676","181676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31523","2014-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of (a) burglary, (b) sexual assault, (c) grievous bodily harm, (d) rape, (e) manslaughter, (f) attempted murder, (g) forgery, (h) fraud, (i) theft of a motor vehicle, (j) theft from a person, (k) robbery, (l) sexual activity with a child under 16, (m) sexual activity with a child under 13, (n) sexual assault of a female, (o) rape of a male, (p) rape of a female, (q) sexual assault of a male, (r) child abduction, (s) abandoning children aged under two years, (t) cruelty or neglect of children, (u) wounding or other acts endangering life, (v) causing death by aggravated vehicle-taking, (w) causing death by driving while unlicensed or uninsured, (x) causing death of a child or a vulnerable person, (y) causing death by careless driving when under the influence of drink or drugs, (z) manslaughter due to diminished responsibility, (aa) causing death by reckless driving, (bb) threat or conspiracy to murder, (cc) perverting the course of justice, (dd) violent disorder, (ee) kidnapping, (ff) blackmail, (gg) intent to supply a controlled drug, (hh) possession of a controlled drug, (ii) criminal damage, (jj) arson, (kk) common assault, (ll) dangerous driving and (mm) firearms offences and received a custodial sentence of (i) less than six months, (ii) less than 12 months, (iii) less than two years and (iv) less than four years in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182211","182211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31524","2014-01-13","Department for Education","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish his Department's annual report and accounts for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182146","182146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31525","2014-01-09","Home Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the role of (a) existing and (b) new airport infrastructure in combating illegal immigration by reducing the risk of landside transfers; and what recent representations she has made to the Airports Commission on this matter.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182053","182053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31526","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of shifts at maritime rescue co-ordination centres were staffed at below risk-assessed levels in 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182049","182049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31527","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions both the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Belfast, and the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Stornoway, were simultaneously staffed at below risk-assessed levels between 1 January 2013 and 31 December 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182045","182045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31528","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Liverpool was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in December 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182046","182046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31529","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions both the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Belfast, and the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Stornoway, were staffed at below risk-assessed levels at the same time in December 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182051","182051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31530","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Stornoway was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in December 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182047","182047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31531","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Belfast was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in December 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182048","182048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31532","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have died in each year since 2000 while detained or resident in (a) a NHS mental health unit and (b) any other mental health unit funded by the NHS.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181692","181692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31533","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the NHS has to record the ethnicity of patients who die while detained in mental health units; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181691","181691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31534","2014-01-09","Home Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures she is taking to address concerns in the African/Caribbean community about the use of stop and search; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181690","181690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31535","2014-01-09","Home Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many investigations conducted by the Independent Police Complaints Commission have resulted in criminal prosecutions in each of the last 10 years; and how many of these prosecutions resulted in convictions.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181689","181689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31536","2014-01-09","Home Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what work her Department is undertaking to improve the policing of minority communities and the confidence that these communities have in their local constabulary.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181687","181687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31537","2014-01-09","Home Office","2014-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures the Government is taking to promote public confidence in the Independent Police Complaints Commission; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181688","181688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31058","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to announce the procurement of new high speed electric rolling stock for the upgraded Midland Mainline.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181555","181555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31059","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to announce its preferred bidder for the Crossrail rolling stock contract before the second quarter of 2014.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181556","181556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31060","2014-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Indian counterpart on prisoners remaining imprisoned after completing their sentences in the Punjab and Haryana regions.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181541","181541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31061","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the overall benefits to local councils of upgrading pedestrian crossings to a puffin standard that detects pedestrians and can accommodate much lower walking speeds with minimal impact on vehicle traffic.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181558","181558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31062","2014-01-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding his Department spent on flood defences in Hartlepool constituency in (a) 2007-08, (b) 2008-09, (c) 2009-10, (d) 2010-11, (e) 2011-12 and (f) 2012-13; and how much funding his Department has allocated for flood defences in Hartlepool constituency in (i) 2013-14, (ii) 2014-15 and (iii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181538","181538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31063","2014-01-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Government's Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, published in August 2013, Action Point 9, whether the Offshore Wind Investment Organisation to deliver inward investment into the UK has been established; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181537","181537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31064","2014-01-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Government's Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, published in August 2013, Action Point 6, whether a finalised engagement plan has been produced with Norstec and CORES; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181535","181535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31065","2014-01-08","Department for Education","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will provide funding to High Tunstall College of Science in Hartlepool constituency to replace the roof and building damaged in extreme weather in December 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181539","181539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31066","2014-01-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Government's Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, published in August 2013, Action Point 4, how many Share Fair events for supply chain opportunities have been organised and delivered to date.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181536","181536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31067","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to create an additional neuromuscular care advisor post for the North East region; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181525","181525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31068","2014-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the international community tackles the persecution of Christians.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181440","181440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31069","2014-01-08","Department for Education","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what initiatives his Department has put in place to tackle bullying within schools and online since 2010; and what assessment has been made of their effectiveness.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181617","181617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31070","2014-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, under what legislation cyber-bullying offences are currently prosecuted; and how many prosecutions for cyber-bullying have been undertaken in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181618","181618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31071","2014-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of figures recently released by the Trussell Trust on the use of food banks in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181451","181451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31072","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department's policy on the removal of asylum seekers permits deportation to countries assessed by the Foreign and Commonwealth Office as being under a volatile threat from a number of terrorist organisations.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181427","181427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31073","2014-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been loaned to benefits claimants as short-term benefit advances in each month since April 2013; and how much was loaned under the crisis loan scheme in each of the 12 months up to April 2013.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181428","181428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31074","2014-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 September 2013, Official Report, column 235W, on food banks, whether his Department has seen any evidence linking welfare reforms to the increased use of food banks.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181511","181511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31075","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Payment Systems Regulator will examine the creation of a common-low-cost platform for challenger banks to access the payment system following its creation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181593","181593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31076","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the role and purpose of the Scheme companies following the establishment of the Payment Systems Regulator in 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181595","181595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31077","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what consideration he has given to rolling the Scheme companies into a single payment scheme following the establishment of the Payment Systems Regulator in 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181594","181594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31078","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to ensure that work on (a) account number portability, (b) developing a low-cost platform to support access by challenger banks to the payment system and (c) using payments data to tackle financial crime and fraud is not delayed in the period before the establishment of the Payment Systems Regulator; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181596","181596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31079","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what enforcement powers the Payment Systems Regulator will be able to use when it becomes operational in 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181597","181597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31080","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what range of financial penalties for compliance failure the new Payment Systems Regulator will be able to impose when it becomes fully operational in 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181610","181610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31081","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will consider establishing a shadow Payment Systems Regulator during the period before the Payment Systems Regulator becomes fully operational in 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181598","181598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31082","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the relationship will be between the Payment Systems Regulator and the Bank of England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181591","181591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31083","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the relationship will be between the Payment Systems Regulator and the Competition and Markets Authority; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181592","181592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31084","2014-01-09","Department for Education","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish an impact assessment on recent changes to further education support for 18 year olds.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181567","181567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31085","2014-01-09","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the security of online submission of tax returns; and what estimate he has made of the costs to those who have submitted returns to copycat sites in the last five years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181436","181436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31086","2014-01-09","Cabinet Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposed EU directive on public procurement 2011/0438 (COD).","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181437","181437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31087","2014-01-09","Cabinet Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2013, Official Report, column 587W, on electronic government, when he plans to update the digital landscape research.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181439","181439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31088","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure cyber security and clinical safety for electronic medical applications.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181441","181441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31089","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Public Service Vehicles Accessibility Regulations 2000 to oblige bus operators to provide audio guidance on alighting points for passengers using their services, with particular reference to the needs of blind people and the visually impaired.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181438","181438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31090","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to the Secretary of State for Transport dated 19 November 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Inspector Damian O'Reilly, transferred from the Secretary of State for Transport.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181602","181602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31091","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 25 November 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms E. Miller.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181603","181603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31092","2014-01-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 2 December 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Dr R. Kelly.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181601","181601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31093","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 25 November 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Tariq Razzaq.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181606","181606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31094","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 25 November 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr A. W. Tewolide.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181608","181608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31095","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 25 November 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Thomas Kaplanidis.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181609","181609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31096","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 25 November 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Mohammed Shar Nooh.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181607","181607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31097","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 26 November 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Asif Khan Uriakhel.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181604","181604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31098","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 26 November 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Miss Elfreda James.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181605","181605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31099","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he intends to reply to the letter to the Financial Secretary to the Treasury dated 3 December 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr David Feltham.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181600","181600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31100","2014-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications have been made to the Employment Tribunal in each month since July 2013; how many of those have included an application for fee remittance in each such month; how many fee remittance applicaitons have been processed in each such month; and what proportion of those fee remittance applications have been processed within the 48 hour target turnover in each such month.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181504","181504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31101","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will assess the potential effect on patient care of raising NHS general practice funding from 8.5 per cent to 11 per cent by 2017.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181434","181434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31102","2014-01-09","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letters of 30 October and 17 December 2013 from the hon. Member for Birkenhead on the implications of the Scrap Metal Dealers Act 2013 for legitimate businesses.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181435","181435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31103","2014-01-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what information her Department holds on the use by local library authorities of their powers to charge, by annual subscription, reservation charge or loan charge, for loans of sets of music scores to borrowers living or working in their area.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181508","181508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31104","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the refusal in the Court of Appeal on appeal from the upper tribunal (Administrative Appeals Chamber) on 23 October 2013, of his appeal against the decision made by the Upper Tribunal in CDLA/0735/2009, when disabled claimants entitled to receive the care component of disability living allowance following moves to other EU countries may now expect to receive these payments.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181615","181615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31105","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what basis the French départements d'outre mer of French Guyana, Martinique, Reunion and Guadaloupe are included as part of mainlaind Europe for the purpose of his Department's calculation of entitlement to winter fuel payments.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181614","181614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31106","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many individuals in Barrow and Furness constituency are in receipt of housing benefit; and how many such people are (a) under 25 and (b) under 25 and with a dependent child.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181611","181611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31107","2014-01-09","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many instances of shoplifting occurred in (a) Barrow and Furness constituency and (b) Cumbria in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181612","181612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31108","2014-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what additional resources he has made available to each local authority for clear up and repairs following the floods of December 2013 and January 2014.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181613","181613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31109","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects a decision to be taken on the devolution of Northern Rail services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181512","181512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31110","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the total amount of (a) publicly-funded and (b) private investment in the railways since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181530","181530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31111","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what total premium payments have been made by Northern Rail since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181526","181526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31112","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what fees have been paid by the Government to Virgin West Coast since the introduction of the management contract in December 2012.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181527","181527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31113","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential risks and benefits of devolving Northern Rail services.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181513","181513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31114","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the future government funding requirements in the event that responsibility for Northern Rail services is devolved.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181514","181514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31115","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the profits made by Virgin West Coast since the introduction of the management contract in December 2012.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181516","181516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31116","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what subsidy has been paid by the Government to Virgin West Coast since its franchise was extended in December 2012.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181528","181528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31117","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential benefits to rail passengers of management contracts with operators.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181529","181529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31118","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the split in funding will be between central government and local authorities in the event that responsibility for Northern Rail services is devolved.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181515","181515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31119","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential benefits to the public purse of Directly Operated Railways operating Northern Rail services if it is not possible to agree a new contract with the incumbent operator.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181459","181459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31120","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make a statement on the effects of the second phase of High Speed 2 on (a) East Lancashire and (b) Hyndburn constituency.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181430","181430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31121","2014-01-09","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers were transferred to hospital in (a) Hyndburn constituency and (b) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181584","181584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31122","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been in receipt of pension credits in Hyndburn constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181585","181585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31123","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost per visit was to (a) a GP, (b) accident and emergency and (c) a walk-in centre in (i) England and (ii) East Lancashire in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181586","181586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31124","2014-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, column 158W, on housing: construction, how many of the 267,500 units with planning permission that had been listed as having started on site have subsequently been put on hold.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181564","181564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31125","2014-01-09","Cabinet Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) betting shops and (b) payday loan shops that have opened in each of the last three years in England.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181565","181565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31126","2014-01-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many hectares of land owned by county councils have been made available for housing development in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181448","181448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31127","2014-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities have made applications for assistance under the Bellwin Scheme to meet the costs of flooding in the last three months.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181548","181548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31128","2014-01-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his most recent estimate is of the number of residential units with planning permission; and how many of those (a) have started on site and (b) are yet to start on site.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181540","181540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31129","2014-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to provide assistance under the Bellwin Scheme in respect of current flooding at a rate of 85 per cent or 100 per cent of eligible expenditure.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181549","181549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31130","2014-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households have left their homes as a result of flooding in the last three months.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181550","181550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31131","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 758W, on jobseeker's allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber and 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 756W, on employment and support allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber, how many people were receiving (a) jobseeker's allowance, (b) employment and support allowance - support group and (c) employment and support allowance - work-related group in (i) October 2012 and (ii) each month since then.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181647","181647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31132","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 758W, on jobseeker's allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber and 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 756W, on employment and support allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber, how many people receiving employment and support allowance were moved from the support group to the work-related group; of those how many appealed that decision and of those appealing how many were (a) moved back to the support group as a consequence of the appeal, (b) not moved back to the support group as a consequence of the appeal and (c) still awaiting their appeal decision in October 2012 and each month since then.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181648","181648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31133","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 758W, on jobseeker's allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber and 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 756W, on employment and support allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber, how many people receiving employment and support allowance were moved from the support group to the work-related group; of those how many sought a review of that decision and of those seeking a review how many were (a) moved back to the support group as a consequence of the review, (b) not moved back to the support group as a consequence of the review and (c) still awaiting the decision on their request for review in each month since October 2012.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181649","181649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31134","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 758W, on jobseeker's allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber and 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 756W, on employment and support allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber, how many people receiving employment and support allowance were moved (a) from the support group to the work-related group and (b) from the work-related group to the support group in each month since October 2012.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181650","181650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31135","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 758W, on jobseeker's allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber and 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 756W, on employment and support allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber, how many people receiving jobseeker's allowance (JSA) had their JSA withdrawn as a result of their alleged failure to comply with conditions laid down by his Department in October 2012 and each month since then.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181651","181651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31136","2014-01-09","Department for Education","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the report Validation of Kings Science Academy Financial Management and Governance Self-Assessment covering the period 12 September 2011 to 21 October 2011.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181447","181447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31137","2014-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he intends to respond to the letter of 20 November 2013 from the hon. Member for Bishop Auckland on employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181423","181423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31138","2014-01-09","Department for International Development","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to tackle female genital mutilation overseas.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181560","181560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31139","2014-01-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many applications were made to become a Renaissance Major Partner Museum in 2011-12; and how many such applications were successful.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181562","181562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31140","2014-01-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the criteria are to receive core funding from the Department as a national museum.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181561","181561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31141","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether Ministers in his Department have discussed or received recommendations from other governmental agencies improving his Department's response to subject access requests.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181563","181563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31142","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many officials in his Department were (a) responsible for and (b) available to complete subject access requests (i) nationally and (ii) in each region in 2013.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181566","181566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31143","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what procedures and contingencies his Department has put in place to ensure that responses to subject access requests are completed within the 40 day deadline stipulated by the Data Protection Act 1998.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181624","181624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31144","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the attrition rate was for midwives in the last year for which data is available; what proportion of midwifery students (a) failed to complete their training and (b) failed to obtain their degree in the last five years; how many midwives left the profession within two years of qualifying; and how many midwives are due to retire in the next two years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181559","181559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31145","2014-01-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much large-scale solar capacity has had planning approval (a) accepted and (b) rejected in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181519","181519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31146","2014-01-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many planning applications for (a) onshore and (b) offshore wind farms were (i) approved and (ii) rejected in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181518","181518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31147","2014-01-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many planning applications for large-scale solar projects have been (a) approved and (b) rejected in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181520","181520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31148","2014-01-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much (a) onshore and (b) offshore wind capacity (i) received planning approval and (ii) was rejected in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181517","181517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31149","2014-01-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average time was from the original application for (a) onshore and (b) offshore wind farms to those wind farms coming online in 2013.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181521","181521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31150","2014-01-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average length of time from the original application for large-scale solar projects to those projects coming online was in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181522","181522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31151","2014-01-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change on the time taken to receive planning permission for onshore and offshore wind farms.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181570","181570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31152","2014-01-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress has been made to date on the Government's commitment for 50 per cent of the National Careers Service workforce to hold a relevant qualification at Qualifications and Credit Framework level 6 by 2015; and what assessment he has made of the likelihood that the target will be met.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181583","181583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31153","2014-01-09","Department for International Development","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what meetings she has had with (a) non-governmental organisations and (b) UK civil society relating to the Kuwait II Syria Donor Conference.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181589","181589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31154","2014-01-09","Department for International Development","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the total cost of redundancy has been for staff of her Department since June 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181590","181590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31155","2014-01-08","Department for International Development","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff from her Department have received a redundancy payment since June 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181569","181569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31156","2014-01-09","Department for International Development","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her international counterparts on the Kuwait II Syria Donor Conference.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181587","181587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31157","2014-01-09","Department for International Development","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she last discussed the Kuwait II Syria Donor Conference with the Prime Minister.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181588","181588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31158","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Civil Aviation Authority on the weight of flight recorder equipment and the effect it would have on helicopter performance if universally equipped on the UK helicopter fleet.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181619","181619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31159","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Civil Aviation Authority on the likely cost of equipping flight recorder equipment in all public sector helicopter fleets across the UK.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181620","181620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31160","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2013, Official Report, column 324W, how many (a) deaths and (b) injuries were caused in the 169 helicopter accidents in the past 10 years where no flight recorder was present; and how many (i) deaths and (ii) injuries were caused in helicopter accidents in the last 10 years where flight recorder equipment was present.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181621","181621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31161","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the European Aviation Safety Agency (EASA) or other European Ministers on implications of EASA's forthcoming rule making programme for the regulation of flight recorder equipment in helicopters across European states.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181622","181622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31162","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with helicopter manufacturers and commercial operators in the UK on the potential for voluntary initiatives to ensure the presence of flight recorder equipment on all helicopters.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181623","181623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31163","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will examine in conjunction with the Civil Aviation Authority the adequacy of the existing parameters of regulation for helicopter safety.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181616","181616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31164","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether payment of vehicle excise duty will be monitored through (a) a chip on a vehicle windscreen or registration plate or (b) the registration plate alone following the removal of the requirement to display a paper tax disk on vehicle windscreens.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181572","181572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31165","2014-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the privatisation of the Defence Support Group on (a) the provision of military vehicle maintenance investigations and (b) road safety.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181503","181503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31166","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons he has declined recent requests to meet representatives of the Trussell Trust.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181547","181547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31167","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to meet representatives of the Trussell Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181552","181552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31168","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on cold weather payments in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181553","181553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31169","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many young people who have been in receipt of jobseeker's allowance for over a year have a degree.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181551","181551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31170","2014-01-09","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2013, Official Report, column 366W on children: day care, what information his Department collects on claims made for tax relief for workplace nurseries.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181465","181465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31171","2014-01-09","Department for Education","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) childminders, (b) school nurseries and (c) private and voluntary nursery providers offering free nursery provision for (i) two year-olds and (ii) three and four year-olds.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181575","181575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31172","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has allocated to fund the breastfeeding pilot scheme in South Yorkshire and Derbyshire.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181577","181577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31173","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the trends in the number of baby banks; what estimate he has made of the number of baby banks in the most recent period for which figures are available; and what estimate he has made of the number of families accessing baby banks.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181576","181576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31174","2014-01-09","Department for Education","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which schools are trialling nursery places for two year-olds; and what assistance those schools are receiving from his Department.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181574","181574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31175","2014-01-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the objectives of the inquiry into the sustainability of UK farming and food sectors are; and how they will apply to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181637","181637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31176","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will consider the recommendations of the APPG for Pancreatic Cancer's report, Time to Change the Story: A plan of action for pancreatic cancer.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181638","181638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31177","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date HM Revenue and Customs' offices in Newry will be closed.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181639","181639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31178","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide funding for the Society for General Microbiology for its microbiologists to continue their ongoing research into new treatments for infections and to enable them to carry on their progress in developing an HIV vaccine.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181640","181640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31179","2014-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government has offered to the Russian government following the recent terrorist attacks in that country.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181641","181641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31180","2014-01-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Telephone Preference Service in blocking unwanted cold calls.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181484","181484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31181","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of revenue lost to the Exchequer through the avoidance of VAT and excise duty on beer in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181499","181499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31182","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police forms have been standardised; and what the take up of standardised forms by police forces in England and Wales has been.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181509","181509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31183","2014-01-08","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-06","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, how much the House of Commons Service has paid Hays in the last 12 months; and how much was paid to Hays in that period to advertise positions in the House Service.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181485","181485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31184","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much palm oil was imported for bio-fuels in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181494","181494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31185","2014-01-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment he has made of the licensing of nuclear facilities to utilise the UK's existing nuclear waste stockpile.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181500","181500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31186","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of shares by value owned by individuals.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181501","181501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31187","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many contracts her Department has awarded in the last 10 years to (a) Professor Christian Dustmann and (b) the Centre for Research and Analysis of Migration.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181495","181495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31188","2014-01-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of (a) the accessibility of registered footpaths and (b) their state of maintenance.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181491","181491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31189","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what advice she provides to police forces about action to be taken against individual or groups who threaten or take action against those legally selling alcohol.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181482","181482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31190","2014-01-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to phase out the use of peat in garden compost.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181493","181493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31191","2014-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's plans are for continuing anti-piracy patrols off the coast of Somalia and in the Indian Ocean.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181498","181498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31192","2014-01-08","Cabinet Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had with the Charity Commission about action to prevent tax fraud by charities.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181483","181483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31193","2014-01-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proposals she is considering for the formal commemoration of the 200th anniversary of the Battle of Waterloo.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181466","181466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31194","2014-01-08","Department for International Development","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what schemes her Department currently supports for off-grid electricity supply.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181467","181467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31195","2014-01-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of progress towards EU standard charges for mobile telephones.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181468","181468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31196","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what arrangements exist for the deportation of prisoners to Ukraine.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181476","181476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31197","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department provides to ensure that individuals with TB but without recourse to public funds are provided with shelter and support for the duration of their treatment.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181472","181472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31198","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that online purchases are taxed at the appropriate rate.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181477","181477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31199","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative to amend public health law to permit the detention of individuals who have infectious TB and refuse to comply with prescribed treatment.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181473","181473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31200","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the value for money of the PFI contract at the Princess Royal Hospital Bromley.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181474","181474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31201","2014-01-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on the right of consumers to receive bills by post.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181475","181475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31202","2014-01-08","Department for International Development","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the benefit to children in the developing world of golden rice.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181486","181486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31203","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many overseas students were reported by their colleges as not attending courses in the last year; and how many such students were (a) investigated and (b) deported.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181478","181478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31204","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of levels of fitness of school children (a) nationally and (b) by region.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181487","181487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31205","2014-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost of providing judge's lodgings was in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181469","181469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31206","2014-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the government of South Africa on the crash of Cessna ZS-KOX on 9 September 2004.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181470","181470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31207","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of taking the M6 Toll Road into public ownership.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181471","181471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31208","2014-01-08","Attorney General","2014-01-06","To ask the Attorney General, what further steps he will take to recover payments made to former senior staff at the Serious Fraud Office that were not properly authorised.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181488","181488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31209","2014-01-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many medical students are currently studying at universities in England; and how many such students are UK citizens.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181479","181479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31210","2014-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many unpaid fines there were in the West Midlands in the latest period for which figures are available; and what the monetary value was of those fines.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181496","181496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31211","2014-01-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of data centres on electricity demand; and what discussions he has had with the industry on ways in which demand could be reduced without affecting performance.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181489","181489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31212","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many complaints have been made about the issuing of private parking tickets in the last year; how many have been upheld; and how many companies have been barred from access to the DVLA data base.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181480","181480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31213","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many companies were suspended from receiving vehicle keeper data in 2013.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181497","181497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31214","2014-01-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the costs to fire authorities of dealing with fires at recycling storage depots.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181490","181490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31215","2014-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners were repatriated in 2013 to (a) China, (b) Vietnam, (c) Pakistan, (d) India, (e) Nigeria and (f) Jamaica.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181481","181481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31216","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nursing training places were provided in each region in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181492","181492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31217","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of his Department's progress on implementing the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence's recommendation that funding should be made available to provide patients with three full cycles of IVF.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181523","181523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31218","2014-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of small and medium-sized enterprises recommended by the Network Technical Authority for the G-cloud route to market have been granted access by his Department.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181424","181424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31219","2014-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that small and medium-sized enterprises can bid for procurement contracts without being subcontractors for larger companies.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181429","181429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31220","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on Christmas cards and postage in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181457","181457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31221","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what professional coaching he and other Ministers in his Department have received in the last 12 months; and what the cost was of that coaching.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181455","181455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31222","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on cosmetic make-up in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181456","181456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31223","2014-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government has taken and plans to take to promote the protection of the Hazaras in Pakistan.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181507","181507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31224","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on pot plants in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181505","181505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31225","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on child health of the Government's decision to abolish the Healthy Schools Programme.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181506","181506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31226","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to ask the Child Poverty Action Group for its views when policies are being changed on (a) expenditure and (b) those of working age claiming benefits.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181554","181554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31227","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on the continuation of a national free bus pass for pensioners.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181557","181557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31228","2014-01-09","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-06","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, if he will undertake a consultation on measures to enable hon. Members carrying babies to be able to do so in the division lobbies.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181636","181636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31229","2014-01-09","Cabinet Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps are taken to ensure that Ministerial visits to constituencies are conducted separately from party political activity.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181625","181625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31230","2014-01-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the desirability of the present practice of the Advertising Standards Authority (ASA) in consulting only one designated expert when assessing claims of medical efficacy in advertising and marketing material; and if she will encourage the ASA to adopt a robust peer-reviewed assessment process for such claims in line with the assessments made by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence and other public bodies.","Biography information for David Tredinnick","David Tredinnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181502","181502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31231","2014-01-08","Department for Education","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what budget the National College for Teaching and Leadership has allocated to school-centred initial teacher training (SCITT) in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15; and what estimate he has made of the number of new SCITTs that will be supported in each of those years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181510","181510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31232","2014-01-09","Department for Education","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of more schools providing school-centred initial teacher training on the role of universities in the provision of initial teacher training.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181542","181542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31233","2014-01-09","Department for Education","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what financial incentives the National College for Teaching and Leadership has offered to schools to become a school-centred initial teacher training provider.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181543","181543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31234","2014-01-09","Department for Education","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons and when Ministers encouraged the National College for Teaching and Leadership to promote school-centred initial teacher training in addition to School Direct.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181545","181545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31235","2014-01-09","Department for Education","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools have been encouraged by the National College for Teaching and Leadership to express an interest in becoming a school-centred initial teacher training provider.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181544","181544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31236","2014-01-09","Department for Education","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what communications his Department has issued to (a) universities and (b) other providers in respect of the expansion of school-centred initial teacher training.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181546","181546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31237","2014-01-09","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and which tax avoidance partnership schemes are undergoing legal proceedings.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181573","181573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31238","2014-01-09","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are employed by HM Revenue and Customs to investigate tax avoidance partnerships.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181579","181579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31239","2014-01-09","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how  much HM Revenue and Customs raised by tackling tax avoidance partnerships in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181578","181578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31240","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the public's perception of the influence of Ernst & Young on the reform of corporation tax legislation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181533","181533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31241","2014-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will place in the Library a copy of the performance targets contained in his Department's contract with Atos Healthcare for delivering the work capability assessment.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181534","181534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31242","2014-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what methodology his Department uses to calculate savings to the public purse from removing the MoD Guard Service personnel from some military sites.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181571","181571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31243","2014-01-08","Department for Education","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support children with cancer in the education system.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181599","181599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31244","2014-01-09","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his most recent estimate is of the cost to the UK of implementation of the Scottish rate of income tax.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181446","181446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31245","2014-01-09","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria are used to assess proposals to create new devolved taxes under the Scotland Act 2012; and whether any such proposals have been made.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181464","181464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31246","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average number of daily vehicle movements on the M6 motorway between junctions 4 and 12 was in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181425","181425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31247","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average number of daily vehicle movements on the M6 toll road was in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181426","181426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31248","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure the long-term security of the neuromuscular care advisor role in the East Midlands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181524","181524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31249","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure clinical nurse specialists are available to everyone living with a brain tumour.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181452","181452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31250","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will distribute the Brain Tumour Charity's HeadSmart symptoms awareness cards to every clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181453","181453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31251","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that quality of life issues inform the process of deciding which treatments are available nationally for people living with brain tumours.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181454","181454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31252","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department and NHS are doing to improve access to care and quality of life services for patients and carers affected by brain tumours in light of the National Cancer Patient Experience Survey 2012-13.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181461","181461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31253","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that GPs diagnose brain tumours as quickly as possible.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181449","181449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31254","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of the symptoms of all cancer types to enable GPs and other healthcare providers to make earlier diagnoses and referrals.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181458","181458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31255","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what performance indicators his Department uses to measure the quality and accessibility of care and support services for people living with rare cancers.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181460","181460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31256","2014-01-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to extend credit protection as found in section 54 of the Consumer Credit Act 1974 to goods bought through a hire purchase agreement which have not been received.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181568","181568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31257","2014-01-09","Attorney General","2014-01-06","To ask the Attorney General, what advice has been given to the Crown Prosecution Service in England and Wales when considering whether to charge an alleged perpetrator following domestic abuse complaints.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181631","181631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31258","2014-01-09","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many domestic violence related homicides there were in each police force area in England and Wales in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181632","181632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31259","2014-01-09","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many homicide reviews have been carried out in England and Wales in each of the last three years; and in how many such cases was there evidence of domestic abuse or violence prior to such a homicide.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181633","181633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31260","2014-01-09","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance has been given to police and crime commissioners on the priority that should be given to crimes involving domestic abuse or violence.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181634","181634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31261","2014-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether males convicted of domestic abuse or violence will be supervised by the National Probation Service under the Government's Transforming Rehabilitation arrangements.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181635","181635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31262","2014-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-molestation orders were issued in respect of domestic abuse in England and Wales in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181626","181626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31263","2014-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-molestation orders in respect of domestic abuse were breached in England and Wales in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181627","181627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31264","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what advice has been issued by her Department to police services in England and Wales in respect of how to investigate complaints of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181628","181628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31265","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many call outs there were per police force in England and Wales following complaints of domestic abuse in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181629","181629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31266","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of repeat victims of domestic abuse in England and Wales by the same perpetrator.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181630","181630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31267","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of domestic abuse were reported in England and Wales for the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181642","181642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31268","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of domestic abuse were found to have occurred in England and Wales in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181643","181643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31269","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many allegations of domestic abuse in England and Wales (a) were investigated by the police and (b) resulted in an individual being charged in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181644","181644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31270","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what was the number of (a) prosecutions for domestic abuse, (b) commencement of trials in matters relating to domestic abuse, (c) findings of guilty in matters relating to domestic abuse and (d) findings of not guilty in matters connected with domestic abuse in England and Wales in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181645","181645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31271","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what was the number of reported cases of domestic abuse that were discontinued by the Crown Prosecution Service in England and Wales in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181646","181646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31272","2014-01-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the science and research budget for the next financial year.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181450","181450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31273","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of what the effects would be of the carbon price floor on average wholesale electricity prices in each of the first five years of its operation if all other factors affecting the price remained unchanged.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181532","181532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31274","2014-01-08","HM Treasury","2014-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of what the effects of the carbon price floor would be on consumer electricity bills in each of the first five years of its operation if all other factors affecting the price were unchanged.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181531","181531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31275","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many pages of the environmental statement on High Speed 2 were omitted from USB sticks; and how many such sticks were distributed with information missing.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181445","181445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31276","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims for personal independence payments have been (a) begun and (b) concluded in (i) Wales and (ii) Wrexham since June 2013.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181442","181442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31277","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the current average waiting time in Wales from a consultation being carried out by an independent health professional in relation to a personal independence claim to an assessment being made in respect of that claim is.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181443","181443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31278","2014-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the current average waiting time in Wales from commencement of a personal independence claim to a consultation being carried out by an independent health professional in relation to that claim is.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181444","181444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31279","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many road users have been killed or seriously injured between (a) junction 10 and junction 13 of the M1 motorway, (b) junctions 19 and 20 on the M4 motorway, (c) junctions 15 and 17 on the M5 motorway, (d) junctions 4 and 5 and junctions 8 and 10a on the M6 motorway and (e) junctions 3a and 7 on the M42 motorway in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181582","181582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31280","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the potential cost to the public purse of the Government's proposal to regulate longer distance rail tickets on a single leg basis cost.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181580","181580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31281","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the Government's pilot to sell longer distance rail tickets on a single leg basis cost.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181581","181581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31282","2014-01-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what the criteria were for the distribution of youth contract funding; and for what reasons no such funding was allocated to rural districts.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181463","181463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31283","2014-01-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of households that will see their gas and electricity bills increase as a result of the limitation of the number of tariffs which gas and electricity suppliers can offer.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181422","181422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31284","2014-01-09","Department for Transport","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what feasibility studies he has (a) recently commissioned and (b) is considering commissioning for extensions to the planned HS2 network.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181462","181462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31285","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Office for National Statistics on retention of statistical health outputs relating to (a) winter-related deaths, (b) health inequalities, (c) cancer deaths and (d) alcohol-related deaths.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181432","181432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31286","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff have been employed by her Department and its agencies for the purposes of immigration enforcement in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181431","181431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31287","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library a copy of his Department's response to the Office for National Statistics' Consultation on Statistical Products 2013.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181433","181433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31309","2014-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the scope for cutting red tape in the farming industry.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 901870","901870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31464","2014-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's latest evaluation is of the badger cull pilots.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 901862","901862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31610","2014-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to publish the research commissioned by his Department into food aid provision and access.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 901860","901860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30978","2014-01-08","Department for Transport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the case for lowering the assumed 1.2 metres per second walking speed used for calculating crossing times in his Department's guidance.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181383","181383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30979","2014-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2013, Official Report, column 626W, on Palestinians, what views the Government communicated to the Palestinian Authority prior to or during the meeting of the International Olive Council on the Palestinian Authority's membership of the Council.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181356","181356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30980","2014-01-07","Department of Health","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department gives NHS trusts and bodies regarding the opening hours of pharmacies, with particular regard to (a) 24 hour and (b) Sunday opening; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181367","181367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30981","2014-01-07","Department of Health","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2013, Official Report, column 252W, on stress, what assessment he has made of the Royal Brompton and Harefield NHS Foundation Trust and Imperial College London research on whether stress-induced ischaemia can result in elevation of cardiac troponin; and in what ways that research has informed his Department's policies.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181346","181346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30982","2014-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, columns 48-9W, on standard of living, which reports and policy evaluations on the subjective wellbeing of jobseekers and employment interventions his Department has published in the last 12 months; and if he will publish a web-link to each such report and evaluation.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181345","181345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30983","2014-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, columns 50-2W, on work capability assessment: Wales, what the (a) number and (b) proportion has been of people who underwent work capability assessments and had a mental health condition in each region and constituent part of the UK to date.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181347","181347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30984","2014-01-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 424W, on secondments, to which private-sector organisations the civil servants in 2011-12 were seconded.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181348","181348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30985","2014-01-07","Department of Health","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 413W, on depressive illnesses, if he will commission research into changes in the average age of the onset of depression over the last 50 years and the consequences of such changes for policy development.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181349","181349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30986","2014-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 760W, on social security benefits, at what rate claimants are asked to repay such advances; and whether any (a) interest and (b) other charge is applied.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181344","181344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30987","2014-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether a claimant who makes his Department or a jobcentre aware that they are in financial need will always then be informed that they may be eligible to claim a short-term benefit advance; and if not, under what circumstances such a person will be informed.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181417","181417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30988","2014-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department gives jobcentre staff on when to inform people that they may be eligible for a short-term benefit advance.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181418","181418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30989","2014-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, under what circumstances a benefit claimant in financial need is eligible for a short-term benefit advance.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181419","181419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30990","2014-01-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress his Department has made in implementing the findings of its 2010 study on the extent of the use of snares.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181393","181393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30991","2014-01-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to consult on proposals to regulate or ban the use of snares.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181394","181394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30992","2014-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseeker's allowance claimants in the UK were entitled to short-term benefit advances between April and December 2013; and how many such advances were issued to jobseeker's allowance claimants in the UK between April and December 2013.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181384","181384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30993","2014-01-07","Home Office","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents the Metropolitan Police Service attended in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181395","181395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30994","2014-01-07","Department for Transport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to review the current guidance on pedestrian crossings and the amount of time given to pedestrians to cross the road.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181370","181370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30995","2014-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the breakdown in negotiations between BAE Systems and the United Arab Emirates regarding the purchase of Typhoon fighter jets.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181363","181363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30996","2014-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what consideration he has given to providing additional protection to staff who remain at the British Embassy in Juba.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181377","181377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30997","2014-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent consideration he has given to closing the British Embassy in Juba; and what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Defence on providing additional protection for staff who remain at the British Embassy in Juba.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181378","181378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30998","2014-01-08","Department for International Development","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in South Sudan; what estimate she has made of the number of British nationals who remain in that country; and what assessment she has made of the safety of UK aid workers who remain in the country.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181379","181379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30999","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visa applications are currently on hold pending the outcome of the High Court judgment regarding the minimum income threshold for sponsoring a non-EEA partner and dependent children applying using the family route.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181397","181397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31000","2014-01-07","Department for Education","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to increase teaching about parliamentary democracy and government in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181366","181366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31001","2014-01-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to update the ETSU-R-97 assessment methodology for the noise impact of wind turbine generators.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181385","181385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31002","2014-01-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when his Department plans to consult on changes to the Warm Home Discount for 2015-16 onwards.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181386","181386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31003","2014-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether a claimant of jobseeker's allowance who is accepted onto a course of higher education beginning in January is eligible to claim benefit until that course begins.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181362","181362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31004","2014-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will require Capita to provide a freephone or 03 number for its personal independence payment claimant helpline.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181361","181361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31005","2014-01-07","Department for Transport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the annual cost of running the driving theory test under his Department's contract with Pearson Driving Assessments Ltd is; and what estimate he has made of the annual cost of running that test under the contract with Learn Direct from September 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181392","181392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31006","2014-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Minister for Defence Equipment, Support and Technology last visited Gosport; and when he next plans to visit.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181387","181387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31007","2014-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Minister for International Security Strategy last visited Gosport; and when he next plans to visit.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181388","181388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31008","2014-01-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding his Department provided for delivery of basic skills training by (a) providers graded 1 or 2 by Ofsted and (b) other providers in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181389","181389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31009","2014-01-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations his Department has received from colleges and other providers on (a) funding data not being reconciled by the Skills Funding Agency's systems and (b) resulting delays in payment to private providers.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181391","181391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31010","2014-01-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to support the delivery of basic skills provision in response to the findings of the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development Skills Outlook 2013, published in November 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181390","181390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31011","2014-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential benefits to claimants of disability benefits of allocating such claimants a named point of contact throughout the process of their claim; and if he will make this his policy.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181354","181354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31012","2014-01-07","Home Office","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many failed asylum seekers were returned successfully to (a) China and (b) Iran in the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Tom Harris","Mr Tom Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181351","181351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31013","2014-01-07","Department for Education","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) mean and (b) maximum time taken to respond to letters from (i) members of the public, (ii) organisations and (iii) hon. Members was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181350","181350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31014","2014-01-07","Cabinet Office","2014-01-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had on the use of public service mutuals in the provision of fire services.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181405","181405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31015","2014-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimates his Department has made of the net number of jobs that have been produced by each enterprise zone since their creation.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181355","181355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31016","2014-01-08","Home Office","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were extradited (a) to and (b) from the UK under a European arrest warrant in each of the last three years; and how many such people were accused of sexual offences.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181407","181407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31017","2014-01-08","Department of Health","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many calls were received by NHS111 on (a) 24, (b) 25 and (c) 26 December 2013; and how many clinicians were on duty at NHS111 on those dates.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181408","181408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31018","2014-01-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the total net change in central government funding to (a) Middlesbrough Council and (b) Redcar and Cleveland Council has been since May 2010.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181409","181409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31019","2014-01-07","Department for Transport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people aged under 22 (a) applied for a driving licence and (b) passed their driving test in (i) Great Britain, (ii) Scotland, (iii) Wales and (iv) each English region in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181406","181406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31020","2014-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what measures are in place to record whether people terminating their jobseeker's allowance claims enter employment.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181420","181420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31021","2014-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who terminated their jobseeker's allowance claims that (a) entered employment and (b) continued to be unemployed in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181421","181421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31023","2014-01-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she last met the Chairman of UK Athletics to discuss the forthcoming UK Athletics Championships.","Biography information for Baroness Jowell","Dame Tessa Jowell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181396","181396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31024","2014-01-07","Department of Health","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2013, Official Report, columns 248-9W, on cancer: drugs, what discussions he has had with NHS England about future publication arrangements for expenditure information on the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181369","181369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31025","2014-01-07","Department of Health","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of an overspend in the Cancer Drugs Fund on cancer patients' access to medicines.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181352","181352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31026","2014-01-07","Department of Health","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the effect of negative technology appraisals from the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence on the demand for medicines through the Cancer Drugs Fund since (a) April 2013 and (b) the creation of the Fund in 2010.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181353","181353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31027","2014-01-07","Department of Health","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2013, Official Report, columns 248-9W, on cancer: drugs, what steps NHS England plans to take to improve the (a) collection and (b) analysis of data about spending through the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181368","181368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31029","2014-01-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will introduce a non-commercial, licence-funded digital radio station for children.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181365","181365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31030","2014-01-08","Department for International Development","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the UK is doing to promote good governance and anti-corruption initiatives through the G20.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181381","181381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31031","2014-01-08","Cabinet Office","2014-01-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to encourage other members of the Open Government Partnership to implement their National Action Plans.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181380","181380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31032","2014-01-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the EU Accounting and Transparency Directives are to be transposed into UK law.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181382","181382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31033","2014-01-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the need for public beach operators to (a) carry out risk assessments and (b) provide a minimum level of life saving equipment on public beaches.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181398","181398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31034","2014-01-09","Department of Health","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funds the Government has spent on research for myalgic encephalomyelitis since 2010; and what funds the Government plans to spend on the study of that condition in the next five years.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181399","181399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31035","2014-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many training teams his Department has deployed to Libya since the death of Colonel Gaddafi.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181372","181372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31036","2014-01-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average cost was to the National Grid per MWHr of electricity generated by the Non-Balancing Mechanism category of the Short Term Operating Reserve in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181376","181376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31037","2014-01-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the average carbon dioxide emissions per MWHr of electricity generated by the Non-Balancing Mechanism category of the Short Term Operating Reserve in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181375","181375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31038","2014-01-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the average carbon dioxide emissions per MWHr of electricity generated by the Short Term Operating Reserve in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181374","181374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31039","2014-01-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many newly recruited firefighters have opted out of the firefighters' pension scheme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181371","181371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31040","2014-01-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average cost was to the National Grid per MWHr of electricity generated by the Short Term Operating Reserve in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181373","181373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31041","2014-01-07","Department for Transport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department will re-commence the work on a direct Heathrow Airport link to High Speed 2, which was suspended in January 2013.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181411","181411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31042","2014-01-07","Department for Transport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the addresses of the 67 dwellings that will be significantly affected by noise from High Speed 2 as stated in the Environmental Statement on High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181412","181412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31043","2014-01-07","Department for Transport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list the 300 existing businesses that will be required to relocate together with their full addresses and the number of employees of each company as stated in the Environmental Statement on High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181413","181413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31044","2014-01-07","Department for Transport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what additional support will be available to those businesses that will be forced to relocate as set out in the Environmental Statement on High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181414","181414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31045","2014-01-07","Department for Transport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list the 1,510 jobs together with the organisations that provides them that HS2 Ltd states are at risk as set out in 7.10 of the non-technical summary of the Environmental Statement on High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181415","181415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31046","2014-01-07","Department for Transport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will give the full addresses of (a) the six Grade II listed buildings that will be demolished, (b) the four Grade II listed buildings that will be altered and (c) the eight Grade II listed buildings that will be removed and relocated together with (i) the estimated dates of such demolition, commencement of alterations and removal and (ii) the full addresses of the relocation sites under plans for High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181416","181416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31047","2014-01-07","Department for Transport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the full addresses of the 339 dwellings and 21 community facilities that will be demolished if High Speed 2 proceeds as the Government currently plans.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181410","181410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31048","2014-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2013, Official Report, columns  474-5W, on armed forces covenant, what funding has been allocated to military charities covering Devon and Cornwall.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181357","181357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31049","2014-01-07","Department for Education","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free schools for autistic children have been set up in the UK; and how many such applications are currently being considered by his Department.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181364","181364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31050","2014-01-07","Department for Transport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost of further study of the Isle of Grain option outlined in the interim report of the Airports Commission; and which contractors have been engaged to complete this work.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181359","181359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31051","2014-01-07","Department for Transport","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department is conducting or has commissioned research on the issue of the age of tyres on buses and coaches.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181358","181358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31052","2014-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which UK Parliamentarians visited the (a) Embassy or High Commission and (b) residence of head of mission in (i) Angola, (ii) Democratic Republic of Congo, (iii) Mongolia, (iv) Papua New Guinea, (v) Indonesia, (vi) Equatorial Guinea, (vii) Venezuela and (viii) Turkmenistan in 2013, other than for the purpose of a Ministerial, IPU, CPA or Select Committee visit.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181360","181360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31053","2014-01-07","Department of Health","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require an evidence-based psychiatric or psychological assessment with an accepted diagnostic protocol which would require a doctor to have training and experience in psychological or psychiatric medicine before being able to authorise abortions under ground C of the Abortion Act 1967.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181343","181343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31054","2014-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will amend the 1975 Armed Forces Pension Scheme so that no surviving spouse loses their entitlement if they re-marry or cohabit with a new partner.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181402","181402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31055","2014-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate (a) the proportion of people who have received jobseeker's allowance sanctions who are disabled and (b) the proportion of people of working age who have a disability in the UK.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181401","181401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31056","2014-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces widows who receive a pension through the 1975 Armed Forces Scheme have voluntarily surrendered their pensions on remarriage or cohabitation since the introduction of the scheme.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181403","181403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31057","2014-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces widows who receive a pension through the Armed Forces Scheme 1975 have voluntarily surrendered their pensions on remarriage or cohabitation in 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181404","181404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30709","2014-01-06","Cabinet Office","2013-12-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what consultations his Department conducted with other Government departments and agencies when developing the template for the pan-government web platform gov.uk; what pilot studies were conducted on the user-friendliness of that platform; what reports were prepared on the feedback from such pilots; what the cost was of developing the platform; and what feedback has been received from users since the platform went live.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181777","181777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30710","2014-01-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of (a) recent research published in the US into radon gas contamination of shale gas gathered from fracking and (b) the implications of that research for prospective hydraulic fracturing in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181778","181778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30711","2014-01-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the volumes of naturally occurring radioactive materials (NORM) which may be extracted from the earth in future fracking operations in the UK; what proposals he plans to make for the conditioning, treatment, packaging and long-term management of such radioactive wastes; what information his Department holds on how the US has handled such NORM waste; and what assessment he has made of how the UK can learn from the US experience.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181780","181780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30712","2014-01-06","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish all plans to upgrade Prestatyn Magistrates' Court made in the last six years; and what the current status of these plans is.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181887","181887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30713","2014-01-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she has taken to ensure that all local and national radio stations have equal prominence of access to listeners in the event of digital switchover.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181822","181822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30714","2014-01-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many reports there have been of illegal incursions of Spanish vessels in British Gibraltar Territorial Waters in 2013.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181835","181835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30715","2014-01-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the flight time and combat range is for a fully armed F35B.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181833","181833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30716","2014-01-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how the F35B will be refuelled from the air when carrier-based and operating away from UK shore; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181834","181834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30717","2014-01-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps jobcentres take to ensure that jobseeker's allowance claimants are aware that they can apply for hardship grants.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181825","181825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30718","2014-01-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of jobseeker's allowance claimants sanctions were subsequently overturned on appeal in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181826","181826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30719","2014-01-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps jobcentres take to ensure that jobseeker's allowance claimants are aware that they may appeal sanction decisions.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181827","181827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30720","2014-01-06","Department for Education","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what date the Mentora Academies Trust was approved as a suitable sponsor for academies; and whether that approval is still in force.","Biography information for Sir Tony Baldry","Sir Tony Baldry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181803","181803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30721","2014-01-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in respect of which projects the British Council has collaborated with (a) BAU Bahcesehir University and (b) the BAU Trust in (i) Turkey and (ii) other countries.","Biography information for Sir Tony Baldry","Sir Tony Baldry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181804","181804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30722","2014-01-06","Department for Education","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what date the BAU Foundation Trust was approved as a suitable sponsor for academies; and whether that approval is still in force.","Biography information for Sir Tony Baldry","Sir Tony Baldry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181802","181802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30723","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cases of suspended driving licences involving the DVLA's medical officer have been outstanding for (a) three, (b) three to six and (c) over six months; how many cases there were in each such category 12 months ago; and what steps he is taking to reduce the number of such cases.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181832","181832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30724","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Alstom West Coast Traincare is responsible for all train maintenance on the West Coast Main Line.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181914","181914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30725","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether maintenance staff employed by Alstom West Coast Train Care will return to Virgin Trains under the provisions of the Transfer of Undertakings (Protection of Employment) Regulation 2006, in the event of the sale of Alstom West Coast Traincare.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181910","181910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30726","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether maintenance staff employed by Alstom West Coast Train Care will move to another contract under the provisions of the Transfer of Undertakings (Protection of Employment) Regulation 2006, in the event of the sale of Alstom West Coast Traincare.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181911","181911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30727","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Alstom has informed his Department that it plans to sell Alstom West Coast Traincare.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181912","181912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30728","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have held with Alstom in respect of the future of Alstom West Coast Traincare.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181913","181913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30729","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who is currently responsible for the maintenance of trains on the West Coast Main Line; and at what depots this maintenance takes place.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181915","181915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30730","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what arrangements his Department plans to make to ensure the continuation of train maintenance on the West Coast Main Line in the event of the sale of Alstom West Coast Traincare.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181916","181916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30731","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on train reliability and quality in the event that Alstom West Coast Traincare is sold.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181917","181917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30732","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who will own the rolling stock provided for (a) the Intercity Express programme, (b) the Thameslink Rolling Stock project and (c) Crossrail.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181924","181924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30733","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what obligations there are in the franchise and contract extension for Virgin Trains to maintain its rolling stock; and whether those obligations specify the number and location of maintenance depots.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181918","181918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30734","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to introduce the regulation of fair rates of return for the rolling stock operating companies recommended by the McNulty Rail Value for Money study.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181925","181925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30735","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have held with Alstom in respect of its decision to restructure its transport sector.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181919","181919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30736","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to hold rolling stock in the public interest as recommended by the McNulty Rail Value for Money study.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181926","181926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30737","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consultants have been used to provide advice on train leasing arrangements in the last five years; and what conflicts of interest they declared.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181922","181922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30738","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what leasing costs have been paid to rolling stock leasing companies on each franchise in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181923","181923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30739","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of market share of the rolling stock leasing companies.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181930","181930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30740","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consultancy costs his Department has incurred in the last five years in respect of advice on train leasing arrangements.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181931","181931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30741","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total leasing costs are that have been paid to rolling stock leasing companies in the last 10 years.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181932","181932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30742","2014-01-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on the potential contribution of increased rail freight capacity to (a) regional economic growth and (b) economic growth in West Yorkshire.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181933","181933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30743","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has prepared contingency plans for Directly Operated Rail Services, or a subsidiary of Directly Operated Rail Services, to operate Northern Rail Services in the event that it is not possible to agree a new contract with the incumbent operator.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181985","181985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30744","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of potential benefits to the public purse of Directly Operated Railways operating Northern Rail services in the event that it is not possible to agree a new contract with the incumbent operator.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181986","181986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30745","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether train operating companies qualify for Schedule 8 payments from Network Rail when timetabled rail passenger services are cancelled in advance of bad weather.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181973","181973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30746","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total premium payments made by Northern Rail since 2010 are.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181987","181987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30747","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what Government subsidy has been received by Northern Rail since 2010.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181988","181988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30748","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what revenue support has been received by Northern Rail since 2010.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181989","181989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30749","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what fees have been paid to Virgin West Coast by the Government since the introduction of the management contract in December 2012.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181990","181990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30750","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of former British Rail freight sidings currently owned by freight operating companies would be of greater benefit to rail freight industry (a) in West Yorkshire and (b) on the East Coast Main Line if they were acquired by Network Rail.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181974","181974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30751","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what subsidy has been paid by the Government to Virgin West Coast since their franchise was extended in December 2012.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181991","181991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30752","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the (a) risk and (b) benefits of devolving Northern Rail services.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181992","181992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30753","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the average quantity of effluent that is discharged directly onto railway tracks each week.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181975","181975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30754","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of potential Government funding requirements in the event that responsibility for Northern Rail services is devolved.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181993","181993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30755","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of trains which still discharge effluent directly onto railway tracks.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181976","181976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30756","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the allocation of funding responsibilities will be between central government and local authorities in the event that responsibility for Northern Rail services is devolved.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181994","181994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30757","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the new short-term franchise for Northern Rail services is a contract extension or a new contract.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181995","181995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30758","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of trains which do not have effluent retention tanks.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181977","181977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30759","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consultation his Department has undertaken with passengers regarding the award of a short-term franchise for Northern Rail services.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181996","181996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30760","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on which routes trains still discharge effluent onto railway tracks.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181978","181978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30761","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to his Department in respect of (a) consultancy fees and (b) other matters has been in respect of the short-term franchise for Northern Rail services.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181997","181997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30762","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made representations to the (a) rolling stock operating companies and (b) train operating companies to end the discharging of effluent onto railway tracks.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181979","181979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30763","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made representations to the (a) rolling stock operating companies and (b) train operating companies to modify rolling stock which currently do not have effluent retention tanks.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181980","181980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30764","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps have been taken by (a) rolling stock operating companies and (b) train operating companies to modify rolling stock which does not have retention tanks for effluent.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181998","181998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30765","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government requires all new rolling stock on UK railways to have effluent retention tanks.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181999","181999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30766","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department issues guidelines on the frequency which train effluent tanks must be emptied.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182000","182000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30767","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effect on the safety of (a) rail workers and (b) passengers of the discharge of effluent directly onto railway tracks.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182001","182001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30768","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which train operating companies have received Schedule 8 payments from Network Rail for unplanned disruptions to timetabled rail passenger services that occurred on (a) 27 October 2013, (b) 28 October 2013 and (c) 29 October 2013; and what the amount (i) applied for and (ii) paid by Network Rail was in each case.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181981","181981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30769","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it a requirement that all new railway rolling stock to be introduced in the next 10 years will be configured to retain (a) the existing role of conductor and guard and (b) on-board catering facilities.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182002","182002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30770","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what new railway rolling stock will be introduced in the next 10 years; by what dates; and on what routes.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182003","182003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30771","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that Schedule 8 payments from Network Rail to train operating companies for unplanned disruptions to timetabled rail passenger services that occurred on (a) 27 October 2013, (b) 28 October 2013 and (c) 29 October 2013 will be passed on to passengers.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181982","181982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30772","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions with Passenger Focus he has had regarding Schedule 8 payments from Network Rail to train operating companies for unplanned disruptions to timetabled rail passenger services that occurred on (a) 27 October 2013, (b) 28 October 2013 and (c) 29 October 2013.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 181983","181983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30773","2014-01-06","Department for Transport","2013-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Government plans to make a decision on the devolution of Northern Rail services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182005","182005"
