"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64501","2014-07-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, for what reasons he decided against change following his review into his Department's check-off system for employees' trade union subscriptions.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202858","202858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64502","2014-07-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department has spent on the Warm Front scheme in York local authority area in each year since the inception of that scheme.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202847","202847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64503","2014-07-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) single-pensioner households in York and (b) two-pensioner households in York have received Warm Front assistance in each year since the inception of that scheme; and what the average spend has been on each such household.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202846","202846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64504","2014-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of waste collected in City of York has been recycled in each year since 2008-09; and what funding his Department provided to City of York local authority to increase recycling rates in each of those years.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202848","202848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64505","2014-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much has been spent on biodiversity on the public forest estate in each year since 2004-05.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202849","202849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64506","2014-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much land in Yorkshire was given over to organic farming in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202850","202850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64507","2014-07-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many onshore wind turbines there were in North Yorkshire in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202851","202851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64508","2014-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many hectares of Forestry Commission public forest estate there was in Yorkshire and the Humber in each year since 2008-09; and what the make-up of such forest was.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202852","202852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64509","2014-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much Government spending there was on public forest estate in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202853","202853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64510","2014-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2014, Official Report, column 201W, on the Central African Republic, how much funding the UK will allocate to the deployment of the team of experts to the Central African Republic to investigate sexual violence abuses; how many specialists will be deployed from the UK; when the team of experts will be deployed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202856","202856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64511","2014-07-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, by what process Tony Blair was appointed to the post of Middle East peace envoy; and who approved that appointment.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202942","202942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64512","2014-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of (a) the value of the Senior Pacific Police Leadership Program; and (b) the effect of the level of investment in the program by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202871","202871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64513","2014-07-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise respect for human rights, the rule of law and the case of Mr Alexander Sodiqov with Tajik Foreign Minister Sirojidin Aslov during his upcoming visit to the UK.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202904","202904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64514","2014-07-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that the Gloria Greenwood murder and trial of the suspects is discussed during any future visit to the UK by government ministers from St Lucia.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202947","202947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64515","2014-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policy towards Burma of the recently published brief by the Chin Human Rights Organisation entitled The state of freedom of religion or belief for Chin in Burma, 2013.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202954","202954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64516","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on NHS general dental services in North Yorkshire in 2008-09 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202898","202898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64517","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many organ donations have been received in Yorkshire and the Humber in 2008-09 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202899","202899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64518","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the starting salary of a full-time equivalent NHS nurse in York was in (a) cash and (b) real terms in 1996-97 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202892","202892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64519","2014-07-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on funding for medical research of Scottish independence.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202905","202905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64520","2014-07-02","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the number of avoidable deaths from breast cancer.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202906","202906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64521","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients had been waiting for (a) over six months and (b) three months for in-patient admission at York Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust in March 1997 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202887","202887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64522","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were waiting for elective admission at York Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust on 1 April in 1996 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202888","202888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64523","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the mean and median waiting time was for treatment at accident and emergency in York Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust in 2007-08 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202889","202889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64524","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were waiting for a first out-patient appointment at York Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust on 1 April and 1 October in 2004 and on the same dates in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202890","202890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64525","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the purpose is of NHS England's review of specialised services commissioning; on what date the decision to commission the review was taken; when he expects the review to conclude; whether he intends to consult on the outcome of the review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202935","202935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64526","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average gross earnings of a full-time equivalent NHS nurse were in (a) cash and (b) real terms in (i) England and (ii) York in 1996-97 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202891","202891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64527","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual basic pay per full-time employee for qualified nursing, midwifery and health visiting staff in (a) England, (b) the former North Yorkshire and York Primary Care Trust (PCT), (c) Vale of York Clinical Commissioning Group and (d) York Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust was in 1996-97 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202893","202893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64528","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent NHS (a) hospital doctors, (b) GPs, (c) dentists, (d) nurses and midwives, (e) other clinical staff and (f) staff in total were employed in (i) York and (ii) North Yorkshire in 1996-97 and in each year since; and what the staff costs in each category were in 1996-97 (A) in cash terms and (B) at current prices.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202894","202894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64529","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) GPs, (b) nurses, (c) other clinical staff and (d) staff in total were employed in GP surgeries in the City of York in 1996-97 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202895","202895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64530","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many admissions there were for alcohol-related illnesses in (a) York, (b) North Yorkshire and York Primary Care Trust area and (c) England in 2008-09 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202896","202896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64531","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many finished consultant episodes there were at York Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust in each year since 2008-09 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202897","202897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64532","2014-07-02","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans (a) his Department and (b) NHS England have to capture the experiences of cancer patients outside hospital settings.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202946","202946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64533","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to respond to the letter sent to his Department by Jeena International on 27 May 2014 on the misrepresentation of its organisation in a Parliamentary debate on abortion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202914","202914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64534","2014-07-02","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans NHS England has to conduct the National Cancer Patient Experience survey in 2015.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202903","202903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64535","2014-07-02","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will promote the roll-out of the values and behaviours of the six Cs beyond nursing, midwifery and care staff.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202941","202941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64536","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Care Act 2014 and the care and support statutory guidance, what guidance his Department gives to local authorities on the action they should take if they receive evidence that self-funders and those with personalised care budgets are not paying social care firms enough to pay their staff at least the minimum wage, including remuneration for travel time between appointments.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202968","202968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64537","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what resources will be transferred from NHS England to clinical commissioning groups following the implementation of the recommendations in Prescribed Specialised Services Commissioning Intentions 2014-15 and 2015-16.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202951","202951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64538","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Care Act 2014 and the care and support statutory guidance, whether self-funders and those with personalised care budgets are under an obligation to show that they are paying social care firms enough to pay their staff at least the minimum wage, including remuneration for travel time between appointments.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202967","202967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64539","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what services currently commissioned by NHS England will be commissioned by clinical commissioning groups following the implementation of the recommendations in Prescribed Specialised Services Commissioning Intentions 2014-15 and 2015-16.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202952","202952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64540","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NHS England's review of specialised services commissioning to conclude; who is leading the review; what (a) NHS England employees and (b) other interested parties are participating in the review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202924","202924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64541","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that there should be equality of access to treatment for patients in England with specialised conditions.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202919","202919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64542","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the British Medical Association's press release of 27 May 2014 entitled Abortion guidance ignores gender complexity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202949","202949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64543","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the taking of minutes in meetings conducted by his departmental officials with representatives of (a) other Government departments and (b) outside organisations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202915","202915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64544","2014-07-02","Home Office","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, further to the Answer of 25 June 2014, Official Report, column 210W, on human trafficking, how many calls in each of the years from 2011 to 2014 came from (a) victims, (b) other police forces, (c) the UK border force, (d) other professionals and (e) the public; and how many (i) traffickers were arrested and (ii) victims rescued as a result of information provided by those calls.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202902","202902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64545","2014-07-01","Department for International Development","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which community-based women's organisations in Burma receive funding from her Department to assist victims of sexual violence by the Burmese army.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202920","202920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64546","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Decision Notice of 14 May 2013 on the extension of the reserved legal activities, what steps he is taking to educate consumers on (a) the different types of providers, (b) their respective protections and (c) options for redress.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202956","202956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64547","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons he decided against change following his review into his Department's check-off system for employees' trade union subscriptions.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202859","202859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64548","2014-07-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent on car driving lessons and tests for prisoners in 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202938","202938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64549","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Deerbolt spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202862","202862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64550","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Chelmsford spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202863","202863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64551","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Coldingley spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202864","202864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64552","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Cookham Wood spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202865","202865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64553","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Dartmoor spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202900","202900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64554","2014-07-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners recorded as taking car driving lessons or tests in 2013 (a) absconded and (b) attempted to abscond during such lessons or tests.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202936","202936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64555","2014-07-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) security category and (b) sentence type was of each prisoner recorded as taking car driving lessons and tests in 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202937","202937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64556","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Decision Notice of 14 May 2013 on the extension of the reserved legal activities, what new guidance he has issued on will writing for the legal profession.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202957","202957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64557","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Decision Notice of 14 May 2013 on the extension of the reserved legal activities, what discussions he has had with the will writing industry on strengthening existing regulation of authorised persons in this area.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202958","202958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64558","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received requesting the Government to intervene to require the British Pregnancy Advisory Service to remove advice on its website which alleges that gender-selective abortion is not illegal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202913","202913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64559","2014-07-01","Department for Transport","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what transport grant was given to York Unitary Authority in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202843","202843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64560","2014-07-01","Department for Transport","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was spent on concessionary travel spending in York Unitary Authority in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202844","202844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64561","2014-07-01","Department for Transport","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many serious and fatal road accidents there were in York Unitary Authority in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202845","202845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64562","2014-07-01","Department for Transport","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the performance of the Maritime and Coastguard Agency during the search for the Water Rail between 20 and 22 May 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202922","202922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64563","2014-07-01","Department for Transport","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether MRCC Aberdeen was staffed at below risk assessed levels on any shifts between 20 May and 22 May 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202901","202901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64564","2014-07-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants have been sanctioned in each month since October 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202907","202907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64565","2014-07-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what budget was set for the youth contract in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202908","202908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64566","2014-07-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent on the youth contract in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202909","202909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64567","2014-07-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department is currently pursuing plans for jam jar bank accounts under the universal credit programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202948","202948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64568","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of (a) children, (b) pensioners and (c) households fell below 60 per cent of contemporary median equivalised income (i) before and (ii) after housing costs in 2007-08 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202925","202925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64569","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) the City of York local authority area and (b) York Central constituency were in receipt of (i) the basic state pension and (ii) pension credit in 2008-09 and in each year since; and what the average weekly value of pension credit received was in each case during those periods.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202926","202926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64570","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total cost incurred by his Department was of appeals against employment and support allowance decisions in 2010 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202927","202927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64571","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people wait more than (a) three, (b) six, (c) nine and (d) 12 months to receive a tribunal appeal decision following an employment and support allowance decision; and what steps the Government is doing to speed up that process.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202928","202928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64572","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time is that people wait to receive employment and support allowance following a successful tribunal appeal.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202929","202929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64573","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in (a) York Central constituency and (b) York Unitary Authority area received winter fuel payments in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202930","202930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64574","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households with a person aged 75 or over in (a) York Central constituency and (b) York Unitary Authority area were eligible for a free television licence in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202931","202931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64575","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) York Central constituency and (b) York Unitary Authority area received pension credit in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202932","202932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64576","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children in Yorkshire were in (a) relative and (b) absolute poverty in 1997-98 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202933","202933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64577","2014-07-01","HM Treasury","2014-06-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many families in (a) York Central constituency and (b) York Unitary Authority area received child and working tax credits in 2009 and in each year since.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202934","202934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64578","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2014, Official Report, columns 171-2W, on children: maintenance, how much of the amount is written off in child maintenance arrears since November 2012; how much is attributable to (a) a request from the parent with care to write off the arrears, (b) the death of a non-resident parent, (c) the death of a parent with care, (d) an interim maintenance assessment between 1993 and 1995 and (e) a debt where the non-resident parent had been told that no further action would ever be taken.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202917","202917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64579","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference the Answer of 27 June 2012, Official Report, column 296, on children: maintenance, what proportion of Child Support Agency arrears cases include arrears that have been suspended; and what steps have since been taken to establish the proportion of cases where arrears have been (a) temporarily and (b) permanently suspended.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202921","202921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64580","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2014, Official Report, columns 171W, on children: maintenance, on how many occasions where contingency measures had to be employed by the Department's Child Maintenance Group (CMG) to support the work of the Child Maintenance Options Service it was the case that call demands exceeded forecasted volumes; how many CMG staff were deployed on each such occasion; and in which office or offices of the CMG these trained contingency staff were located.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202918","202918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64581","2014-07-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants have become ineligible for the benefit as a consequence of increased income since October 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202945","202945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64582","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what average amount of child maintenance arrears is owed to parents with care.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202867","202867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64583","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many child support agency arrears cases are cases where there is no ongoing liability.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202868","202868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64584","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Child Support Agency has in place to review decisions taken to temporarily suspend action to recover child maintenance arrears and to establish whether the circumstances which led to the temporary suspension of recovery action have changed.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202870","202870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64142","2014-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many delegates from manufacturers based in Northern Ireland were invited to the BIS Manufacturing Summit 2014 held on 19 June 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202561","202561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64143","2014-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many applicants for the Start-Up Loans Scheme have been received from Northern Ireland; and what value of such loans have been provided for new businesses in Northern Ireland since the scheme was launched.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202565","202565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64144","2014-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what work the National Space Agency is doing to support the development of a regional space small and medium-sized enterprise sector in Northern Ireland; and what steps his Department has taken to support space-related events and conferences for decision-makers, the public, industry or academia in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202605","202605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64145","2014-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many young people from (a) Harrogate and Knaresborough constituency, (b) North Yorkshire and (c) Yorkshire and the Humber (i) applied for and (ii) started a degree course in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202646","202646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64146","2014-07-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reason allowing employers which wish to continue with current apprenticeship funding arrangements to do so was not listed as an option in his Department's recent consultation on the future of apprenticeships.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202656","202656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64147","2014-07-01","Cabinet Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the cost to industry of his Department's requirement for Level 2 Building Information Modelling.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202615","202615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64148","2014-06-30","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-26","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what additional central government funding is available to electoral registration officers for the purpose of electoral registration in each of the last 10 years; and which local authorities were successful in bidding for such funding.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202603","202603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64149","2014-06-30","Cabinet Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what Government spending was in reform of the process of procurement and across central Government in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202636","202636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64150","2014-07-01","Cabinet Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many private sector employees aged over 21 and under the state pension age have gross earnings between £111 and £192 per week in each constituent part and region of the UK.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202586","202586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64151","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of reserve servicemen who have been allocated the wrong tax code by HM Revenue and Customs as a result of their additional income accruing from military duties.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202559","202559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64152","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with the (a) Prudential Regulation Authority and (b) Financial Conduct Authority about reports of UK banks paying allowances to employees in order to avoid the EU's bonus cap; and what steps he plans to take to reduce such practices.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202634","202634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64153","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will estimate the additional receipts accruing to the Exchequer as a result of changes in levels of employment since May 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202645","202645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64154","2014-07-02","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will meet representatives of financial institutions to discuss how those institutions can assist customers to get the best return on their savings.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202658","202658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64155","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much corporation tax was raised by HM Treasury in Northern Ireland in the last full financial year.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202564","202564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64157","2014-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what input officials in his Department sought from their counterparts in the Northern Ireland Executive in preparation for the UK's attendance at the Education, Youth, Culture and Sport Council held in Brussels on 20 and 21 May 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202604","202604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64158","2014-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if his Department will estimate the level of financial benefit in (a) Harrogate and Knaresborough constituency and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber as a result of the upcoming launch of the Tour de France.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202643","202643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64159","2014-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what quantitative criteria have been used to set to remote the risk probability of a collision involving a Tornado aircraft.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202641","202641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64160","2014-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which contracts with his Department worth over £50 million are behind schedule owing to the failure of suppliers to deliver to an agreed schedule; and in the case of each such contract, who the suppliers were.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202639","202639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64161","2014-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much of the £1.2 billion underspend in his Department's equipment budget in 2012-13 arose as a result of programme slippage; what programmes were behind schedule; and for what reason those programmes were behind schedule.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202638","202638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64162","2014-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the £72.3 billion allocated in the Defence and Equipment Plan 2013 supporting existing in-service equipment, how much of that allocation is devoted to (a) nuclear propulsion and (b) nuclear weapons.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202640","202640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64163","2014-07-01","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many local authorities in England use external contractors to assist with the delivery of childcare services excluding fostering and adoption.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202593","202593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64164","2014-07-01","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what meetings Ministers in his Department have had on the outsourcing of local authority children's services since May 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202592","202592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64165","2014-07-01","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has contributed funds to assist local authorities in the payment of external contractors to deliver childcare services excluding fostering and adoption.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202589","202589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64166","2014-07-01","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much local authorities have spent on external contractors employed to deliver childcare services, excluding fostering and adoption in (a) 2014 to date and (b) each of the last three years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202587","202587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64167","2014-06-30","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to record cases of bullying as reported by victims in schools by counts of cyber-bullying and similar sub-categories.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202637","202637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64168","2014-07-02","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to make e-books available from public libraries.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202660","202660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64169","2014-06-30","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) primary and (b) secondary school places have been created in (i) Harrogate and Knaresborough constituency, (ii) Yorkshire and the Humber and (iii) the North of England since May 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202648","202648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64170","2014-07-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of potential changes in the number of jobs at the National Careers Service arising from the Government's digital-by-default policy.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202577","202577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64171","2014-07-01","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he plans to take to ensure that young people without access to the necessary computer equipment have access to a digital-by-default careers service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202578","202578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64172","2014-07-01","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to ensure that (a) young people in custody and (b) other difficult-to-reach young people are able to access a digital-by-default careers service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202579","202579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64173","2014-06-30","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of levels of literacy and numeracy in (a) primary school leavers and (b) secondary school leavers in (i)Harrogate and Knaresborough constituency, (ii) Yorkshire and the Humber, (iii) the North of England and (iv) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202644","202644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64174","2014-07-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans he has to make changes to mandatory green energy charges on consumer bills; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202576","202576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64175","2014-07-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he expects the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change to publish its Fifth Assessment Report.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202659","202659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64176","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to ensure that the recent reductions in wholesale gas prices available to energy companies are benefiting consumers.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202635","202635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64177","2014-07-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, to which locations pending applications for hydraulic fraturing relate.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202657","202657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64178","2014-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research his Department has undertaken of the effect of the Badger Vaccination Deployment Project on the incidence of bovine TB in cattle.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202590","202590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64179","2014-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to expand the training provided by the Badger Vaccination Deployment Project.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202591","202591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64180","2014-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people have been prosecuted for setting intertidal nets in England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202560","202560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64181","2014-07-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has had discussions with his counterparts in the devolved administrations on the proposed National Pollinator Strategy to reverse the decline in the bee population in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202661","202661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64182","2014-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential suffering felt by badgers through gaseous methods of slaughter.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202630","202630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64183","2014-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which policies of other countries he has assessed with regards to the gassing of badgers.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202631","202631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64184","2014-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the government of Bahrain about the death of Abdulaziz al-Abbar.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202558","202558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64185","2014-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the release of Eyal Yifrah, Gilad Sha'ar and Naftali Frenkel, who were abducted in the West Bank on 12 June 2014.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202606","202606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64186","2014-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to consult with interested hon. Members before the next Ministerial visit to Colombia.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202607","202607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64187","2014-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress he has made in ensuring that Palestinian children are interrogated only in the presence of their parents and lawyers.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202608","202608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64188","2014-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the government of Indonesia on human rights in West Papua.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202599","202599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64189","2014-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Colombian counterpart seeking clarification of the actions being taken by the Colombian government to ensure the safety of land restitution claimants in that country.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202585","202585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64190","2014-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 710W, on Palestinians, what response Prime Minister Netanyahu's office made on the issue of demolitions in East Jerusalem or the rest of the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202651","202651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64191","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether Ministers from the devolved administrations were invited to attend the Global Dementia Legacy Event in London in June 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202562","202562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64192","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with its counterparts in Northern Ireland ahead of the Global Dementia Legacy Event in London on 19 June 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202563","202563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64193","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the Care Act 2014 Part 1 regulations to be laid before the House.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202566","202566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64194","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the Government has spent on prostate cancer research in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202567","202567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64195","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure the same standard of care across the country for those diagnosed with prostate cancer.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202568","202568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64196","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will include prostate cancer in the next Be Clear on Cancer awareness campaign; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202569","202569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64197","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for appointments at GP surgeries.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202575","202575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64198","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adults with (a) autism and (b) learning disabilities accessed care and support under the Fair Access to Care Standards eligibility criteria in (i) Easington constituency, (ii) County Durham, (iii) North East England and (iv) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202595","202595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64199","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adults with autism in England receive support having previously been identified by a local authority as being at risk of abuse or neglect.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202594","202594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64200","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that national guidelines on asthma care are implemented; what data his Department is gathering to improve asthma care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202655","202655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64201","2014-07-01","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passport applications have been processed by the passport office in Belfast in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202588","202588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64202","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions she has had with the Lord Chancellor on the introduction of section 77 of the Criminal Justice and Immigration Act 2008 in relation to data protection offences; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202612","202612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64203","2014-06-30","Cabinet Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment her Department has made of trends in the level of crime in (a) Harrogate and Knaresborough constituency, (b) North Yorkshire and (c) Yorkshire and the Humber in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202647","202647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64204","2014-07-03","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to establish a statutory system of guardianship to support victims of child trafficking.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202632","202632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64205","2014-07-03","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to recognise child trafficking as a separate offence to adult trafficking.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202633","202633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64206","2014-07-01","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made by the Cyber Crime Reduction Partnership over the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202611","202611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64207","2014-07-01","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will ensure that the regulations governing the new contract for the specialist support providers allow bids to provide ongoing care and support once victims exit the shelter service, at the end of the 45 days period irrespective of whether they have received a Conclusive Grounds decision.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202652","202652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64208","2014-07-01","Cabinet Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress has been made by the UK Computer Emergency Response Team since its launch on 31 March 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202609","202609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64209","2014-07-01","Department for International Development","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which overseas organisations funded by her Department restrict employment to members of particular faiths.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202613","202613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64210","2014-07-01","Department for International Development","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the level of food, fuel and medical supplies entering Gaza each day.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202616","202616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64211","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2014, Official Report, column 458W, on open prisons, what data his Department holds on the number of (a) prisoners in an open prison who previously breached a licence condition while released on temporary licence and (b) prisoners in open prisons who have previously absconded or escaped from prison on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202556","202556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64212","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to increase the penalties for uninsured drivers.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202610","202610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64213","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions the disciplinary punishment of additional days was imposed on prisoners in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202642","202642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64214","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Sudbury spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours per week spent working by prisoners in that prison was in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202584","202584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64215","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Swaleside spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours per week spent working by prisoners in that prison was in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202583","202583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64216","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Styal spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours per week spent working by prisoners in that prison was in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202582","202582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64217","2014-07-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the NSPCC's Order In Court campaign seeking change changes to the way the criminal justice system treats children.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202662","202662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64218","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will strengthen levels of protection of elderly and vulnerable people by allowing the Office of the Public Guardian to investigate abuses of power of attorney in cases where these powers have been revoked.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202570","202570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64219","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to increase levels of protection for elderly and vulnerable people who fall victim to abuse of power of attorney.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202573","202573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64220","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Durham spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours per week spent working by prisoners was in that prison in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202625","202625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64221","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will take steps to expand the investigatory powers of the Office of the Public Guardian to better protect elderly and vulnerable people in cases in which power of attorney is abused; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202574","202574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64222","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Sutton Park spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours per week spent working by prisoners was in that prison in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202626","202626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64223","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Eastwood Park spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours per week spent working by prisoners was in that prison in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202627","202627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64224","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Edmonds Hill spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours per week spent working by prisoners was in that prison in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202628","202628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64225","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Elmley spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours per week spent working by prisoners was in that prison in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202629","202629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64226","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Stocken spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours per week spent working by prisoners in that prison was in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202580","202580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64227","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Stoke Heath spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours per week spent working by prisoners in that prison was in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202581","202581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64228","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he will take to introduce safeguards to power of attorney to better protect elderly and vulnerable people from abuses of that power.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202571","202571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64229","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many successful prosecutions for abuse of power of attorney were brought forward in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202572","202572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64230","2014-06-30","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many people are in prisons in Northern Ireland for terrorist-related offences; what the age profile is of those prisoners; what assessment she has made of that age profile; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202557","202557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64231","2014-07-01","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when she last met the (a) CEO and (b) Chair of the British Business Bank to discuss how that organisation can more effectively support Northern Ireland businesses; and if she will make statement.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202614","202614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64232","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many and what proportion of people were deleted from the electoral register after the second year of non-response to electoral canvass in the 10 local authorities with the (a) greatest and (b) smallest decreases; and what parliamentary constituencies are covered by such local authorities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202600","202600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64233","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which 50 local authorities had the largest decrease in electoral registration between December 2012 to March 2014; and which parliamentary constituencies cover such local authorities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202601","202601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64234","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which local authorities have failed standard 3 door-to-door canvassing more than once and (a) have and (b) have not applied for additional central government funding for electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202602","202602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64235","2014-06-30","Department for Transport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre at Belfast was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in (a) April 2014 and (b) May 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202596","202596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64236","2014-06-30","Department for Transport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre at Stornoway was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in (a) April 2014 and (b) May 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202597","202597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64237","2014-06-30","Department for Transport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre at Liverpool was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in (a) April 2014 and (b) May 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202598","202598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64238","2014-07-01","Department for Transport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have had with trade union representatives from the maritime sector on the employment and related implications of implementing the maritime fuel suulphur regulations in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202649","202649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64239","2014-07-01","Department for Transport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has commissioned or received any (a) internal or (b) external reports on the effectiveness of sulphur technology on maritime vessels.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202650","202650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64240","2014-07-01","Department for Transport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's responsibility is for long range search and rescue at sea.","Biography information for Lord Arbuthnot of Edrom","Mr James Arbuthnot","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202654","202654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64241","2014-07-01","Department for Transport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department intends to acquire aircraft to carry out long range search and rescue at sea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Arbuthnot of Edrom","Mr James Arbuthnot","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202653","202653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64270","2014-07-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what work the British Business Bank is doing in Northern Ireland to promote its services to small businesses located there.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202620","202620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64271","2014-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of his Department's consumption in kWh of (a) gas and (b) electricity in each month since June 2010; and what the cost of such consumption has been in each such month.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202700","202700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64272","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which powers and responsibilities the Financial Conduct Authority has not inherited from the Office of Fair Trading; and which financial regulatory body has inherited each such power and responsibility.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202724","202724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64273","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will review the scope of the consumer credit regulatory powers of the Financial Conduct Authority.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202725","202725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64274","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what requirement will be placed on Wonga to track down the address of each customer due financial compensation for unfair and misleading debt collection practices.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202726","202726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64275","2014-06-30","Cabinet Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many grades there are in the Civil Service.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202819","202819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64276","2014-06-30","Cabinet Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what security standards his Department mandates with Level 2 Building Information Modelling.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202666","202666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64277","2014-07-01","Cabinet Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2014, Official Report, column 228W, on billing, what the value is of the sums being claimed by outstanding creditors at 31 May 2014.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202832","202832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64278","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 29W, on gold: prices, and the academic draft report of February 2014, by Professor Rosa Abrantes, Adviser to the EU and International Organisation of Securities Commission on Financial Benchmarks, entitled Gold Price Fix, and her reports of systemic manipulation of the twice daily gold fix over several years, if he will make an assessment of the effect of (a) US regulatory authorities' interventions in the gold market and (b) such interventions on gold market-related securities in ISAs.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202836","202836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64279","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring foward legislative proposals to amend the statutory powers of the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) to permit the FCA to investigate alleged illegal actions undertaken before its creation.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202688","202688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64280","2014-07-01","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what role his Department played in the decision to separate Lloyds and TSB.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202713","202713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64281","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of his Department's consumption in kWh of (a) gas and (b) electricity in each month since June 2010; and what the cost of such consumption has been in each such month.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202710","202710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64282","2014-07-01","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2014, Official Report, column 197W, on Mapeley, whether HM Revenue and Customs reviewed these commercial provisions following the raising of financial concerns by Mapeley in November 2001.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202739","202739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64283","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on the regulation of the practice of dark pool trading by high frequency bank traders.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202699","202699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64284","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 29W, on gold: prices, and to the Financial Conduct Authority's decision to fine Barclays Bank for gold fix manipulation, if he will make an assessment of the effect of (a) US regulatory authorities' interventions in the gold market and (b) such interventions on gold market-related securities in ISAs.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202775","202775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64285","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of how many pumps were available in each fire and rescue authority (a) during periods of Fire Brigades Union strike action in 2013-14 and (b) on comparable non-strike days in the same period.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202818","202818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64286","2014-07-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's publication of work carried out by the Government Actuary's Department Costings and Correspondence on 12 June 2014, what plans he has to bring forward new proposals based on options set out in that document negotiations on firefighters' pensions.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202716","202716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64287","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of his Department's consumption in kWh of (a) gas and (b) electricity in each month since June 2010; and what the cost of such consumption has been in each such month.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202701","202701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64288","2014-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many councils in (a) England, (b) Wales and (c) Scotland funded discretionary housing payments beyond the funds allocated to them by his Department in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202667","202667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64289","2014-06-30","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to school clothing grants via (a) vouchers and (b) cash or cheque to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202668","202668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64290","2014-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to free (a) swimming and (b) other leisure services to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202669","202669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64291","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has given to local authorities on dealing with trees that are subject to a preservation order.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202789","202789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64292","2014-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what future foreign visits the Minister for Sport, Tourism and Equalities has planned in relation to her departmental duties; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202720","202720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64293","2014-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the cost was of the Minister for Sport, Tourism and Equalities' recent visit to Brazil; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202721","202721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64294","2014-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will publish the official appointments which took place during the Minister for Sport, Tourism and Equalities' recent visit to Brazil; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202722","202722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64295","2014-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many foreign visits the Minister for Sport, Tourism and Equalities has made arising from her departmental roles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202723","202723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64296","2014-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the importance of regional tourism in the UK; and what steps he has taken to support small, local hospitality businesses.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202718","202718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64297","2014-07-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of films made in the UK as co-productions with foreign companies in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202729","202729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64298","2014-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to help the tourism industry retain its role as a key provider of skills and training for the UK workforce.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202719","202719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64299","2014-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings of the Great Britain Tourism Survey that domestic trips in the UK fell by three million in 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202781","202781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64300","2014-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the cost is of all foreign visits undertaken by the Minister for Sport, Tourism and Equalities as part of her official duties to date.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202727","202727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64301","2014-07-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of cinemas in operation in (a) Scotland, (b) England, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland in each year between 1997 and 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202734","202734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64302","2014-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of his Department's consumption in kWh of (a) gas and (b) electricity in each month since June 2010; and what the cost of such consumption has been in each such month.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202702","202702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64303","2014-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the titles of all reports covering the effects of the use of a UK nuclear weapon produced by (a) his Department and (b) the Atomic Weapons Establishment and its predecessor body for his Department in the last 30 years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202696","202696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64304","2014-07-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what Russian Navy ships HMS Severn intercepted in the English Channel on 25 June 2014; and whether HMS Severn was assigned to the Fleet Ready Escort role at that time.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202834","202834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64305","2014-06-30","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to benefits from the pupil premium to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202675","202675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64306","2014-06-30","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to free early education to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202676","202676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64307","2014-06-30","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department takes to promote the teaching of water safety in schools.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202697","202697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64308","2014-06-30","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of his Department's consumption in kWh of (a) gas and (b) electricity in each month since June 2010; and what the cost of such consumption has been in each such month.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202703","202703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64309","2014-07-01","Department for Education","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will review whether the recent guidance, keeping children safe in education, distinguishes between legislation which applies to further education colleges as opposed to sixth form colleges; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202690","202690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64310","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to the Warm Home Discount to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202670","202670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64311","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to WaterSure to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202671","202671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64312","2014-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what deadline has been set by his Department for former oil refineries being converted to bulk storage and distribution terminals to make the necessary upgrades to meet post-Buncefield standards; and how rigorously such standards are being enforced by the Environment Agency.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202808","202808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64313","2014-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that former oil refineries being converted to bulk storage and distribution terminals meet post-Buncefield health and safety requirements.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202807","202807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64314","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the duration in days that airports in the south east of England would be able to run at full aviation fuel demand capacity in the event of an emergency on the scale of the Buncefield explosion in 2005.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202806","202806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64315","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what mechanisms his Department has put in place to monitor the amount of available capacity in the UKOP, GPSS and MLP UK pipeline systems.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202801","202801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64316","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department has taken to ensure equality of access to the  UKOP, GPSS and MLP UK pipeline systems.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202802","202802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64317","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what strategic level his Department has agreed with industry for the amount of motor gasoline, diesel and aviation fuel products required to meet the compulsory stock oligations.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202803","202803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64318","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion as a percentage of the compulsory stock obligations for motor gasoline, diesel and aviation fuel products are currently being held physically on the UK mainland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202804","202804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64319","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the duration in days that the South East of England fuel demand could run at full capacity based on current stock levels of (a) refined petrol and (b) diesel products in the event of an emergency on the scale of the Buncefield explosion in 2005.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202805","202805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64320","2014-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of marine dredging applications that will be dealt with by the Marine Management Organisation using the online marine licensing system in 2014-15.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202815","202815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64321","2014-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the average length of time taken by the Marine Management Organisation to approve a marine dredging application using the outline marine licensing system since 2009.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202816","202816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64322","2014-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many inshore fisheries and conservation authorities in England have bylaws to prohibit the setting of intertidal nets; and how many land-based officers in each authority police and enforce those bylaws.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202817","202817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64323","2014-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many marine dredging applications have been dealt with by the Marine Management Organisation using the online marine licensing system since 2009.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202809","202809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64324","2014-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department (a) has funded or (b) plans to fund badger vaccination against bovine TB in this calendar year.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202736","202736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64325","2014-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Answer to the hon. Member for Brighton, Pavilion of 25 November 2013, Official Report, column 20W, on bovine tuberculosis, whether his Department has since commissioned any research about the safety, humaneness and effectiveness of gassing badgers.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202742","202742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64326","2014-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress he has made on provision for the kennelling and seizure of suspected dangerous dogs; and what changes he expects to make to the regulations on dangerous dogs.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202747","202747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64327","2014-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much resource his Department plans to provide as matched funding for badger vacination to tackle bovine TB in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202618","202618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64328","2014-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of his Department's consumption in kWh of (a) gas and (b) electricity in each month since June 2010; and what the cost of such consumption has been in each such month.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202704","202704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64329","2014-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many cases of lungworm in dogs have been identified in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202698","202698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64330","2014-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the three Israeli teenagers kidnapped in the West Bank on 12 June 2014; and what steps he has taken to secure their release.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202712","202712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64331","2014-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of his Department's consumption in kWh of (a) gas and (b) electricity in each month since June 2010; and what the cost of such consumption has been in each such month.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202705","202705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64332","2014-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his future plans are for the level of staff and budget resourcing on his Department's Ending Sexual Violence Initiative.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202714","202714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64333","2014-07-01","HM Treasury","2014-06-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps are being taken in response to EU Council Regulation 692/2014 to (a) identify goods originating in Crimea or Sevastopol and exclude them from entry into the UK and (b) ensure no individual or business based in the UK provides, directly or indirectly, financing, financial assistance or insurance or reinsurance related to the import of such goods from Crimea or Sevastopol.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202740","202740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64334","2014-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for the UK of the decision of the EU Council to implement restrictive measures on trade with Crimea and Sevastopol on 25 June 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202624","202624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64335","2014-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Embassy in Saudi Arabia provides support and protection to human rights activists in that country.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202665","202665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64336","2014-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when it is planned that government ministers from St Lucia will next visit the UK.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202663","202663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64337","2014-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss with his counterparts in St Lucia the effectiveness of the St Lucian (a) criminal justice system and (b) forensic laboratories in relation to the investigation of the Gloria Greenwood murder and prosecution of suspects.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202664","202664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64338","2014-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise the case of Fowzan al-Harbi with the Saudi Arabian government.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202746","202746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64339","2014-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what resources his Department plans to commit to the Implementation Plan for the UK's National Action Plan on United Nations Security Council Resolution 1325.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202774","202774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64340","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many knee replacement revisions were carried out by the NHS in England in the last three years; and how long the average time interval was between total knee replacement and subsequent revision procedures.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202778","202778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64341","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost was of NHS knee replacement operations and subsequent revisions in England in the last three years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202779","202779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64342","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS knee replacement operations were carried out in England, by region, in the last three years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202780","202780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64343","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the current waiting times are for NHS knee replacement operation in England, by region.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202777","202777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64344","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2014, Official Report, column 241W, on billing, what the value was of all outstanding legacy creditors on 1 June 2014.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202741","202741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64345","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of his Department's consumption in kWh of (a) gas and (b) electricity in each month since June 2010; and what the cost of such consumption has been in each such month.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202706","202706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64346","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to (a) free prescriptions, (b) free eye tests and (c) free dental care to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202672","202672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64347","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to Healthy Start vouchers and vitamins to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202673","202673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64348","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the costs to the NHS of untreated liver disease in one person.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202827","202827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64349","2014-07-01","Cabinet Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people aged (a) under 18 and (b) 18 years and over died as a consequence of a condition related to alcohol misuse in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202826","202826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64350","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many members of staff and at what grades work for the National Clinical Director for Cancer.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202828","202828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64351","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what organisations or individuals Ministers or officials of his Department have met to discuss standardised packaging of tobacco in the last 12 months; which Ministers or officials were present at those meetings; and who represented each organisation present at those meetings.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202831","202831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64352","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people aged (a) under 18 and (b) 18 years and over were admitted to hospital with a condition related to alcohol misuse in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202829","202829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64353","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the availability of a range of housing and care options for people with physical disabilities and learning difficulties.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202793","202793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64354","2014-07-01","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children aged (a) under 10 and (b) 10 years and over were admitted to hospital with a (i) primary and (ii) secondary diagnosis of liver disease in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202830","202830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64355","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with providers of residential care for people with physical impairments and learning difficulties on proposals for home closure.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202794","202794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64356","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many places in residential care homes were available for people with (a) physical impairments and (b) learning difficulties or complex needs in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202795","202795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64357","2014-07-01","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made on reaching a settlement with Raytheon Systems Ltd on the e-Borders programme; and when the arbitration progress is scheduled to be completed.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202833","202833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64358","2014-07-03","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure that participants in the Glasgow Commonwealth Games 2014 are prevented from staying in the UK illegally after the Games have finished.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202835","202835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64359","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of police hunts for all prisoners who have absconded or escaped from prisons in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202787","202787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64360","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of her Department's consumption in kWh of (a) gas and (b) electricity in each month since June 2010; and what the cost of such consumption has been in each such month.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202707","202707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64361","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to make a decision on the request to authorise water cannon for use by the police in England and Wales; and if she will place in the Library a copy of the advice and business case she has received on the use of water cannon in mainland UK.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202717","202717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64362","2014-07-01","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional support she is providing to the passport office in Belfast.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202621","202621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64363","2014-07-01","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what financial provision her Department has made to cover the (a) ongoing legal costs of and (b) costs of a potential settlement resulting from the binding arbitration process brought by Raytheon Systems Ltd.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202733","202733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64364","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the report by the Independent Chief Inspector of Borders and Immigration, Investigation into the Establishment of the Performance and Compliance Unit, published in May 2013, what steps have been taken in response to recommendation 1 of that report.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202743","202743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64365","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the report by the Independent Chief Inspector of Borders and Immigration, Inspection into the Handling of Asylum Applications made by Unaccompanied Children, published in October 2013, what steps have been taken in response to recommendations 1, 3, 4 and 8 of that report.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202744","202744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64366","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the report by the Independent Chief Inspector of Borders and Immigration, Inspection of the UK Border Agency's handling of legacy asylum and migration cases, published in November 2012, what steps have been taken in response to recommendation 1 of that report.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202745","202745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64367","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times an escaped person has been categorised as a high harm person and the senior management team believe there is a high risk of reputational damage to the Home Office as set out in the Home Office Guidance on Escaped Detainees at immigration removal centres in the last four years.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202824","202824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64368","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of detainees who have escaped from detention or from escort in each of the last four years have been returned to detention.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202823","202823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64369","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of the police hunt for Michael Wheatley who absconded from HM Prison Standford Hill on 3 May 2014.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202784","202784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64370","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times the Gold Suite has been opened at each Immigration Removal Centre in England and Wales in the last year; and what the nature was of each incident that caused it to be opened.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202820","202820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64371","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Immigration Removal Centre detainees have (a) escaped from detention, (b) escaped whilst being escorted and (c) attempted to escape each IRC in the last four years; and how many such people are still at large.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202821","202821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64372","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) Red incidents and (b) Amber incidents have occurred at each Immigration Removal Centre in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202822","202822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64373","2014-07-01","Department for International Development","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's policy in funding overseas organisations that restict their employment to members of particular faiths.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202622","202622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64374","2014-06-30","Department for International Development","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of her Department's consumption in kWh of (a) gas and (b) electricity in each month since June 2010; and what the cost of such consumption has been in each such month.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202708","202708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64375","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to (a) legal aid and (b) remission from court costs to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202674","202674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64376","2014-07-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Whitemoor spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202691","202691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64377","2014-07-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Winchester spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202692","202692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64378","2014-07-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Wolds spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202693","202693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64379","2014-07-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Wood Hill spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202694","202694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64380","2014-07-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Wormwood Scrubs spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202695","202695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64381","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost was of each (a) prison place and (b) prisoner in each prison in England and Wales in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202798","202798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64382","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many officials in his Department are currently employed to work on the sentence calculation helplines.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202799","202799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64383","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the marginal cost was of one extra prisoner being accommodated in each prison in England and Wales when each prison is functioning at its operational capacity in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202797","202797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64384","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost was of each (a) prison place and (b) prisoner in the case of (i) male and (ii) female prisoners in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202796","202796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64385","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of sentence was for (a) the total prison population and (b) foreign national prisoners, by type of offence, in 2012.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202783","202783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64386","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the names are of all prisoners who have absconded from prison and currently not been returned; and if he will specify in each such case (a) the offence each absconder originally committed and (b) the length of custodial sentence they were serving when they absconded.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202782","202782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64387","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people died in (a) on adult and (b) youth custody in each year since 2010; what their age was at the time of death; whether each such person was on (a) remand and (b) serving a custodial sentence of what length; which offence each such person was convicted; what the offence they were convicted of; and what the cause of death was in each case.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202765","202765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64388","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national prisoners were repatriated to their home countries to serve their custodial sentence in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202766","202766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64389","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the list of preferred bidders for the Tier 1 Community Rehabilitation Company contracts.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202763","202763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64390","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national prisoners were repatriated under foreign prisoner transfer agreements to their home countries to serve their custodial sentence in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202767","202767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64391","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the preferred bidders under the Transforming Rehabilitation process will be announced; when winning bidders will be announced; and when winning bidders will take over the running of the Tier 1 Community Rehabilitation Company contracts.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202768","202768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64392","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Low Newton spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours per week spent working was by prisoners in that prison in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202769","202769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64393","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Littlehey spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours per week spent working was by prisoners in that prison in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202770","202770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64394","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Lindholme spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours per week spent working was by prisoners in that prison in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202771","202771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64395","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Lincoln spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which figures are available; and the average number of hours per week spent working was by prisoners in that prison in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202772","202772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64396","2014-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Long Lartin spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the latest date for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours per week spent working was by prisoners in that prison in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202773","202773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64397","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people are currently employed in prisons to calculate the release date of prisoners.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202788","202788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64398","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost per (a) prison place and (b) prisoner in each category of prison was in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202786","202786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64399","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many indeterminate sentence prisoners have been considered and (a) approved and (b) rejected for release on temporary licence; and how many of these had received approval from him for transfer to open conditions.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202825","202825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64400","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the ratio of prison officers to inmates in prisons in England and Wales was, by category of prison, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202790","202790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64401","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the ratio of prison officers to inmates in prison in England and Wales was, by prison establishment, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202791","202791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64402","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many safety officers are employed by probation trusts to help (a) female and (b) male victims of domestic violence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202792","202792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64403","2014-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many prisoners have completed university degrees inside prison in each of the last 10 years; and what the cost to the public purse was of that education.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202785","202785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64404","2014-07-01","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what support her Department has given to secure the establishment of US immigration, customs and agricultural pre-clearance at Belfast International Airport.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202623","202623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64405","2014-07-01","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what role she will play in the forthcoming talks between party leaders in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202689","202689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64406","2014-06-30","Scotland Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to court fees exemptions to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out in Scotland.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202684","202684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64407","2014-06-30","Scotland Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to repayment of children's welfare loans to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out in Scotland.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202685","202685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64408","2014-06-30","Scotland Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to education maintenance allowance to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out in Scotland.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202686","202686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64409","2014-06-30","Scotland Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to the energy assistance package, stage 3, to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out in Scotland.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202687","202687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64410","2014-06-30","Scotland Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to NHS prescriptions to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out in Scotland.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202681","202681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64411","2014-06-30","Scotland Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to NHS dentistry exemptions to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out in Scotland.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202682","202682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64412","2014-06-30","Scotland Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to free school meals to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out in Scotland.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202680","202680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64413","2014-06-30","Scotland Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to legal aid to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out in Scotland.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202683","202683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64414","2014-06-30","Scotland Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, which official welfare-related engagements in Scotland (a) he and (b) other Ministers in his Department have attended together with Ministers in the Department of Work and Pensions since May 2010.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202814","202814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64415","2014-06-30","Scotland Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to the statement of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Scotland, giving evidence to the Scottish Parliament's Welfare Reform Committee on 26 June 2014, that 'I want an analysis of the use of foodbanks that everybody can subscribe to', whether his Department (a) is producing, (b) has commissioned or (c) plans to produce or commission any new research into the use of foodbanks in Scotland.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202813","202813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64416","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, on what specific date the Electoral Commission plans to publish its estimate of the number of people missing off the electoral register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202762","202762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64417","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what estimate the Electoral Commission has made of the number of local authorities who conducted a dry run in data matching and did not repeat this to the Electoral Commission.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202761","202761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64418","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what estimate the Electoral Commission makes of how many registered electors move house and (a) re-register and (b) fail to re-register to vote each year.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202755","202755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64419","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if the Electoral Commission will publish the 10 local authorities with the biggest (a) increase and (b) decrease in the net number of electors following the 2013 annual canvass.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202760","202760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64420","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many times an electoral registration officer (ERO) has to fail Standard Three before the Electoral Commission will refer the ERO to the Minister of State for the Cabinet Office for the purpose of improving the performance of the ERO.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202756","202756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64421","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the target was for each voter registration drive of the last five years of the number of electors they hoped to register; how much was allocated for each campaign; and how much the Electoral Commission planned to spend on each registration drive.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202748","202748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64422","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the postal vote matching rates were during the data matching dry run in each (a) local authority area and (b) constituency in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202749","202749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64423","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if the Electoral Commission will conduct research into the use of data matching of local and national databases to better identify people who are entitled to register to vote but who are not registered.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202750","202750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64424","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, on what date the discussions between the Electoral Commission and the Cabinet Office on sanctions against electoral registration officers (EROs) who refuse to conduct door-to-door canvassing as per Standard Three began; when those discussions will conclude; whether the conclusions of those discussions will be made available to (a) hon. Members with EROs who failed Standard Three, (b) the Political and Constitutional Reform Committee and (c) councillors within failed local authorities; and if he will place in the Library the conclusions of those discussions.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202757","202757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64425","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if the Electoral Commission will publish the names of the 10 local authorities with the (a) smallest and (b) biggest percentage increase in registration after the implementation of the Standard Three door-to-door canvassing for 2013 canvass; and which parliamentary constituencies each such local authority covers.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202758","202758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64426","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what number and percentage of electors were added to the electoral register as a result of the implementation of standard three door to door canvassing in each constituent part and region of the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202751","202751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64427","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if the Electoral Commission will make it their policy to gather information on registration levels on an annual basis.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202752","202752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64428","2014-06-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, on which dates the Electoral Commission will report to (a) Parliament and (b) individual hon. Members on the progress on the implementation of individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202759","202759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64429","2014-07-01","Department for Transport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2014, Official Report, column 536W, on shipping: exhaust emissions, whether he intends to have a UK review of the effect of the new sulphur regulation limits before 2019.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202732","202732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64430","2014-07-01","Department for Transport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his comments of 18 June 2014, Official Report, column 127WH, on sulphur regulations, whether he has (a) commissioned and (b) received any specific assessment of the potential effect on diesel prices in the UK as a result of implementation of the new sulphur regulation limits.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202731","202731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64431","2014-06-30","Department for Transport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of his Department's consumption in kWh of (a) gas and (b) electricity in each month since June 2010; and what the cost of such consumption has been in each such month.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202709","202709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64432","2014-07-01","Department for Transport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what investigation his Department plans to undertake into the causes of the increase in motorway deaths from 2012 to 2013.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202728","202728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64433","2014-07-01","Department for Transport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2014, Official Report, column 536W, on shipping: exhaust emissions, what discussions his officials have had with the European Commission on securing EU finance to assist shipowners and ports to comply with the new sulphur regulation limits.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202730","202730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64434","2014-07-01","Department for Transport","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department took over responsibility for long-range search and rescue at sea when the Ministry of Defence abandoned its acquisition of Nimrod aircraft.","Biography information for Lord Arbuthnot of Edrom","Mr James Arbuthnot","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202619","202619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64435","2014-06-30","Women and Equalities","2014-06-26","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, with reference to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 575W, on the Equality and Human Rights Commission, when she plans to place the requested information on the Dignity at Work conferences in the libraries of both Houses.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202776","202776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64436","2014-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which official welfare-related engagements (a) he and (b) other Ministers in his Department have attended in Scotland since May 2010.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202811","202811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64437","2014-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to address the current geographical imbalance in Independent Living Fund (ILF) use by local authorities in the allocation of transitional funding as the ILF comes to an end.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202800","202800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64438","2014-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the statement by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Scotland, giving evidence to the Scottish Parliament's Welfare Reform Committee on 26 June 2014, that 'there isn't any doubt that there are some people who've gone to foodbanks because they have been subject, for example, to sanctions or delays in receiving benefits'.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202812","202812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64439","2014-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the statement of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Scotland, giving evidence to the Scottish Parliament's Welfare Reform Committee on 26 June 2014, that 'I want an analysis of the use of foodbanks that everybody can subscribe to', whether his Department (a) is producing, (b) has commissioned or (c) plans to commission any new research into the use of foodbanks.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202810","202810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64440","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2014, Official Report, column 345W, on employment and support allowance (ESA), how many work programme job outcome payments there were in each ESA prognosis customer group in Great Britain between 1 June 2011 and 31 December 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202735","202735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64441","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what target his Department sets for the amount of time for people to receive an accurate assessment for personal independence payments under (a) normal rules claiming and (b) special rules claiming.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202764","202764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64442","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2014, Official Report, columns 170-1W, on employment and support allowance, how many decisions on eligibility for employment and support allowance have been made in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202737","202737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64443","2014-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps are being taken to better identify those personal independence payment claimants who could be assessed solely on the basis of evidence without the need for face-to-face assessments.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202753","202753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64444","2014-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will provide financial assistance to people facing delays to personal independence payments applications.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202754","202754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64445","2014-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to a jobcentre plus discount travel card to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202677","202677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64446","2014-07-01","Cabinet Office","2014-06-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people currently claiming jobseeker's allowance are aged (a) 16, (b) 17, (c) 18, (d) 19, (e) 20, (f) 21, (g) 22, (h) 23, (i) 24 and (j) 25 years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202617","202617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64447","2014-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to cold weather payments to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202678","202678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64448","2014-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of extending entitlement to funeral payments to all claimants of universal credit once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202679","202679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64449","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2014, Official Report, columns 345-6W, on employment and support allowance, how many claimants in the WRAG with a prognosis of two years or more who made (a) a new claim - initial assessment and (b) a new claim - repeat assessment were judged that return to work was unlikely in the longer term.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202738","202738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64450","2014-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of his Department's consumption in kWh of (a) gas and (b) electricity in each month since June 2010; and what the cost of such consumption has been in each such month.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202711","202711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64451","2014-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will place in the Library the methodology and assumptions used to populate the Help to Work sections of Table 2.1, page 78, Autumn Statement 2013, Cm 8747 showing financial savings arising from the programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202715","202715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63827","2014-06-30","Attorney General","2014-06-25","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the fall in the percentage rate of convictions in rape cases between 2012-13 and 2013-14; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202401","202401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63828","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will hold discussions with Lloyds Bank on (a) the proposed closure of its contact centre in Warrington and (b) the possibility of other jobs being based there.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202353","202353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63829","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many hydraulic fracturing licences are pending approval in (a) England, (b) Lancashire and (c) Hyndburn constituency.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202358","202358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63830","2014-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeships there were in London on 31 May (a) 2010 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202354","202354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63831","2014-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to improve skill levels in the construction industry.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202372","202372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63832","2014-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will request that the Office of Fair Trading investigates the level of competition in the car insurance industry.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202297","202297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63833","2014-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings of the British-Irish Council he has taken part.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202300","202300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63834","2014-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department has spent on funding for trade union representatives studying Trade Union Congress (TUC) learning aims in (a) each of the last five years and (b) 2014-15; and what his estimate is of funding in (i) 2015-16 and (ii) any future years for which budgets are available.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202334","202334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63835","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will hold discussions with Lloyds Bank on the effect of the proposed closure of its contact centre in Warrington on women workers who cannot re-locate because of (a) childcare or other caring responsibilities and (b) a lack of adequate public transport provision.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202352","202352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63836","2014-06-30","Cabinet Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what audit he has made of (a) ICL mainframes, (b) IBM mainframes and (c) other legacy ICT systems in Government departments and the availability of skills needed to maintain them; and when each relevant maintenance contract falls due.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202463","202463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63837","2014-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the IT system being developed by his Department for universal credit will be fully operating.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202350","202350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63838","2014-07-01","Cabinet Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people working (a) at No. 10 Downing Street and (b) on the Prime Minister's staff since May 2010 have not been required to undergo security vetting; how many such staff have undergone security vetting; and what the job titles and responsibilities are of all such staff.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202412","202412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63839","2014-07-01","Cabinet Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff working (a) at No. 10 Downing Street and (b) for the Prime Minister (i) have been allowed to attend National Security Council meetings and (ii) had access to Top Secret meetings or documents without being required to have had a security vetting, since May 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202411","202411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63840","2014-06-30","Cabinet Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the (a) total value of public service contracts that have been awarded to voluntary sector organisations in each year since 2008-09 and (b) proportion of overall public expenditure which was spent on public service contracts with voluntary sector organisations in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202407","202407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63841","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints have been made about HM Revenue and Customs in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202416","202416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63842","2014-07-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what his policy is on future public subsidies to onshore solar energy projects; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202360","202360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63843","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the proportion of families currently paying for childcare that will be eligible for the proposed tax-free childcare scheme.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202294","202294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63844","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the take-up of tax-free childcare by parents in each income (a) decile and (b) percentile.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202296","202296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63845","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps he has taken to support businesses with five or fewer staff.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202335","202335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63846","2014-06-30","HM Treasury","2014-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the speech delivered by the Chief Secretary to the Treasury in New York on 25 June 2014 represents the policy of the Government.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202346","202346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63847","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the potential additional cost to the Traffic Penalty Tribunal Appeals Service if a 25 per cent discount on the full price of their parking ticket is given to motorists who lose an appeal against that parking ticket at tribunal.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202309","202309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63848","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on permitting motorists to park briefly on double yellow lines, single yellow lines or loading bays; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202322","202322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63849","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, against what criteria he will consider the recovery of an appeal against the refusal of an application for planning permission for a wind turbine.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202324","202324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63850","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he will answer Question 200690 tabled by the hon. Member for Leeds Central on 13 June 2014.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202295","202295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63851","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library correspondence he has received from Essex County Council and Brentwood Council on changes to councillors' eligibility for the Local Government Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202283","202283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63852","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library the impact assessment his Department prepared alongside its response to the consultation on local authority parking.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202288","202288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63853","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library all responses to his Department's consultation on local authority parking.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202289","202289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63854","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what statistics his Department holds on the use of fixed penalty notices in each local authority area.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202290","202290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63855","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent in legal fees during the judicial review brought against his Department on the solar farm at Ellough Airfield, Suffolk.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202291","202291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63856","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to support (a) public sector and (b) private sector provision of extra care housing facilities for older people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202382","202382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63857","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what monetary thresholds were applied to the cost-per-quality adjusted life year quoted in the evidence submitted as part of his Department's work with the Inter-departmental Group for the Valuation of Life and Health review in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202428","202428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63858","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the localisation of council tax support on the operation and activities of parish and town councils.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202394","202394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63859","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that council tax support funding is passed on from billing authorities to parish and town councils in 2014-15.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202395","202395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63860","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the total value of (a) public service contracts and (b) grants that were awarded by local authorities to voluntary sector organisations in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202409","202409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63861","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the performance of Queen's Park Community Council since its establishment on 1 April 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202396","202396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63862","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to make parish and town councils aware of the general power of competence in the Localism Act 2011.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202397","202397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63863","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the additional cost of additional appeals to the Parking Traffic Appeals Service if a 25 per cent discount is given to motorists who lose an appeal at tribunal against the issue of a parking ticket.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202438","202438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63864","2014-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department provided to billing authorities for council tax support schemes in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202393","202393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63865","2014-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department's proposed constitution on society lotteries, which was first announced in December 2012, will consider ways to help the sector maximise returns to good causes.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202398","202398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63866","2014-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on how much society lotteries have generated for good causes in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202399","202399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63867","2014-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has (a) taken in each of the last three years and (b) plans to take in the next two years to ensure that war memorials are properly maintained and kept in a good state of repair; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202338","202338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63868","2014-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many fires have occurred onboard each variant of Joint Strike Fighter aircraft; and what the cause was of each fire.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202365","202365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63869","2014-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what risk rating was placed on a collision involving a Tornado and another aircraft in (a) 1991, (b) 1998 and (c) 2010.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202364","202364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63870","2014-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times an RAF aircraft has engaged an enemy aircraft beyond visual range by firing a beyond visual range air-to-air missile in the last 30 years; what aircraft it was fired from; and what the target and missile was in each case.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202366","202366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63871","2014-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much was spent on the Unmanned Sea Vehicle-based Mine Countermeasures Hydrographic Programme Sweep Demonstrator project.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202367","202367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63872","2014-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Shallow Water Influence Minesweeping System was purchased; on what vessels it operated from; whether it is still operational; and what the total cost of the system has been.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202361","202361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63873","2014-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost is of the Weapon Handling and Launch System and Submerged Signal Ejector support contract.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202362","202362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63874","2014-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Weapon Handling and Launch support contract includes an obligation on the contractor to provide waterfront support in the loading and unloading of (a) conventional and (b) nuclear weapons in (i) the UK and (ii) abroad.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202363","202363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63875","2014-07-01","Department for Education","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on how many occasions ministerial authorisation has been granted for expenditure which exceeded his Department's internal efficiency control thresholds for (a) advertising, marketing and communications, (b) consultancy and (c) external recruitment; and what the (i) purpose and (ii) value of any such agreed expenditure has been in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202359","202359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63876","2014-06-30","Department for Education","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2014, Official Report, column 284W, on children: day care, if he will estimate the average annual cost of childcare in the UK for a child aged (a) two and under and (b) three to four using his Department's Childcare and Early Years Survey of Parents 2012-13 data.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202400","202400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63877","2014-07-01","Department for Education","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many transactions were made by each (a) Minister and (b) official in his Department on government procurement cards held by his Department in the last financial year; and what the cost, date and reasons for each such transaction was.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202410","202410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63878","2014-06-30","Department for Education","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will place in the Library copies of the Property Data Survey Programme results for schools in Sandwell local authority area.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202385","202385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63879","2014-06-30","Department for Education","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children receive free school meals in each (a) free school and (b) local authority area where a free school has been established.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202406","202406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63880","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer for 4 March 2014, Official Report, column 765W, on carbon emissions, to which other technologies that Answer refers to; and whether this would still be the case if the carbon footprint of backup technologies was factored in.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202392","202392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63881","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he expects to publish the British Geological Survey's assessment of the hydrocarbon resources in the Weald area of the south of England.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202357","202357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63882","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department is taking to simplify regulations applying to the UK's shale gas industry.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202356","202356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63883","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to ensure that the distribution of shale gas community benefit funds go to those households closest to potential drilling sites.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202368","202368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63884","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to ensure that the risk of flooding is taken into account in any potential shale gas sites.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202369","202369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63885","2014-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will publish all documentation relating to the nuclear power investment signed with the Prime Minister of China covering Chinese state companies on 17 June 2014; and if he will publish all subsequent documentation.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202370","202370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63886","2014-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the explicit monetary value per quality-adjusted life was in the context of the Health benefits from air pollution reduction, as quoted as part of his Department's submission to the Inter-Departmental Group for the Valuation of Life and Health review in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202421","202421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63887","2014-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the explicit monetary value per quality-adjusted life was in the context of the Flood Risk Management, as quoted as part of the Environment Agency's submission to the Inter-Departmental Group for the Valuation of Life and Health review in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202422","202422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63888","2014-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the details of the new parliamentary elections law in Egypt.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202337","202337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63889","2014-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he had held with his Egyptian counterpart on the new parliamentary elections law in that country.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202336","202336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63890","2014-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last discussed violence against women and girls with representatives of the Indian government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202405","202405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63891","2014-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his Department's National Action Plan on Women, Peace and Security 2014-2017, in what way, as part of the implementation of that plan, women's participation at grassroots level will be measured.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202388","202388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63892","2014-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2014, Official Report, columns 367-8W, on armed conflicts: minerals, which companies have joined or have applied to join the Voluntary Principles on Security and Human Rights initiative.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202436","202436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63893","2014-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2014, Official Report, columns 367-8W, on armed conflicts: minerals, which UK companies he has met to discuss the Voluntary Principles on Security and Human Rights.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202437","202437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63894","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Food Standards Agency's submission to the Inter-Departmental Group for the Valuation of Life and Health review and all evidence submitted to the series of interviews with his Department's staff conducted by researchers from the University of Leeds in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202419","202419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63895","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what monetary thresholds were applied to the cost-per-quality adjusted life year quoted in the evidence submitted as part of his Department's work with the Inter-departmental Group for the Valuation of Life and Health review in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202429","202429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63896","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Health Protection Agency's submission to the Inter-Departmental Group for the Valuation of Life and Health review and all evidence submitted to the series of interviews with his Department's staff conducted by researchers from the University of Leeds in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202418","202418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63897","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mechanisms are in place to ensure that those clinical commissioning groups providing financial support to a neighbouring clinical commissioning group does not suffer a reduction in its own provision of services as a result.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202462","202462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63898","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the explicit monetary value per quality-adjusted life was in the context of 'Evaluation of new pharmaceutical products or medical devices', as quoted as part of the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence's submission to Inter-departmental Group for the Valuation of Life and Health review in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202426","202426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63899","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the total value of public service contracts that were awarded by (a) his Department and (b) NHS bodies to voluntary sector organisations in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202408","202408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63900","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to support calorific labelling on alcoholic drinks.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202378","202378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63901","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of potential links between alcohol and obesity.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202375","202375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63902","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department gathers on the number of people who move to another GP practice.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202345","202345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63903","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adults with autism in England receive support under the current social care system; and how many such adults will receive support under the system proposed in the Care Act 2014 Part 1 regulations.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202344","202344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63904","2014-07-02","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP appointments were missed in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202305","202305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63905","2014-07-02","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings he has had with patient groups to discuss the difficulties patients face in booking appointments with their GP.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202308","202308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63906","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical commissioning groups are running financial deficits requiring financial support from neighbouring clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202339","202339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63907","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the proposed changes to the social care system in the Care Act 2014 Part 1 regulations on adults with autism.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202340","202340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63908","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total cost to the NHS was of providing free flu vaccinations in each of the last four years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202341","202341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63909","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to begin negotiations with Novartis on the procurement of the vaccine for meningitis B as part of the primary infant immunisation schedule.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202342","202342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63910","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contingency plans he has in place to deal with an outbreak of Ebola virus in the UK.","Biography information for Richard Harrington","Richard Harrington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202299","202299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63911","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of (a) NHS staff, (b) pregnant women and (c) pensioners took up influenza vaccinations in each of the last four years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202301","202301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63912","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) mean and (b) median duration to assessment, duration to treatment and duration to departure was in (i) type 1 and (ii) all accident and emergency departments in each month in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202302","202302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63913","2014-07-02","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to the NHS of missed appointments.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202304","202304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63914","2014-07-02","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of missed GP appointments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202306","202306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63915","2014-07-02","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures are currently in place to record the number of missed GP appointments.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202307","202307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63916","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the explicit monetary value per quality-adjusted life was in the context of Interventions and Regulations, as quoted as part of his Department's submission to the Inter-Departmental Group for the Valuation of Life and Health review in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202424","202424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63917","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library a copy of the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence's submission to the Inter-Departmental Group for the Valuation of Life and Health review and all evidence submitted to the series of interviews with his Department's staff conducted by researchers from the University of Leeds in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202420","202420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63918","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what monetary thresholds were applied to the cost-per-quality adjusted life year quoted in the evidence submitted as part of the Food Standards Agency's work with the Inter-departmental Group for the Valuation of Life and Health review in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202430","202430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63919","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what monetary thresholds were applied to the cost-per-quality adjusted life year quoted in the evidence submitted as part of the Health Protection Agency's work with the Inter-departmental Group for the Valuation of Life and Health review in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202431","202431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63920","2014-06-30","Department of Health","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the explicit monetary value per quality-adjusted life was in the context of Advice on Nuclear power, centre for infections and modelling, as quoted as part of his Department's submission to the Inter-Departmental Group from the Valuation of Life and Health review in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202425","202425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63921","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the explicit monetary value per quality-adjusted life was in the context of Homicide and crime categories of wounding, sexual offences, common assault and robbery, as quoted as part of her Department's submission to the Inter-Departmental Group for the Valuation of Life and Health review in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202423","202423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63922","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her contribution of 12 June 2014, Official Report, column 693, which countries have agreed to accept the one year extension passports to be issued to UK citizens living abroad.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202319","202319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63923","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps UK Visas and Immigration can take to prevent no cases of Ebola reaching the UK.","Biography information for Richard Harrington","Richard Harrington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202298","202298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63924","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many contract or temporary employees were employed in (a) the Case Resolution Directorate and (b) the Case Assurance and Audit Unit in each year of those bodies' existence; and what proportion of the overall staff of such bodies were contract or temporary employees.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202285","202285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63925","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full-time employees were employed in (a) the Case Resolution Directorate and (b) the Case Assurance and Audit Unit in each year of those bodies' existence.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202286","202286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63926","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost was of renaming (a) the Case Resolution Directorate in 2011 and (b) the Case Assurance and Audit Unit in 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202287","202287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63927","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the statement of 24 June 2014, Official Report, column 206, on student visas, on what date her Department first became aware of the systematic cheating taking place in the tests of the Educational Testing Service.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202332","202332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63928","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the statement of 24 June 2014, Official Report, column 206, what the terms of reference are of the working group established, who the members of that group are and when that group is first expected to meet; and if she will make a written statement to the House on the conclusion of that group's work.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202328","202328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63929","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the statement of 24 June 2014, Official Report, column 206, on student visas, how many students wrongly awarded language certificates (a) remain in the UK, (b) have an address known to her Department and (c) have been deported.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202331","202331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63930","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the statement of 24 June 2014, Official Report, column 206, on student visas, what due diligence tests her Department undertook on the Educational Testing Service prior to awarding the company a contract for delivering language tests for visa applications.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202330","202330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63931","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the statement of 24 June 2014, Official Report, column 206, on student visas, whether she is seeking financial compensation from the Educational Testing Service.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202329","202329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63932","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost was of running (a) the Case Resolution Directorate, (b) the Case Assurance and Audit Unit and (c) the Older Live Cases Unit in each year of those bodies' operations.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202312","202312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63933","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many contract or temporary employees are employed in the Older Live Cases Unit; and what proportion of the overall staff count are contract or temporary employees.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202313","202313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63934","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made towards ending the testing of household products and ingredients on animals; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202373","202373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63935","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full-time staff are employed in the Older Live Cases Unit.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202314","202314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63936","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for emergency travel documents for children have been received by the Passport Office since 16 June 2014.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202391","202391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63937","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department issues to companies which carry out the required checks on individuals applying for spouse visas on the appropriate amount of time for those checks to be completed.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202404","202404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63938","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the Exchequer of the asylum and immigration system once fee income has been deducted has been in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202386","202386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63939","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to encourage more rape victims to report that crime to the police and to ensure that they are treated appropriately when they do so.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202402","202402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63940","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passports have been issued under the Government's new passport fast-tracked free policy since that policy came into effect.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202389","202389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63941","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications by overseas-based British citizens for the extension of an existing passport for one year have been received by the Passport Office since her recent announcement on changes in passport policy.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202390","202390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63942","2014-06-30","Home Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what monitoring her Department carries out on the amount of time taken by its contractor companies to carry out the required checks on people applying for spouse visas to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202403","202403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63943","2014-06-30","Department for International Development","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of UK aid to Burma is channelled through Burmese government-approved organisations or mechanisms.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202347","202347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63944","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Doncaster spent in cells in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202343","202343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63945","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners aged 75 and over there were in each type of prison in (a) 2010 and (b) the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Duncan Hames","Duncan Hames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202351","202351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63946","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of cases in which compulsory mediation and information meetings would have been appropriate in 2013-14; and what funding is being made available in 2014-15 to provide that service.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202292","202292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63947","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent on independent adjudicators in each public and private prisons and young offender institution in each month since January 2013.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202348","202348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63948","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Drake Hall spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which data is available.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202315","202315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63949","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Downview spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which data is available.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202316","202316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63950","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Dover spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which data is available.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202317","202317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63951","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours per week prisoners in HM Prison Dorchester spent (a) in cells and (b) working in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such prisoners were classed as unemployed on the last date for which data is available.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202318","202318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63952","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) prosecutions and (b) convictions there have been in relation to offences under section 57 of the New Roads and Street Works Act 1991 in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202384","202384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63953","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish all impact assessments his Department has made on privatising the Ministry of Justice Shared Services in Newport.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202381","202381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63954","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy to regularly provide details on private sector bodies who collaborate with public sector bodies on projects which are subject to the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202371","202371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63955","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many remote sites for giving evidence in court are open in each region of England and Wales.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202355","202355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63956","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions on potential job losses in Newport took place between his Department, the Home Office and Steria prior to the decision to privatise the Ministry of Justice Shared Services.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202380","202380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63957","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy that civil partnerships can be dissolved at any county court.","Biography information for Dr Thérèse  Coffey","Dr Thérèse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202469","202469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63958","2014-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the annual cost of imprisoning foreign national offenders in UK prisons has been in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202470","202470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63959","2014-06-30","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will commission an independent assessment of the effect of changes to funding levels of the Northern Ireland Human Rights Commission and its compliance with the Paris Principles.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202284","202284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63960","2014-06-30","Prime Minister","2014-06-25","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will take steps to establish a Cabinet Committee chaired by the Chancellor of the Exchequer to direct and co-ordinate policy on the development of shale gas.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202387","202387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/63961","2014-06-30","Department for Transport","2014-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what monetary thresholds were applied to the cost-per-quality adjusted life year quoted in the evidence submitted as part of his Department's work with the Inter-departmental Group for the Valuation of Life and Health review in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 202427","202427"
