"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855722","2018-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answers of 26 February 2018 to Questions 128460 and 128462, whether his Department holds the average yearly cost per vessel of (a) Type 23, (b) Type 45, (c) Hunt Class, (d) Sandown Class and (e) Albion Class vessels.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131028","131028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855723","2018-03-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the findings of the Royal College of Psychiatrists', published on 21 February 2018, on mental health trust income levels, if will he provide information on the level of funding for mental health committed to in the current financial year; and what the funding will be spent on.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131029","131029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855724","2018-03-07","Home Office","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to enable additional unaccompanied asylum-seeking children in France who have family members in this country to be admitted to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131030","131030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855725","2018-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to assist Mr and Mrs Dennis Ryalls to ascertain the cause of the death of their son, Benjamin Ryalls, in Mombasa, Kenya on 24 July 2012.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131031","131031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855726","2018-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2018 to Question 128462, whether his Department has estimated figures for the total yearly cost of operating the following the (a) Type 26, (b) Type 31e and (c) River Class OPV Batch 2 vessels when in service.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131032","131032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855727","2018-03-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much meat was detained at the 15 cold stores inspected as part of Russell Hume inquiry.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131033","131033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855728","2018-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people that will sell their home because of the introduction of the replacement loan for support for mortgage interest payments.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131034","131034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855729","2018-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, What assessment (a) his Department and (b) NHS England has made of the potential resource efficiencies of redesigning NHS Inflammatory Bowel Disease services outside of the hospital setting.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131035","131035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855730","2018-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the number of unplanned admissions to A&E departments due to inflammatory bowel disease by hospital trust was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131036","131036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855731","2018-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance the NHS provides to operational delivery networks on tackling hepatitis C to minimise variation in the effectiveness of local care services throughout England.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131037","131037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855732","2018-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will list the companies that manufacture and supply smokeless solid fuels into the UK (a) industrial and (b) domestic markets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131038","131038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855733","2018-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many contracts his Department has awarded to Boeing since 27 September 2017.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131039","131039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855734","2018-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will issue guidance on accessing free and impartial financial advice on the support for mortgage interest payments loan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131040","131040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855735","2018-03-07","Home Office","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for The Home Department, if she will issue unexplained wealth orders in respect of members of the Gaddafi Family and Libyan associates who reside in the UK or who claim ownership of assets frozen in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131041","131041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855736","2018-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the replacement loan for support for mortgage interest payments is based on the Gilt interest rate.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131042","131042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855737","2018-03-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many homes have been built on flood plains since January 2017.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131043","131043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855738","2018-03-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has any powers to intervene over the removal of Channel 4 HD services from the Freesat satellite television network.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131044","131044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855739","2018-03-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128375, on Universal Credit: Internet, if he will publish a timetable for those features mentioned which have a higher priority than the establishment of an online password reset function for universal credit claimants.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131045","131045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855740","2018-03-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128375, on Universal Credit: Internet, if she will she set an estimated year of delivery for the development of an online password reset function for universal credit claimants.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131046","131046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855741","2018-03-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128375, on Universal Credit: Internet, what funding the Government has made available for the development of IT systems for universal credit; and which private contractors her Department has commissioned to develop such systems.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131047","131047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855742","2018-03-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2018 to Question 128116, what the average time taken is between (a) a complaint being received on the equalisation of the state pension age and (b) the completion of checks on that complaint to establish it can be accepted for examination by her Department's independent case examiner.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131048","131048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855743","2018-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on UK agriculture of the UK leaving the EU single market and Customs Union.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131049","131049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855744","2018-03-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Government plans to make it its policy to remove EU citizenship from UK citizens once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131050","131050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855745","2018-03-07","Department for International Development","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department monitors the delivery and spending of UK aid in the Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131051","131051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855746","2018-03-07","Department for International Development","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that aid to the Palestinian Authority does not fund radicalisation.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131052","131052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855747","2018-03-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to minimise the extent of liabilities imposed on small business owners by the operation of section 75 of the Pensions Act 1995.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131053","131053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855748","2018-03-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the provision of additional funds to local authorities to improve the fire safety of their housing stock in the 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131054","131054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855749","2018-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many herds were located in each of the badger cull areas of the first (a) Gloucestershire, (b) Somerset and (c) Dorset cull zones for each of the (i) three pre-cull years and (ii) first four years of the culls.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131055","131055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855750","2018-03-07","Cabinet Office","2018-03-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff his Department has in Scotland; where those staff are located; and what the roles of those staff are.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131056","131056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855751","2018-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many new herd incidents were there in (a) the first Gloucestershire, (b) the first Somerset and (c) the first Dorset cull zone for (i) each of the three years before the cull and (ii) each of the first four years of the cull.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131057","131057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855752","2018-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many officially TB free status withdrawn cases there were in (a) the first Gloucestershire, (b) the first Somerset and c) the first Dorset cull zone in (i) each of the last three years before the culls and (ii) for each of the first four years of the culls.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131058","131058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855753","2018-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many staff his Department has in Scotland; where those staff are located; and what the roles of those staff are.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131059","131059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855754","2018-03-08","Home Office","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what evidence will be required for EU citizens to prove five years of continuous residency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131060","131060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855755","2018-03-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what methodologies in addition to the UN Inter-agency Standing Committee’s Sanctions Assessment Handbook his Department uses to assess the humanitarian effects of sanctions.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131061","131061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855756","2018-03-08","Treasury","2018-03-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 21 February 2018 to Question 126717, if he will publish (a) the total value of suspected breaches to each sanctioned country and terrorist group, (b) which banks and financial institutions are suspected of having breached the sanctions; and (c) criminal and other action taken against those responsible for suspected breaches of sanctions.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131062","131062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855757","2018-03-08","Treasury","2018-03-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many breaches of financial sanctions there were in (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016; and what the aggregate value of such breaches was.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131063","131063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855759","2018-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number of child custody cases heard in court (a) prior to and (b) since the removal of legal aid for early advice per year.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131064","131064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855760","2018-03-08","Home Office","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February to Question 124886, whether FSR-C-133 was issued to any providers during its development.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131065","131065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855761","2018-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions how much of the Jobcentre Plus Flexible Support Fund budget was spent on (a) transport, (b) childcare, (c) training and (d) other costs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131066","131066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855762","2018-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much and what proportion of the Flexible Support Fund was unspent in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131067","131067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855763","2018-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been spent on the childcare element of (a) tax credits and (b) universal credit in (i) total and (ii) in each region in each of the past five years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131068","131068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855764","2018-03-07","Department for Education","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many learners have been supported through Care to Learn funding in each of the last five years; and how much has been spent through that same funding in (a) total (b) in each region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131069","131069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855765","2018-03-07","Department for Education","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many adult learners were funded in 2016-17 to participate on (a) maths and English courses, (b) English courses only, (c) maths courses only and (d) English for Speakers of Other Languages courses only in each region.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131070","131070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855766","2018-03-07","Department for Education","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many adult learners were funded in 2011-12 to participate on (a) maths and  English courses, (b) English courses only, (c) maths courses only and (d) English for Speakers of Other Languages courses only in each region.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131071","131071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855767","2018-03-07","Department for Education","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of funded adult learners in 2016-17 on (a) maths and English courses, (b) English courses only, (c) maths courses only and (d) English for Speakers of Other Languages courses only, have achieved their qualification in each region.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131072","131072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855768","2018-03-07","Department for Education","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of funded adult learners in 2011-12 on (a) maths and English courses, (b) English courses only,  (c) maths courses only and (d) English for Speakers of Other Languages courses only achieved their qualification in each region.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131073","131073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855769","2018-03-08","Department for Education","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 129125, on Schools, where that information is held.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131074","131074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855770","2018-03-08","Home Office","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of the 1 November 2017 to Question 110846, when she plans to publish (a) The Review on Counter Terrorism Strategy and (b) Understanding the costs of cyber-crime: a report of key findings from the costs of cyber-crime working group.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131075","131075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855771","2018-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to (a) investigate the lack of information given to pregnant women prescribed with sodium valproate in the 1970s and (b) introduce a national compensation fund for people affected by the effects of sodium valproate being prescribed to pregnant women.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131076","131076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855772","2018-03-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to research published by the Family and Childcare Trust on childcare costs published in February 2018, whether her Department has plans to change the current limit on childcare costs covered by universal credit.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131077","131077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855773","2018-03-08","Department for Education","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the press release issued by his Department on 8 February 2018 on the consultation on Social Work England, if he will set out (a) the members and (b) the terms of reference for (i) the Advisory Group and (ii) the Regulatory Expert Group.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131078","131078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855774","2018-03-08","Department for Education","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2018 to Question 124482, on Children’s Centres, what evidence his Department has gathered since September 2015 to inform a consultation on children's centres.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131079","131079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855775","2018-03-08","Department for Transport","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, in he will meet with the Minister for Loneliness to discuss the role of reliable and timely bus services in helping to alleviate social isolation.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131080","131080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855776","2018-03-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on (a) jobs and (b) patient care of the potential reduction of genetic testing facilities in Newcastle.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131081","131081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855777","2018-03-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government has plans to commission an external evaluation of the 100,000 genomes project.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131082","131082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855778","2018-03-07","Department for Education","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what number and proportion of academy schools have received a financial notice to improve in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131083","131083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855779","2018-03-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of instances of physical restraint recorded at (a) North Essex Partnership NHS Foundation Trust, (b) South Essex Partnership NHS Foundation Trust and (c) Essex Partnership University NHS Foundation Trust in (i) 2015-16, (ii) 2016-17 and (iii) 2017-18.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131084","131084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855780","2018-03-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of inpatient suicide deaths recorded at (a) North Essex Partnership NHS Foundation Trust, (b) South Essex Partnership NHS Foundation Trust and (c) Essex Partnership University NHS Foundation Trust in (i) 2015-16, (ii) 2016-17 and (iii) 2017-18.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131085","131085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855781","2018-03-08","Department for Education","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much free school meals monies is returned annually to the provider when not used by the intended child.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131086","131086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855782","2018-03-07","Department for Education","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Ofsted inspections of adult education providers have involved inspectors undertaking on-site visits to sub-contracted provision (a) in the UK and (b) in each region of the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131087","131087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855783","2018-03-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Youth Full Time Social Action Review published in January 2018, what steps he is taking to widen participation in youth full-time social action programmes, particularly by people from low income backgrounds.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131088","131088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855784","2018-03-07","Department for Transport","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential change to traffic volumes in Bristol after the removal of tolls on the Severn Bridge.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131089","131089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855785","2018-03-08","Cabinet Office","2018-03-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans his Department has to promote voter registration.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131090","131090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855786","2018-03-08","Home Office","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will assess the potential merits of expanding the definition of refugees to include people displaced by environmental factors.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131091","131091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855787","2018-03-08","Department for International Development","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to vet people who volunteer for overseas placements on Government-backed schemes.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131092","131092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855788","2018-03-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 September 2017 to Question 9140, on General Practitioners: Enfield, what information NHS England holds on how many and which GP practices (a) closed and (b) opened in the London Borough of Enfield in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131093","131093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855789","2018-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the situation in Yemen; and what plans the UK Government has to call for work towards an immediate ceasefire in that country.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131094","131094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855790","2018-03-12","Department for International Development","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's bilateral aid spending on HIV and AIDS is specified for work with (a) women and girls, (b) the LGBT+ community, (c) men who have sex with men and (d) intravenous drug users.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131095","131095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855791","2018-03-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many claims were made against people by companies or people instructing (a) Gladstones Solicitors (Knutsford) and (b) BW Legal in English and Welsh courts in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131096","131096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855792","2018-03-08","Treasury","2018-03-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claims for relief under the Business Premises Renovation Allowance scheme were granted to Signature Living Ltd in (a) 2015-16 (b) 2016-17; and what the value of each of those claims was.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131097","131097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853246","2018-03-06","Home Office","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the inspection regime is for Compass contracts; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130695","130695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853247","2018-03-07","Attorney General","2018-03-02","To ask the Attorney General,  what steps the CPS has taken as a result of the BBC Panorama programme, Undercover: Britain's Immigration Secrets of 4 September 2017.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130696","130696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853248","2018-03-07","Department for International Development","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Government response to the Fifth Report of the International Development Committee, Session 2014-15, HC 816, whether the Department has developed its position paper on health systems strengthening.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130697","130697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853249","2018-03-06","Home Office","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's publication, Immigration Bail, version 1.0, published on 12 January 2018, what estimate she has made of the number of immigration detainees who will face homelessness if they are released without bail accommodation under schedule 10 of the Immigration Act 2016.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130698","130698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853250","2018-03-06","Home Office","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether destitution qualifies as an exceptional circumstance for the provision of accommodation for immigration bail applicants.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130699","130699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853251","2018-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time was that it took to process an immigration appeal in the last twelve months; and what targets are set for processing and bringing to a conclusion such appeals.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130700","130700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853252","2018-03-07","Department for Education","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect on students of the loss of teaching hours as a result of the university lecturers’ pension strike.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130701","130701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853253","2018-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of his Department’s cloud-hosting contracts have been awarded to (a) hyperscale cloud providers and (b) UK SMEs; and what the value was of those contracts in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130702","130702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853254","2018-03-07","Department for Education","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of his Department’s cloud-hosting contracts have been awarded to (a) hyperscale cloud providers and (b) UK SMEs; and what the value of those contracts was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130703","130703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853255","2018-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many and what proportion of his Department’s cloud-hosting contracts have been awarded to (a) hyperscale cloud providers and (b) UK SMEs; and what the value of those contracts was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130704","130704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853256","2018-03-07","Department for Education","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the volume of UK citizens’ data held by companies (a) supplying cloud services to his Department and (b) contracted to deliver cloud services on behalf of his Department that is subject to information requests from US Government bodies.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130705","130705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853257","2018-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure skilled EU professionals have their professional qualifications recognised after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130706","130706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853258","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many completed second or third personal independence payment assessment planned award reviews there have been of people with (a) Parkinson's disease, (b) multiple sclerosis, (c) motor neurone disease, (d) rheumatoid arthritis and (e) cystic fibrosis by year of repeat assessment since the introduction of personal independence payments in 2013; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130707","130707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853259","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease have been given personal independence payment awards of (a) enhanced rate daily living and (b) enhanced rate care by length of award in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130708","130708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853260","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson’s disease who previously received the (a) higher rate mobility component and (b) higher rate care component under disability living allowance received (i) a lower rate of award or (ii) no award following reassessment for personal independence payments in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130709","130709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853261","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson’s disease with an indefinite disability living allowance award received a (a) one-year award  (b) two-year award or (c) no award following reassessment for personal independence payments in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130710","130710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853262","2018-03-07","Home Office","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to change IT systems to allow information on the (a) average length of time for a decision on asylum support applications and (b) length of stay in initial accommodation for people applying for s95 non-emergency asylum support to be published.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130711","130711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853263","2018-03-06","Home Office","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward the date by which the assessment of the evidence from minimum unit alcohol pricing implementation in Scotland will be published.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130712","130712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853264","2018-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he will enable (a) onshore wind and (b) solar technologies to compete in the Contract for Difference mechanism.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130713","130713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853265","2018-03-06","Home Office","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has bring forward legislative proposals under the Digital Charter, published on 25 January 2018, to exempt repeat viewing of terrorist propaganda for civil society organisations, including journalists and researchers, working on terrorism-related issues.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130714","130714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853266","2018-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2018 to Question 129578, how many households in Yorkshire and the Humber his Department has written to regarding the change in Support for Mortgage Interest from a benefit to a loan.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130715","130715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853267","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on legal aid for early advice on housing issues.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130716","130716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853268","2018-03-07","Home Office","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-UK EU nationals have applied for permanent residency since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130717","130717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853269","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of reinstating legal aid for early advice in respect of housing law.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130718","130718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853270","2018-03-07","Home Office","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-UK EU nationals have been granted permanent residency since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130719","130719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853271","2018-03-07","Home Office","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-UK EU nationals have been refused permanent residency since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130720","130720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853272","2018-03-07","Home Office","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications submitted by non-UK EU nationals for permanent residency that have been received since 23 June 2016 are still being processed.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130721","130721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853273","2018-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to publish the results of desktop studies that have been used to test for combustible materials for use on high-rise buildings.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130722","130722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853274","2018-03-07","Home Office","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) average and (b) longest waiting time for completion of the process for a non-UK EU national to gain permanent residency has been since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130723","130723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853275","2018-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether Euroclass B-F materials passed fire safety tests conducted for the Government in 2017; and whether the results of those tests have formed the basis of his Department's guidance to landlords.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130724","130724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853276","2018-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the total sleep-in back pay liability for providers in (a) North Norfolk constituency and (b) the Norfolk County Council area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130725","130725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853277","2018-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of the British Standard 8414 large-scale fire tests.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130726","130726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853278","2018-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received on (a) the safety of Euroclass B-F cladding and insulation and (b) concerns regarding the British Standard 8414 large-scale fire test.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130727","130727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853279","2018-03-07","Department for Education","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many two year-old children were eligible for childcare places for disadvantaged two-year olds in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130728","130728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853280","2018-03-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport of 1 March 2018, Official Report, column 965, on Leveson Inquiry, for what reason he did not include the number of people who signed petitions in his evaluation of people in favour of reopening the Leveson Inquiry’in that Ministerial Statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130729","130729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853281","2018-03-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport of 1 March 2018, Official Report, column 965, on the Leveson Inquiry, if he will publish the total proportion of respondents to the government consultation on the Leveson inquiry including (a) directly and (b) people who signed petitions that were in favour of reopening that inquiry.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130730","130730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853282","2018-03-07","HM Treasury","2018-03-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether Atos or any other contractor has been found to be have failed on any part of the contract related to providing the website services which generate eligibility codes for (a) tax-free childcare and (b) 30 hours of funded childcare.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130731","130731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853283","2018-03-07","Department for Education","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions his Department has had since September 2015 with (a) other government departments, (b) the children’s sector and (c) early years' practitioners on the consultation on children’s centres.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130732","130732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853284","2018-03-07","Department for Education","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of levels of pay in the early years and childcare sector on settings' capacity to employ staff qualified to Level 3 or above.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130733","130733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853285","2018-03-07","Department for Education","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) companies and (b) other organisations have submitted bids to the tendering process for the early years baseline assessment.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130734","130734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853286","2018-03-07","Home Office","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the value of cloud-hosting contracts with (a) Amazon Web Services, (b) Oracle Fusion, (c) Microsoft Azure, (d) Vodafone, (e) DXC, (f) SCC and (g) UKCloud was in financial years (i) 2012-2013, (ii) 2013-2014, (iii) 2014-2015, (iv) 2015-2016 and (v) 2016-2017.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130735","130735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853287","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many unpaid work requirements have been handed down by the courts as part of community orders in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130736","130736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853288","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how long the average unpaid work requirement handed down by the courts as part of community orders in each year since 2010 was.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130737","130737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853289","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of community orders involved an unpaid work requirement in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130738","130738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853290","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average occupancy rate for the care and separation unit in each prison in England and Wales was in 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130739","130739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853291","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average occupancy rate for the care and separation unit in each prison in England and Wales was in 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130740","130740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853292","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average occupancy rate for the care and separation unit in each prison in England and Wales was in 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130741","130741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853293","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average occupancy rate for the care and separation unit in each prison in England and Wales was in 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130742","130742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853294","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average occupancy rate for the care and separation unit in each prison in England and Wales was in 2013.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130743","130743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853295","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average occupancy rate for the care and separation unit in each prison in England and Wales was in 2012.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130744","130744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853296","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average occupancy rate for the care and separation unit in each prison in England and Wales was in 2011.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130745","130745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853297","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average occupancy rate for the care and separation unit in each prison in England and Wales was in 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130746","130746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853298","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions additional days of imprisonment were awarded in each prison in each year since 2010; and how many days in total were awarded in each prison in that same period.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130747","130747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853299","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice,  what the average proportion of prisoners on an Assessment, Care in Custody and Teamwork programme in each prison was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130748","130748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853300","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners in each prison have been on an Assessment, Care in Custody and Teamwork programme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130749","130749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853301","2018-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many use of force incidents have been recorded in each prison since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130750","130750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853302","2018-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions his Department refused to approve a subcontractor proposed by Interserve in each year since 2010; what the reason given for each such refusal was; and what the name of each such proposed subcontracting company was.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130751","130751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853303","2018-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions his Department refused to approve a subcontractor proposed by Amey in each year since 2010; what the reason given for each refusal was; and what the name of each proposed subcontracting company was.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130752","130752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853304","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions his Department refused to approve a subcontractor proposed by a private contractor in each year since 2010; what the reason given for each such refusal was; which contractor proposed each such subcontract; and what the name of each such subcontractor was.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130753","130753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853305","2018-03-07","Department for Transport","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits extending the eligibility for the older person's bus pass to 60 year olds in England.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130754","130754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853306","2018-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of the 20 per cent deduction to repay rent arrears from the universal credit personal allowance, on personal debt and income.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130755","130755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853307","2018-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department plans to (a) review the level of deduction from the universal credit standard allowance to repay rent arrears and (b) introduce flexibility within the system for landlords to request deductions at a lower level.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130756","130756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853308","2018-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants are re-paying benefit overpayments; what the (a) mean and (b) median value is of those overpayments; and what the average period is for those benefit payments to be recovered in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130757","130757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853309","2018-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if the Government will bring the Balanced Scorecard approach for public procurement of food and drink in line with the 2015 SACN sugar recommendations.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130758","130758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853310","2018-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many Departments are compliant with (a) Government Buying Standards and (b) the balanced scorecard approach for the procurement of food and drink.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130759","130759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853311","2018-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of local authorities which use (a) Government Buying Standards and (b) the balanced scorecard for the public procurement of food and drink.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130760","130760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853312","2018-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support local authorities to use the (a) Government Buying Standards and (b) balanced scorecards in the procurement of food and drink.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130761","130761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853313","2018-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will ensure support for British horticulture in the balanced scorecard approach for public procurement of food and drink.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130762","130762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853314","2018-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to respond to the letter of 25 January 2018 from the hon. Member for Leeds West on the Leeds Flood Alleviation Scheme.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130763","130763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853315","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of women subject to post-release supervision by Community Rehabilitation Companies (CRC) were recalled to prison for non-compliance by CRC area in England and Wales in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130764","130764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853316","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many litigants in person have been through the courts in family and housing cases in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130765","130765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853317","2018-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect on delays to court proceedings of the increase in the number of litigants in person during the last five years.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130766","130766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853318","2018-03-07","Department for Transport","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the extension of the 26-30 railcard to people living in Sussex.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130767","130767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853319","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were receiving (a) severe disability premium, (b) enhanced disability premium or (c) severe and enhanced disability premiums as of May 2017.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130768","130768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853320","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will collate centrally information on the number of people claiming (a) enhanced disability premium, (b) severe disability premium or (c) enhanced and severe disability premiums alongside a payment of income-based employment and support allowance as of May 2017.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130769","130769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853321","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have lost access to transitional protections through natural migration to universal credit.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130770","130770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853322","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have lost access to transitional protections through natural migration to universal credit were in receipt of (a) enhanced disability premium, (b) severe disability premium or (c) enhanced and severe disability premiums at the time of their migration.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130771","130771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853323","2018-03-07","Home Office","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what checks are carried out on goods arriving into the UK from outside the EU at the point of entry.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130772","130772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853324","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 7685, what progress has been made on (a) developing a pathway for adults with eating disorders, (b) issuing implementation guidance for providers and (c) data collection to assess the feasibility of introducing a mandatory waiting time standard for adults with eating disorders.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130773","130773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853325","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect on employment support allowance (ESA) claimants resident in Brighton and Hove in the (a) support group and (b) work related activity group of having to travel to Lewes for ESA assessments; if she will provide an ESA assessment centre in Brighton and Hove; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130774","130774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853326","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people over 19 years of age were referred to non-specialist services for eating disorders in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130775","130775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853327","2018-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will uphold Natural England's agreement to commit to a three-year funding cycle for the National Trails.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130776","130776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853328","2018-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will fund from the public purse the 13 National Trails for £1.6 million annually until 2021.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130777","130777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853329","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on reducing the cost of the drug Sativex in order to allow that drug to be prescribed to people suffering from MS.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130778","130778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853330","2018-03-07","Department for Transport","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to restrict parking on pavements to remove potential obstructions for the visually impaired.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130779","130779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853331","2018-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what events Ministers of his Department attended during Eating Disorders Week between 26 February and 4 March 2018.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130780","130780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853332","2018-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of a disruption in the EU internal energy market on the price of electricity for energy-intensive​ industries such as the steel sector.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130781","130781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853333","2018-03-07","Cabinet Office","2018-03-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on how many occasions a Government Minister has overruled the views of an Inquiry Chair received under the Government’s requirement to consult the Chair of an Inquiry under section 14(3) of the Public Inquiries Act 2005 to cancel a Public Inquiry established under that Act before it completes.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130782","130782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853334","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department's policy is on the provision in the NHS of interpretation services for refugees.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130783","130783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853335","2018-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the average daily proportion of the UK’s electricity which was generated from coal was for the week beginning Monday 26 February 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130784","130784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850666","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with companies inheriting contracts from Carillion on the extension of TUPE rights to Carillion employees.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129916","129916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852518","2018-03-01","Department for Transport","2018-03-01","What steps his Department is taking to prepare transport infrastructure for severe winter weather.","Biography information for Rachel Maclean","Rachel Maclean","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904124","904124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852519","2018-03-01","Department for Transport","2018-03-01","Whether his Department plans to respond to the Peninsula Rail Task Force report and set out a rail strategy for the South West.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904121","904121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852549","2018-03-06","Cabinet Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many homes have been built on land released through the One Public Estate programme since 2013.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130548","130548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852550","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the accuracy of claims that Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe has (a) been offered home imprisonment instead of furlough by an Iranian judge and (b) that such imprisonment is conditional upon the interest repayment of an historic debt owed by the UK Government to the Government of Iran.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130549","130549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852551","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to allocate funding for a new hospital for Southport and Ormskirk NHS Trust.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130692","130692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852552","2018-02-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to make available on the NHS a balloon-type device to prevent still-birth deaths.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130550","130550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852553","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many properties there were in (a) London and (b) Hampstead and Kilburn constituency which were registered to owners based overseas in each year since 2016.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130551","130551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852554","2018-03-06","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many and what proportion of his Department’s cloud hosting contracts have been awarded to (a) hyperscale cloud providers and (b) UK SMEs; and what the value was of those contracts in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130552","130552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852555","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of her Department’s cloud hosting contracts have been awarded to (a) hyperscale cloud providers and (b) UK SMEs; and what the value was of those contracts in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130553","130553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852556","2018-03-06","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the volume of UK citizens’ data held by companies (a) supplying cloud services to his Department and (b) contracted to deliver cloud services on behalf of his Department that is subject to information requests from US Government bodies.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130554","130554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852557","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the volume of UK citizens’ data held by companies (a) supplying cloud services to her Department and (b) contracted to deliver cloud services on behalf of her Department that is subject to information requests from US Government bodies.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130555","130555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852558","2018-03-06","Cabinet Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the volume of UK citizens’ data held by companies (a) supplying cloud services to his Department and (b) contracted to deliver cloud services on behalf of his Department that is subject to information requests from US Government bodies.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130556","130556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852559","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which members of her Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130557","130557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852560","2018-03-06","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which of his Department's contracts with Carillion since January 2016 were done with Open Book Contract Management.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130558","130558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852561","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which of his Department's contracts with Carillion since January 2016 were done with Open Book Contract Management.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130559","130559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852562","2018-03-06","Department for Transport","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which of his Department's contracts with Carillion since January 2016 were done with Open Book Contract Management.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130560","130560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852563","2018-03-06","Home Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which of her Department's contracts with Carillion since January 2016 were done with Open Book Contract Management.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130561","130561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852564","2018-03-06","Cabinet Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which of his Department's contracts with Carillion since January 2016 were done with Open Book Contract Management.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130562","130562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852565","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of breakdowns which have affected bi-mode trains since their introduction in October 2017.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130563","130563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852566","2018-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contracts his Department has agreed with Boeing in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130564","130564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852567","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether guidance issued by her Department to jobcentre staff includes a requirement to contact a (a) healthcare professional, (b) family member and (c) support worker  before a sanction is imposed on a vulnerable universal credit claimant.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130565","130565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852568","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Advice of Decision-Makers Memorandum 02/18, whether a claimant of employment support allowance can be sanctioned if they do not (a) consider a referral to professional service, (b) research local self-help centres and support groups appropriate to that claimant's health condition and (c) look at the Expert Patient Programme online.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130566","130566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852569","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national offenders were convicted of (a) murder, (b) manslaughter, (c) sexual offences, (d) rape and (e) serious assaults in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130567","130567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852570","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department provides for (a) feasibility studies for rail enhancement projects and (b) rail enhancement projects outside of the parish covered by the Statement of Available Funds for Control Period 6; and what the application process is for that funding.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130568","130568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852571","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2018 to Question 128964 on social services: national minimum wage, what the timescale is for his Department's further market analysis to assess the impact on the social care sector nationally; and if he publish that analysis and make copies of it available in the Library.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130569","130569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852572","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128880, on how many occasions the MPAM team did not to respond to written correspondence from an hon. Member within the service standard of 20 working days from receipt in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130570","130570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852573","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the information contained in the migration transparency data release provided in the Answer of 28 February 2018 to Question 128881, what definition her Department uses for a straightforward case; and how many and what proportion of cases have been classified as a straightforward case in each five years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130693","130693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852574","2018-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to Answer of 13 February 2018 to Question 126358  and the letter to the Secretary of State from the hon. Member for Edinburgh East, what his policy is on the sale of electronic shock collars.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130571","130571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852575","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to change the level of financial support provided by his Department under the personal independence payment scheme for claimants who have Primary Orthostatic Tremor.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130572","130572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852576","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to Answer of 6 February 2018 to Question 126173 on Department for Education: Telephone Services, how many of those helplines will continue to be funded by his Department after March 2018.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130694","130694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852577","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the implications for the planning applications he has called in relating to sites in Hatfield Peverel, Essex of the assessment in the Five Year Housing supply statement as of 31 December 2017 published by Braintree District Council that the Council has exceeded the five year supply of deliverable sites under the Liverpool methodology.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130573","130573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852578","2018-03-06","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will list the (a) dates and (b) attendees of meetings representatives of his Department that do not include the permanent secretary or ministers have held with (a) Beatty, (b) Barclays, (c) Dalmore Capital, (d) Equitix, (e) Innisfree, (f) Interserve, (g) Semperian and (h) Veolia in the last 12 months including the period not covered by the HMT ministers meetings data published on the 14th December 2017.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130574","130574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852579","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of India on the release of Jagtar Singh Johal.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130575","130575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852580","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost per mile of installing WiFi and mobile phone connectivity on the West Coast Main Line.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130576","130576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852581","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) all-electric and (b) hybrid vehicles are operated by his Department and its agencies.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130577","130577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852582","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Pakistani nationals were deported following the completion of their sentence in the last 12 months.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130578","130578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852583","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  when the last time was that each Minister in her Department met the Departments Chief Scientific Adviser.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130579","130579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852584","2018-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people have been arrested, charged and convicted for non-compliance of not ensuring that their dog is microchipped.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130580","130580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852585","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the cost of installing smart meters in domestic properties has been to date; and what estimate his Department has made of savings to domestic consumers of that installation.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130581","130581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852586","2018-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his oral contribution of 20 February 2018, Official Report, column 5, when the committee of wise people to consider future UK-French collaboration will be established.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130582","130582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852587","2018-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the change in level of the network cost component of household energy bills in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130583","130583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852588","2018-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made an assessment of the reasons for the change in the level of fuel poverty between 2014 and 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130584","130584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852589","2018-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking which support job creation schemes in Coventry South constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130585","130585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852590","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of trends in the level of female unemployment in Coventry South constituency since 2010; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130586","130586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852591","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Independent review of Full-Time Social Action, published in January 2018, what plans he has to discuss the recommendations made in that review with the Minister for Sport and Civil Society.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130587","130587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852592","2018-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February to Question 127853, on West Bank: Demolition, what steps his Department is taking to (a) prevent the re-occurrence of demolitions of classrooms in the West Bank and (b) work with international partners and organisations to provide alternative facilities for children directly affected by those demolitions.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130588","130588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852593","2018-03-06","Department for Transport","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total amount of compensation paid by Network Rail to rail operators was for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130589","130589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852594","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the views of people living in care homes are taken into account during consultations on the Green Paper on care and support for older people.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130590","130590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852595","2018-03-06","Home Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, the number of asylum applications made in the UK by people aged under 18 that have been approved in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130591","130591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852596","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of immigration caps on the ability of NHS Trusts to recruit staff from non-EU countries.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130592","130592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852597","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking ensure that the responses of people who do not have access to the internet are taken into account in its forthcoming consultation on care and support for older people.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130593","130593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852598","2018-03-06","Department for International Development","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the proportion of UK humanitarian aid to Yemen which has reached its intended beneficiaries in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130594","130594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852599","2018-03-06","Department for International Development","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent estimate she has made of the proportion of humanitarian assistance entering Yemen through Hodeidah port in the last three years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130595","130595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852600","2018-03-06","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many hon. Members and ministers received income tax relief on expenses in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130596","130596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852601","2018-03-06","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief for trading losses against capital gains in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130597","130597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852602","2018-03-06","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief on Stamp Duty Land Tax for demutualisation of an insurance company in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130598","130598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852603","2018-03-06","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief on Stamp Duty Land Tax for diplomatic privileges in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130599","130599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852604","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many leaseholders received Stamp Duty Land Tax relief for collective enfranchisement in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130600","130600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852605","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received Stamp Duty Land Tax relief for compliance with planning obligations in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130601","130601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852606","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief on Stamp Duty Land Tax for transfers in consequence of the reorganisation of parliamentary constituencies in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130602","130602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852607","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief on Stamp Duty Land Tax for alternative property finance in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130603","130603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852608","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief on Stamp Duty Land Tax for alternative finance investment bonds in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130604","130604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852609","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much money her Department has spent on promoting the universal credit helpline since it became a free number; and in what ways her Department is promoting that helpline.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130605","130605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852610","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief from Inheritance Tax for deaths on active service in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130606","130606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852611","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received a reduced rate of VAT on children’s car seats in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130607","130607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852612","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received a reduced rate of VAT on contraceptive products in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130608","130608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852613","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received a reduced rate of VAT on smoking cessation products in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130609","130609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852614","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received a reduced rate of VAT on women’s sanitary products in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130610","130610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852615","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has contacted all universal credit claimants to advise them that the helpline is now free to call.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130611","130611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852616","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received a zero rate of VAT on cycle helmets in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130612","130612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852617","2018-03-06","Cabinet Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department holds information on the number of people that died by suicide who were experiencing a financial crisis at the time of their death.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130613","130613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852618","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in the Nigerian Government on respect for religious freedom.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130614","130614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852619","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of debt and financial difficulty on recovery rates of people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130615","130615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852620","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic steps his Department is taking to help end the conflict in South Sudan.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130616","130616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852621","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department plans to publish the findings of the Deloitte and King's College audit of the liability of the social care sector for sleep-in shifts.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130617","130617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852622","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) arrests and (b) convictions were made relating to offences committed under the Hunting Act 2004 in the last two years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130618","130618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852623","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the findings of the Deloitte and King's College audit of the liability of the social care sector for sleep-in shifts.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130619","130619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852624","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of births that take place (a) in obstetric maternity units, (b) in midwife-led units that are (i) freestanding and (ii) alongside an obstetric unit, (c) at home, and (d) in any other setting.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130620","130620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852625","2018-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many reports his Department received of foxes killed by trail hunts by police force area in 2017.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130621","130621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852626","2018-03-06","Home Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to Question 125869, on police: taxis, tabled on 31 January 2018.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130622","130622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852627","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Government of Tanzania on the destruction of places of worship by local authorities within its jurisdiction; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130623","130623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852628","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had discussions with Northern Ireland authorities on safety advice being provided to fans travelling to the 2018 World Cup Finals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130624","130624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852629","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland authorities on the roll-out of superfast and ultrafast broadband in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130625","130625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852630","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of security co operation between the UK and Israel.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130626","130626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852631","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of  staff employed by UK Universities are citizens of (a) another EU member state (b) a non-EU state.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130627","130627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852632","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the strength of the UK's relationship with Jamaica when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130628","130628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852633","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of academic staff employed by UK universities spend more than 180 days working in academic institutions in other EU member states as part of their contract of employment.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130629","130629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852634","2018-03-06","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the economic consequences for the North East of leaving the Customs Union after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130630","130630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852635","2018-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the naval security situation in the territorial waters of the Republic of Cyprus.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130631","130631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852636","2018-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Turkey regarding Turkish Navy ships operating in proximity to the territorial waters of the Republic of Cyprus.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130632","130632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852637","2018-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has recently received reports of Cypriot airspace being entered by Turkish aircraft.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130633","130633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852638","2018-03-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State, the hon. Member for Wycombe has held meetings with Shanker Singham in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130634","130634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852639","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of support available to people experiencing mental health difficulties to help them manage their personal finances.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130635","130635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852640","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that financial lenders provide appropriate support to customers experiencing mental health difficulties.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130636","130636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852641","2018-03-06","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) women and (b) men in each local authority area in England started an apprenticeship in each sector subject area in 2016-17.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130637","130637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852642","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of debt and financial difficulty on recovery rates of people mental health problems.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130638","130638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852643","2018-03-06","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2018 to Question 127246, on Schools: Standards, if he will list the (a) number and (b) names of academy schools which have had their funding agreement terminated and have not yet been re-brokered.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130639","130639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852644","2018-03-06","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that child poverty does not have a detrimental effect on educational attainment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130640","130640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852645","2018-03-06","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2018. to Question 127246, on Schools: Standards, what the timescale was for each academy school which had its funding agreement terminated in the last 12 months to be rebrokered.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130641","130641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852646","2018-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many US (a) military personnel, (b) contractors and (c)civilians are stationed at RAF Fylingdales.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130642","130642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852647","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the governance arrangements are for United States Visiting Force bases in the UK.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130643","130643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852648","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the Government fully meeting the costs in the care sector of any liability and back-pay relating to sleep-in shifts.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130644","130644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852649","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2018 to Question 120663, on Right to Buy Scheme: Fraud, how many individual investigations the Department has launched into fraud associated with right to buy purchases.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130645","130645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852650","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of NHS hospitals in England which have introduced free parking or concessionary rates for staff who car-share since 2014.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130646","130646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852651","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of NHS hospitals in England which prioritise parking for staff whose daily duties require them to travel by car.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130647","130647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852652","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the accessibility by public transport of hospitals outside London.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130648","130648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852653","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the accessibility by public transport of hospitals in rural areas.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130649","130649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852654","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of NHS hospitals in England which manage their own parking facilities.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130650","130650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852655","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of NHS hospitals in England which have outsourced the management of their parking facilities to a private company.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130651","130651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852656","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of NHS hospitals in England which have a Private Finance Initiative contract associated with their parking facilities.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130652","130652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852657","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of NHS hospitals in England which have entered into a Private Finance Initiative associated with their parking facilities since 2010.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130653","130653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852658","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to support employees of ToysRUs and Maplin.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130654","130654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852659","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2018 to Question 120654, on Local Government: Training, what direct funding his Department offers for training for (a) leaders of local authorities and (b) local authority cabinet members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130655","130655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852660","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if officials of his Department will meet patient organisations to ensure the patient voice is heard during the re-negotiation of the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130656","130656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852661","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with NHS England on the timetable for the introduction of Herceptin (trastuzumab) biosimilars for use in the NHS.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130657","130657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852662","2018-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure services forces accommodation is completed (a) on time and (b) within budget at the planned super garrison at Catterick.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130658","130658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852663","2018-03-06","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2018 to Question 128697, whether payments made to school efficiency advisers by his Department will come from existing budgets or whether additional funding has been granted to the Department for that purpose.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130659","130659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852664","2018-03-06","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made on providing a sharia-compliant alternative student finance system.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130660","130660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852665","2018-03-06","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2018 to Question 128697, what data his Department collects on how many schools employ a school business professional; and what the (a) remit and (b) typical rate of pay is of those professionals.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130661","130661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852666","2018-03-06","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2018 to Question 128697, what additional advice or service the Department considers that schools’ existing school business professional may be able to provide in their role as a school efficiency adviser that they have not already provided in the course of their existing employment.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130662","130662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852667","2018-03-06","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether a sharia-compliant alternative student finance system will be available for people beginning university courses in September 2018.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130663","130663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852668","2018-03-06","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2018 to Question 128697, who is responsible for recruiting self-employed school efficiency advisers; what the criteria for employment are; where those posts have been advertised; how many candidates have applied to date; and how many of those applicants have been accepted.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130664","130664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852669","2018-03-06","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February to Question 128697, how many school efficiency advisers are already employed by schools as a school business professional; and how many of those advisers are self-employed.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130665","130665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852670","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the number of jobs in the shale gas industry in (a) 2025 and (b) 2030; whether those estimates have changed since estimates for the number of such jobs in those years made in (i) 2012 and (ii) 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130666","130666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852671","2018-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to her Department's guidance, Advice for decision-making: staff guide, updated on 15 February 2018, what assessment she has made of whether work-related activity includes (a) considering referrals to professional services, (b) researching local self-help centres and support groups appropriate to a claimant’s health condition and (c) looking at the Expert Patient Programme online and listing reasons on how it could benefit a claimant.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130667","130667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852672","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of the roll-out of Universal Credit on levels of child poverty.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130668","130668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852673","2018-03-05","Department for International Development","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has allocated to deafness programmes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130669","130669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852674","2018-03-05","Department for International Development","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much his Department has allocated to deafness programmes in each country for which aid was provided in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130670","130670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852675","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many dogs from the Defence Animal Centre have been re-homed in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130671","130671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852676","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the combined pre-qualification questionnaire and invitation to negotiate (ITN) to industry for the Type 31e general purpose frigate competitive design phase (CDP).","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130672","130672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852677","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much money was spent on digital court services in each of the last three years; and what that funding was used for.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130673","130673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852678","2018-03-06","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending Stamp Duty Reserve Tax to transactions in a broader range of financial assets, such as corporate bonds and derivatives, based on the residency principle whereby liability is incurred if the ultimate buyer is a UK taxpayer.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130674","130674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852679","2018-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what guidance his Department provides to UK diplomatic posts overseas on the official terminology that should be used to refer to the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130675","130675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852680","2018-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department is undertaking a review of the Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130676","130676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852681","2018-03-06","Department for Transport","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with (a) Hitachi and (b) GWR on the delay in the delivery of new rolling stock for use on the London-South Wales mainline.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130677","130677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852682","2018-03-06","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, on how many occasions he visited (a) Brussels, (b) Luxembourg, (c) Paris, (d) Berlin and (e) Dublin in the last six months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130678","130678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852683","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason Baroness Cumberlege's review of vaginal mesh implants will not include an audit of ventral mesh rectopexy surgery.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130679","130679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852684","2018-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the planned relocation of (a) 160 Brigade HQ and (b) HMS Cambria will take place.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130680","130680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852685","2018-03-06","HM Treasury","2018-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when (a) he or (b) HM Revenue and Customs officials last met representatives of the Roadchef Employee Benefits Fund.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130681","130681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852686","2018-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the British Ambassador to NATO and (b) the Turkish Ambassador to NATO on the Turkish military operation in Afrin.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130682","130682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852687","2018-03-06","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of how effectively early years providers are using the early years pupil premium.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130683","130683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852688","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of amending s2(A)(1) of the Road Traffic Act 1988 to ensure that the police are able to chase alleged criminals on mopeds without the risk of subsequent conviction.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130684","130684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852689","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will respond to the Chief Executive of the National Day Nurseries Association comments to Nursery World that the workforce survey indicates a staffing crisis in nurseries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130685","130685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852690","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to revise the Government’s Early Years Workforce Strategy following the findings of the National Day Nurseries Association 2017-18 workforce survey.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130686","130686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852691","2018-03-06","Department for International Development","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps she has taken to help prevent a famine in South Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130687","130687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852693","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many welfare cases were granted legal aid in each year since 2011-12; and how many of those cases involved a challenge to a decision to remove an entitlement to benefits.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130688","130688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852694","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for civil legal aid were granted for (a) settling applications for permission to appeal to the Upper Tribunal (Administrative Appeals Chamber), (b) representation in the Court of Appeal and the Supreme Court and (c) representation in proceedings for judicial review in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130689","130689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852695","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of welfare cases involving disability benefits which were granted legal aid in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130690","130690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852696","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2017 to Question 115087 on Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme, whether a decision has been made on the timing of negotiations with industry on the next Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130691","130691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851469","2018-02-28","Department for International Development","2018-02-28","What steps her Department has taken in response to the recent outbreak of plague in Africa.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904084","904084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851470","2018-02-28","Department for International Development","2018-02-28","What proportion of her Department's aid spending is committed to tackling religious persecution.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904085","904085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851471","2018-02-28","Department for International Development","2018-02-28","What steps her Department is taking to reduce the global prevalence of HIV and AIDS.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904086","904086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851472","2018-02-28","Department for International Development","2018-02-28","What steps her Department is taking to tackle the humanitarian crisis in Yemen.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904087","904087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851473","2018-02-28","Department for International Development","2018-02-28","What steps her Department is taking to promote food security in developing countries by increasing crop yields.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904088","904088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851474","2018-02-28","Department for International Development","2018-02-28","What steps her Department is taking to tackle the humanitarian crisis in Yemen.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904090","904090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851475","2018-02-28","Department for International Development","2018-02-28","What steps she is taking to support people with disabilities in developing countries.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904092","904092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851506","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to inform consumers of (a) the limitations on the interoperability of first generation meters when changing energy supplier and (b) how those limitations will be tackled through the roll-out of second generation meters.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130269","130269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851507","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department plans to take steps to encourage companies to improve the health and well-being of their employees.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130270","130270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851508","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what contingency plans his Department has made to manage the teachers' pensions scheme in the event of Capita being unable to fulfil its contractual obligations.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130271","130271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851509","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support the wave and tidal energy sector in the South West.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130272","130272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851510","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has plans to stop HMRC promoting an 0843 premium rate customer service number on its website instead of the local rate 0300 number.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130273","130273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851511","2018-03-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his Department's policy is on maintaining the rights and entitlements of children under the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130274","130274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851512","2018-03-05","Department for International Trade","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the value was of trade deals agreed by Scottish-based businesses which took part in the January 2018 trade visit to China by the Prime Minister.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130275","130275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851513","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much the Government has invested in the roll-out of superfast broadband in the South West.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130276","130276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851514","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much the Government has invested in the roll-out of superfast broadband in South Gloucestershire.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130277","130277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851515","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much the Government has invested in the roll-out of superfast broadband in the Thornbury and Yate constituency.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130278","130278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851516","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many homes have been connected to superfast broadband in the South West.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130279","130279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851517","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many homes have been connected to superfast broadband in South Gloucestershire.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130280","130280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851518","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many homes have been connected to superfast broadband in the Thornbury and Yate constituency.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130281","130281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851519","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to increase access to full fibre-to-the-property broadband in rural areas.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130282","130282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851520","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that internet service providers supply customers with the internet speeds that they have advertised.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130283","130283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851521","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support job creation schemes in St Helens South and Whiston constituency; and how much Regional Growth Fund money has been allocated to (a) that constituency and (b) the North West.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130284","130284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851522","2018-03-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2018 to Question 127136 and Answer of 23 February 2018 to Question 128683, what classification was given by his Department to the document EU exit analysis-Cross Whitehall briefing.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130285","130285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851523","2018-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to make funding available for local authorities to monitor particulate matter PM2.5 and PM10.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130286","130286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851524","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with the Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government about office space at the Waterfront in Dudley.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130287","130287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851525","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the Child Maintenance Service's collect and pay system.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130288","130288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851526","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that rape crisis centres are adequately funded.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130289","130289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851527","2018-03-05","Attorney General","2018-02-28","To ask the Attorney General, what steps he is taking to improve the system of evidence disclosure in criminal justice cases.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130290","130290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851528","2018-03-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to publish the Computable General Equilibrium model estimates of the economic effect of the UK leaving the EU on other EU member states which are currently being undertaken.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130291","130291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851529","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which method her Department used to estimate the number of recipients of Support for Mortgage Interest who have access to funds and therefore would not need to use the new loan system.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130292","130292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851530","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the effectiveness of Serco in informing Support for Mortgage Interest recipients about the transition to loans; what estimate her Department has made of the number of people not yet informed on that transition; and what representations her Department has received on the adequacy of the service provided by Serco in providing comprehensive information on that transition.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130293","130293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851531","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the value is of Serco's contract to undertake Support for Mortgage Interest replacement loans work; and what terms that contract contains on performance-related pay.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130294","130294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851532","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has received representations from the Government of Poland on displaying a Supermarine Spitfire in Poland to commemorate the Polish contribution to the Battle of Britain.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130295","130295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851533","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of GP practices offer a six week postnatal check-up; and what information his Department holds on the take-up of such checks at those practices.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130296","130296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851534","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that recipients of employment support allowance with the severe disability premium do not have payments reduced when they move to an area where universal credit has been implemented.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130297","130297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851535","2018-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which members of his Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130298","130298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851536","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which members of his Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130299","130299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851537","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which members of his Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130300","130300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851538","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which members of his Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130301","130301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851539","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which members of her Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130302","130302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851540","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which members of his Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130303","130303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851541","2018-03-05","Department for International Development","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which members of her Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130304","130304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851542","2018-03-05","Department for International Trade","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which members of his Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130305","130305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851543","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which members of his Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130306","130306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851544","2018-03-05","Northern Ireland Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which members of her Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130307","130307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851545","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which members of his Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130308","130308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851546","2018-03-05","Scotland Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, which members of his Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130309","130309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851547","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which members of his Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130310","130310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851548","2018-03-05","Wales Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which members of his Department's board are responsible for ensuring the proper application of the business appointment rules for former Ministers and senior civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130311","130311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851549","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the Support for Mortgage Interest caseload was by (a) local authority area and (b) parliamentary constituency for the most recent twelve months for which data is available.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130312","130312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851550","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the independent review by David Anderson QC entitled Attacks in London and Manchester, published in December 2017, what assessment her Department has made of ending the operational use of the terms domestic extremism and international counter-terrorism.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130313","130313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851551","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2018 to Question 126937, what target her Department sets for the completion of Stage 2 complaints relating to the Independent Assessment Service.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130314","130314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851552","2018-03-05","Northern Ireland Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what her policy is on the recognition in Northern Ireland of same sex marriages performed in the UK.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130315","130315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851553","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what further steps the Government is taking to secure a UN resolution condemning persecution of the Rohingya in Myanmar and calling for the return of refugees’ citizenship.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130316","130316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851554","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of how much would be saved on an annual basis if tax relief on personal pension contributions was capped at the basic rate, based on the total amount of personal pension contributions in 2016-17.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130317","130317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851555","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for how long the e-forum for SENCOs was unavailable; and what steps he is taking to ensure that that e-forum remains fully operational after its recent recovery.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130318","130318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851556","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proposals he has to improve the accuracy and comprehensiveness of medical evidence supplied to Work Capability Assessments.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130319","130319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851557","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to encourage all parties to abide by the Minsk agreements.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130320","130320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851558","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the recent enactment of the Donbass Reintegration law by the Ukrainian Parliament on the implementation of the Minsk agreements.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130321","130321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851559","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether (a) he, (b) his predecessor, (c) current or former Ministers of his Department and (d) officials of his Department held meetings with contractors who had been encouraged to apply to carry out work relating to the incoming early years baseline assessment in which that assessment was discussed and before details of the contracts were made public.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130322","130322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851560","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the implications for its policies on the East Coast mainline of the findings of a Populus poll in 2017 that 76 per cent of the UK population favour returning railways to public ownership.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130323","130323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851561","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many members of his Department's staff have been paid an incorrect wage in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130324","130324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851562","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to improve the visibility of police officers in local communities.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130325","130325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851563","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to improve (a) trust and (b) confidence between police and local communities.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130326","130326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851564","2018-03-05","Department for International Development","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to widen participation in her Department's volunteer programmes, particularly by people from low income backgrounds.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130327","130327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851565","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to introduce a tapered income for entitlement to free school meals under universal credit in order to incentivise being in employment.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130328","130328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851566","2018-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons the Government's command paper, Health and Harmony: the future for food, farming and the environment in a Green Brexit, Cm. 9577, published on 27 February 2018, does not reference the role of agricultural policy in supporting public health and tackling diet-related disease.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130329","130329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851567","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has received reports that Sudanese nationals returning from Belgium to Sudan were (a) detained, (b) interrogated and (c) tortured in Sudan.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130330","130330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851568","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of ending the Tier 1 (Post-Study Work) visa on the ability of businesses to recruit people with the necessary skills.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130331","130331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851569","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what dates (a) each of the remaining Trafalgar class submarines are planned to leave service and (b) each of the  Astute class are planned to enter service with the Royal Navy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130332","130332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851570","2018-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans for seven Astute class submarines to be constructed; and what name is planned for the seventh boat.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130333","130333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851571","2018-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for how long HMS Ambush remained out of service as a result of her collision with a surface vessel in July 2016.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130334","130334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851572","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Transport of 27 February 2018, Official Report, column 794, what methodology is used to allocate revenue raised from vehicle excise duty to (a) road construction projects and (b) roads maintenance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130335","130335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851573","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to support the UK hospitality industry’s job growth target of employing an additional 19,000 jobs in the sector by 2020.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130336","130336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851574","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government plans to support the hospitality industry’s upcoming campaign entitled Hospitality Works; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130337","130337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851575","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what representations his Department has received on the potential effect on the hospitality sector of the proposed merger between the Association of Licensed Multiple Retailers and the British Hospitality Association.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130338","130338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851576","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients stayed at an NHS hospital in England for 14 days or longer in 2017.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130339","130339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851577","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients stayed at an NHS hospital in England for 30 days or longer in 2017.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130340","130340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851578","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England charge visitors of inpatients to park.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130341","130341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851579","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England charge staff to park.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130342","130342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851580","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England have introduced (a) free parking and (b) concessionary rates for blue badge holders since 2014.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130343","130343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851581","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England have introduced (a) free parking and (b) concessionary rates for frequent outpatient attenders since 2014.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130344","130344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851582","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England have introduced (a) free parking and (b) concessionary rates for (i) visitors with relatives who are gravely ill and (ii) carers of such people since 2014.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130345","130345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851583","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England have introduced (a) free parking and (b) concessionary rates for (i) visitors of relatives who have an extended stay in hospital and (ii) carers of such people since 2014.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130346","130346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851584","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England have introduced (a) free parking and (b) concessionary rates for staff working shifts that prevent the use of public transport since 2014.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130347","130347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851585","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England have introduced (a) free parking and (b) concessionary rates for volunteers since 2014.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130348","130348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851586","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of safeguarding checks that are in place for home schooled children.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130349","130349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851587","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of whether there is an attainment gap between home schooled children and children in formal education.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130350","130350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851588","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the regulations that are in place to protect home schooled children from abuse, extremism and radicalisation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130351","130351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851589","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what regulations are in place to ensure that parents are suitably qualified to teach their home schooled children.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130352","130352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851590","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2018 to Question 128612, whether the proposed Sharia-compliant alternative student finance product will be available for students applying for university in the 2018-19 academic year.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130353","130353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851591","2018-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to set a target for recycling disposable coffee cups.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130354","130354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851592","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, in how many medical negligence claims against the NHS which were settled in 2016-2017 legal proceedings were issued; and in how many such claims damage payments were made.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130355","130355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851593","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many medical negligence claims against the NHS were taken to trial in 2016-2017; and in how many such trials damages were awarded.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130356","130356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851594","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the level of Air Passenger Duty on the UK’s global aviation connectivity (a) nationally and (b) by region compared to other European countries.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130357","130357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851595","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the rate of Air Passenger Duty on trade links after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130358","130358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851596","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of Air Passenger Duty rates on the development of new routes from UK airports compared with such development from other EU airports; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130359","130359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851597","2018-03-05","Cabinet Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128318, on the One Public Estate Programme, how many of those submitted applications included partnerships with government departments.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130360","130360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851598","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the British intellectual property sector and the businesses that rely upon that sector.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130361","130361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851599","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2018 to Question 127503, if he will take additional steps to promote to local authorities the availability of funding for Traveller pitches.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130362","130362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851600","2018-03-05","Cabinet Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128095, on Government Departments: Procurement, whether any payment was made to that third party.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130363","130363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851601","2018-03-05","Cabinet Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128092, whether it is his policy that contracts would be assessed to be of sufficient risk that Open Book Contract Management would be used in cases where the supplier of such contracts is a strategic supplier who has triggered one of the high risk criteria in the Strategic Suppliers Risk Management Policy.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130364","130364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851602","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women are serving sentences in prison for each (a) offence category used in his Department's offender management statistics and (b) Home Office offence code where appropriate.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130365","130365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851603","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2018 to Question 127599, on Courts: Buildings, how much was spent on the modernisation of each of those courts in the 12 months prior to being closed.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130366","130366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851604","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer on 8 January 2018 to Question 120804, what recent assessment he has made of the annual cost to the Exchequer of providing intermediary relief to those claiming it under existing Stamp Duty Reserve Tax rules.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130367","130367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851605","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support people with mental health difficulties who experience financial difficulties.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130368","130368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851606","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of high frequency trading strategies on the resilience of UK financial markets.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130369","130369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851607","2018-03-05","Cabinet Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were employed on (a) short-term contracts and (b) in temporary positions in all sectors of the economy in each of the last three months.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130370","130370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851608","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Transport of 27 February 2018, Official Report, column 793, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of trains in the north of England which will be (a) replaced and (b) refurbished by 2020.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130371","130371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851609","2018-03-05","Cabinet Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128315, on One Public Estate Programme, how many such grants have been offered; to whom those grants have been awarded; and how much money each offeree has received.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130372","130372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851610","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of school leavers have participated in higher education in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130373","130373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851611","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the efficiency of ambulance services in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130374","130374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851612","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of local bus services in (a) Coventry South constituency, (b) Coventry and the (c) the West Midlands since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130375","130375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851613","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his counterpart in Estonia and what issues were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130376","130376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851614","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his counterpart in Latvia and what issues were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130377","130377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851615","2018-03-05","Cabinet Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128318, on One Public Estate Programme, if he will provide that same data by whether those bids were successful.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130378","130378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851616","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has issued instructions to local authorities to build up reserves.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130379","130379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851617","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has issued instructions to police authorities to build up financial reserves.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130380","130380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851618","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will place a copy of the routine oral questions asked during face-to-face medical assessments for (a) personal independence payment and (b) employment and support allowance in the Library.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130381","130381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851619","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the effect of pensions auto-enrolment on the income of low-paid workers.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130382","130382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851620","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to close the attainment gap between boys who are eligible for free school meals and other pupils in Birkenhead.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130383","130383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851621","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128316, on Network Rail: Property, what the (a) proceeds and (b) costs were in each of those years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130384","130384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851622","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Indian counterpart on the treatment of Christians in India.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130385","130385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851623","2018-03-05","Department for International Development","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance is being made available to Palestinian refugees affected by the conflict in Syria.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130386","130386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851624","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to help stop the supply of arms to al-Shaabab in Somalia and Kenya.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130387","130387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851625","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2018 to question 127068, how much of those financial remedies incurred by G4S was in relation to each contract that company has held with his Department; and for what reasons each such financial remedy was imposed.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130388","130388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851626","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2018 to Question 127288 on prisons: health services, in what format information on the funding of healthcare in prisons is held.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130389","130389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851627","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 129249, on victim support schemes, what estimate his Department made of the cost of providing the information sought.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130390","130390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851628","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to regulate the activities of private detectives.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130391","130391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851629","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 129247, on victim support schemes, what estimate his Department made of the cost of providing the information sought.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130392","130392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851630","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 129250, on victim support schemes, what estimate his Department made of the cost of providing the information sought.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130393","130393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851631","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2017 to Question 127066, on Ministry of Justice: Public Opinion, what estimate his Department has made of the potential cost of collecting data on focus groups and opinion polling conducted by his Department.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130394","130394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851632","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2018 to Question 126350, whether prison governors will be empowered to bring prison maintenance back in house.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130395","130395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851633","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to reduce the length of time that unemployed people spend out of work.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130396","130396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851634","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department next plans to publish information on the capital costs of individual free schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130397","130397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851635","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of unemployment in the Thornbury and Yate constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130398","130398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851636","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she made of trends in the level of unemployment in South Gloucestershire since 2010.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130399","130399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851637","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment has she made of trends in the level of unemployment in the South West since 2010.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130400","130400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851638","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment has she made of trends in the level of female unemployment in the Thornbury and Yate constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130401","130401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851639","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment has she made of trends in the level of female unemployment in South Gloucestershire since 2010.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130402","130402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851640","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of female unemployment in the South West since 2010.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130403","130403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851641","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of youth unemployment in the Thornbury and Yate constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130404","130404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851642","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment has she made of trends in the level of youth unemployment in South Gloucestershire since 2010.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130405","130405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851643","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment has she made of trends in the level of youth unemployment in the South West since 2010.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130406","130406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851644","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of shotgun and firearms certificates that have been granted where the applicant's doctor has not participated in the licensing process in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130407","130407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851645","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of GPs who are co-operating with the system of placing a marker on the medical notes of a person who has shotgun and firearm certificates.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130408","130408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851646","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what training members of the armed forces receive in respect of the initiative on the prevention of sexual violence in conflict.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130409","130409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851647","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of GPs in each police constabulary area who are not participating in the firearms licensing process.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130410","130410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851648","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with Babcock Defence Support Group on the future use of the Forthside estate in Stirling.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130411","130411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851649","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the level of charges that GPs pass on to applicants for medical reports required for new or renewed shotgun and firearms certificates.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130412","130412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851650","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions have taken place between his Department and Stirling Council on the future use of his Department's Forthside estate in Stirling.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130413","130413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851651","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions have taken place between his Department and Babcock DSG on (a) the future of that company's operations in Scotland and (b) the location of a mobile base of operation in Scotland.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130414","130414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851652","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has held with the devolved administrations on the Government's response to the Matthew Taylor review of modern working practices; and what the outcomes of those discussions were.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130415","130415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851653","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has had with the Scottish Government on (a) the Productivity Leadership Group and (b) the scope of that group's activities with Scottish businesses.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130416","130416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851654","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national offenders are subject to multi-agency public protection arrangements.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130417","130417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851655","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2018 to Question 123796, which joint exercises with South Korea he plans the UK to participate in over the next two years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130418","130418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851656","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2018 to Question 123796, which joint exercises with the US he plans the UK to participate in over the next two years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130419","130419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851657","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2018 to Question 123796, which joint exercises with Japan he plans the UK to participate in over the next two years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130420","130420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851658","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2018 to Question 123796, how many personnel from the (a) Army, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Royal Air Force are planned to participate in joint exercises with South Korea over the next two years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130421","130421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851659","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2018 to Question 123796, how many personnel from the (a) Army, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Royal Air Force are planned to participate in joint exercises with the US over the next two years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130422","130422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851660","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2018 to Question 123796, how many personnel from the (a) Army, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Royal Air Force are planned to participate in joint exercises with Japan over the next two years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130423","130423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851661","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many operations at Wirral University Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust have been (a) postponed and (b) cancelled in the most recent three months for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130424","130424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851662","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients by type of operation are currently on a waiting list for an operation at Wirral University Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130425","130425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851663","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total cost is of the Electric Vehicle Homecharge Scheme to date; and how many people have used that scheme.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130426","130426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851664","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the criteria are for accessing her Department's knife crime community fund.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130427","130427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851665","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will discuss with (a) HM Treasury, (b) the Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government, (c) the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, and (d) other key stakeholders steps to establish the funding necessary to the deliver the key strategic rail infrastructure improvements identified by the Great Eastern Main Line Rail Task Force.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130428","130428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851666","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of the (a) A12 widening scheme and (b) the dualling and upgrading the A120 between Braintree and Marks Tey.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130429","130429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851667","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on ensuring that all people with pre-payment meters who are eligible for the winter fuel payment have that payment applied automatically.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130430","130430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851668","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department takes to retrospectively pay winter fuel payments to eligible recipients with pre-paid meters who have not had that payment applied by their energy supplier.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130431","130431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851669","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals convicted of sex offences in the UK are awaiting deportation in (a) custody and (b) the community; and how many foreign nationals convicted of sex offences in the UK were deported in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130432","130432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851670","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128441, Fracking: Wells, what the evidential basis is for the statement that the estimate that there could be 155 fracking wells by around 2025 is considered out of date.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130433","130433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851671","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2018 to Question 129007 on Asa Hutchinson, if he will publish the ministerial-level meetings where the case has been discussed; and whether the case was raised at the bi-annual UK-UAE Taskforce meeting of 28 February 2018.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130434","130434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851672","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to collect data on the number of women who have had vaginal mesh surgery who experienced (a) pain, (b) a reduction in the quality of sex life, (c) constant urinary infections and (d) a reduction in the quality of life.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130435","130435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851673","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of banning vaginal mesh for (a) pelvic organ prolapse and (b) stress urinary incontinence; what steps his Department is taking to improve surgical training those procedures; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130436","130436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851674","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of surgical mesh implants have shrunk after being inserted.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130437","130437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851675","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to provide extra funding to the Metropolitan Police to tackle knife crime.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130438","130438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851676","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to publish a knife crime strategy in response to recent fatalities in London.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130439","130439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851677","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many community support police officers there were in each London borough in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130440","130440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851678","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of take-up for the new loan product that will replace Support for Mortgage Interest in April 2018 is people currently in receipt of that benefit.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130441","130441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851679","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2018 to Question 126730, what the total cost to the Exchequer is of the tax-free childcare scheme not including the cost of 30 hours free childcare.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130442","130442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851680","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2018 to Question 127702, whether all of the recipients of Support for Mortgage Interest have now been contacted regarding the cessation of that benefit.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130443","130443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851681","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2018 to Question 126793, on Ministry of Justice: consultants, what estimate his Department made of the cost of providing the information sought.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130444","130444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851682","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2018 to Question 127038, on courts: video conferencing, what estimate his Department made of the cost of providing the information sought.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130445","130445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851683","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2018 to Question 127040, on courts: video conferencing, what estimate his Department made of the cost of providing the information sought.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130446","130446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851684","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that there is sufficient workforce capacity to deliver the Faecal Immunochemical Test.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130447","130447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851685","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2018, to Question 126333, on Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012, whether her Department plans to publish the list of organisations and experts it plans to invite to submit evidence to the post-implementation review of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 once that list has been determined.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130448","130448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851686","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of key performance indicators in contracts signed by his Department since 2010 have been met in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130449","130449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851687","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many key performance indicators in each contract signed by his Department since 2010 have (a) been met and (b) not been met in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130450","130450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851688","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what financial deductions have been made under each contract signed by his Department since 2010 which contain key performance indicators in each year since 2010; and for what reason those deductions were made in that same period.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130451","130451"
