"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39388","2014-02-26","House of Commons Commission","2014-02-21","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2013 to the hon. Member for Lichfield, Official Report, column 4W, on wi-fi; what progress the Parliamentary Information and Communications Technology service has made in looking at ways of securely improving the wi-fi service to a wider range of devices.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188809","188809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39389","2014-02-25","Department for International Development","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many publications her Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188884","188884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39390","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publication was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188885","188885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39391","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of using ethylene glycol-based anti-freeze products deliberately with the intention to poison in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188902","188902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39392","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the budget was for each judges' lodging in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188839","188839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39393","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 603W, on prisoners: self-harm, how many and what proportion of (a) self-harm incidents and (b) suicides occur when an Assessment Care in Custody Teamwork document is open; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188842","188842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39394","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many successful prosecutions for fraud in (a) England and (b) Cornwall have been for cases involving trade on the website eBay in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188913","188913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39395","2014-02-25","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many publications her Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188886","188886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39396","2014-02-26","Department for International Development","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if he will make it the Government's policy to press for the adoption of an international goal that no baby should be born without a midwife present in order to reduce deaths among newborns; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188911","188911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39397","2014-02-25","Scotland Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188887","188887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39398","2014-02-25","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188888","188888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39399","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will meet Google to discuss copycat websites which charge for driving licence renewals.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188873","188873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39400","2014-02-25","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his speech to the National Rail conference on 29 October 2013, entitled Why HS2 will spread prosperity, what alternative options his Department considered to free up rail capacity; and for what reasons it has been decided that High Speed 2 will be the most cost-effective and economically beneficial way to free up capacity as opposed to (a) double-decker carriages and (b) other capacity increasing options.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188841","188841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39401","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the reliability and punctuality of passenger services on the North Cotswold Line; and if he will instruct First Great Western to commence publishing this information separately in its Passenger Charter figures.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188793","188793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39402","2014-02-25","Wales Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188890","188890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39403","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188891","188891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39404","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2014, Official Report, columns 95-6W, on employment and support allowance, if he will publish the contractual quality targets applied to Atos.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188864","188864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39405","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2014, Official Report, column 96W, on employment and support allowance, if he will place in the Library a copy of the operational guidance on the termination of employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188863","188863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39406","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations he has received on the situation of those women born between 1951 and 1953 who will receive a smaller weekly state pension income than a man with the same date of birth from 2016; if he will make it his policy to guarantee that no women born betwene 1951 and 1953 with an equivalent number of qualifying years receive a smaller state pension income on a weekly basis than as a man with the same date of birth commencing in 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188898","188898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39407","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment he has made of the incidence of poverty among (a) single women pensioners and (b) other pensioners.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188899","188899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39408","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to section 96 of the Welfare Reform Act 2012, what information he used to determine estimated average earnings when setting the rates for the Household Benefit Cap for 2014-15.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188860","188860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39409","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households have had their benefits reduced as a result of the household benefit cap in (a) the London Borough of Brent and (b) Brent Central constituency.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188912","188912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38891","2014-02-24","Attorney General","2014-02-13","To ask the Attorney General, whether the Crown Prosecution Service records the number of domestic violence prosecutions that are conducted without the participation of the victim.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188414","188414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38892","2014-02-24","Attorney General","2014-02-13","To ask the Attorney General, who will conduct the Crown Prosecution Service (CPS) review of the effects on changes in charging guidance on referrals from the police to the CPS in rape cases; when the review will conclude; and if a report of the review will be made public.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188415","188415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38893","2014-02-24","Attorney General","2014-02-13","To ask the Attorney General, whether the Crown Prosecution Service (CPS) review of the effects of changes in charging guidance on referrals of rape case from the police to the CPS will also look at referrals of cases of domestic violence and child abuse.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188417","188417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38894","2014-02-24","Attorney General","2014-02-13","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Written Statement of 30 January 2014, Official Report, column 39WS, on Serious Fraud Office (Contingencies Fund Advance), for what reasons the Serious Fraud Office was unable to settle its material liabilities without a supplementary estimate at that point in the financial year.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188571","188571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38895","2014-02-24","Attorney General","2014-02-13","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Written Statement of 30 January 2014, Official Report, column 39WS, on Serious Fraud Office (Contingencies Fund Advance), what proportion of the additional funds that the Serious Fraud Office (SFO) has requested from HM Treasury is intended for use in (a) providing blockbuster investigations and (b) meeting the costs of legal actions in which the SFO is the respondent rather than the prosecutor.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188572","188572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38896","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many of the applications for non-apprenticeship further education loans have been subsequently accepted and paid.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188561","188561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38897","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many of the applications in total for further education loans have been subsequently accepted and paid.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188562","188562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38898","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much of the 24+ advanced learner loans budget for 2013-14 has been spent.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188563","188563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38899","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of businesses are owned by women in each region.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188557","188557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38900","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many applications have been received for non-apprenticeship further education loans so far under the 24+ advanced learner loans scheme.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188559","188559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38901","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many applications are anticipated in 2013-14 for non-apprenticeship further education loans.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188560","188560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38902","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether there has been any fall in participation in further education from learners aged 24 and above as a result of 24+ advanced learner loans.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188549","188549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38903","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average loan amount given to a learner under the 24+ advanced learner loan model is.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188550","188550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38904","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment has been made as to how level 3 apprenticeships will be funded via the adult skills budget in 2014-15.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188551","188551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38905","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what change there has been in participation in further education from learners aged 24 and above as a result of 24+ advanced learner loans; and whether any such change was reflected in his Department's impact assessment of that policy.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188553","188553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38906","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the proportion of each 24+ advanced learner loan which will never be repaid.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188554","188554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38907","2014-02-24","Cabinet Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of (a) men and (b) women are self-employed in each (i) occupational and (ii) industry group in each region.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188555","188555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38908","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment has been made of the effect of funding level 3 apprenticeships via the adult skills budget on apprenticeships and other qualifications.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188552","188552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38909","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average income of self-employed (a) men and (b) women is in each region.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188556","188556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38910","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding or support his Department has provided to the Year of Code.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188533","188533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38911","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Government cuts off costly calls, published on 13 December 2013, for what reasons banks and transport operators were not included in his Department's proposals to require private companies to use geographic rates for telephone enquiries.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188423","188423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38912","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many small businesses in (a) the West Midlands, (b) Worcestershire and (c) Redditch have benfited from the Funding for Lending Scheme.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188451","188451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38913","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has for the employer ownership of skills initiative in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188452","188452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38914","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which local enterprise partnerships submitted final European Structural and Investment Fund strategies to his Department by the end of January 2014.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188472","188472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38915","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on the creation of new research institutions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188498","188498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38916","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the value of publicly funded bursaries or scholarships available to students wishing to study (a) biology, (b) chemistry, (c) physics, (d) electrical engineering, (e) mechanical engineering, (f) computing and (g) mathematics at an undergraduate level was for the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188504","188504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38917","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has to improve the ability of UK firms to adopt new technologies.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188505","188505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38918","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which universities had departments of (a) biology, (b) chemistry, (c) physics, (d) electrical engineering, (e) mechanical engineering, (f) computing and (g) mathematics in (i) 1997, (ii) 2010 and (iii) the latest date for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188497","188497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38919","2014-02-24","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-13","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2014, Official Report, column 695W, on electoral register, what applicants to the Rock Enrol! initiative were told in the reply they received informing them of the outcome of the process.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188431","188431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38920","2014-02-24","Cabinet Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what funding or support his Department has provided to the Year of Code.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188531","188531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38921","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much tax was paid on residential rental income in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013 in (i) the UK and (ii) Greater London.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188537","188537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38922","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much tax is levied on a (a) 330ml bottle of beer with an alcohol by volume of four per cent, (b) 750ml bottle of wine with an alcohol by volume of 11 per cent and (c) 700ml bottle of Scotch whisky with an alcohol by volume of 40 per cent.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188538","188538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38923","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of how much the average UK consumer pays each year in (a) fuel duty, (b) alcohol excise duties and (c) tobacco duties.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188539","188539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38924","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to support small and medium-sized enterprises in the hospitality sector.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188540","188540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38925","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of tax free childcare national insurance contributions' relief available for workplace nurseries.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188523","188523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38926","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of incorrect P800 notices likely to be sent in July 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188524","188524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38927","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the economy of (a) the UK and (b) the South West of the track disruption caused by flooding in 2014.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188547","188547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38928","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps HM Revenue and Customs has taken to tackle cases of employees being paid below the minimum wage in Bradford.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188577","188577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38929","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps have been taken to facilitate the undertaking given by the Chief Secretary to the hon. Member for Eddisbury on 4 December 2013, Official Report, column 928, to secure an answer to the question asking where among the published documents on HS2 a comparison of the economic benefits of using double-decker carriages to relieve the problem of capacity on the West Coast Main Line as against the economic benefits of relieving capacity through HS2 can be found.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188585","188585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38930","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many pensioners have been affected by the 2012 Budget announcement not to increase the age-related personal allowance of £10,660 from 2012-13; and what the average amount is of additional tax pensioners affected by that change paid from 2012-13.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188399","188399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38931","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will introduce a one-off levy on bonuses given to investment bankers in 2014 to help fund measures needed to assist flood victims.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188410","188410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38932","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of households in (a) the UK and (b) each region that are subject to the high income child benefit charge and failed to meet the self-assessment deadline of 31 January 2014.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188450","188450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38933","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the payment system for the collection of taxation through HM Revenue and Customs is able to process taxation in a currency other than sterling.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188490","188490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38934","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the Consumer Code for Homebuilders.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188481","188481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38935","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on the introduction of a statutory redress mechanism for new homebuyers.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188482","188482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38936","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on training by the Fire Service College in (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2013-14 to date; how much he expects to spend in (i) this financial year and (ii) the next two financial years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188488","188488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38937","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2014, Official Report, column 652W, on housing benefit, whether local authorities will continue to decide on applications for reimbursement of service charging on adaptation following the full introduction of Universal Credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188446","188446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38938","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer to the right hon. Member for Leeds Central of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 560W, on housing: floods, if he will bring forward measures to levy fines on developers who build on flood plains and other flood threatened areas against advice by the Environment Agency not to build on those sites; and if he will use the money raised to support recurrent flood victims.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188439","188439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38939","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the recommendations of the National Flood Forum as to the use of alternatives to sandbags to increase the efficiency of barriers and post-flood community restitution.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188411","188411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38940","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will oppose any application for a protective costs order from the Lymington River Association in respect of the latest application for an oral hearing from the Lymington River Association in respect of the operation of Wightlink Ferries in the Lymington River.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188401","188401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38941","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the effect on the economy of the Isle of Wight of the legal costs of dealing with previous and current applications from the Lymington River Association in relation to the operation of ferry services in the Lymington River.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188402","188402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38942","2014-02-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the BBC Trust and the Arts Council on encouraging the BBC and other broadcasters to use British Chinese actors and presenters in their broadcasts; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188405","188405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38943","2014-02-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether an impact assessment was carried out in respect of the decision by UK Sport to reduce funding for synchronised swimming and water polo.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188453","188453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38944","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will review the system of allocation of funding for flood defences and the current division of such funding between capital and revenue; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188461","188461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38945","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will ban payday lending advertisements on military bases; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188448","188448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38946","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will undertake a feasibility study on establishing a credit union open to British military personnel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188449","188449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38947","2014-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to Question 187339 of 11 February 2014, where each vacancy is located; and what the role of each position is.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188564","188564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38948","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answers of 10 February 2014, Official Report, columns 470-1W, on army: training, what assessment he has made of the effect on future capability of infantry and Parachute Regiment recruit training courses being run at less than full capacity.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188545","188545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38949","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answers of 10 February 2014, Official Report, columns 470-1W, on army: training, what steps are being taken to ensure that the position will improve in 2014-15.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188546","188546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38950","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Answer of 10 February 2014, Official Report, column 587, how many locally employed interpreters were employed by the government in Afghanistan in the last 10 years; how many such interpreters have come to the UK; how many such interpreters have been given (a) a financial and resettlement package and (b) an intimidation package, in Afghanistan; and how many (i) applications and (ii) refusals have been made in each such case.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188542","188542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38951","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many three and four year olds in each parliamentary constituency receive free early years education outside of reception classes.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188534","188534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38952","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding or support his Department has provided to the Year of Code.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188530","188530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38953","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the publication of 13 February 2014, on the Regulation of Childcare consultation report, what estimate he has made of the number of schools that will now start to offer out-of-hours 8 to 6 care as a result.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188528","188528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38954","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local authorities provided information to the Education Funding Agency regarding high needs funding for people aged between five and 25 years old by 23 December 2013; which local authorities failed to meet this deadline; and which local authorities had failed to provided the information by 31 January 2014.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188478","188478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38955","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the uptake of funding for free school lunches for reception, year 1 and year 2 pupils in state schools; and whether there will be clawback of this funding where uptake is less than 100 per cent.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188548","188548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38956","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Aldridge-Brownhills of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 534W, on pupils: disadvantaged, when data on the number of eligible pupils in each school which will be used to allocate the pupil premium for 2014-15 and beyond will be available.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188580","188580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38957","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether information about the statutory guidance on social care for deafblind children and adults guidance will be included in Special Educational Needs Code of Practice.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188573","188573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38958","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether sixth form colleges are able to access the funding announced on 5 February 2014 to encourage graduates to teach mathamatics.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188464","188464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38959","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many adoption breakdowns occurred in each of the years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188471","188471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38960","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, column 101W, on pupils: disadvantaged, what estimate his Department has made of the number of pupils who will benefit from the pupil premium in (a) the West Midlands, (b) Worcestershire and (c) Redditch.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188455","188455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38961","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, column 213W, on foster care, when his Department's human resources policy for staff who foster or are kinship carers will be available.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188444","188444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38962","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made towards the replacement of the Integrated Children's System, as recommended in the Munro Review.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188468","188468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38963","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of current legislative provisions to protect social workers from violence when carrying out their work.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188469","188469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38964","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2014, Official Report, column 549, when the consultation will be published; what criteria is outlined in the consultation; when it started; who is being consulted; and if he will look to address the problem of absenteeism amongst Traveller communities.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188503","188503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38965","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will carry out a review of the effectiveness of child guardians and the effect their involvement has on the length of care proceedings.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188470","188470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38966","2014-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2014, Official Report, column 284W, on energy: finance, how much private sector investment has been made to help provide long-term sustainable energy in (a) the West Midlands, (b) Worcestershire and (c) Redditch.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188456","188456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38967","2014-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make it his policy that any company involved in illegal blacklisting should not be awarded a Nuclear Decommissioning Authority contract.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188566","188566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38968","2014-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether he has undertaken any work to provide current Magnox employees opportunities to engage in nuclear new build.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188565","188565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38969","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of the Department for Transport of 11 February 2014, Official Report, columns 525-6W, on Government Departments: unmanned air vehicles, which remotely piloted aircraft systems his Department employs to collect data; which policies are supported by the collection of such data; and where those systems are operated. [R]","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188570","188570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38970","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the total expenditure was of each of his Department's expenditure agencies and executive non-departmental public bodies in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15, broken by capital and revenue.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188521","188521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38971","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) staff and (b) full-time equivalent staff were employed by each of his Department's executive agencies and executive non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188517","188517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38972","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the indicative budget is of each of his Department's executive agencies and executive non-departmental public bodies for 2015-16, broken down by (a) capital and (b) revenue.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188514","188514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38973","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government contribution to the budget of each of his Department's executive agencies and executive non-departmental public bodies was for (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15, broken down by capital and revenue.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188515","188515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38974","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government contribution to the indicative budget of each of his Department's executive agencies and executive non-departmental public bodies is expected to be for 2015-16, broken down by capital and revenue.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188516","188516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38975","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what income was received by each of his Department's expenditure agencies and executive non-departmental public bodies from non-government sources, broken down by source in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188519","188519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38976","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what changes to the total number of (a) staff and (b) full-time equivalent staff employed by each of his Department's executive agencies and executive non-departmental public bodies are expected in 2014-15.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188518","188518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38977","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what contibution each of his Department's expenditure agencies and executive non-departmental public bodies made to the budget of (a) his Department and (b) HM Treasury in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13, (iv) 2013-14 and (v) 2014-15.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188520","188520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38978","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the Environment Agency spent on flood defence measures in Shrewsbury in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188433","188433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38979","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2013, Official Report, column 786W, on veterinary medicine: antibiotics, when the detailed measures being developed for the Government Antimicrobial Resistance Strategy will be published.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188432","188432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38980","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many planning applications have been given (a) standing advice and (b) bespoke advice by the Environment Agency in each local authority area; and what his estimate is in each of the years after 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188489","188489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38981","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much is forecast to be spent on flood defence measures in Shrewsbury in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188434","188434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38982","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what schemes the Environment Agency West Midlands has planned for flood defences in Shrewsbury over the next five years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188435","188435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38983","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on the Government's Preventing Sexual Violence Initiative in Burma.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188398","188398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38984","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government supports the establishment of an international investigation into human rights abuses against the Rohingya in Burma.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188476","188476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38985","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to ascertain whether any Burmese Army soldiers who are currently receiving training from the British Army previously committed war crimes, or crimes against humanity.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188474","188474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38986","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking (a) to support the Middle East peace talks and (b) to encourage all concerned parties to engage constructively in the negotiations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188477","188477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38987","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support (a) civil society in Israel and Palestine and (b) groups which are campaigning for peace.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188479","188479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38988","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of Article 26 of Afghanistan's draft criminal procedure law, prohibition of questioning an individual as a witness, on domestic violence or forced marriage prosecutions in that country; and what representations he has made to the Afghan government since the draft code was approved by the Afghan Parliament.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188445","188445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38989","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what funding his Department provides to the British Embassy in Pyongyang; and for what purpose such funding is provided.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188454","188454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38990","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent reports of rocket fire from Gaza into Israel.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188541","188541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38991","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2013, Official Report, column 151W, on Burma, whether he has raised the case of Naw Ohn Hla with his Burmese counterpart following her re-arrest in December 2013.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188581","188581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38992","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2013, Official Report, column 352W, on Burma, whether he has raised the case of Daw Bawk Ja with his Burmese counterpart; and what reports he has received on whether she has been released.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188582","188582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38993","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people with mental health conditions being moved from local authority care to hospital care in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188544","188544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38994","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, columns 624-5W, on obesity: sugar, when he expects the Scientific Advisory Committee's review of Carbohydrates and Health to conclude.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188543","188543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38995","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will hold discussions with the Nursing and Midwifery Council on that body reversing the increase in its compulsory annual fee.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188536","188536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38996","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the minutes all advice given to NHS England by the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group on (a) individual funding requests for the treatment of patients with stereotactic ablative radiotherapy and (b) funding requests for the prescription of cancer drugs not approved by the National Institute for Care Excellence.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188511","188511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38997","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the advice given to the Clinical Director for Specialised Services of NHS England by the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group and the Direct Commissioned Service Committee on the cancellation of the NHS Innovations budget.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188513","188513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38998","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the minutes of all meetings of NHS England's Patient and Public Engagement Steering Group to date.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188510","188510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38999","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the recommendations made by the 2011 National Radiotherapy Implementation Group report into stereotactic radiotherapy remain the standard by which progress in the treatment of stereotactic radiotherapy is measured.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188509","188509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39000","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on which NHS England committees or advisory groups the Specialised Healthcare Alliance (SHCA) sits; and who represents the SHCA on such committees or groups.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188512","188512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39001","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of patients with depression were given mindfulness-based therapies in each primary care trust area in England in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188568","188568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39002","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the names and professional qualifications of those who conducted NHS England's stereotactic radiosurgery and stereotactic radiotherapy intercranial needs assessment and service review of January 2014.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188465","188465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39003","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ground E abortions were diagnosed by (a) amniocentesis, (b) ultrasound, (c) chronic villus sampling and (d) other diagnostic tests in each of the last 10 years; what other methods of diagnosis were listed under other; and how many such diagnoses which did not result in abortion were recorded in the same period.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188483","188483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39004","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has for the future funding of the HIV/AIDS support funding line after March 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188462","188462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39005","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2014, Official Report, column 606, if he will assess the effects of e-cigarettes on passive smokers in cars; and what estimate he has made of the cost of prescribing e-cigarettes through the NHS.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188502","188502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39006","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people with (a) Type 1 and (b) Type 2 diabetes in Peterborough constituency in each year since 2001; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188499","188499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39007","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the (a) diagnosis and (b) treatment of brain tumours in children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188500","188500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39008","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what NHS England's budget for neonatal services will be in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188507","188507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39009","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to table 39 on page 36 of NHS England's stereotactic radiosurgery and stereotactic radiotherapy intercranial needs assessment and service review of January 2014, how many of the hospitals listed have devices dedicated solely to providing intercranial stereotactic radiotherapy.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188467","188467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39010","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made of potential savings from the implementation of the recommendation of NHS England's stereotactic radiosurgery and stereotactic radiotherapy intercranial needs assessment and service review, published in January 2014.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188475","188475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39011","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department takes to identify illegal abortion referrals; whether the competence for such scrutiny rests with the Chief Medical Officer alone; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188484","188484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39012","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the quality and availability of sexual health and HIV testing and prevention services in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188463","188463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39013","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to section 68, page 18 of NHS England's stereotactic radiosurgery and stereotactic radiotherapy intercranial needs assessment and service review of January 2014, how many intercranial patients Plymouth hospital has treated stereotactically in each of the last two years; whether Plymouth hospital has a device dedicated solely to providing intercranial stereotactic radiotherapy; and for what reason Plymouth hospital was chosen to make the assessment assumptions.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188466","188466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39014","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which local authorities have made dementia a public health priority.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188397","188397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39015","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what use his Department plans to make of information on female genital mutilation reported by acute hospitals after September 2014.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188442","188442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39016","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects that the second stage of the review of the suspension of services at the Leeds Children's Heart Surgery Unit will be published.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188420","188420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39017","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the reason is for the time taken to publish the second stage of the review of the suspension of services at Leeds Children's Heart Surgery Unit.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188421","188421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39018","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many congenital heart disease procedures have been carried out at each of the children's heart surgery units in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188403","188403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39019","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will update the House on the proposed timescale for the release of funding for the 3Ts redevelopment of the Royal Sussex County Hospital.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188416","188416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39020","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library a copy of the report entitled The medical implications of vehicle-mounted water cannon with special reference to the Ziegler Wasserwerfer 9000 (WaWe 9) system, published by the Defence Science and Technology Laboratory in 2013.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188418","188418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39021","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many deaths have been recorded from volatile substance abuse in (a) North Staffordshire and (b) the UK in each of the last five years; and what steps he is taking to prevent volatile substance abuse among children and young adults.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188480","188480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39022","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of the Department for Transport of 11 February 2014, Official Report, columns 525-6W, on Government Departments: unmanned air vehicles, which remotely piloted aircraft systems her Department employs to collect data; which policies are supported by the collection of such data; and where those systems are operated. [R]","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188569","188569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39023","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what aid her Department provided in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013 to support victims of rape and sexual violence by Burmese armed forces.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188522","188522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39024","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many abortions funded by her Department were procured in jurisdictions other than the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188501","188501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39025","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department is having with the government of Burma to reduce the risk of the census in March 2014 triggering communal violence and increasing ethnic tensions.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188473","188473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39026","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she has put in place to ensure value for money in the provision of overseas aid to abortion providers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188437","188437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39027","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much financial support the Government has provided in aid to procure abortion services overseas in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188436","188436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39028","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much financial support the Government provided to (a) Marie Stopes International, (b) the International Planned Parenthood Federation and (c) the United Nations Population Fund in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188438","188438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39029","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has asked the police formally to investigate allegations of mistreatment at the Medomsley Detention Centre.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188443","188443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39030","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the changes announced under the Rehabilitation of Offenders Act 1974 will also apply to CRB checks.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188558","188558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39031","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of custodial sentence handed down to people found guilty of (a) the offence of making or possessing an explosive under suspicious circumstances, (b) weapons training for terrorism and (c) training for terrorism was in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188576","188576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39032","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many instances of breaches by offenders released on licence there were in each year since 2002.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188583","188583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39033","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many instances of offenders remaining at large after (a) recall and (b) temporary release there were in each year since 2002.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188584","188584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39034","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made on the establishment of an independent investigation into war crimes and crimes against humanity in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188508","188508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39035","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to publish his Department's guidance on the economic impact of highways maintenance and disrepair.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188492","188492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39036","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2014, Official Report, column 12W, on road traffic control: schools, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential use of alternative methods of transport to reduce road congestion around primary schools.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188457","188457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39037","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2014, Official Report, column 555W, on High Speed 2: railway line, whether his Department has received further representations on this issue; and what his policy is on outside investment in High Speed 2 infrastructure.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188458","188458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39038","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take immediate steps to reverse the recently-announced decision by Dialogue by Design that it will only accept responses to the Environment Statement Consultation on High Speed 2 that are under 25MB.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188486","188486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39039","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average time for processing a driving licence application by the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency was in each of the years from 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188396","188396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39040","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average time was for issuing a registration certificate to vehicle keepers by the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188419","188419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39041","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for his Department's review of all rail infrastructure west of Exeter.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188409","188409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39042","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average time was for processing an application for confirmation of non-eligibility for a grounds of disability by the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188422","188422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39043","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the operations of Wightlink Ferries of the legal costs of dealing with previous and current applications from the Lymington River Association in relation to the operation of ferry services in the Lymington River.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188400","188400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39044","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average time was for issuing vehicle registration marks by the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188412","188412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39045","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average time was for registering and issuing tachograph cards by the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188413","188413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39046","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he take steps to facilitate direct flights from Heathrow to Ahmedabad in Gujarat, India; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188404","188404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39047","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will meet with representatives of the Motorcycle Action Group and the British Motorcyclists Federation to consider the potential benefits of re-evaluating vehicle excise duty in the context of the Government's environmental targets.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188406","188406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39048","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make if his policy not to increase the requirements of roadworthiness testing of powered two-wheelers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188407","188407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39049","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will reduce staff numbers in his Department commensurately with the delegation of decision-making to a local level; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188408","188408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39050","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Highways Agency takes to minimise litter on the highways.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188574","188574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39051","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date the £26 million for rail flood resilience work in the South West will be transferred from his Department to Network Rail.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188575","188575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39052","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase the take-up of electric vehicles.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188567","188567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39053","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department is conducting on the impact of enabling Part Six of the Traffic Management Act 2004 with regards to infringements made in mandatory cycle lanes.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188535","188535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39054","2014-02-24","Wales Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which Government Department has overall responsibility for ensuring that safe standards are achieved in protecting school children in Wales from the dangers of asbestos in (a) local authority schools and (b) schools outside local authority control.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188424","188424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39055","2014-02-24","Wales Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which Government Department is responsible for the (a) health and (b) safety in relation to asbestos of children attending schools in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188425","188425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39056","2014-02-24","Wales Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which Government Department has the overall responsibility for issuing guidance to schools in Wales on (a) the risks to children from asbestos and (b) the management of asbestos in schools.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188427","188427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39057","2014-02-24","Wales Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which Government Department has the overall responsibility for issuing guidance to the general public on (a) the risks to children from asbestos and (b) the management of asbestos in homes in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188428","188428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39058","2014-02-24","Wales Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which Government Department has the overall responsibility for advising the Welsh Government on (a) the risks to children from asbestos in schools and (b) the measures that should be taken to control those risks in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188429","188429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39059","2014-02-24","Wales Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which Government Department is responsible for the (a) health and (b) safety in relation to asbestos of children in Wales when they are not at school.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188426","188426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39060","2014-02-24","Wales Office","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which Government Department has the overall responsibility for ensuring that safe standards are achieved in protecting children in Wales at home from the dangers of asbestos.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188430","188430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39061","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2013, Official Report, column 489W, on industrial health and safety: temperature, what steps he has taken to clarify with the Health and Safety Executive what level of temperature in the workplace would exceed that considered reasonable.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188440","188440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39062","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on small and medium-sized businesses of the changes announced in October 2013 by the Health and Safety Executive to health and safety regulations.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188447","188447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39063","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the press release by the Health and Safety Executive entitled HSE announces important legislation changes, what plans he has to review the changes made in October 2013 to health and safety regulations; and what consideration he has given to recommendations put forward by small and medium-sized businesses.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188441","188441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39064","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of disability living allowance in the postcodes (a) G76, (b) G46 and (c) G78 have been sanctioned by his Department in the last five years; and what the reasons were for those sanctions.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188459","188459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39065","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of jobseeker's allowance in the postcodes (a) G76, (b) G46 and (c) G78 have been sanctioned by his Department; and what the reasons were for those sanctions.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188460","188460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39066","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of housing benefit resident in postcodes (a) G76, (b) G46 and (c) G78 have been sanctioned; and for what reasons in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188487","188487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39067","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many face to face work capability assessments on the Isle of Wight have been outstanding for longer than (a) one month, (b) two months, (c) three months and (d) four months.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188493","188493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39068","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the payment systems for delivery of benefits through the Department is able to process payments in a currency other than sterling.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188491","188491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39069","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the efficiency of Atos in undertaking face-to-face assessments on the Isle of Wight.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188485","188485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39070","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support is available for those on zero hours contracts whose income falls below jobseeker's allowance minimum for short periods of time.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188532","188532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39071","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many successful enforcements actions by the Pensions Regulator against foreign-owned companies in connection with allegations of pension abandonment have taken place since the formation of that body.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188506","188506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39072","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of employment and support allowance in postcode (a) G76, (b) G46 and (c) G78 have been sanctioned and for what reasons in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188495","188495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39073","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of child benefit resident in postcodes (a) G76, (b) G46 and (c) G78 have been sanctioned; and for what reasons in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188496","188496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39074","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the face-to-face personal independence payment assessment to be conducted by Atos as referred to in his letter to the hon. Member for the Isle of Wight of 15 January 2014 under reference FBH 44237 will take place.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188494","188494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39075","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the amount saved on benefits payments by those on zero-hours contracts whose income falls below the minimum jobseeker's allowance qualification for short periods of time but who do not sign on.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188529","188529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39076","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much of the spending on Work Choice in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13 is accounted for by (i) DEL costs of the programme, (ii) service fees, (iii) placement fees and (iv) 26 week sustainment fees.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188525","188525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39077","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much of the spending on the Work Choice programme in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13 is grant-in-aid funding for Remploy.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188526","188526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39078","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the projected expenditure for the Work Choice programme is for each year between 2010-11 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188527","188527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39079","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken by Atos Healthcare was to undertake face-to-face assessments for benefit claimants on (a) the Isle of Wight and (b) nationally since it began to deliver that service.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188579","188579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39080","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants have (a) entered into and (b) completed mandatory reconsideration periods; and what financial support aside from jobseeker's allowance is available to support such claimants during that period.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188578","188578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39325","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to help older people claim the benefits to which they are entitled.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902618","902618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39724","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on introducing a cap on care costs.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902628","902628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38540","2014-02-24","Attorney General","2014-02-12","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of staff recruited to the Law Officers' Departments since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188066","188066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38541","2014-02-24","Attorney General","2014-02-12","To ask the Attorney General, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of the Law Officers' Departments' Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of the Law Officers' Departments' Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188308","188308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38542","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with (a) other departments and (b) external stakeholders on whether small businesses should be included in the Flood Re scheme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188298","188298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38543","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, why small businesses are not included in the Flood Re scheme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188296","188296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38544","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the financial effect of the exclusion of small businesses from the Flood Re scheme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188297","188297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38545","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his most recent estimate is of the number of businesses affected by recent flooding.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188299","188299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38546","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received on the Flood Re scheme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188300","188300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38547","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will provide funding for young adults on EHCPs between the ages of 19 to 25 who are able and wish to go on to higher education.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188364","188364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38548","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what guidance his Department issues on whether apprenticeships are included in higher education for the purposes of education, health and care plans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188367","188367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38549","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of staff recruited to his Department since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188065","188065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38550","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will commission research on the potential effects of adoption of a living wage on economic growth; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188243","188243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38551","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what amount in (a) grants, (b) loan guarantees and (c) other financial assistance the Government has given to small and medium-sized enterprises in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188244","188244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38552","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of his Department's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of his Department's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188307","188307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38553","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the operation of the Start-Up Loans Scheme in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188257","188257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38554","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of successful applicants to the Start-Up Loans Scheme in Northern Ireland are based in North Down constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188258","188258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38555","2014-02-24","Cabinet Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance is issued to Government departments on using funds from the public purse for the provision of unhealthy foods for visitors and at meetings.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188220","188220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38556","2014-02-24","Cabinet Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of staff recruited to his Department since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188067","188067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38557","2014-02-24","Cabinet Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps to ensure that future censuses allow people to identify their ethnicity as British Kashmiri.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188193","188193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38558","2014-02-24","Cabinet Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when his Department's guidance on the appropriate use of compromise agreements and confidentiality clauses will be circulated to all Government departments.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188368","188368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38559","2014-02-24","Cabinet Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of his Department's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of his Department's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188309","188309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38560","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will increase the threshold of pension pots before the recipients can receive a lump sum.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188294","188294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38561","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the report produced for the Wine and Spirit Trade Association entitled Economic Impact Assessment into the Wine and Spirit Industry in the UK and its conclusion on the effect of the alcohol duty escalator on the wider economy.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188295","188295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38562","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employers made use of the provisions of Regulation 5 of the Income Tax (Exemption of Minor Benefits) Regulations 2002 in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188330","188330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38563","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, by how much and what proportion of the cost of an average bottle alcohol excise duty has increased between (a) 1997 and 2010 and (b) 2010 and the present day; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188290","188290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38564","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of his Department's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of his Department's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188327","188327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38565","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish the Government's response to his Department's consultation on tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188351","188351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38566","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish an impact assessment for tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188352","188352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38567","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people employed by large accountancy firms were (a) involved in and (b) consulted on the draft General Anti-Abuse Rule Regulations and whether the draft proposals were circulated to the Big Four accountancy firms before publication.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188393","188393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38568","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the total investment of British banks in the national debt for (a) Greece, (b) Spain, (c) Italy and (d) Ireland.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188394","188394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38569","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of additional revenue accruing to the Exchequer of (a) changes in place since 2010 and (b) planned changes to come into force by 2015 to the lifetime allowance for tax relief on pension contributions.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188192","188192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38570","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made by his Department in implementing the commitment contained in the Government's action plan for transgender equality to improve guidance for employers and customers for the implications of gender reassignment for tax purposes.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188099","188099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38571","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will issue guidance for employers and customers for people who do not wish to be identified for tax purposes as a particular gender.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188100","188100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38572","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of staff recruited to his Department since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188083","188083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38573","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effects of a cap on lifetime allowance for tax relief on pension contributions.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188191","188191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38574","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of current levels of business rates on small firms; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188217","188217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38575","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his Answers of 6 September 2013, Official Report, column 579W and 16 December 2013, Official Report, column 429W, on excise duties: tobacco, what his policy is on imposing restrictions on the personal imports of cigarettes by travellers from certain EU member states, as provided for by Article 4 of Council Decision 2010/12/EU.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188199","188199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38576","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward proposals to (a) enable peer-to-peer lending platforms to be included in individual savings accounts (ISAs) and (b) introduce more flexibility in the rules governing ISAs.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188271","188271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38577","2014-02-24","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of mortgage regulations to protect homeowners who took out mortgages before October 2008 from changes to the terms of tracker mortgages; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188245","188245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38578","2014-02-26","HM Treasury","2014-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what capacity his Department has to monitor the transfer of funds from individuals in the UK to recipients in other countries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188249","188249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38579","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on what date he plans to make a decision on the planning application relating to Rushden Lakes and Skew Bridge, deferred by him on 11 February 2014.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188242","188242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38580","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will extend the deadline for local authorities to finalise and submit their local neighbourhood plans including provision for a five-year supply of sites for housing under the National Planning Policy Framework.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188251","188251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38581","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will implement a moratorium on approving planning applications for greenfield sites in Addisbury constituency before local neighbourhood plans are finalised; and if he will make it his policy that a draft local plan should be taken into account when considering such planning applications.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188252","188252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38582","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the success of business improvement districts.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188272","188272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38583","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his statement of 10 February 2014, Official Report, column 574, on flooding, what definition of areas at high risk of flooding is used to record building in such areas; what the nature is of the objections to developments included in the figure of 99.3 per cent; and what locations of the developments objected to was.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188276","188276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38584","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to speed up the business rates appeals process.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188215","188215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38585","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to announce the decision on the Rushden Lakes planning application.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188188","188188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38586","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of staff recruited to his Department since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188068","188068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38587","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress has been made by his Department in implementing the commitments contained in the Government's action plan for transgender equality; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188095","188095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38588","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to answer Question 184489, tabled on 22 January 2014 for written Answer 27 January 2014.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188384","188384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38589","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will provide funding to compensate the Grand Theatre, Morecambe for increases in the rent of their car park.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188366","188366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38590","2014-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of his Department's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of his Department's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188310","188310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38591","2014-02-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of her Department's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of her Department's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188311","188311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38592","2014-02-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much Sport England has given to local authorities for the provision of public swimming facilities in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188197","188197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38593","2014-02-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of staff recruited to her Department since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188069","188069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38594","2014-02-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much arts funding (a) in total and (b) per head of population was allocated in (i) the North-West and (ii) Warrington in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188178","188178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38595","2014-02-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she will publish her consultation on statutory restrictions on community radio.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188124","188124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38596","2014-02-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will take steps to ensure that the proposed new statutory code of press regulation prohibits the media harassment of witnesses granted anonymity in court proceedings; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188135","188135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38597","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to protect children from online paedophiles.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188230","188230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38598","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) rape, (b) sexual assault and (c) sexual harassment referrals there were from the armed forces in (i) 2012 and (ii) 2013; how many such cases were directed for trial; how many trials were held; how many guilty verdicts were recorded; what the gender was of each person so referred to in the cases; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188152","188152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38599","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2014, Official Report, column 351W, on Defence Advisory Notices, whether he intends to make the Defence Advisory Notice System compulsory.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188213","188213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38600","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the causes of the four per cent rise in complaints of discrimination, harassment or bullying in the service environment by army other ranks in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188148","188148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38601","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what changes have been made in the (a) Army, (b) RAF and (c) Royal Navy in response to a number of cases of harassment reported to the Service Complaints Commissioner by 2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188149","188149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38602","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps have been taken by the RAF in response to the Service Complaints Commissioner's report 2012 of the trebling of cases of bullying; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188150","188150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38603","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps have been taken by the Army in response to the Service Complaints Commissioner's report 2012 on cases of bullying; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188151","188151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38604","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of staff recruited to his Department since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188070","188070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38605","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of his Department's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of his Department's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188312","188312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38606","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on the development of the Automated Logistic Information System (ALIS); and if he will make a statement on what part ALIS plays in his Department's IT rationalisation programme.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188301","188301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38607","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 552, on redundancy, what the job title and salary is of each post filled by individuals re-hired by his Department.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188332","188332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38608","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the in-service date for the first tranche of F35 Joint Combat Aircraft will be.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188303","188303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38609","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information he has received from Lockheed Martin on the readiness statistics for the F35B; and whether he is confident that this aircraft will reach levels of readiness comparable to the F-22.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188304","188304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38610","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2014, Official Report, column 549W, on armed forces: housing, how many service personnel were placed temporarily in hotels in (a) Plymouth and (b) nationally in each of the last 12 months; and what the cost to the public purse was of use of hotels for this purpose.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188345","188345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38611","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to further improve the Royal Navy's anti-smuggling operations in the Caribbean.","Biography information for Mr Lee Scott","Mr Lee Scott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188343","188343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38612","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many ports in the UK the Queen Elizabeth Class aircraft carrier simulator successfully navigated and docked at.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188386","188386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38613","2014-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many nuclear-qualified Suitably Qualified and Experienced Personnel have been required by his Department in each of the last three years; and how many such posts were vacant in each such year in each location.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188387","188387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38614","2014-02-24","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to his Office's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of his Office's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188313","188313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38615","2014-02-24","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, whether he raised the case of Mr Huber Ballesteros with President Santos during his recent visit to Colombia; and what the outcome was of any such discussions.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188196","188196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38616","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that children with autism are not excluded from the classroom.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188182","188182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38617","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made by his Department in implementing the commitments contained in the Government's action plan for transgender equality; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188088","188088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38618","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of staff recruited to his Department since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188071","188071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38619","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which Government department has responsibility for asbestos policy for schools in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188046","188046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38620","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with Ofsted about altering the evaluation schedule to better incentivise healthy outcomes for pupils.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188238","188238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38621","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, columns 105-6W, on special educational need, what guidance his Department gives schools on whether to enter special educational need pupils in the English Baccalaureate instead of GCSEs.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188219","188219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38622","2014-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Health and Safety Executive has specialist expertise on the risks of asbestos to children.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188132","188132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38623","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which Government department is responsible for the management of asbestos in schools in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188123","188123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38624","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will enter into talks with the National Union of Teachers and NAWUWT to resolve their trade disputes.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188212","188212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38625","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, column 76W, on integrated chronology tool, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that children's social care departments comply with the requirements of statutory safeguarding guidance, Working Together to Safeguard Children 2013.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188240","188240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38626","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, columns 217-8W, on special educational needs (SEN), what guidance his Department plans to issue to local authorities on building on existing parent partnership services in order to provide information, advice and support to parents and young people up to 25 years old with SEN, about education, health and social care.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188241","188241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38627","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he expects the next round of priority school building funds to be available.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188277","188277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38628","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of his Department's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of his Department's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188314","188314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38629","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants employed by academies and free schools which converted from the maintained sector were subject to changes in the terms and conditions of their employment contracts (a) when that conversion took place and (b) subsequently.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188350","188350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38630","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether local authorities will be expected to include (a) habilitation services and (b) other specialist services in their local offer for children and young people with special educational needs.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188341","188341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38631","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) whole families, (b) mothers and (c) fathers have used CANParent vouchers for each provider in each year since the introduction of the scheme.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188354","188354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38632","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department spent on the CANParent voucher scheme in each year since that scheme's introduction; and what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the scheme in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188353","188353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38633","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how (a) habilitation and (b) other specialist services will be commissioned after implementation of the provisions of the Children and Families Bill.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188338","188338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38634","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the role of the local offer will be in the commissioning of habilitation and other specialist services.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188337","188337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38635","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to update the publication Quality Standards: Delivery of Habilitation Training (Mobility and Independent Living Skills) for Children and Young People with a Visual Impairment, published in January 2011; and whether that guidance will be put on a statutory footing.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188336","188336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38636","2014-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, for what reasons his Department has not made a full assessment of how many individuals have been removed from fuel poverty as a result of the Energy Companies Obligation.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188305","188305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38637","2014-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how his Department will measure the effectiveness of the Energy Companies Obligation alleviations fuel poverty.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188306","188306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38638","2014-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of his Department's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of his Department's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188315","188315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38639","2014-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he plans to take to ensure that unsuitable cavity wall insulation is no longer used in homes that are prone to flooding or at risk of flooding.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188278","188278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38640","2014-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what financial assistance is available for homeowners whose homes have been affected by flooding to replace current insulation with material suitable for homes in flood risk areas.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188281","188281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38641","2014-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many solid wall properties remain to be insulated in the UK.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188282","188282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38642","2014-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many applications for each renewable technology have been made for 33kW connections under section 37 of the Electricity Act 1989 over the last 12 months.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188209","188209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38643","2014-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what criteria his Department used to establish which technologies should be considered an established technology for the purposes of contracts for difference competitive auctioning from 2014.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188164","188164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38644","2014-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the total value of payments made by domestic customers to British Gas for the installation of energy efficiency measures in their homes under the Energy Company Obligation as at 31 December 2013.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188057","188057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38645","2014-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of staff recruited to his Department since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188072","188072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38646","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of staff recruited to his Department since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188073","188073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38647","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether farmers still require his Department's permission before moving closed herds during the recent flooding period; and how many such applications his Department has (a) received and (b) granted.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188174","188174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38648","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of properties that have been flooded in 2014.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188176","188176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38649","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the total cost of including properties built in accordance with National Planning Policy guidelines since 2009 in the Flood Re scheme.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188177","188177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38650","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to help angling clubs in (a) West Lancashire and (b) England tackle the decline in fish stocks.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188118","188118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38652","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement on 24 May 2012, Official Report, column 83WS, on Gangmasters Licensing Authority (GLA), what steps have been taken to introduce repayment orders to the operations of the GLA; and if he make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188125","188125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38653","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to enforce the Balai Directive among the greyhound industry when importing greyhounds from the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188166","188166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38654","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the total value of the damage to flood and coastal defences in each local authority area in Cumbria caused by recent floods and storms is; and how much funding his Department is making available for repairs to those defences.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188216","188216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38655","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) cattle and (b) other livestock which have been moved as a result of recent floods; and what assessment he has made of the effect of such movement on the spread of bovine TB.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188228","188228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38656","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 560W, on floods: insurance, what assessment he has made of the number of properties built in accordance with National Planning Policy frameworks but which are deemed as high flood-risk by the insurance industry; and what his policy is on including such policies in the Flood Re scheme.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188239","188239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38657","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that animal welfare legislation is enforced in the transportation of equine species from the UK to other countries.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188250","188250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38658","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of his Department's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of his Department's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188316","188316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38659","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the current timescale for extending the River Thames Scheme to Teddington; and if he will make it his policy to fast-track such an extension.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188291","188291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38660","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations he has received from the Environment Agency on the proposed extension of the River Thames Scheme to Teddington.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188292","188292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38661","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Environment Agency will take to investigate the extent to which the management of the Jubilee River contributed to recent water levels in the lower Thames region.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188293","188293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38662","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the UK's position was on permitting EU nations to purchase fishing rights from other EU nations; and which UK fishing rights have been sold under such provision to other countries.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188395","188395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38663","2014-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Statement of 6 January 2014, Official Report, column 24, on flooding, what participation (a) he, (b) Ministers and (c) officials of his Department have had.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188383","188383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38664","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations his Department has made to the food and drink industry on reducing the levels of (a) sugar and (b) salt in processed foods.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188362","188362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38665","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the development by Iran of a new and more powerful generation of uranium enrichment centrifuges.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188381","188381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38666","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent reports that Iran has test fired an advanced long-range ballistic missile with radar-evading capabilities.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188380","188380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38667","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 534W, what response his Department received from the Egyptian government on restoring democratic elections in Egypt; and what further reports he has received on when democratic elections in Egypt will be restored.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188385","188385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38668","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on how many occasions the advice of the Acension Island Council was not followed by the (a) Administrator and (b) Governor of Ascension Island in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188268","188268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38669","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of his Department's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of his Department's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188317","188317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38670","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to encourage other nations in the region to support the UK's anti-drug smuggling operations in the Caribbean.","Biography information for Mr Lee Scott","Mr Lee Scott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188342","188342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38671","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with President Yoweri Museveni about Uganda's proposed anti-homosexuality legislation.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188226","188226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38672","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reason the Government did not send a delegation to the conference on the humanitarian impact of nuclear weapons that began in Mexico on 13 February 2014; for what reasons this decision was not announced until the day before the conference began; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188254","188254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38673","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what day his Department will fly the flag of Ascension Island in 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188270","188270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38674","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will grant (a) permanent habitation rights and (b) full local democratic rights to those people living on Ascension Island.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188267","188267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38675","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the Report by ACF International entitled, The Truth about the Assassination of 17 aid workers in Sri Lanka, published on 13 December 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188198","188198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38676","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for New Forest East, on 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 191W, on Afghanistan, how much has been reported as misused in reports he has received in his Department from the United Nations and from advisers within line Ministries in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188203","188203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38677","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the number of people killed in the Du Chee Yar Tan massacre in Burma.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188195","188195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38678","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of staff recruited to his Department since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188074","188074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38679","2014-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether grassroots women's rights organisations from conflict-affected countries have been invited to the Preventing Sexual Violence summit in June 2014.","Biography information for Sandra Osborne","Sandra Osborne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188056","188056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38680","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Office for National Statistics about providing data on breast cancer incidence and survival by clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188055","188055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38681","2014-02-24","Cabinet Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many breast cancer patients in each Clinical Commissioning Group footprint have survived breast cancer for (a) one year and (b) five years, in each year from 1996 to 2012.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188054","188054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38682","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of staff recruited to his Department since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188076","188076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38683","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training and support his Department provides to military doctors who subsequently enter civilian service; and whether his Department monitors the performance of such doctors relative to the performance of other doctors.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188194","188194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38684","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether there is a specified timeframe in which NHS hospital trusts are required to issue a patient's discharge information to their GP.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188183","188183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38685","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued to NHS hospital trusts on the issuing of discharge notes to a patient's GP.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188184","188184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38686","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that NHS hospital trusts improve the time taken to issue a patient's discharge information to their GP.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188119","188119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38687","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made by his Department in implementing the commitments contained in the Government's action plan for transgender equality; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188089","188089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38688","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of women who had an abortion in each of the last five years but were using some form of artificial contraceptive when they became pregnant; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188051","188051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38689","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what requirements there are on local authorities and commissioned care agencies to ensure the health and wellbeing of a client on the occasions a carer is unable to attend an appointment.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188111","188111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38690","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been allocated by Health and Wellbeing Boards towards (a) primary and secondary care for type-2 diabetes and (b) prevention of type-2 diabetes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188200","188200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38691","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 14 February 2014, Official Report, column 712, with reference to the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation's Code of Practice published in June 2013, under what circumstances he would not fulfil his duty to ensure the Joint Committee's recommendations are practicable.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188214","188214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38692","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been allocated by Health and Wellbeing Boards towards lifestyle weight management programmes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188201","188201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38693","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent meetings his Department has had with Tier 2 providers on lifestyle weight managment programmes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188202","188202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38694","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what evidence has been submitted to the Chantler Review of standardised packaging of tobacco which is considered to be outside the remit of that Review; why each such submission is so considered; and whether he plans to publish such evidence.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188153","188153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38695","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what systems his Department has to monitor how many care appointment visits are cancelled by care organisations paid by local authorities.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188115","188115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38696","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of positive cases of (a) HIV and (b) hepatitis C reported in 2013 among (i) people who had migrated to the UK within the last two years and (ii) people residing in the UK on visa.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188156","188156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38697","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) budget and (b) number of staff is assigned to work in the Obesity Project Team at Public Health England.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188207","188207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38698","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring oversight of pregnancy and abortion counselling services within the responsibilities of the Care Quality Commission.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188205","188205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38699","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the (a) costs for and (b) other effects on GP practices of delays in NHS hospital trusts issuing a patient's discharge information promptly.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188117","188117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38700","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the quality and impartiality of advice provided by pregnancy and abortion counselling services.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188206","188206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38701","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many referrals (a) the Minister of State for Public Health and (b) his predecessor made to the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence to develop guidance on public health.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188221","188221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38702","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons stakeholder submissions to NHS England's stakeholder engagement programme for specialised services were not collected directly by NHS England but sent to the Specialised Healthcare Alliance.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188127","188127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38703","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his future plans are for introducing Enriched Culture Medium testing for Group B Strep.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188108","188108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38704","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what fees (a) NHS England and (b) the NHS and NHS London paid to (i) the Specialised Healthcare Alliance and (ii) JMC Partners in the last three years; and for what work such fees were paid.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188131","188131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38705","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking through NHS policy frameworks to ensure that clinical commissioning groups reliably and consistently commission secondary fracture prevention services.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188126","188126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38706","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the cost to local authorities of cancelled or unattended carer visits in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188112","188112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38707","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether local authorities are required to pay care agencies for appointments where the carer fails to attend the appointment or the provider cancels the appointment.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188113","188113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38708","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has specialist expertise on the asbestos risks to children.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188133","188133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38709","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what requirements his Department places on local authorities to record or declare the number of visits cancelled or unattended by carers to clients under the care of a local authority.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188110","188110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38710","2014-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what criteria are employed in the decision on which method of stem cell research to fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188147","188147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38711","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings Ministers in his Department have had with the Specialised Healthcare Alliance in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188128","188128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38712","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the (a) names of all members of NHS England's Clinical Priorities Advisory Group and Direct Commissioned Service Committee and (b) declaration of interests of all members of NHS England's Clinical Priorities Advisory Group and Direct Commissioned Service Committee.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188129","188129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38713","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he will take to ensure that no people receiving fees from pharmaceutical companies are directly involved in NHS England's specialised commissioning services or sit on any NHS England committees.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188130","188130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38714","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will investigate the advice given by private abortion providers to pregnant women on the illegality of gender selective abortion.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188106","188106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38715","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of cases in which GP practices are not notified of a patient's discharge timeframe have not been discharged by the NHS hospital trust within the stated timeframe at (a) Southport and Ormskirk NHS Hospital Trusts (b) all NHS hospital trusts in the North West of England and (c) England.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188120","188120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38716","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons he decided not to publish the findings of the review carried out by the Health and Social Care Information Centre at the request of NHS England on the possibility of pseudonymising data extracted under the care.data scheme at source.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188256","188256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38717","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that psychiatric inpatients who are not living at home are aware of the effects of the care.data scheme on their medical data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188255","188255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38718","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of levels of access to mindfulness-based therapy.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188266","188266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38719","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to promote research into a cure for lung diseases.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188232","188232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38720","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Copeland, of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 616W, on medical records: database, whether the full findings of the survey evaluating the Better information means better care leaflet will be made public; what the sample size and sampling methodology is of this survey; and who will carry out the survey on behalf of NHS England.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188235","188235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38721","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospitals he plans to build by 2015.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188233","188233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38722","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) cardiac surgeons and (b) nurses have been appointed in the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188234","188234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38723","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 616W, on medical records: databases, Question 186539, when he expects NHS England to complete the survey; and if he will publish the detailed results of the survey.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188246","188246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38724","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that people with a visual impairment or a learning disability are aware of and understand the care.data scheme.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188253","188253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38725","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 616W, on medical records: databases, Question 186539, what plans he has for remedial action to ensure that those who have not received a leaflet are informed fully of the scheme to which the leaflet, Better information means better care, relates.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188247","188247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38726","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the National Institute for Clinical Excellence will publish its updated guidance on obesity.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188208","188208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38727","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 608W, on accident and emergency departments: departmental services, how many patients have presented at accident and emergency departments where the patient's first treatment was dental treatment in each region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188248","188248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38728","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the amount spent on research to develop drugs to treat cancer in children in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188348","188348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38729","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what amount his Department spent on habilitation services for children and young people under the age of 25 in the last (a) 12 and (b) 24 months.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188340","188340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38730","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what amount his Department has allocated to provision of habilitation services for blind and partially-sighted children and young people under the age of 25 in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188339","188339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38731","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make representations to the European Commission on changing regulations that exempt pharmaceutical companies from testing cancer drugs on children on the grounds that the cancer the drug treats does not not occur in children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188346","188346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38732","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many pharmaceutical companies operating in the UK are engaged in developing drugs to treat cancer in children.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188347","188347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38733","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS England review of adult congenital heart disease services has spent on external communication consultants from each employed company to date.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188175","188175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38734","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to provide ambulance crews with additional specialised equipment to allow them to deal safely with moving larger patients.","Biography information for Mr Lee Scott","Mr Lee Scott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188335","188335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38735","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of his Department's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of his Department's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188318","188318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38736","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the proposals of the Better Care Together Review, what progress his Department has made in implementing proposals for a super hospital to serve the whole of Morecambe Bay.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188378","188378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38737","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the risk to human health from contaminated water and sewage entering people's homes as a result of flooding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188372","188372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38738","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment NHS England made of a potential conflict of interest prior to commissioning Specialised Healthcare Alliance to produce a report as part of its strategy for commissioning specialised services in the future.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188382","188382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38739","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of liver disease he estimates were cases of obesity induced liver disease in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188391","188391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38740","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the national GP training curriculum is dedicated to mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188389","188389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38741","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital admissions were due to medicine non-adherence in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188390","188390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38742","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of patients failing to turn up for NHS appointments.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188388","188388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38743","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations his Department has made to the food and drink industry on reducing the levels of (a) sugar and (b) salt in processed foods.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188363","188363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38744","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to safeguard the health of people whose homes have been flooded by contaminated water and sewage; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188373","188373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38745","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many named people without indefinite leave to remain are currently listed on the (a) National Operations Database, (b) Case Information Database, (c) National Allegations Database, (d) Migration Refusal Pool, (e) Warnings Index and (f) Watch Lists.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188359","188359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38746","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to publish revised guidance on procedures for dispersing and accommodating pregnant women who seek asylum in the UK.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188376","188376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38747","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of her Department's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of her Department's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188319","188319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38748","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to receive a reply to his letter to the interim director general, UK Visas and Immigration of 8 January 2014 on behalf of a constituent, CTS ref M294/14.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188224","188224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38749","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to receive a reply to his letter to the interim director general, UK Visas and Immigration of 15 January 2014 on behalf of a constituent, CTS ref M697/14.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188225","188225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38750","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress she has made on introducing a regulatory system for private investigators; and when she expects such a system to become operational.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188231","188231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38751","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the UK Border Force in safeguarding public health.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188158","188158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38752","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what analysis she has made of the factors accounting for the variation in performance between each police force dissemination rate and detection rate in fraud cases.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188121","188121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38753","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many positive cases of active pulmonary tuberculosis were prevented (a) indefinitely and (b) temporarily from entering the UK in 2013.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188159","188159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38754","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many hate crimes have been committed against transgender people in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188097","188097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38755","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that regular checks on online retailers' compliance with laws on the sale of alcohol are carried out.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188114","188114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38756","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to increase pre-entry medical screening for those wishing to reside in the UK for more than six months.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188157","188157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38757","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the statement of 12 February 2014, Official Report, column 713, on police integrity, what progress has been made towards ensuring that those officers under investigation for misconduct are not allowed to avoid sanctions or charges through leaving the force; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188204","188204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38758","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that supermarkets and other businesses have measures in place to ensure that young people cannot purchase alcohol online for delivery.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188116","188116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38759","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the income provided to the Educational Testing Service for English language tests by (a) individuals, (b) companies and (c) her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188048","188048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38760","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the proposed (a) terms of reference, (b) method and (c) timescale of her Department's investigation into language tests organised by the Educational Testing Service.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188047","188047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38761","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her Answer of 3 February 2014, Official Report, column 35W, on re-employment, how much was paid to the staff referred to as part of their retirement package.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188058","188058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38762","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of progress the Government has made on tackling hate crimes against transgender people.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188098","188098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38763","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made on implementing the commitments contained in the Government's action plan for transgender equality to review how gender identification is represented in passport application forms and passports; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188091","188091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38764","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for British citizenship have been made by foreign and Commonwealth personnel (a) currently or (b) recently serving in the armed forces who have been refused citizenship on the grounds that the good character request is not met; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188104","188104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38765","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department ceased to record on passports the holder's (a) profession, (b) place of birth, (c) date of birth, (d) country of residence, (e) height, (f) eye colour, (g) hair colour, (h) special peculiarities and (i) distinguishing features; for what reasons the Government decided to cease recording each of the characteristics on passports; what rules it currently applies to people of indeterminate sex and people who do not identify as either gender in relation to how they describe their gender on passports; what consideration she has given on the need to record a person's sex on passports; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188102","188102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38766","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase the resources allocated to fraud investigation.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188185","188185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38767","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she last met the Secretary of State for Education to discuss campaigns against female genital mutilation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188180","188180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38768","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria will be used to determine the allocation of funds from the Female Genital Mutilation Community Engagement Initiative.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188181","188181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38769","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what analysis she has made of the reasons for the disproportionately lower fraud case detection rate in metropolitan police forces compared to non-metropolitan forces.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188186","188186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38770","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of staff recruited to her Department since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188077","188077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38771","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what analysis she has made of the reasons for the disparity in fraud cases referred to individual police forces by the City of London Police and the number of such cases followed through to arrest.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188187","188187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38772","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of staff recruited to her Department since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188078","188078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38773","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what mechanism her Department has put in place to assess and demonstrate the effect of Making Financial Markets Work for the Poor Programme on people in poverty.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188172","188172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38774","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to monitor its expenditure on disaster risk reduction.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188173","188173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38775","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many abortions funded by her Department were (a) procured in jurisdictions other than the UK and (b) provided in cases of rape in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188049","188049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38776","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 304W, on re-employment, how much was paid to the staff referred to as part of their retirement package.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188061","188061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38777","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department ensures value for money in overseas aid to abortion providers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188050","188050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38778","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much financial support was provided as aid to procure abortion services overseas in each of the last 10 years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188052","188052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38779","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much financial support was provided to (a) Marie Stopes International, (b) the International Planned Parenthood Federation and (c) the United Nations Population Fund in each of the last 10 years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188053","188053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38780","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what mechanism her Department has put in place to assess and demonstrate the effect of Mozambique Regional Gateway Programme on people in poverty.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188170","188170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38781","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what mechanism her Department has put in place to assess and demonstrate the effect of the South Asia Regional Trade and Integration Programme on people in poverty.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188171","188171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38782","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to monitor commitments made by the Palestinian Authority on the educational goals set by the Palestinian National Plan.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188154","188154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38783","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the funding given to the Palestinian Authority aimed at improving educational progress.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188155","188155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38784","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the goal set by the Palestinian National Plan to modernise the Palestinian education system.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188146","188146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38785","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has for determining future funding to the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188163","188163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38786","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to develop her Department's strategic priority on violence against women and girls in Afghanistan; and whether those programmes will focus on preventing violence as well as responding to violence.","Biography information for Sandra Osborne","Sandra Osborne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188107","188107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38787","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department takes to ensure that UK aid funding does not help promote anti-Semitic or otherwise inappropriate material in schools in the Palestinian territories.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188160","188160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38788","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of her Department's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of her Department's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188320","188320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38789","2014-02-24","Department for International Development","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to implement its 2006 disaster risk reduction policy goals of allocating approximately 10 per cent of its funding in response to natural disasters to preparedness and mitigation measures; and what the target date for reaching that target is.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188377","188377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38790","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will expand the Samaritans and Listener Scheme within prisons in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188379","188379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38791","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will place in the Library staff codes of conduct currently in use at secure children homes.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188374","188374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38792","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the total cost to the public purse of constructing the new prison in Wrexham; and what estimate he has made of the amount that will come from (a) his Department's budgets and (b) other Government budgets.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188370","188370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38793","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many investigations into injuries of children resident in secure children homes have taken place since 2010; and how many such investigations have concluded that restraint of the child by a member or members of staff have been found to be the cause of the injury.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188375","188375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38794","2014-02-24","Department for Education","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the annual cost is of a place at a secure children's homes; and what estimate his Department has made of the likely annual cost of a place at secure college or secure training college.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188369","188369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38795","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of spending on construction of the new prison in Wrexham in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15, (c) 2015-16, (d) 2016-17  and (e) 2017-18.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188358","188358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38796","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of his Department's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of his Department's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188321","188321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38797","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the contract for construction of the new prison in Wrexham will be signed.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188334","188334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38798","2014-02-24","Department for Transport","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many new drivers accumulated six penalty points within the two year probationary period in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188333","188333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38799","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) name, (b) position and (c) date of appointment is of all current High Court and circuit judges who have identified as belonging to an ethnic monitory.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188356","188356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38800","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when construction will (a) begin and (b) be completed on the new prison in Wrexham.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188355","188355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38801","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent representations he has received on the potential merits of making squatting in commercial buildings a criminal offence.","Biography information for Mary Macleod","Mary Macleod","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188344","188344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38802","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department plans to make a decision on who will run the new prison in Wrexham.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188357","188357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38803","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will issue guidance on when a sentence issued at a summary hearing within the armed forces becomes spent under the National Police Records (Recordable Offences) Regulations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188105","188105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38804","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that implementation of new regulations by the Solicitors Regulation Authority will result in deaf and hard of hearing clients having access to interpreters when seeking legal counsel from solicitors' firms.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188109","188109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38805","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to provide courts with additional powers to prevent the media harassment of witnesses nominally granted anonymity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188134","188134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38806","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average payment was; and how many payments were made to legal aid providers for judicial review cases that were refused at permission stage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188237","188237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38807","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the reasons are for his proposal to increase the upper age limit of jurors to 75 while that of judges remains 70.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188229","188229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38808","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will provide a breakdown by ethnic background, age cohort and gender of lay magistrates in each panel for each year from 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188223","188223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38809","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints have been received by Serco in relation to the contract for Community Payback in London since taking over that contract.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188280","188280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38810","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new criminal offences have been created in each year since May 2010; and what the predicted effect was on the number of prisoners for each such offence.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188279","188279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38811","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 226W, on re-employment, how much was paid to the staff referred to as part of their retirement package.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188060","188060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38812","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of staff recruited to his Department since 5 May 2010 identified their ethnicity as (a) white British and (b) from a minority ethnic background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188079","188079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38813","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission research to develop treatment guidelines to be followed across the prison estate for males and females who self-harm; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188137","188137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38814","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of individuals who took their own lives within (a) one month and (b) two months at the end of a custodial sentence in each year between 2010 and 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188136","188136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38815","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy to introduce comprehensive psychological assessments for a prisoner who has carried out an episode of self-harm; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188139","188139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38816","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss with the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence developing self-harm guidelines within the prison estate.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188138","188138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38817","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many randomised trials of treatments for mental health issues and self-harm have been carried out by academic researchers within the prison estate since 2008; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188145","188145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38818","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what levels of regulatory approval are required before academic research can be undertaken within the prison estate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188144","188144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38819","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will assess the number of episodes of self-harm within the prison estate involving (a) prisoners and (b) custodial staff; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188141","188141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38820","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many training places are available each year for custodial staff in (a) suicide prevention and (b) self-harm prevention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188142","188142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38821","2014-02-24","Department of Health","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce a minimum threshold for moving an individual out of the prison estate and into a psychiatric setting; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188143","188143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38822","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy to introduce a system of case reviews of prisoners engaging in multiple acts of self-harm to determine likely contributory factors; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188140","188140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38823","2014-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the provisions in the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Rehabilitation of Offenders Act 2012 for sentences to be aggravated for any offence motivated by hostility towards the victim on the grounds of being transgender were commenced; and how many aggravated sentences of this kind have been imposed since commencement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188094","188094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38824","2014-02-24","Home Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many offences have been recorded in the UK as motivated by hostility towards the victim on the grounds of being transgender in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188093","188093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38825","2014-02-24","Leader of the House","2014-02-12","To ask the Leader of the House, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to his Office's Ministers is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of his Office's Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188322","188322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38826","2014-02-24","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the size, in square metres, of the offices assigned to each of her Department's Ministers and non-departmental public bodies is; and how many officials, at what grade, work in the private offices of each of her Department's Ministers and non-departmental public bodies is.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188323","188323"
