"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427785","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding the UK has allocated to the International Foundation for Electoral Systems over the last five years; and how much such funding was allocated to that body for the purpose of overseeing elections in Burma.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15746","15746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427786","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what effect the outcome of the elections in Burma in November 2015 will have on her Department's funding to projects in that country.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15730","15730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427787","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what projects her Department (a) has and (b) is planning to facilitate transition in Burma from dictatorship to democracy.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15744","15744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427788","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what additional support her Department plans to give to Ethiopia because of drought in that country in 2015-16.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15904","15904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427789","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16014","16014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427790","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will discuss with (a) EU partners and (b) the World Food Programme to ensure food supplies to people affected by the famine in Ethiopia.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15776","15776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427791","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make representations requesting reforms of the management and administration of the World Food Programme to improve its effectiveness and efficiency.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15777","15777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427792","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to support the eradication of malnutrition.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16005","16005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427793","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to implement the family test; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15846","15846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427794","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many of her Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps she has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16022","16022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427795","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) number of suicides took place and (b) what this number is as a proportion of the total by individuals who were not on the Assessment, Care in Custody and Teamwork programme in prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15827","15827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427796","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) average and (b) maximum time taken by his Department to process applications for a warrant to transfer inmates to a (i) mental health unit and (ii) to a different ward within a mental health unit was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15828","15828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427797","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) wildlife crime investigations and (b) wildlife crime prosecutions the National Wildlife Crime Unit has been directly involved with since it was formed.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16012","16012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427798","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of his Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps he has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16023","16023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427799","2015-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been (a) murdered, (b) assaulted and (c) subject to a  violent crime committed by people released from prison on licence in (i) England and (ii) Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15823","15823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427800","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16015","16015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427801","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Department of Health on proposed fixed cost regime change to the civil procedure rules; and what consequences the proposed changes will have on his Department's policies.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15948","15948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427802","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of space in prisons is used for educational purposes.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15749","15749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427803","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many different (a) GCSE, (b) A-level and (c) NVQ subjects are available for prisoners to study through the Prison Service.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15752","15752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427804","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent representations he has received on expansion and improvement of educational facilities in prisons; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15750","15750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427805","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to broaden the range of educational subjects taught in prisons.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15751","15751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427806","2015-11-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps her Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16016","16016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427807","2015-11-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many of her Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps she has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16024","16024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427808","2015-11-16","Prime Minister","2015-11-10","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he raised the issue of persecution and human rights abuse of Christians living in China during the recent state visit by President Xi Jinping.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16003","16003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427809","2015-11-16","Cabinet Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to end civil service performance quotas.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15951","15951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427810","2015-11-16","Prime Minister","2015-11-10","To ask the Prime Minister, what matters relating to (a) nuclear disarmament and (b) nuclear non-proliferation he discussed with the Prime Minister of India during his visit to London in November 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15834","15834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427811","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Prime Minister's letter of 10 November 2015 to the President of the European Council, whether the Government has conducted (a) an environmental impact assessment, (b) a sustainability assessment and (c) a carbon emissions assessment of his proposals for a new settlement for the UK in a reformed EU.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15835","15835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427812","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the evidential basis is for the Prime Minister's statement to the press of 21 October 2015 that Hinkley Point nuclear power station will produce reliable and affordable electricity.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15694","15694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427813","2015-11-16","Scotland Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps his Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16017","16017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427814","2015-11-16","Scotland Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with ministerial colleagues on City Deals for (a) Aberdeen, (b) Edinburgh and (c) Inverness.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15939","15939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427815","2015-11-16","Scotland Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many of his Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps he has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16025","16025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427816","2015-11-16","Scotland Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he had with women's organisations in Scotland prior to his proposal to devolve responsibility for abortion legislation to the Scottish Parliament.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16070","16070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427817","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2015 to Question 14459, whether the Civil Aviation Authority plans to make the conclusions of the review into the safety of operations at RAF Northolt publicly available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15829","15829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427818","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many of his Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps he has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16026","16026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427819","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much capital spending per head of population was spent on transport projects in (a) Warrington and (b) Cheshire in each of the past five years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15943","15943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427820","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Statement of 10 November 2015, HCWS301, (a) how many Volkswagon vehicles have been retested to date, (b) how many such vehicles he expects to be retested and (c) what the findings were of the retest in relation to discrepancies in (i) nitrogen oxide and (ii) carbon dioxide emission figures; what recent estimate he has made of the cost of the retest programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16052","16052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427821","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Statement of 10 November 2015 HCWS301, how many (a) types and (b) brands of vehicles he estimates (i) the UK, (ii) Germany and (iii) other countries will test as part of the broader testing programme for emissions deficiencies.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16004","16004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427822","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many delays on the Great Western mainline have qualified for schedule 4 compensation payments since work to electrify that line commenced.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16000","16000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427823","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much is paid in Schedule 4 compensation payment to train operations for delayed journey.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16057","16057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427824","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16018","16018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427825","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost of testing all vehicles for emissions for (a) each car and (b) in total; and whether the Government will finance the total programme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15973","15973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427826","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information he holds on whether Sir Peter Hendy's review of Network Rail's programme plans will consider extending electrification to Plymouth and the South West Peninsula.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15925","15925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427827","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of buses are low-floor buses; and what change in bus usage there has been as a result of introducing low-floor buses.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15917","15917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427828","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of households in rural areas meet the minimum criteria for the bus availability indicator.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15914","15914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427829","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of households are able to reach a (a) hospital, (b) GP, (c) jobcentre, (d) primary school, (e) secondary school and (f) place of employment in 20 minutes by public transport.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15916","15916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427830","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of how much UK households spent on taxi and private hire vehicle journeys in 2013-14.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15915","15915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427831","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many performance indicators the Office of Road and Rail uses to assess the performance of Network Rail.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15901","15901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427832","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the procurement contract for the new Hitachi Intercity Express Programme specifies the internal layout and specification of rolling stock.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15902","15902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427833","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to deal with overcrowding on Bolton's commuter trains.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15699","15699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427834","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he and Network Rail have to remove level crossings on the mainline between Plymouth and Reading.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15700","15700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427835","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effect on Eastbourne's local economy of potential reductions in connectivity of future rail projects along the South Coast; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15704","15704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427836","2015-11-16","Wales Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, on what grounds the decision was taken to refuse Crown consent for provisions within the Environment Bill currently passing through the Welsh Assembly.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15808","15808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427837","2015-11-16","Wales Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps his Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16019","16019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427838","2015-11-16","Wales Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the differences in provision of healthcare in areas adjoining the border between England and Wales.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15876","15876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427839","2015-11-16","Wales Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many of his Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps he has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16027","16027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427840","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of (a) the number of people in receipt of the Carer's Allowance and (b) the total cost of the Carer's Allowance scheme in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16066","16066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427841","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for material changes to safety cases covering oil and gas installations were submitted to the Health and Safety Executive in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15821","15821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427842","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many operators in the North Sea have yet to submit a safety case assessment to the Health and Safety Executive for the purposes of compliance with the provisions of the EU Directive on the safety of offshore oil and gas operations.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15822","15822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427843","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of his Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps he has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16028","16028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427844","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have flowed off employment and support allowance with a work capability assessment decision of fit for work since 2011; and how many such people's death was at the same time as defined in the document Mortality Statistics: Employment and support allowance, incapacity benefit or severe disability allowance, published in August 2015.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15942","15942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427845","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have (a) sight loss and (b) hearing loss in (i) Barnsley East, (ii) Barnsley, (iii) South Yorkshire and (iv) Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15844","15844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427846","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues on the implementation of the family test throughout the Government.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15994","15994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427847","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseekers have been sanctioned in East Kilbride, Strathaven and Lesmahagow constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16058","16058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427848","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether 18 to21 year olds in supported housing services will still be able to claim housing benefit after April 2017.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15853","15853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427849","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cumulative loss of pension income to women born in the 1950s following the increase in state pension age in the Pensions Act 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16036","16036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427850","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the document Fixing the Foundations: Creating a more prosperous nation, Cm 9098, if he will publish his Department's analysis that links reform of the welfare system to increasing the UK's productivity.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16037","16037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427851","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of women in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency who were born in the 1950s and will see an increase in their state pension age as a result of the Pensions Act 2011.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16035","16035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427852","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseekers who have registered disabilities in East Kilbride, Strathaven and Lesmahagow have been sanctioned in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15891","15891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427853","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial assistance is available for parents who have lost children to pay for funeral costs.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15871","15871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427854","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16020","16020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427855","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people flowed off IB/SDA with a work capability assessment decision of fit for work since December 2011; and how many such people's death was at the same time defined in Mortality Statistics: Employment and support allowance, incapacity benefit or severe disability allowance, published in August 2015.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16044","16044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427856","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to mitigate the effect of changes in employment and support allowance for those diagnosed with cancer who have been placed in the Work-Related Activity Group.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15969","15969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427857","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have not been able to request employment and support allowance paid at the assessment rate pending an appeal since March 2015.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15766","15766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427858","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions Health and Safety Executive inspectors from the Energy Division and predecessor divisions issued improvement notices to operators of offshore oil and gas installations in each year since 2005-06; and what proportion of those notices were served in relation to maintenance issues in each such year.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15801","15801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427859","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many safety case assessments the Health and Safety Executive has received from installation operators in the oil and gas sector in each of the last three years; and what the rate of compliance of that sector is with the provision of the EU Directive on the safety of offshore oil and gas operations.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15798","15798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427860","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many improvement notices have been issued by Health and Safety Executive inspectors to operators of offshore oil and gas installations in 2015-16; and what proportion of those notices were issued in response to maintenance matters.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15799","15799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427861","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will assess the costs and benefits of classifying parentally-agreed child support as income for means-tested benefits.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15896","15896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427862","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff in the Health and Safety Executive have worked on processing safety case assessments from installation operators in the oil and gas industry in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15820","15820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427863","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy that people who increase their earnings from work should always be financially better off as a result.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15813","15813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427864","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the regulatory requirements of the EU Directive on the safety of offshore oil and gas operations have been fully implemented; and which regulatory bodies are represented on the Offshore Safety Directive Regulator.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15819","15819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427865","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 7.4 of the Explanatory Memorandum for the Rent Officers (Housing Benefit and Universal Credit Functions) (Local Housing Allowance Amendments) Order 2015 (S.I., 2015, No. 1753), when he plans for the first instalments of additional funding under the Targeted Affordability Fund to be made available to local authorities.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15701","15701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427866","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been recipients of the new enterprise allowance in (a) St Helens North, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK since it began.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15718","15718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427867","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what programmes being taken forward by his Department are subject to Project Assessment Reviews instead of Gateway Reviews.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15727","15727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427868","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance has been issued to Jobcentre Plus staff on the application of benefit sanctions where a parent is unable to comply with the conditions for that benefit because of lack of suitable childcare.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15691","15691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427869","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many parents have received a sanction for failure to comply with conditions for receipt of benefits because suitable childcare was not available to enable them to comply.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15692","15692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428149","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on support for people with mental health conditions who claim jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902131","902131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428177","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of provision of pharmacy services in central London outside working hours.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902108","902108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428195","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that refugees can be settled in Europe without making dangerous journeys by boat.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902162","902162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428261","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in what circumstances a judge could refuse to approve an interception warrant under clause 19(2) of the draft Investigatory Powers Bill.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902171","902171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428262","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to improve parliamentary oversight of the Security Service.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902161","902161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428263","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the likelihood of the Government's net migration target being met.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902160","902160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428264","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on changing the police funding formula.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902159","902159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428265","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on changing the police funding formula.","Biography information for Suella Braverman","Suella Fernandes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902164","902164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428266","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that police forces are able to maintain existing levels of frontline policing over the next five years.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902166","902166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428267","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle domestic violence.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902163","902163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428268","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of changes to support for asylum seekers on local authority services.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902165","902165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428346","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what additional financial support he plans to make available to the NHS to deal with pressure on services in winter 2015-16.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902116","902116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428501","2015-11-18","Wales Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what progress has been made on the proposals for a Cardiff City Deal.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902193","902193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428555","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to improve the availability of off-patent drugs for novel uses through non-legislative measures.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902130","902130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428556","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to improve the availability of off-patent drugs for novel uses through non-legislative measures.","Biography information for Joanna Cherry","Joanna  Cherry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902127","902127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428726","2015-11-18","Wales Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits for his Department of merging the Wales, Scotland and Northern Ireland Offices to make a Department for the regions.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902185","902185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428946","2015-11-18","Wales Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Government support for the tourism sector in Wales.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902195","902195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428947","2015-11-18","Wales Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Government support for the tourism sector in Wales.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902192","902192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426979","2015-11-16","Attorney General","2015-11-09","To ask the Attorney General, what steps his Department has taken to embed the family test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15371","15371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426980","2015-11-16","Attorney General","2015-11-09","To ask the Attorney General, what steps his Department is taking to implement the family test; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15400","15400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426981","2015-11-16","Attorney General","2015-11-09","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate he has made of the total expenditure on (a) in-house advocates and (b) external advocates in (i) magistrates' courts and (ii) the Crown court in each year since 2010-11; and what the average saving to the Crown Prosecution Service was from using in-house advocates in each of those years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15558","15558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426982","2015-11-16","Attorney General","2015-11-09","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate he has made of Crown Prosecution Service expenditure on (a) victim liaison units and (b) witness care units in real terms in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15559","15559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426983","2015-11-16","Attorney General","2015-11-09","To ask the Attorney General, how many (a) victim liaison officers and (b) witness care officers were employed by the Crown Prosecution Service in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15560","15560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426984","2015-11-16","Attorney General","2015-11-09","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate he has made of expenditure in (a) 2014-15 prices and (b) as a proportion of total Departmental spending on (i) temporary agency staff, (ii) consultants, (iii) non-payroll staff, (iv) administration and (v) marketing and advertising in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15443","15443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426985","2015-11-16","Attorney General","2015-11-09","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate he has made of the amount of expected underspend for his office against departmental expenditure limits in 2015-16.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15536","15536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426986","2015-11-16","Attorney General","2015-11-09","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2015 to Question 11888, for what reason the (a) prosecution cost per defendant and (b) overall spend per completed case has increased since 2010-11.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15538","15538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426987","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish a timetable for the review of post-16 education and training by area; and  when such reviews will take place.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15483","15483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426988","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his Department's publication, Reviewing post-16 education and training institutions, of 20 July 2015, how much his Department expects to save as a result of implementing the proposals set out therein.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15484","15484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426989","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when post-16 education will be reviewed in Merseyside under the area review process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15485","15485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426990","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2015 to Question 13713, for what reasons all of Lord Green of Hustierpoint's updates on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership dated before 6 August 2015 cannot be deposited in the Library.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15564","15564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426991","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government is taking to increase the access to finance of small and medium-sized enterprises seeking to export.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15566","15566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426992","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department has attracted in investment to regenerate the site of the Royal Hospital Haslar; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15451","15451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426993","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the likely impact of freezing the earnings repayment thresholds for 24+ Advanced Learner Loans on the Resource Account and Budgeting charge of outstanding debt which will be written off for 24+ Advanced Learner Loans.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15530","15530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426994","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the likely impact of proposed changes to student loan repayment thresholds on repayment regimes for those students who take out 24+ Advanced Learner Loan and who study for an Access to HE qualification but then do not complete an HE qualification.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15527","15527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426995","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Cabinet Office on proposals in the Higher Education White Paper on removing HEFCE-funded providers from the scope of the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15555","15555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426996","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the likely impact of proposed changes to student loan repayment thresholds on repayment regimes for students who take out 24+ Advanced Learner Loan and who study for a Level 3 qualification who then study for and complete an HE qualification.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15528","15528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426997","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the Resource Account and Budgeting charge of outstanding debt which will be written off for 24+ Advanced Learner Loans in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15529","15529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426998","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which organisations he has met to discuss the findings of the research study into pregnancy discrimination in the workplace published by his Department and the Equality and Human Rights Commission on 24 July 2015.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15474","15474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426999","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on director conduct of the funding of insolvency litigation being brought under the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15406","15406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427000","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to embed the family test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15372","15372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427001","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent estimate he has made of the number of employees who receive payment of service charges, tips, gratuities and cover charges through their employer; and in what industries such employees work.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15369","15369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427002","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the level of growth of small and medium-sized enterprises across West Yorkshire since 2010.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15617","15617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427003","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will list (a) his Department's correspondence and (b) meetings with the former hon. Member for Redcar between May 2010 and May 2015 on SSI Redcar.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15649","15649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427004","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to promote British business in (a) Australia, (b) Canada and (c) New Zealand.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15690","15690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427005","2015-11-16","Cabinet Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department spent in (a) real terms and (b) as a proportion of departmental spending on (i) temporary agency staff, (ii) consultants, (iii) non-payroll staff, (iv) administration and (v) marketing and advertising for each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15650","15650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427006","2015-11-16","Cabinet Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what (a) contracts and (b) sub-contracts (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department have awarded (A) Netcracker Technology and (B) Computer Sciences Corporation.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15644","15644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427007","2015-11-16","Cabinet Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department has taken to embed the family test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15373","15373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427008","2015-11-16","Cabinet Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he expects the Verify identity assurance system to be fully operational; and what services he expects to be included in that system.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15581","15581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427009","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential risks to undersea internet and telephony cables; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15454","15454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427010","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish the television advertising schedule and list the television channels being used for the Great Britain campaign; and if he will estimate the cost of (a) producing the commercials for that campaign and (b) each television advertising slot by time and date of broadcast.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15569","15569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427011","2015-11-16","Cabinet Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many users are on the Verify identity verification system.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15535","15535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427012","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many representations he has received from (a) hon. Members and (b) members of the public on the activities of Concentrix on behalf of HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15445","15445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427013","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of in-work households in Salford in receipt of tax credits with an underlying entitlement to working tax credit in each of the last five tax years did not have a claim with an underlying entitlement to working tax credit in the following year.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15467","15467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427014","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of increasing the provision of export finance in productivity.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15551","15551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427015","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the British Business Bank will support UK productivity.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15388","15388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427016","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to implement the family test; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15403","15403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427017","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he and his Cabinet colleagues have had with their counterparts in the Irish government on the potential effect of the UK's withdrawal from the EU on all-island trade and the economy of Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15383","15383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427018","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2015 to Question 14136, what work the Government has undertaken to implement the commitments made in paragraphs (a) 1, (b) 2, (c) 3, (d) 8 and (e) 10 of the 2013 Lough Erne G8 Leaders' Communiqu since January 2014; and what assessment he  has made of the level of progress against those commitments.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15389","15389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427019","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2015 to Question 13786, what (a) arrears, (b) compensation and (c) other remedies have been issued to victims of modern slavery in relation to the 60 cases opened since February 2015.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15390","15390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427020","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2015 to Question 13786, what penalties have been issued to employers in relation to the 60 cases opened since February 2015.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15391","15391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427021","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average duration of an in-work tax credit claim containing an underlying entitlement to working tax credit have for claimants in Salford (a) in them last full year for which figures are available and (b) year to date.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15516","15516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427022","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total number of on-flows and off-flows tax credits was in Salford in the most recent (a) 12 and (b) 24 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15517","15517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427023","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is his policy to maintain the level of funding to the NHS from national insurance contributions (NICs) regardless of the overall amount raised by NICs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John McNally","John Mc Nally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15552","15552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427024","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of in-work households in Salford in receipt of tax credits with an underlying entitlement to working tax credit in each of the last five years had not had a claim with an underlying entitlement to working tax credit in the proceeding tax year.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15518","15518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427025","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of tax credit claimants who will be eligible for the Government's planned 30 hours of free childcare per week; and what the average reduction in childcare cost will be for each such claimant.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15635","15635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427026","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 November 2015 to Question 14749, if his Department will estimate the number of families whose income will be reduced as a result of proposed changes to tax credits.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15643","15643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427027","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of tax credit claimants receive 30 hours of free childcare per week once the childcare costs disregard for housing benefit has been accounted for.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15642","15642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427028","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the leaders of the Greater Manchester Combined Authority on future provision of funding for the arts after the devolution agreement comes into effect.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15640","15640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427029","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of tax credit claimants who claim housing benefit are entitled to a higher rate of housing benefit due to the childcare cost disregard.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15656","15656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427030","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax credit claimants have a child aged (a) one, (b) two, (c) three and (d) four.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15654","15654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427031","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of tax credit claimants have a child under the age of five and claim support for childcare costs.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15655","15655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427032","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the Government decided on the priorities for the National Infrastructure Commission; and for what reason digital connectivity was not chosen as one of those providers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15687","15687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427033","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether local planning authorities can limit community housing developments proposed in the dispersal policies of a local plan due to the lack of sufficient infrastructure, shops, services or employment to support such a development.","Biography information for Nadhim Zahawi","Nadhim Zahawi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15674","15674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427034","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will exempt housing co-operatives from the right to buy scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15675","15675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427035","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to increase the number of housing co-operatives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15676","15676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427036","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the value of artwork and antiques held by local authorities.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15618","15618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427037","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the projected average age of a first time buyer in 2020.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15594","15594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427038","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to allow local councils to ban overseas and off-plan sales.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15595","15595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427039","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential for the Fund for European Aid to the Most Deprived to assist efforts to help homeless EEA nationals in the UK.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15440","15440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427040","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the Government has received from the Fund for European Aid to the Most Deprived in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15438","15438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427041","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homelessness applications were made to local authorities as a result of an applicant losing their home to repossession in each of the last 10 years; and in what proportion of such applications the people were accepted as unintentionally homeless and in priority need.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15423","15423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427042","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure the routine use by his Department of the family test; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15396","15396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427043","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken to embed the family test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15374","15374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427044","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to publish his review of the residential conversion threshold for agricultural buildings.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15549","15549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427045","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to promote Small Business Saturday.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15505","15505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427046","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what planning consents have been granted for the site of the Royal Hospital Haslar; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15463","15463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427047","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proposals he has received from local and regional government on directly electing mayors; and if hewill make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15550","15550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427048","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of the total number of households have been owner occupiers in each of the last 10 years in each London (i) borough and (ii) constituency.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15573","15573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427049","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of new replacement homes for housing association homes to be sold under the proposed extension of right-to-buy entitlements which will be (a) local authority owned social housing, (b) housing association social housing and (c) private rented sector housing.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15572","15572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427050","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the residence requirements are for (a) existing right-to-buy entitlements and (b) the proposed extension of right-to-buy to housing association tenants for (i) non-EU foreign nationals, (ii) EU foreign nationals and (iii) UK citizens.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15571","15571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427051","2015-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on proposed devolution deals of the Quality Control Scheme Board's decision to not recommend the re-franchising of bus services in Tyne and Wear.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15582","15582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427052","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the average cost of a home bought by a first-time buyer in each of the last 10 years for each London (a) borough and (b) constituency.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15574","15574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427053","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of first time buyers there were in each London (a) borough and (b) constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15575","15575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427054","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the financial effect on the Horserace Levy Scheme of betting operators locating their online services off-shore; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15577","15577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427055","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress his Department has made on plans to introduce a Horserace Betting Right; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15578","15578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427056","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential benefit to sport of the introduction of a Sport Betting Right; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15580","15580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427057","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the contribution of fixed and mobile telecommunications infrastructure to productivity between (a) 2005 and 2010, (b) 2010 and 2015 and (c) 2015 and 2020.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15531","15531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427058","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of a Sport Betting Right on betting operators; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15579","15579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427059","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps are taken by (a) his Department and (b) Ofcom to investigate objections to the content of a UK-licenced radio station made by a foreign government.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15444","15444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427060","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to increase the availability of superfast broadband in (a) Warrington North constituency, (b) Culcheth and (c) Burtonwood.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15570","15570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427061","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to embed the family test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15370","15370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427062","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the withdrawal of Government funding of free TV licenses from the over 75 on future availability of such free licences.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15519","15519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427063","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to support the provision of playing pitches in local areas for community requirements.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15615","15615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427064","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding his Department has provided to support the arts in the West Midlands in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15657","15657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427065","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the proportion of households which have access to superfast broadband in (a) St Helen North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15673","15673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427066","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) contracts and (b) sub-contracts (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department have awarded (A) Netcracker Technology and (B) Computer Sciences Corporation.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15645","15645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427067","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Government's policy is on the provision of incremental annual pay rises for personnel of the armed forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15679","15679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427068","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how the construction of a new Royal Navy facility in Bahrain will further assist UK forces operating in the Middle East to resolve the conflicts there in which they are currently engaged.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15680","15680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427069","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total cost of overseas military operations was in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15658","15658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427070","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, by what proportion UK military capabilities have been reduced in the last five years; and what assessment he has made of the resources available to the armed forces to defend the UK in the event of a major conflict.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15666","15666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427071","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much Department for International Development expenditure his Department reported to NATO as defence spending in each year from 2006 to 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15626","15626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427072","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2015 to Question 13126, how many of the refugees who have arrived at RAF Akrotiri have (a) claimed asylum, (b) had such asylum claims accepted and (c) had such asylum claims rejected to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15382","15382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427073","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the physical and mental health of refugees arriving by boat at RAF Akrotiri; and what steps he plans to take to ensure the wellbeing of those refugees.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15381","15381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427074","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) Grade I listed buildings, (b) Grade II* listed buildings, (c) Grade II listed buildings and (d) scheduled monuments his Department owns; under which top level budget those buildings and monuments fall; and what plans he has for their disposal.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15408","15408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427075","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to embed the family test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15350","15350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427076","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department retains any formal interest in the site of the Royal Hospital Haslar.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15452","15452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427077","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) the amount of any underspend expected against departmental expenditure limits in the current fiscal year and (b) his Department's latest forecast of total AME spend for this year is; and what the forecasts were for those sums at the time of the Summer Budget 2015 and March Budget 2015.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15567","15567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427078","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent (a) in real terms and (b) as a share of departmental spending on (i) temporary agency staff, (ii) consultants, (iii) non-payroll staff, (iv) administration and (v) marketing and advertising for each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15568","15568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427079","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has received notification of, or has itself noted, any unusual submarine activity in the vicinity of internet and telephony cables in the Atlantic Ocean; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15450","15450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427080","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, to whom and for what price the site of the Royal Hospital Haslar was sold.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15464","15464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427081","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on how many sets of British brothers were killed in the First World War.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15512","15512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427082","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that British veterans who develop cancer through exposure to asbestos are entitled to the same level of compensation as civilians.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15511","15511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427083","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage schools to teach (a) CPR and (b) other life-saving methods.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15513","15513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427084","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations she has received from local authorities on the time taken to implement Education Health Care Plans.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15605","15605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427085","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the time taken to introduce Education Health Care Plans; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15606","15606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427086","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will list all the free school projects that have been withdrawn or cancelled to date; and what the cost to the public purse was of the withdrawal or cancellation of each such project.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15557","15557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427087","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her officials met with their counterparts in the devolved administrations in the last three years; and what the subjects for discussion or agreement were at each of those meetings.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15521","15521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427088","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, why school and academy sixth forms have not been included in recommendations arising out of reviews of post-16 education and training; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15482","15482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427089","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Department's publication, Reviewing post-16 education and training institutions, of 20 July 2015, how much her Department expects to save as a result of implementing the proposals set out therin.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15486","15486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427090","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of provision of play opportunities for children with disabilities and complex needs.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15366","15366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427091","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to respond to its call for evidence on the cost of providing childcare published on 15 June 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15355","15355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427092","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2015 to Question 13930, how many key stage one children receiving universal infant free school meals would not be eligible for such meals through a benefit-related claim.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15407","15407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427093","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that local education authorities do not specify the designs of building extensions when attributing funding from the Education Funding Agency to schools for building projects, as in relation to the case of Greave Primary School in Hazel Grove.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15431","15431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427094","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations she has received from representatives of Greave Primary School on the process through which the funding for that school's building extension project from the Education Funding Agency has been arranged by the Stockport Local Education Authority.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15432","15432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427095","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure the routine use by her Department of the family test; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15397","15397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427096","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department spent on (a) temporary agency staff, (b) consultants, (c) non-payroll staff, (d) administration and (e) marketing and advertising (i) in 2014-15 prices and (ii) as a proportion of her Department's expenditure in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15385","15385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427097","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's forecast expenditure against Departmental Expenditure Limits is in 2015-16; and what her Department's forecast Annually Managed Expenditure in 2015-16 was (a) at the time of the March Budget, (b) at the time of the Summer Budget and (c) on 10 November 2015.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15378","15378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427098","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the report from Sense, The case for play, published 22 June 2015; and what the implications of that report are for her Department's policies.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15553","15553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427099","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Government plans to respond to the First Report of the House of Lords Select Committee on Affordable Childcare, Session 2014-15, HL Paper 117.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15422","15422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427100","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to maintain the current staff-child ratio for childcare providers and child minders until 2020.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15416","15416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427101","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what amount her Department has spent to date on underwriting salaries of staff at free schools whose schools did not open or open on time.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15417","15417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427102","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many planning areas in England are in need of additional secondary school places by September 2016; in how many of those planning areas has there never been an application to open a secondary or all-through mainstream free school; and in how of those planning areas there are no secondary or all-through mainstream free schools.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15418","15418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427103","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many planning areas in England are in need of additional primary school places by September 2016; in how many of those planning areas there has never been an application to open a primary or all-through mainstream free school; and in how of those planning areas there are no primary or all-through mainstream free schools.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15419","15419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427104","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many written complaints her Department received about academy brokers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15414","15414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427105","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy brokers there are; and how much her Department spent on academy brokers in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15415","15415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427106","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to change the rules on staff-pupil ratios in early education settings.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15420","15420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427107","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to increase the number of early education places for children (a) under the age of three and (b) aged three and four; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15421","15421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427108","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what joint work she and her French counterpart are undertaking on providing governance and capacity-building support for francophone Africa.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15623","15623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427109","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government plans to increase the number of qualified staff working on early education settings.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15624","15624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427110","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will discuss with the Treasury the introduction of three-year funding plans for colleges to align with the period of the Spending Review.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15621","15621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427111","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to develop a long-term policy to assist colleges in recruiting maths and English teachers.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15622","15622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427112","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that school (a) staff and (b) pupils are protected from violence in schools.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15660","15660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427113","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to (a) recruit more teachers and (b) otherwise ensure that schools do not experience a shortage of teaching staff.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15689","15689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427114","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which power plants are due to come offline in March 2016; and what plans she has to ensure peak energy demands are met after those plants come offline.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15681","15681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427115","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2015 to Question 11089, what statistical analysis or impact assessment her Department has made of the effect of the proposed cut to feed-in tariffs on small businesses in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15672","15672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427116","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what guidance her Department provides to local authorities on reducing energy consumption and carbon dioxide emissions.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15619","15619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427117","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many domestic customers (a) Scottish Power, (b) SSE, (c) E.on, (d) British Gas, (e) EDF, (f) Npower, (g) First Utility, (h) Ovo and (i) Cooperative Energy each have.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15597","15597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427118","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the progress of local authorities in reducing carbon dioxide emissions.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15620","15620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427119","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the average annual energy bill for domestic customers of (a) Scottish Power, (b) SSE, (c) Eon, (d) British Gas, (e) EDF, (f) NPower, (g) First Utility, (h) Ovo and (i) Cooperative Energy in 2014.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15401","15401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427120","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that oil produced in UK waters is sent to oil refineries in the UK.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15410","15410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427121","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the contribution of the energy sector to productivity between (a) 2005 and 2010, (b) 2010 and 2015 and (c) 2015 and 2020.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15533","15533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427122","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of business energy taxation on productivity between (a) 2005 and 2010, (b) 2010 and 2015 and (c) 2015 and 2020.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15532","15532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427123","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2015 to Question 13387, what information her Department holds on the number of sites approved for fracking in England and Wales; what the location is of each such site; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15604","15604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427124","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will list the average wholesale price for electricity in (a) nominal and (b) real pounds sterling for each year from 2000 to 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15590","15590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427125","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what difference there is between the wholesale price for electricity and the representative market price for baseload electricity referred to in her Departmental Minute of 21 October 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15591","15591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427126","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information her Department holds on the date when EDF ordered the pressure vessel heads for Hinkley Point C; and how many pressure vessel heads for Hinkley Point C have already been manufactured.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15585","15585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427127","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the cost per megawatt hour of electricity is from the (a) Hunterston B, (b) Heysham 1&2, (c) Torness, (d) Hatlepool, (e) Sizewell, (f) Dungeness B and (g) Hinkley Point C power stations.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15586","15586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427128","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she expects to make a decision to proceed with an order for a European pressurised reactor at Sizewell C.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15587","15587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427129","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she will make a decision to proceed with the order for a Chinese-designed reactor at Bradwell.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15588","15588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427130","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the amount of 4 to 19 billion referred to in her Departmental Minute of 21 October 2015 as the total support to HPC is (a) the actual total cash amount or (b) the present value of the total cash amount of the support to be paid to EDF.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15589","15589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427131","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of households are with their home, regional incumbent, supplier for electricity and gas in each electricity supply region.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15471","15471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427132","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with shooting bodies on ensuring an effective trap is developed to replace the Fenn trap.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15514","15514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427133","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will place in the Library the report on the suspension of the digital service for the Basic Payment Scheme for farmers which was commissioned by her Department and the Rural Payments Agency in March 2015.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15470","15470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427134","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that crustaceans being sold in UK retail or wholesale premises are not still alive and sealed in plastic bags.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15603","15603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427135","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the owners of Heathrow Airport on ensuring that that airport meets UK and EU air quality standards; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15479","15479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427136","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an estimate of the effect on the rural economy of the reduction in grouse shooting caused by poor weather in 2015.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15515","15515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427137","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department has taken to improve air quality at Heathrow Airport; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15480","15480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427138","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will assess the potential merits of providing legal protection to the professional title of veterinary nurse.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15353","15353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427139","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the timetable is for the review of the Code of Practice for Privately Kept Non-Human Primates; and whether that review will include consultation with (a) members of the public and (b) animal welfare organisations.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15358","15358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427140","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department spent on (a) temporary agency staff, (b) consultants, (c) non-payroll staff, (d) administration and (e) marketing and advertising (i) in 2014-15 prices and (ii) as a proportion of her Department's expenditure in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15387","15387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427141","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect of the family test on her Department's policies; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15404","15404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427142","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's  forecast expenditure against Departmental Expenditure Limits is in 2015-16; and what her Department's forecast Annually Managed expenditure in 2015-16 was (a) at the time of the March Budget, (b) at the time of the Summer Budget and (c) on 10 November 2015.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15377","15377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427143","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the time taken for Anguilla to respond to his Department's consultation on a public register of beneficial ownership; and what assessment he has made of the legitimacy of the reasons for the time that was taken.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15393","15393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427144","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2015 to Question 14454, what (a) funding and (b) other support the Government has offered UNHCR to identify people for resettlement to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15524","15524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427145","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which Minister in his Department is responsible for atrocity prevention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15522","15522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427146","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 9 November 2015 to Question 14485, whether he has made an assessment of whether aerial bombing of Hayden Hospital in Yemen could represent a breach in international humanitarian law.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15523","15523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427147","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2014 to Question 219424, what financial support the Government has (a) provided since 1 January 2015 and (b) budgeted to provide in the future to support local governance in opposition-controlled areas.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15525","15525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427148","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's counter-extremism budget was for (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15; and how much has been budgeted for (i) 2015-16 and (ii) future financial years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15526","15526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427149","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of Christians who have left Iraq in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15439","15439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427150","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will (a) discuss with the Moroccan Ambassador to the UK and (b) instruct the British Ambassador to Morocco to investigate the condition and treatment of Ali Aarrass who is on hunger strike in Sale prison.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15412","15412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427151","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the options that were agreed by the UK, Morocco and the Saharawi under the 1990-91 ceasefire agreement for a referendum on self-determination in Western Sahara have changed.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15413","15413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427152","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his estimate is of the number of human rights activists and community leaders killed in Colombia during the first eight months of 2015.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15434","15434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427153","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's expenditure against Departmental Expenditure Limits is in 2015-16; and what his Department's Annually Managed Expenditure in 2015-16 was (a) at the time of the March Budget, (b) at the time of the Summer Budget and (c) on 10 November 2015.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15375","15375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427154","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) security and (b) political situation in the Central Africa Republic.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15446","15446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427155","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met (a) the Afghan ambassador to the UK or (b) other representatives of the Afghan government.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15447","15447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427156","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the governments of the Gulf Co-operation Council on improving bilateral trade and security.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15561","15561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427157","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political situation in Kurdistan and the effect this situation has on the threat from Islamic State; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15546","15546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427158","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has provided support for the fish farming industry in Egypt.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15508","15508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427159","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Iranian counterpart on the human rights of the Bahai community in Iran.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15506","15506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427160","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent support the Government has provided to Egypt for oil and shale gas development.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15507","15507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427161","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to raise with the Prime Minister of India during his forthcoming visit the recent death of Sikh protestors in the Punjab following the desecration of the Sikh holy book.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15475","15475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427162","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the resolution of discussions on the sovereignty of oil reserves in the Golan Heights.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15627","15627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427163","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has held with the government of Nigeria on the situation in Biafra.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15602","15602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427164","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the Nigerian government on returning displaced people to areas previously in the control of Boko Haram.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15630","15630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427165","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the Nigerian government combat (a) Boko Haram and (b) other terrorist groups.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15633","15633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427166","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the threat posed by Boko Haram in Nigeria.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15634","15634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427167","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to (a) assess and (b) help improve security at Sharm el-Sheikh airport; and what assessment he has made of the incidence of corruption amongst staff at the airport.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15664","15664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427168","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's aims are for the visit of Indian Prime Minister, Narendra Modi.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15665","15665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427169","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the recent increase in migrants from Haiti to the Turks and Caicos Islands on local resources on those islands.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15661","15661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427170","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to help tackle the (a) recent increase in illegal transport of weapons from Haiti to the Turks and Caicos Islands and (b) the increase in gun crime in those islands.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15662","15662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427171","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to cooperate with his Egyptian counterpart on measures to (a) counter security threats and (b) ensure the safety of air passengers travelling from Egypt.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15663","15663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427172","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Indian government on steps to lift the fuel blockade on Nepal and facilitate the release of humanitarian supplies.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15614","15614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427173","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government had with the Angolan government on the case of Luaty Beiro while he was on hunger strike in prison.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15684","15684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427174","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what action the Government is taking to support the Angolan government in building capacity to support civil society and freedom of expression.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15685","15685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427175","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the level of complaints against Arriva Transport Solutions over its level of service while running Greater Manchester's non-emergency ambulance service; and what steps he is taking to ensure a better service in Greater Manchester in future.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15678","15678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427176","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) furthest and (b) average distance was which patients travelled to in-patient mother and baby units specialising in psychiatric care during the perinatal period in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15647","15647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427177","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many perinatal mental health admissions there were in 2014-15.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15616","15616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427178","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Public Health England advice entitled Take-home naloxone for opioid overdose in people who use drugs, what steps he is taking to encourage local commissioners to adopt a programme of issuing MHRA-licenced take home Naloxone (a) in general and (b) to opioid-dependent prisoners upon their release; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15636","15636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427179","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the number and proportion of people receiving consultant-led mental health treatment within 18 weeks of referral is not recorded centrally; and what plans he has record such information.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15646","15646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427180","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many female inpatient mental health beds there were on (a) Saturday 7 November 2015 and (b) Sunday 8 November 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15631","15631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427181","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the experiences of (a) children on the autism spectrum, (b) adults on the autism spectrum and (c) family members and carers, during the diagnostic process, are collected and published.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15609","15609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427182","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the expected average frequency of evening and weekend work by junior doctors under the proposed changes to junior doctors' contracts.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15473","15473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427183","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to support research into mesothelioma.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15478","15478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427184","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to (a) increase awareness of autism and (b) ensure that diagnosis times are improved.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15608","15608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427185","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average frequency of evening and weekend work by junior doctors in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15472","15472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427186","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps (a) his Department and (b) NHS England is taking to ensure that autism diagnosis waiting times for (i) children and (ii) adults in Northumberland meet NICE guidance.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15607","15607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427187","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that cancer communities are targeted towards all age groups and people with learning disabilities.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15490","15490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427188","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he next plans to review the effectiveness of cancer screening for women.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15491","15491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427189","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking the encourage employers to enable staff to take time off work to attend cancer screening appointments.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15492","15492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427190","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the number of educational programmes on cancer screening.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15493","15493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427191","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that young women attend screening for cervical cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15494","15494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427192","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to promote awareness in schools of the HPV vaccine.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15495","15495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427193","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to introduce a standard dementia test for all people aged between 65 and 70.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15496","15496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427194","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal Colleges on the availability of cancer treatments relating to genetically-edited immune cells.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15497","15497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427195","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of treating endometriosis in the last year.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15498","15498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427196","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with vascular dementia in each of the last five years; and what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of treating that condition in that period.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15499","15499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427197","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to make the innovative blood test to rule out heart attacks available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15500","15500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427198","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of still births; and what steps he is taking to improve communication between coroners and health professionals to inform such steps.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15501","15501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427199","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps NICE has taken to make the Novalung treatment available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15502","15502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427200","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of (a) CPR and (b) other life-saving methods among adults and young people.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15503","15503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427201","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the level of variation in survival rates for people who have had cardiac arrests between regions in England.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15504","15504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427202","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to promote his Department's strategies to prevent cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15489","15489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427203","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the public purse received in reimbursement from each non-EEA country with reciprocal healthcare agreements with the UK for health care provided to their nationals for each year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15460","15460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427204","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the public purse received in reimbursement from each EEA country for healthcare provided to their citizens for each year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15461","15461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427205","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an estimate of the number of additional hospitals that will be required to accommodate the predicted population rise over the next 25 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15462","15462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427206","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will intervene on behalf of Khalid Younis so that he receives drugs needed to treat his chronic myeloid leukaemia condition.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15442","15442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427207","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent from the public purse on reimbursing each non-European Economic Area country for health care provided to UK nationals for each financial year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15459","15459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427208","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent from the public purse on reimbursing each non-European Economic Area country with reciprocal healthcare agreements with the UK for health care provided to UK nationals for each financial year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15458","15458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427209","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 1 December 2014 to Question 216015, what criteria his Department sets for eligibility for free NHS prescriptions for households in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15488","15488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427210","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's expenditure against Departmental Expenditure Limits is in 2015-16; and what his Department's Annually Forecast Managed Expenditure in 2015-16 was (a) at the time of the March Budget, (b) at the time of the Summer Budget and (c) on 10 November 2015.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15376","15376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427211","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the potential benefits of adult education courses for people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15357","15357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427212","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ask NHS England to undertake a further review of clinical commissioning groups' spending on mental health in 2015-16.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15435","15435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427213","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of whether there has been an increase in the use of mental health services by chemsex drug users in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15436","15436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427214","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on (a) temporary agency staff, (b) consultants, (c) non-payroll staff, (d) administration and (e) marketing and advertising (i) in 2014-15 prices and (ii) as a proportion of his Department's expenditure in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15386","15386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427215","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of junior doctors not rostered on at evenings and weekends as a result of the terms of the current junior doctor contract.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15411","15411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427216","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average response time to a 999 call for the emergency services was in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) the Yorkshire and the Humber region and (c) the UK in each year from 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15351","15351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427217","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to make the email and telephone inquiry service within UK Visa and Immigration more user-friendly.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15520","15520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427218","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of child abuse that have been reported to police (a) did and (b) did not lead to a prosecution in the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15509","15509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427219","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with West Yorkshire Police on the review commissioned by the Office of the West Yorkshire Police and Crime Commissioner, and conducted by Greater Manchester Police, into the conviction of Mr Danny Major.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15547","15547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427220","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support she is providing to 16 and 17 year olds who have been victims of child sexual exploitation.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15465","15465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427221","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to protect 16 and 17 year olds from child sexual exploitation.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15466","15466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427222","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what grounds her Department refused entry to the UK to (a) Dr Hasnaa Al Sourani, (b) Dr Amal Shaat, (c) Dr Rula Al Helo and (d) Mr Yousif Abu Rahma; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15610","15610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427223","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many murders related to domestic violence there have been in each year between 1997 and 2014.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15637","15637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427224","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 17 September 2015 to Question 10198, whether funding to settle refugees within the UK will be allocated solely from the overseas aid budget.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15667","15667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427225","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which funding proposals were approved (a) in general and (b) for Sri Lanka by the Asian Development Bank in each of the last three years; whether the Government voted in favour of any of those proposals; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15682","15682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427226","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which funding proposals have been approved by the World Bank in each of the last three years; whether the Government voted against any of those proposals; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15683","15683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427227","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to improve the resilience of healthcare provision in West Africa.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15628","15628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427228","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much Ministry of Defence expenditure her Department considered to be spending on international development in each year from 2006 to 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15625","15625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427229","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will assess the effect on the Nigerian (a) economy and (b) society of (i) Boko Haram and (ii) other terrorist groups.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15632","15632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427230","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's budget was spent on supporting water, sanitation and hygiene services in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Mrs Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15677","15677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427231","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of potential risks associated with vulnerable witnesses and defendants travelling by public transport when considering potential court closures as part of proposals on the future of the court and tribunal estate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15359","15359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427232","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what account he has taken of accessibility of digital services for people who do not have access to the internet when considering potential court closures as part of proposals on the provision of the court and tribunal estate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15360","15360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427233","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential opportunities to enhance local services on pre-existing estates by co-locating services as part of proposals on the provision of the court and tribunal estate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15361","15361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427234","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the average cost to the public purse of a vacated trial in (a) Magistrates' courts and (b) the Crown Court.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15433","15433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427235","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of the family test on his Department's policies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15402","15402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427236","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2015 to Question 14487, whether revenue received from the criminal courts charge have exceeded the cost to the public purse of running such courts since that charge was introduced.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15392","15392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427237","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of trials cracked as a result of the prosecution due to (a) insufficient evidence, (b) witness absent or withdrawn, (c) public interest grounds and (d) adjournment refused in (i) Magistrates' courts and (ii) the Crown Court in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15394","15394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427238","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of trials were ineffective due to the (a) prosecution being engaged in another trial, (b) prosecution advocate failing to attend and (c) prosecution increasing the time estimate due to insufficient time for trial to start in (i) Magistrates' courts and (ii) the Crown Court in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15395","15395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427239","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recommendations his Department has made to the government of (a) Guernsey and (b)Jersey on the definition of legitimate interest in the management of central registers of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15593","15593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427240","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to amend sentencing guidelines to reduce the amount of time that offenders spend in prison.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15510","15510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427241","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2015 to Question 11884, what estimate he has made of the total cost to the public purse of vacated trials due to the prosecution in each year since 2010-11; and how many and what proportion of trials were (a) ineffective and (b) cracked in (i) Magistrates' courts and (ii) the Crown Court for reasons related to the prosecution in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15537","15537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427242","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drones carrying contraband goods have been seized within prison grounds in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15648","15648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427243","2015-11-16","House of Commons Commission","2015-11-09","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, if he will take steps to ensure the inclusion in budgetary provisions for a programme to restore and renew the Palace of Westminster proposals for commemorating Augustus Pugin at St Augustine's Church, Ramsgate.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15347","15347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427244","2015-11-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the UK's withdrawal from the EU on the functioning of the cross-border institutions established by the Good Friday Agreement.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15384","15384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427245","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the illegal trade of cigarettes in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15554","15554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427246","2015-11-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what representations she has made to planning authorities in (a) Northern Ireland and (b) the Republic of Ireland on the proposed 400kV North-South electricity interconnector between County Tyrone and County Meath.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15601","15601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427247","2015-11-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment the Government has made of the risks to the security of electricity supply in Northern Ireland posed by the failure to build and have operational by 2020 the 400kV North-South electricity interconnector between County Tyrone and County Meath.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15599","15599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427248","2015-11-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the Government's policy is on the proposed 400kV North-South electricity interconnector between County Tyrone and County Meath.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15600","15600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427249","2015-11-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with (a) the Northern Ireland Executive's Department of Enterprise, Trade and Investment and (b) her counterpart in the Republic of Ireland on steps to ensure the proposed North-South electricity interconnector is delivered.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15598","15598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427250","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the (a) Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership and (b) Trade in Services Agreement will be subject to a vote in the House following Parliamentary scrutiny.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15441","15441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427251","2015-11-16","Cabinet Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Prime Minister has had discussions with (a) the UN Secretary General, (b) the President of the International Criminal Court and (c) the President of the International Court of Justice on the recent amendments to the ministerial code and compliance with international treaties.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15448","15448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427252","2015-11-16","Scotland Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 9 November 2015 to Question 14925, what for reason his Department's quarterly report of transparency information from July to September 2014 took four months longer to prepare than the report on that information from January to March 2015.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15671","15671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427253","2015-11-16","Scotland Office","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 9 November 2015 to Question 14925, on publications, what deadlines his Department places on its publication of transparency information.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15670","15670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427254","2015-11-16","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-11-09","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what guidance the Electoral Commission has issued to returning officers on responding to requests under the Freedom of Information Act for statistics on electoral registration.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15534","15534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427255","2015-11-16","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-11-09","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what guidance the Electoral Commission has received from the Government on providing the latest electoral registration statistics in response to Freedom of Information requests.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15576","15576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427256","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) complaints have been made about and (b) investigations have been conducted into bus companies by the North East Traffic Commissioners in each year since 2010; and what enforcement action has been taken as a result following each such complaint or investigation.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15584","15584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427257","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost has been of the North East Traffic Commissioners Quality Contact Scheme board to date.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15583","15583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427258","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will support Jet2.com's Onboard Together campaign to reduce disruptive behaviour on aircraft.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15563","15563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427259","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has received assurances from Heathrow Airport that it will meet all of the Airports Commission recommendations before a decision is made on airport expansion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15481","15481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427260","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of (a) Uber vehicles, (b) black cabs and (c) private hire vehicles are wheelchair accessible.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15562","15562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427261","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with freight and haulier representatives on ensuring better access to food, drink and sanitation facilities as part of his Department's development of a strategy to improve the running of Operation Stack; and when he expects to announce his Department's strategy.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15539","15539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427262","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assistance the Government has given to (a) Kent Police, (b) Kent County Council, (c) other operational organisations and (d) businesses to cover costs and losses during the implementation of Operation Stack in 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15540","15540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427263","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the ability of young drivers to gain insurance cover of the recent increase in the insurance premium tax.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15548","15548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427264","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of how many taxi drivers have undergone disability awareness training since the Law Commission's recommendation on that subject published in its report, Taxi and Private Hire Services, on 23 May 2014.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15468","15468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427265","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he intends to implement a single consolidated legislative framework for taxis throughout England and Wales.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15469","15469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427266","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure the routine use by his Department of the family test; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15398","15398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427267","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what penalties there are for London airports which breach the noise quota count designated in the Civil Aviation Act 1982.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15399","15399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427268","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times noise quotas at each London airport have been breached in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15405","15405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427269","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the proportion of people who (a) died and (b) were injured on the road who were vulnerable road users.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15409","15409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427270","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will expand the Cycle to Work salary-sacrifice scheme to provide employees with access to tax-free physical activity accessories and personalised activity plans for themselves and their families.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15349","15349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427271","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the consultation on the Cycling and Walking Investment Strategy will not take place until spring 2016.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15352","15352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427272","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the contribution of competition between airports to the future development of the aviation industry in the South East; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15362","15362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427273","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how often have the noise quotas for London airports been reviewed or updated since their designation in the Civil Aviation Act 1982.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15354","15354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427274","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the finding in the RAC report, Motoring 2015, published in September 2015, that 12 per cent of motorists think it is acceptable to make a short call on a hand-held mobile device whilst driving; and what measures his Department plans to take to research the potential effectiveness and enforcement of legislation on the use of such devices for (a) phone calls and (b) using social media whilst driving.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15363","15363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427275","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to maintain the current level of train services between Eastbourne and Gatwick Airport under any proposals for a second Brighton mainline; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15364","15364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427276","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to (a) reduce times, (b) increase capacity and (c) increase the reliability of rail journeys between Eastbourne and (i) Gatwick Airport, (ii) Brighton and (iii) London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15365","15365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427277","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the projected transport budget per capita in Greater Manchester after the devolution agreement comes into effect.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15641","15641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427278","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the per capita spending was on transport projects in (a) Greater Manchester and (b) London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15638","15638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427279","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the economic benefits of (a) dualling the A17 in its entirety and (b) dualling its single carriageway sections.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15629","15629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427280","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Disabled People of 27 October 2015, Official Report, column 101WH, what assessment he has made of the reason for the high proportion of young people receiving benefit sanctions.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15596","15596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427281","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the time taken for a disability benefit appeal to reach a tribunal in Birmingham.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15611","15611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427282","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will collect statistics on waiting times for disability benefit appeals to reach tribunal to ensure that such cases are not subject to delays.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15612","15612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427283","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's complaints resolution procedure is when an external disability benefit assessor such as Atos or Capita submits an assessment for employment support allowance or personal independence payment which a claimant considers to be inaccurate; and whether claimants should apply to the assessor or to his Department to remedy inaccuracies in their assessment.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15613","15613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427284","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on tackling benefit fraud and error in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15652","15652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427285","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to work with credit reference agencies on addressing benefit fraud and error.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15653","15653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427286","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to mitigate the effects of provisions of the Pensions Act 1995 and the Pensions Act 2011 on women born in the 1950s.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15639","15639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427287","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to transfer housing benefit fraud investigation powers from local authorities to national investigation service.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15651","15651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427288","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the cumulative effect of the Pensions Act 1995 and the Pensions Act 2011 on women born in the 1950s.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15659","15659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427289","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse was of benefit fraud in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2013-14; and what proportion of total expenditure on housing benefit that cost represented in each of those years.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15668","15668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427290","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the reasons for increased benefit fraud in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15669","15669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427291","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that it provides its staff with sufficient guidance to ensure that sanctions are not placed on universal credit claimants who do not have an applicable box to tick on NHS charges claim forms when claiming help with NHS health costs.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15688","15688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427292","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what policy his Department has in place to protect the confidentiality of data disclosed to JCP systems by jobseekers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15686","15686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427293","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of (a) employment and support allowance and (b) jobseeker's allowance are taking adult education courses paid for by his Department.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15356","15356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427294","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 7.4 of the Explanatory Memorandum for the Rent Officers (Housing Benefit and Universal Credit Functions) (Local Housing Allowance Amendments) Order 2015 (S.I., 2015, No. 1753), how the Government plans to define higher rent increases for the purposes of determining eligibility for additional funding under the Targeted Affordability Fund.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15367","15367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427295","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Rent Officers (Housing Benefit and Universal Credit Functions) (Local Housing Allowance Amendments) Order 2015 (S.I., 2015, No. 1753), what total amount will be made available to local authorities under the Targeted Affordability Fund before the date on which those regulations are due to come into force.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15368","15368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427296","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on his policies of the family test; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15348","15348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427297","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what additional support and training his Department offers to unemployed people in order for them to fill long-term vacancies in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15380","15380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427298","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that job vacancy statistics do not double-count jobs advertised through multiple agencies on the job vacancy portal.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15379","15379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427299","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2015 to Question 13612, what the total monetary value is of the debts written off since 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15437","15437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427300","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new claims for housing benefit were made by people who lost their homes to repossession in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15424","15424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427301","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of claims for (a) support for mortgage interest and (b) housing benefit was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15425","15425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427302","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people who made a claim for support for mortgage interest in each year between 1995 and 2009 went into arrears on their (a) interest repayments and (b) capital repayments (i) during the first 13 weeks of the waiting period and (ii) between weeks 13 and 39 of the waiting period.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15426","15426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427303","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people who made a claim for support for mortgage interest in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13, (e) 2013-14 and (f) 2014-15 went into arrears on their (i) interest repayments and (ii) capital repayments during the 13-week waiting period.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15427","15427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427304","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people in receipt of support for mortgage interest who were also in receipt of income-based jobseeker's allowance, reached the end of the two-year limit in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13, (e) 2013-14 and (f) 2014-15.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15428","15428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427305","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people in receipt of universal credit receive help with mortgage costs.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15429","15429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427306","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people who are in receipt of support for mortgage interest are also in receipt of (a) income-based jobseeker's allowance, (b) income-based employment and support allowance, (c) income support and (d) pension credit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15430","15430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427307","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will provide support for women who have been affected financially  as a result of changes brought about by the Pension Act 2011.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15476","15476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427308","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average amount foregone by women who will wait longer to receive their state pension was as a result of changes brought about by the Pension Act 2011.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15477","15477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427309","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how his Department has used benefit off-flow data in the last three years to calculate remuneration for jobcentre (a) managers and (b) advisers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15541","15541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427310","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) advisers and (b) managers were interviewed during the course of the investigation which led to the dismissal of two advisers at Plaistow Jobcentre in May 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15542","15542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427311","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of an increase in the universal credit taper rate on (a) work incentives and (b) progression incentives.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15543","15543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427312","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many advisers worked at Plaistow Jobcentre in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15544","15544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427313","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to roll-out the placement of Jobcentre Plus advisers in food banks.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15545","15545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427314","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2015 to Question 10742, what proportion of people in the work-related activity group of employment and support allowance are also in receipt of personal independence payment.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15487","15487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427315","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the contribution of the provision of free childcare to UK productivity in (a) 2005-2010, (b) 2010-2015 and (c) 2015-2020.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15449","15449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427316","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent from the public purse on the payment of social security benefits to non-UK citizens in each European Economic Area country for each year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15457","15457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427317","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent from the public purse on the payment of social security benefits to non-UK citizens in each non-European Economic Area country for each year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15455","15455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427318","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent from the public purse on the payment of the state pension to non-UK citizens in each European Economic Area country for each year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15456","15456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427319","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent from the public purse on the payment of the state pension to non-UK citizens in each non-European Economic Area country in each year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15453","15453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427320","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average weekly payment was of (a) support for mortgage interest and (b) housing benefit in (i) 2009-10, (ii) 2010-11, (iii) 2011-12, (iv) 2012-13, (v) 2013-14 and (vi) 2014-15.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15556","15556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427321","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the increase in state pension age in the Pensions Act 2011 on women born in the 1950s; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15565","15565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426710","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he made prior to the closure of SSI Redcar of the (a) opportunity to produce foundry coke at Redcar coke ovens and (b) potential market for foundry coke.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15194","15194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426711","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what meetings he has had with (a) the Low Pay Commission, (b) Which? and (c) members of the Trade Union Congress to discuss the payment and administration of service charges, tips, gratuities and cover charges on the income of employees.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15204","15204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426712","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations or advice he has received on the expectation of current students and graduates to repay their student loans under the terms of the current scheme.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15224","15224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426713","2015-11-10","Cabinet Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are employed on zero-hours contracts in their main employment in Lancaster and Fleetwood constituency.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15251","15251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426714","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many of his Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps he has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments that have been carried out; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15327","15327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426715","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2015 to Question 12304, on consumer protection measure, what the names are of the main stakeholders who were alerted to the call for evidence; when those stakeholders were altered; and how those stakeholders were alerted.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15297","15297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426716","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2015 to Question 12304, what the names are of the main stakeholders who the Government consulted on the terms of reference of the Review into Secondary Ticketing Market.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15298","15298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426717","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress his Department has made on introducing loans for postgraduate study.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15302","15302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426718","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15337","15337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426719","2015-11-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with ministerial colleagues on reviewing the Valuation Office Agency process for considering rating assessment appeals.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15282","15282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426720","2015-11-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had about reducing the time taken by the Valuation Office Agency to consider rating assessment appeals.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15285","15285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426721","2015-11-10","HM Treasury","2015-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average time taken was for a rating assessment appeal to be considered by the Valuation Office Agency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15286","15286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426722","2015-11-10","HM Treasury","2015-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many rating assessment appeals are outstanding with the Valuation Office Agency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15287","15287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426723","2015-11-10","Cabinet Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many of his Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps he has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments that have been carried out; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15328","15328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426724","2015-11-10","Cabinet Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15338","15338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426725","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the change in tax revenue as a result of the introduction of new pension freedoms.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15304","15304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426726","2015-11-10","HM Treasury","2015-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the vulnerability of the UK banking system to a Russian debt default; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15271","15271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426727","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much is owed in overpaid tax credits.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15239","15239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426728","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2015 to Question 13969, what information his Department has to help inform policy development on the payment of child and tax credits to foreign nationals.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15241","15241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426729","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of employees paying tax through PAYE and (b) amount paid by such employees on service charges, tips, cover charges and gratuities administered via workplace payrolls for each financial year from 2010 to 2014.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15205","15205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426730","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many reports his Department has received of HM Revenue and Customs' online renewal system failing to record and register information and supporting documentation submitted by claimants wishing to renew their claim for (a) child tax credit and (b) working tax credit in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15225","15225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426731","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will visit the HM Revenue and Customs workforce in Cumbernauld to discuss their long-term employment at the tax centre there.","Biography information for John McNally","John Mc Nally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15226","15226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426732","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his Answer of 30 October 2015 to Question 13346, if he will make it his policy to introduce a dedicated team at the tax credit office in Preston constituency to deal with tax credit cases referred to them by hon. Members.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15228","15228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426733","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will meet providers of (a) supported housing and (b) specified housing to discuss the effect of the proposed change to social rents on the viability of those types of housing.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15201","15201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426734","2015-11-10","Cabinet Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how he plans to implement his policy on local authority procurement policies in relation to boycotts, divestments and sanctions against other countries and the UK defence industry announced on 3 October 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15207","15207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426735","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which Diwali celebrations he, his predecessor or Ministers in his Department attended in 2014 and 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15197","15197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426736","2015-11-10","Cabinet Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he had with the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs when developing his Department's policy on local authority procurement policies and companies' investment and divestment decisions announced on 3 October 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15223","15223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426737","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in the Durham Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15307","15307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426738","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in the Cleveland Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15308","15308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426739","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in the West Sussex Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15309","15309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426740","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in the Surrey Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15310","15310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426741","2015-11-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15339","15339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426742","2015-11-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many of his Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps he has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments that have been carried out; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15329","15329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426743","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in the Northumberland Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15320","15320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426744","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of references of families to the Troubled Families programme have been the result of schools expressing concerns that children are not receiving sufficient food at home since April 2015.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15326","15326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426745","2015-11-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many of his Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps he has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments that have been carried out; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15330","15330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426746","2015-11-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15340","15340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426747","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has received representations from the Nigerian government on the licensing of Radio Biafra.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15265","15265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426748","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which Diwali celebrations he, his predecessor or Ministers in his Department attended in 2014 and 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15196","15196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426749","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many aircraft owned by each service branch of the armed forces are leased to private businesses; and how much is paid to each such branch in respect of such leases.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15199","15199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426750","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2015 to Question 13951, which foreign military awards have been approved for members of the UK armed forces to wear; and what criteria are applied in determining such approval.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15238","15238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426751","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) current and (b) former members of the UK armed forces have been awarded the NATO Africa Medal.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15240","15240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426752","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2015 to Question 14252, what estimate he has made of his Department's likely strength of civilian personnel based in Scotland on 1 April (a) 2016 and (b) 2020 for each top level budget.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15230","15230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426753","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK personnel have served in UN peacekeeping missions in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15232","15232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426754","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on HMS Artful.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15292","15292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426755","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when HMS Artful is planned to be in active service.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15293","15293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426756","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans the Government has for the decommissioning of (a) HMS Torbay, (b) HMS Trenchant, (c) HMS Talent and (d) HMS Triumph.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15294","15294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426757","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the seaworthiness is of (a) HMS Torbay, (b) HMS Trenchant, (c) HMS Talent and (d) HMS Triumph.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15295","15295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426758","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Royal Navy plans to adhere to the 12-nautical mile territorial limit proclaimed by China around the Subi and Mischief reefs in the Spratly archipelago; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15272","15272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426759","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15341","15341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426760","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of his Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps he has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments that have been carried out; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15331","15331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426761","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on maintenance aboard HMS (a) Torbay, (b) Trenchant, (c) Talent and (d) Triumph in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15288","15288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426762","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the seaworthiness is of HMS (a) Astute and (b) Ambush.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15289","15289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426763","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel have been trained aboard HMS (a) Astute and (b) Ambush.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15290","15290"
