"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11990","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times Ministers of his Office have attended the inter-ministerial group on drugs since May 2010.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161577","161577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11991","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times Ministers of his Department have attended the inter-ministerial group on drugs since May 2010.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161578","161578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11992","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times Ministers of his Department have attended the inter-ministerial group on drugs since May 2010.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161579","161579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11993","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many times Ministers of his Department have attended the inter-ministerial group on drugs since May 2010.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161581","161581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11994","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support her Department has given to universities to help implement the Prevent strategy; and what steps she has taken to monitor implementation.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161592","161592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11995","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times the inter-ministerial group on drugs has met since May 2010; how many times more than four Ministers have been present; and how many times the agenda has included (a) drugs education, (b) drug prevention, (c) the role of Public Health England, (d) new psychoactive substances and (e) co-operation between criminal justice and health bodies.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161582","161582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11996","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding his Department has allocated to universities in order to deliver the Prevent strategy; and which universities have received such funding.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161593","161593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11997","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Hizb-ut-Tahrir is active on UK university campuses; and what assessment she has made of the level of any such activity.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161583","161583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11998","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times Ministers of his Department have attended the inter-ministerial group on drugs since May 2010.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161580","161580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11999","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding has been provided to Greenwich Council under the Prevent programme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161585","161585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12000","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentice (a) starts and (b) completions there were in Hull during each of the last four years for which information is available; and in what categories these apprenticeship starts and completions were.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161594","161594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12001","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether Greenwich University was one of the 40 universities contacted by his Department in 2009 under the auspices of the Prevent strategy; and whether his Department received evidence that Greenwich University had conducted an assessment of the risk of radicalisation on its campus.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161586","161586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12002","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeship (a) starts and (b) completions in Hull in the last four years were (i) advertised and (ii) taken up by each age group.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161595","161595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12003","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Hull found work lasting more than six months through the Work Programme since it inception; how many such people were aged under 24; and how many such people had a disability.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161596","161596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12004","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many counter-terrorism intelligence officers have been funded through the Prevent strategy in each of the last five years; and how many such officers served in the Metropolitan Police Force.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161584","161584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12005","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Greenwich University had a Prevent strategy agreed with her Department; and whether it had a dedicated police liaison officer to assist with its implementation.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161587","161587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12006","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what work she has undertaken to create better links between universities, colleges, local authorities and communities engaged in Prevent work.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161588","161588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12007","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding her Department has provided to the National Union of Students to implement the Prevent strategy.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161589","161589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12008","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time for an employment and support allowance appeal was in (a) the UK and (b) Hull for each of the last 24 months; and what proportion of such appeals were successful.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161597","161597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12009","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Prevent strategy regional champions are currently in post; and what assessment she has made of their work.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161590","161590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12010","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which police forces have agreed Prevent strategy programmes with universities.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161591","161591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/163","2013-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what powers he plans to devolve to the proposed North East Combined Authority from 1 April 2014 to enable it to promote better transport, skills and economic development.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161551","161551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the carbon footprint created by the expected greater trade between the US and the EU as a result of the agreement made at the G8 meeting at Lough Erne; and if the Government will conduct an environmental impact assessment of that agreement.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161508","161508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Prime Minister's speech of 14 June 2013 at No. 10 Downing Street, if he will publish in full the evidential basis for the Prime Minister's statement that the Syrian government has used chemical weapons against Syrian people.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161616","161616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3028","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the Palestinian Authority about salaries paid to Palestinian prisoners in Israeli prisons.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161565","161565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3043","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the Israeli government about salaries paid to Palestinian prisoners in Israeli prisons by the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161564","161564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3130","2013-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the name is of each housing initiative announced by the Government since May 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161538","161538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3131","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of unemployed people gained access to work under the Work Programme in each month of its existence.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161539","161539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3132","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much was allocated to seaside towns by each regional development agency in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161540","161540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3133","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) failed and (b) underperforming (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools there were in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161541","161541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3134","2013-06-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 May 2013, Official Report, columns 51-2W, on coastal areas: regeneration, when the Sea Change programme ended; and what the name was of its successor.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161542","161542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3142","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of levels of honeybees in colonies; if he will take steps to support bee farmers whose colonies have suffered losses to restock; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161493","161493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3143","2013-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish figures for the number of wage incentive payments being made to employers through the Youth Contract.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161495","161495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3144","2013-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish the caseload figures for the universal credit pathfinder.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161496","161496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3145","2013-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Work Programme providers have been put on special measures as a result of poor performance in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161497","161497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3146","2013-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the extent to which Youth Contract wage incentive payments are made to employers who would not have otherwise taken on a young employee.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161498","161498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3151","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of resources available to Companies House to enable it to compile and administer the register of beneficial ownership of UK companies which is to be created following the commitment by the Prime Minister at the G8 summit at Lough Erne; when he expects the first such register to be completed; and what public access to the register he expects to be available.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161510","161510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3152","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons the UK is advocating that India as a non-signatory to the Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty should be admitted to the Nuclear Suppliers Group; and if he will (a) place in the Library and (b) post on his Department's website the paper recently presented on behalf of the UK to the annual meeting of the Nuclear Suppliers Group in Prague.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161511","161511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3153","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to bring forward proposals to make bearer shares illegal.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161514","161514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3154","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what funding he plans to devolve to the proposed North East Combined Authority from 1 April 2014 to enable it to promote better transport, skills and economic development.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161550","161550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3155","2013-06-25","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will list (a) the members of the Executive Board of the UK Council on Child Internet Safety since May 2010 and (b) the dates of each board meeting each such member has attended.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161561","161561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3156","2013-06-24","Wales Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, when he plans to announce the Government's response to the Commission on Devolution in Wales Part 1 Report; and what the reason is for the time taken to respond.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161567","161567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3157","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with his Welsh counterpart regarding the status of GCSEs in Wales and the introduction of I-levels in England.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161568","161568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3158","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with his Welsh counterpart regarding plans for the new Menai Science Park, Bangor.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161569","161569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3159","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of reasons for differences in attainment levels between schools in rural communities and schools in large cities.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161622","161622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3160","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to improve attainment levels of children entitled to free shcool meals.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161623","161623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3161","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects construction work to commence on electrification of the North Transpennine rail route.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161617","161617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3162","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the benefit-cost ratio was in his Department's final business case for the Northern Hub project.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161618","161618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3163","2013-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Portas Review on the future of high streets, published in December 2011, what progress has been made on enabling successful business improvement districts (BIDs) to take on more powers and responsibilities and become Super BIDs.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161624","161624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3164","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the pupil premium; and what methodology was used for that assessment.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161619","161619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3165","2013-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Portas Review on the future of high streets, published in December 2011, what progress has been made on bringing forward legislative proposals to allow landlords to become high street investors by contributing to their local business improvement district.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161625","161625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3166","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the correlation between students who are entitled to free school meals and those who go on to (a) further and higher education and (b) apprenticeships.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161620","161620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3167","2013-06-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what information her Department holds on the cost to English Heritage of running Heritage open days in 2013.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161653","161653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3168","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether any officials of his Department have visited schools in (a) Cumbria, (b) West Cumbria and (c) Copeland constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161626","161626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3169","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of correlations between educational attainment levels and (a) location within a rural community, (b) access to extra-curricular activities and (c) other lifestyle factors.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161621","161621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3170","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what amount of investment qualified for Community Investment Tax Relief in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161606","161606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3171","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many public sector employees used payroll giving in (a) 2011 and (b) 2012.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161607","161607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3172","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of her Department's suppliers are social enterprises.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161608","161608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3173","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2013, Official Report, column 455W, on Members: correspondence, if he will make it his policy to reopen the HM Revenue and Customs enquiry centres, closed as part of the pilot scheme, if such a reopening is supported in the public consultation.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161609","161609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3174","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many community interest companies were created in 2012.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161610","161610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3175","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many community development finance institutions received community investment tax relief in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161611","161611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3176","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to prevent female recruits at the Afghan National Army Officer Academy suffering sexual harassment.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161633","161633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3177","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils in schools in England were referred to a pupil referral unit in 2011-12.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161637","161637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3178","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received from those who represent victims of professional negligence on the effectiveness of professional insurance schemes.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161638","161638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3179","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many visitors visited tax exempt heritage assets in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161639","161639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3180","2013-06-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the English Heritage open day scheme.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161640","161640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3181","2013-06-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many open days there are annually in the English Heritage open day scheme.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161641","161641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3182","2013-06-25","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the number and value of tax exempt heritage assets which are (a) land, buildings and their contents, (b) works of art and (c) collections of art.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161654","161654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3183","2013-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the amount that will be spent on universal credit in (a) this year and (b) each of the next four financial years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161656","161656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3184","2013-06-25","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department will continue to be the lead Department on child internet safety.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161664","161664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3185","2013-06-25","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cataract operations were performed in NHS hospitals in 2012-13.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161657","161657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3186","2013-06-25","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether patients who opted out of the Summary Care Record will be required to opt out again from the General Practice Extraction Service.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161658","161658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3187","2013-06-25","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which serious case reviews have been published since 10 June 2010, by (a) date, (b) subject and (c) commissioning local safeguarding children's board.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161665","161665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3188","2013-06-25","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to undertake a public information campaign prior to the commencement of the General Practice Extraction Service.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161659","161659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3189","2013-06-25","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which serious case reviews are currently commissioned but unpublished.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161666","161666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3190","2013-06-25","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which serious case reviews have been produced since 10 June 2010 but are subject to (a) a request not to publish and (b) an exemption from the obligation to publish.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161667","161667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3191","2013-06-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many times she and Ministers of her Department have met officials of S4C to discuss future funding arrangements since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161627","161627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3192","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on the self-regulation of professional bodies; and what assessment he has made of the efficacy of professional insurance schemes.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161629","161629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3193","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the training provided by UK forces to recruits at the Afghan National Army Officer Academy will include training on (a) the law on the Elimination of Violence Against Women and (b) UN Security Council Resolution 1325.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161630","161630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3194","2013-06-25","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what minimum requirement he has placed on public access to tax exempt heritage assets.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161669","161669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3195","2013-06-25","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average number of days the public had access to tax exempt heritage assets was in (a) 2005, (b) 2010 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161670","161670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3196","2013-06-25","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with (a) Ofsted and (b) other organisations on possible links between entitlement to free school meals and low attainment levels; and what steps he is taking to address such factors.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161677","161677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3197","2013-06-25","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he takes to ensure that children who are falling below expected attainment levels in schools otherwise rated by Ofsted as outstanding are receiving appropriate support.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161678","161678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3198","2013-06-25","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests for terrorism offences there have been in each police force area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161691","161691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3199","2013-06-25","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests for drugs offences there have been in each police force area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161692","161692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3200","2013-06-25","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how the pupil premium will be used to improve the education of children attending schools rated by Ofsted  as outstanding.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161679","161679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3201","2013-06-25","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the cost-effectiveness of Bedfordshire Police.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161693","161693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3202","2013-06-25","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average number of police officers is per head of population in each police force in England and Wales.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161694","161694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3203","2013-06-25","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with (a) Ofsted  and (b) other organisations on differences in attainment levels between children in cities and children in rural communities.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161680","161680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3204","2013-06-25","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of the relative attainment levels of students in inner city schools and those in schools in rural areas and coastal towns.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161681","161681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3205","2013-06-25","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the most recent annual average level of serious and acquisitive crime per 1,000 population in each police force in England and Wales is.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161695","161695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3206","2013-06-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what advice his Department issues on the provision of boxing in prisons and young offenders' institutions.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161697","161697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3207","2013-06-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average young offender cost the Exchequer in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161698","161698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3208","2013-06-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average prisoner cost the Exchequer in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161699","161699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3213","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the terms of the tax exempt heritage assets regime were last reviewed.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161642","161642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3214","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the owners of tax exempt heritage assets are required to loan them to national or local galleries and museums.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161643","161643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3215","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he records the number of visits by the public to each tax exempt heritage asset.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161644","161644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3216","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the tax exempt heritage assets as a contribution to public enjoyment of heritage assets.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161645","161645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3217","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what reports he has received from the Office for Nuclear Regulation on its special risk assessment of the pressure vessel of the Sizewell B pressurised water reactor conducted following the serious flaws found in two Belgian PWR pressure vessels at Doel 3 and Thiange 2.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161649","161649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3218","2013-06-24","Prime Minister","2013-06-20","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions he had with President Putin of Russia on nuclear weapons and nuclear disarmament at the bilateral meeting on 16 June 2013.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161650","161650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3219","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the role of UK Financial Investments (UKFI) was in determining the amount of compensation received by Stephen Hester as outgoing Chief Executive of RBS; and whether the compensation paid to Mr Hester had to be authorised by UKFI.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161651","161651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3220","2013-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have claimed universal credit at Ashton-under-Lyne jobcentre since 29 April 2013.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161707","161707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3221","2013-06-27","Department for International Development","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what processes are in place to ensure that UK aid to the Palestinian Authority is not used to pay salaries to Palestinian prisoners in Israeli prisons convicted of terror offences.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161708","161708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3225","2013-06-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what technical expertise her Department has to advise Ministers on internet matters.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161687","161687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3226","2013-06-25","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff earned less than the living wage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161700","161700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5577","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Network Rail about (a) the closure to cyclists of the crossing of the Clacton branch railway line which gives access to the grounds of the University of Essex from the Wivenhoe Trail and (b) similar closures by Network Rail in other parts of the country.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161562","161562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5578","2013-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance he has given to local authorities on the granting of discretionary housing benefit to households which include a resident who has had an organ transplant; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161668","161668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5579","2013-06-25","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on  implementing the principles of the Armed Forces Covenant in respect of members of the armed forces from Commonwealth countries who are obliged to leave the armed forces on the grounds of medical discharge.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161671","161671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5882","2013-06-24","Women and Equalities","2013-06-20","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2013, Official Report, columns 243-4W, on rape: victims support schemes, how the £1,085,000 funding of rape crisis centres was disbursed.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161570","161570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6273","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the environmental effect of increasing the speed limit on motorways to 80 mph.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161573","161573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6274","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of accidents that will potentially be prevented as a result of the introduction of new penalty notices for misuse of the middle lane of motorways.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161634","161634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6275","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department plans to issue on the enforcement of new penalty notices for misuse of the middle lane on motorways.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161635","161635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6415","2013-06-25","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual cost to the public purse is of the Friends and Family Test.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161673","161673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6416","2013-06-25","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the clinical directors for cancer strategic clinical networks have been appointed.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161674","161674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6417","2013-06-25","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he proposes that improvements on cancer patient experience made by providers and commissioners will be rewarded financially.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161675","161675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6418","2013-06-25","HM Treasury","2013-06-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on the importance of maintaining support for medical research charities.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161672","161672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6724","2013-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 24 April 2013, Official Report, columns 928-9W, on criminal proceedings, what the average mean number of days from offence to completion was (a) in each region and (b) in total for (i) magistrates and (ii) Crown courts in England and Wales in (A) 2011-12 and (B) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161701","161701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/68","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make the possession of pornography depicting rape a criminal offence.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161563","161563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6948","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in Barnsley East constituency are employed in the construction sector.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161556","161556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6949","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in Barnsley East constituency are employed in the agriculture sector.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161557","161557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6950","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Barnsley East constituency and (b) Barnsley Local Authority have had access to financial support from the new enterprise allowance to date.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161558","161558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6951","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Barnsley East constituency and (b) Barnsley local authority area have had access to mentoring through the new enterprise allowance to date.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161559","161559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6952","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in Barnsley East constituency are employed in the manufacturing sector.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161560","161560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6975","2013-07-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the role of supporters' trusts in improving governance of football clubs.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161521","161521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7028","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what written communication he has received from the European Commission on criteria under which field trials for bovine TB vaccination can proceed.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161646","161646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7029","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding he has made available for the development of an oral TB vaccine for badgers in each of the last three years; and what funding he plans to make available for this purpose in each of the next two years.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161647","161647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7030","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the total cost including policing of the badger cull programme for each badger killed.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161648","161648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7104","2013-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that households which consume small amounts of electricity are not adversely affected by Ofgem's decision that all electricity tariffs must include a standing charge.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161676","161676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7266","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions his Department has had about the RSPCA's charitable status since May 2010.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161554","161554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7267","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations he made to the RSPCA after paragraph 96 of the Adult Court Bench Book was amended in 2010.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161612","161612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7268","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what representations he made to the RSPCA after paragraph 96 of the Adult Court Bench Book was amended in 2010.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161613","161613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7269","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much legal aid the RSPCA claimed in (a) the five years prior to 2010 and (b) in each year since.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161614","161614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7270","2013-06-24","Attorney General","2013-06-20","To ask the Attorney General, how many claims for trespass and wrongful detention of property have been brought against the RSPCA since 2010.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161615","161615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7271","2013-06-24","Attorney General","2013-06-20","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions for offences of cruelty to animals were brought by (a) the Crown Prosecution Service and (b) the Royal Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals in the five years prior to the amendment of paragraph 96 of the Adult Court Bench Book in November/December 2010 and in each year since.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161571","161571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7372","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what records are held by his Department on the number of NHS staff who have criminal convictions.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161492","161492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7563","2013-06-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many horses were slaughtered in UK abattoirs, by horse passport issuing agency, in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161519","161519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7719","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the consequences of closing Corby ambulance station on the ability of the ambulance trust to meet the eight and 19 minute targets.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161552","161552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7768","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take to implement the commitment in the Prime Minister's recent G8 communiqué statement to tackle the illegal trafficking of protected or endangered wildlife species.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161503","161503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7769","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what use his Department makes of social analytics and horizon scanning software to monitor public opinion on the badger cull; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161555","161555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7961","2013-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what written information claimants will receive on the breakdown of their universal credit entitlements; how frequently such information will be provided; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161655","161655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7962","2013-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of increasing the level of universal credit earnings disregard by (a) 10 per cent, (b) 20 per cent and (c) 30 per cent.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161663","161663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7963","2013-06-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department or its agencies have commissioned research into any potential relationship between clusters of betting shops and the prevalence of anti-social behaviour; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161660","161660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7964","2013-06-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of trends in social housing rent arrears since April 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161661","161661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7968","2013-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of introducing a universal credit second earner disregard at (a) 30 per cent and (b) 50 per cent of the first earner disregard.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161662","161662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8373","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letter to the Minister for Immigration dated 13 May 2013, from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Girma Worke and Mrs Nurya Kedir Gobena.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161543","161543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8374","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letter to the Minister for Immigration dated 13 May 2013, from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Rahman.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161544","161544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8375","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letter dated 13 May 2013, from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms Edwige Nadebe Koagne.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161545","161545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8376","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letter to the Minister for Immigration dated 13 May 2013, from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Daniel Olabode Ogun Mulele.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161546","161546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8377","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letter to the Minister for Immigration dated 9 May 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Mohammad Jawas.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161547","161547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8378","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letter dated 9 May 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr M.S. Anjum.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161548","161548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8379","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letter to the Minister for Immigration dated 8 May 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Godfrey Jones.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161549","161549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8774","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how low income households are being encouraged to receive energy efficiency assistance under the Energy Companies Obligation.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161566","161566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8775","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the proportion of money used by energy suppliers under the Carbon Emissions Reduction Target and Community Energy Saving Programme programmes solely for identifying Super Priority Group customers.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161602","161602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8776","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues in other departments about sharing household data with energy suppliers to ensure a strategic approach to tackling fuel poverty.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161603","161603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8777","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether there has been any successful use of data matching to assist energy suppliers in finding households in fuel poverty.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161601","161601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8778","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what calculations he has made of the potential value of matching household incomes and energy performance certificates data to target households who would benefit from the installation of energy efficiency measures.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161604","161604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8779","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether data collected in the 2011 Census, relating to the number of 16 to 18 year olds in the current year and the next 10 years, matches that provided by the Office of National Statistics in its latest sub-national population projections; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161605","161605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8780","2013-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to encourage local authorities to use funds from the Energy Company Obligation to address energy inefficient housing.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161636","161636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8992","2013-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the president-elect of Iran on future relations and the possibility of mutual re-opening of full diplomatic facilities; and if he will make a statement on relations with that country.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161702","161702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8993","2013-06-27","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his estimate is of the number of job losses proposed as part of the Whittington NHS Trust policy of applying for Foundation Trust status.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161703","161703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8994","2013-06-27","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Mayor of London on his views on London's future health needs.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161704","161704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8995","2013-06-27","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the University College Hospital, Royal Free, The Whittington, Barnet General, North Middlesex and Chase Farm on the future plans for accident and emergency and hospital care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161705","161705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8996","2013-06-27","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what date he expects  the Whittington Health Trust to achieve Foundation Trust status.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161706","161706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9141","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Republic of Ireland on the effects of the National Dairy Council of Ireland's new labelling programme on the ability of farmers in Northern Ireland to export their products for sale in the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161516","161516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9269","2013-06-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many apprentices are currently employed by his Department; and how many are aged (a) under 19, (b) 19 to 25, (c) 26 to 30, (d) 31 to 59 and (e) 60 and over.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161686","161686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9270","2013-06-25","Home Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department takes to ensure that Police and Crime Commissioners (PCCs) comply with their legal responsibilities to publish financial information and disclose details of their own interests and allowances; and whether her Department has any plans to publish a list of non-compliant PCCs.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161688","161688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9271","2013-06-25","Department for Education","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will require local authorities to conduct return interviews with all children who run away or go missing from home or care, within 72 hours of a missing incident.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161689","161689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9272","2013-06-25","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) all frontline health professionals are given training on the warning signs of child sexual exploitation and (b) representatives from both primary and secondary care within any local multi-agency combat child sexual exploitation.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161690","161690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9273","2013-06-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many apprenticeships have been created in her Department in (a) Barnsley Central constituency and (b) South Yorkshire in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011 and (iii) 2012.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161696","161696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9376","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the provision of medical care is equal for those with physical and mental disabilities.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161572","161572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9377","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of local authorities dealing with instances of medical negligence against disabled people.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161600","161600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9378","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve health care for the disabled in Mid Bedfordshire constituency.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161632","161632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9379","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what provision is made available to accommodate families that choose to stay beside an ill family member whilst in extended care in hospital.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161631","161631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9575","2013-06-24","Department for International Development","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has made any estimate of the number of people who (a) are killed and (b) suffer an incapacitating disability as a result of road accidents in developing countries.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161506","161506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9576","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support his Department offers British-based sports manufacturers to export their products.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161507","161507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9577","2013-06-24","Department for International Development","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of child poverty in Kailahun province, Sierra Leone.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161509","161509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9578","2013-06-24","Department for International Development","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department provides support to any programmes to improve road safety in developing countries.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161512","161512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9579","2013-06-24","Department for International Development","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has made any assessment of the effect on development of poor road safety.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161513","161513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9706","2013-06-24","Wales Office","2013-06-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has held with ministerial colleagues on the effect on Wales of planned changes to legal aid.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161652","161652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10356","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects the Apprenticeship Pay Survey 2012 to be published.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161299","161299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10357","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken as a result of the follow-up research he commissioned into apprentices' pay, training and working hours.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161300","161300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11","2013-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans the Prime Minister has to meet Mary Portas on the issue of regenerating high streets.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161285","161285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11000","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions bodies of the deceased were not released by the coroner within 28 days of death in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161363","161363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11001","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints his Department received about each local coroner in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161364","161364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11002","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoner-to-prisoner visits there were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161365","161365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11003","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison-to-prison transfer movements there were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161366","161366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11138","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost was of a place in a (a) secure training centre, (b) local authority children's home and (c) young offender institution in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161445","161445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11139","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders were held in a cell, cubicle or room where the number of occupants exceeded its uncrowded capacity on 31 March 2013 in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161446","161446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11140","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been released on parole licence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161447","161447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11141","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what changes in the level of National Offender Management Service staffing at each prison establishment have been achieved as a consequence of the Comprehensive Spending Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161448","161448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11142","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) men and (b) women were remanded in custody in each month of the last three years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161449","161449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11345","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on retrospective increases in interest rates on existing student loans.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161216","161216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11346","2013-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2013, Official Report, column 138W, on fire services, which procurement routes would permit a fire and rescue authority acting as a commissioner to not open up to competitive tender the services that would be delivered by a spun-out fire brigade public service mutual.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161314","161314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11347","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of ease of access to postgraduate education for students from low-income backgrounds.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161278","161278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11348","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment the Mutuals Taskforce has made of the introduction of procurement options that would permit commissioners to not open to competitive tender the services delivered by a spun-out public service mutual.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161298","161298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11479","2013-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what financial support the Government has given to holocaust memorial groups in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Mark Reckless","Mark Reckless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161256","161256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11593","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that a coherent approach is being taken towards the international sale of arms; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161408","161408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11594","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to attempt to reduce the number of offences committed by individuals who have previously served a prison sentence.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161428","161428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11595","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what role the British Forces Broadcasting Service currently plays in civilian life; and whether he expects this role to change in the next five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161409","161409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11596","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what involvement his Department has had with the VIRTUS combat body armour project; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161419","161419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11597","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effects of the 2011 summer riots on crime statistics in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161429","161429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11598","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the number of prisoners over the age of 60 in the last 20 years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161430","161430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11599","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to protect vehicles from blast attacks, particularly those that target the sides of vehicles.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161420","161420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11600","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the needs of older prisoners compared to younger inmates.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161431","161431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11601","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the rate of private sector employment growth.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161421","161421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11602","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of pensions triple lock on pensioners.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161422","161422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11603","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the prevalence of fly-tipping; and if he will commission a review of steps to prevent it.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161423","161423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11604","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the (a) take up and (b) performance of academies in Romford constituency.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161424","161424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11605","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of policing reforms on community policing.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161425","161425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11606","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health to ensure that older inmates are given adequate support to meet their health requirements whilst in UK prisons.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161433","161433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11607","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of driving under the influence of illegal substances in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161434","161434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11608","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders currently in prisons have previously served a prison sentence.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161426","161426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11609","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of driving under the influence of illegal substances in the London Borough of Havering in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161435","161435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11610","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the proportion of re-offenders in UK prisons over the last 20 years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161427","161427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11611","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the UK's business competitiveness.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161439","161439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11612","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how he plans to increase the number of children taking part in competitive sport at school.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161440","161440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11613","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2013, Official Report, column 241W, on reorganisation, how the new Operating Model will provide transparent processes and improved communications.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161467","161467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11614","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to introduce tougher sentences for those caught driving under the influence of illegal substances.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161436","161436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11745","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2013, Official Report, column 20W, on the Arctic, what assessment he has made of the likelihood of the statistical model used by Meier et al. relative to a driftless autoregressive integrated model.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161269","161269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11783","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many sanctions have been applied to claimants in each quarter since 1 April 2012 in each parliamentary constituency in South East Wales.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161444","161444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3007","2013-06-24","House of Commons Commission","2013-06-19","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many written parliamentary questions were tabled on each of the last 100 sitting days.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161209","161209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3008","2013-06-24","House of Commons Commission","2013-06-19","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many written parliamentary questions were tabled on average on each sitting day in each of the last five parliamentary years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161210","161210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3014","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effects of victim personal statements at Parole Board hearings; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161290","161290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3015","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) administrative and (b) management costs each NHS trust in Essex incurred in each year since 2009; and what proportion of each trust's total expenditure those costs represented.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161301","161301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3016","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the annual cost of the Prison Library Service to the public purse is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161304","161304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3017","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) managers and (b) administrative staff were employed in each NHS trust in Essex in each year since 2009; and what proportion of the total staff of each trust each figure represents.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161305","161305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3018","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners borrowed books through the Prison Library Service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161306","161306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3019","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referrals were made by each police force in England and Wales to the National Ballistics Intelligence Service in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161362","161362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3020","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what definition his Department uses for an extremist when allocating military and non-military aid in Syria.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161367","161367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3021","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the total number of (a) people and (b) people described by his Department as extremists fighting in Syria against government forces.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161368","161368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3022","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2013, Official Report, column 531W, on West Coast Railway Line, what assessment he has made of the effect on the (a) UK and (b) Scottish economies of the deterioration of the public performance measure.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161370","161370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3023","2013-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has for future accountability arrangements for fire and rescue services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161404","161404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3024","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the Government has for future accountability arrangements for ambulance services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161405","161405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3025","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of introducing zero-rate VAT for small and medium-sized enterprise care service providers purchasing specialist care equipment.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161253","161253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3026","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average level of debt was for customers disconnected by their (a) energy and (b) gas supplier in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161254","161254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3027","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the numbers of disabled people likely to return to work as a consequence to changes to disability benefits and the Work Programme.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161255","161255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3029","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of introducing zero-rate VAT for care service providers purchasing specialist care equipment.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161257","161257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3030","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many autistic children whose families reside in Luton access care outside of the borough.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161263","161263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3031","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many households in Luton will fall into the poverty bracket following the implementation of universal credit.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161265","161265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3032","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she last met the Director of Public Prosecutions to discuss human trafficking.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161267","161267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3033","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing the Australian system of cost-sharing between government and the horticultural industry for tree health and plant biosecurity measures in the UK.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161268","161268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3034","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners responded to the consultation on the Victims' Code of Conduct; and if he will make such responses public.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161271","161271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3035","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners responded to public consultations run by his Department in the last year.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161272","161272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3036","2013-06-24","Department for International Development","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many people (a) applied to and (b) participated in the International Citizen Service programme in the last three years; and how many such people applied from addresses in (i) Scotland, (ii) England, (iii) Wales and (iv) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161311","161311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3037","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of people on the Violent Sex Offender Register (a) are currently in prison, (b) have been to prison in the last year and (c) have never been to prison.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161273","161273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3038","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to public funds is of the replacement on security grounds of current vehicle registration certificates by the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency; whether this change was necessitated by a theft of V5C forms; and what steps have been taken to recover these costs.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161296","161296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3039","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many instances of work-related stress were reported by prison staff in the last year.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161274","161274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3040","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will provide guidance to UK tour operators operating in the Occupied Palestinian Territories on the status and legality of Israeli settlement businesses.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161297","161297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3041","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of the population in each probation area are on the Violent Sex Offender Register.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161275","161275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3042","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which people on the Violent Sex Offender Register currently reside in Witham constituency.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161276","161276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3044","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people per 100,000 with HIV who are (a) gay and (b) not gay.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161283","161283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3045","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the effect of freshly squeezed citrus fruit juice on tooth enamel and consequent effects on public health.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161287","161287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3046","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2013, Official Report, column 1071W, on blood: donors, whether the 12 month ban on men who have had sex with men donating blood also applies to donations from those who are stem cell matches for people with illnesses who could benefit from receiving a donation.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161288","161288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3047","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 26 March 2013, Official Report, column 1069W, on Climate Change Levy: bricks, what progress he has made on setting out the scope of the ceramics industry to be exempt from the Climate Change Levy.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161280","161280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3048","2013-06-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2013, Official Report, column 155W, on the Energy Companies Obligation (ECO), if he will take steps to collect data on the number of (a) oil-fired boilers and (b) LPG-fired boilers installed under the ECO scheme.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161317","161317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3049","2013-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent representations he has received on the decision to allow Tesco to build a superstore in Margate.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161282","161282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3050","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to upgrade the A1 North of Tyne and Wear.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161348","161348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3051","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many speed awareness courses were undertaken in each (a) region and (b) constituent part of the UK in each of the last three years; and what the cost of undertaking such a course was in each such area in each such year.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161338","161338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3052","2013-06-24","Department for International Development","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether health will be a priority within the post-2015 development framework.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161349","161349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3053","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of sanctions against Iranian oil and gas companies.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161319","161319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3054","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to engage with Central Asian states on transition in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161330","161330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3055","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which advertising agency prepared his Department's recent campaign for the FRANK website; and if he will publish the brief given to that agency on the preparation of the campaign advertising.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161350","161350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3056","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice his Department gives to the public about the effects of citrus fruit juice on oral hygiene.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161331","161331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3057","2013-06-24","Department for International Development","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent estimate her Department has made of the number of children worldwide who are employed in hazardous work conditions; and what steps her Department is taking to reduce that number.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161320","161320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3058","2013-06-24","Department for International Development","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department provides to India to achieve universal health coverage.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161351","161351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3059","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the development of democracy, human rights and the rule of law in Belarus.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161321","161321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3081","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 20  March 2013, Official Report, columns 714-15W, on Human Papillomavirus, if he will make it his policy to ensure that parents of children about the receive the HPV vaccination are given a copy of the vaccine manufacturer's own patient information leaflet prior to signing a consent form for vaccination.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Mr Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161339","161339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3082","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of his Department's suppliers are social enterprises.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161322","161322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3083","2013-06-24","Department for International Development","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's policy is on the creation of a standalone development goal for universal health coverage.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161352","161352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3084","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the decision of President Karzai to boycott the peace talks in Qatar.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161340","161340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3085","2013-06-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many of her Department's suppliers are social enterprises.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161323","161323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3086","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department provides to local Jobcentre Plus offices on delivering welfare advice and employment-focused programmes through children's centres in their area.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161333","161333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3087","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many of his Department's suppliers are social enterprises.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161324","161324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3088","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many of his Department's suppliers are social enterprises.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161325","161325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3089","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many of his Department's suppliers are social enterprises.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161326","161326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3090","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implementation of UN Resolution 1591 with regards to Sudan and South Sudan.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161341","161341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3091","2013-06-24","Department for International Development","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what technical support her Department offers to developing countries to held them achieve universal health coverage.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161353","161353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3092","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of prisoners in England and Wales awaiting placement on sex offender treatment programmes and the number of places available on such courses annually.","Biography information for James Wharton","James Wharton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161334","161334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3093","2013-06-24","Department for International Development","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what private health insurance projects her Department has supported in developing countries.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161354","161354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3094","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what requests for discussions he has received from his counterpart in the Scottish Government on its potential involvement in the planned high speed rail networks.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161342","161342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3095","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides to clinical commissioning groups on the provision of services through children's centres in their area.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161335","161335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3096","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of those sentenced for retail theft as of 21 May 2013 had more than (a) one, (b) two, (c) five and (d) 10 prior convictions.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161355","161355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3097","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the future viability of UK defence policy if the costs of new nuclear weapons platforms developments were met wholly from his Department's budget.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161343","161343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3098","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what amount his Department and its agencies spent on providing services through children's centres in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161336","161336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3099","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Retail Crime Strategy Group (a) has met since May 2010, (b) last met and (c) next plans to meet.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161356","161356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3100","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on ensuring that individuals with education and health care plans have support and access in to apprenticeships.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161344","161344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3101","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was spent in total on child benefit for families with (a) one, (b) two and (c) three or more children in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161373","161373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3102","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what amount his Department and its agencies spent on providing services through children's centres in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161337","161337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3103","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on the provision of landing slots at Heathrow Airport for use by flights to the UK's regional airports.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161346","161346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3104","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the budget of Bedfordshire Police was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161382","161382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3105","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police community support officers Bedfordshire Police is projected to have by the end of (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161383","161383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3106","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers of each rank Bedfordshire Police is projected to have by the end of (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161384","161384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3107","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many penalty notices were issued for retail theft of under £200 in each of the last five years; and how many notices were subsequently paid in full.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161358","161358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3108","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) police officers of each rank, (b) police community support officers and (c) police staff there were in Bedfordshire police force area in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161385","161385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3109","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people in (a) Peterborough constituency and (b) Peterborough City Council area affected by changes in housing benefit as a result of the under-occupancy penalty; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161381","161381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3110","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of his Department's efforts to open up Government procurement to British small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161359","161359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3111","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he will receive the results of the evaluation of the pilot badger cull.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161360","161360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3112","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will report to Parliament after the pilot badger cull is complete and an evaluation of its effectiveness has been carried out.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161361","161361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3113","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobs were created in each of the principal seaside towns under the Future Jobs Fund in each year of that Fund's existence.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161396","161396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3114","2013-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much was spent through the Working Neighbourhoods Fund in each of the principal seaside towns in each year of the Fund's existence.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161397","161397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3115","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2013, Official Report, columns 595-6W on asylum, if she will provide the relevant figures for the Intake key performance indicator from 2010 to 2013.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161398","161398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3116","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of whether the website of the FRANK drug information campaign is fully compliant with Article 33 of the Convention on the Rights of the Child; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161402","161402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3117","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the treatment by the Burmese Army of ethnic minority peoples in that country.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161347","161347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3118","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Saudi Arabian counterpart on the execution of seven prisoners for armed robbery in that country on 13 March 2013.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161393","161393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3119","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Saudi Arabian counterpart on that country's human rights record.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161394","161394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3120","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps he has taken to encourage people from disadvantaged backgrounds to enter higher education.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161395","161395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3121","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2013, Official Report, column 1077W, on human trafficking, what amount was awarded by government grant to the (a) Refugee Council and (b) Children's Society for the purpose of scoping the practical care arrangements for trafficked children.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161411","161411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3122","2013-06-24","Department for International Development","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has reduced budget support for health initiatives.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161412","161412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3123","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospitals only allow admissions through accident and emergency; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of such a policy on the stress levels of (a) staff and (b) patients.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161413","161413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3124","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what funding the Government has allocated to BBC Turkish Services since 6 May 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161414","161414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3125","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been killed by cattle in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161415","161415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3126","2013-06-24","Attorney General","2013-06-19","To ask the Attorney General, how many indictable-only offences were disposed of by the Crown Prosecution Service by a (a) formal caution and (b) conditional caution in 2012-13 and in each of the preceding seven years by offence category.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161441","161441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3127","2013-06-24","Attorney General","2013-06-19","To ask the Attorney General, how many indictable-only offences were disposed of by the Crown Prosecution Service by a final warning in 2012-13 and in each of the preceding seven years by offence category.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161442","161442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3128","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many specialists work on human trafficking in the UK Border Agency; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161459","161459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3129","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who monitors the performance of the UK national rapporteur on human trafficking.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161466","161466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3135","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2013, Official Report, columns 455-6W, on Revenue and Customs, how many of the additional staff are (a) directly employed civil servants, (b) directly employed temporary staff and (c) externally employed staff through an employment agency; and what the terms and conditions are of all the newly-hired additional staff.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161480","161480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3136","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Hungarian counterpart on the treatment of the Roma minority in Hungary.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161481","161481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3137","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how the UK's industrial production has changed as a proportion of GDP in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161470","161470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3138","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to implement the recommendations of the Review of the Regulation of Cosmetic Interventions led by NHS medical director Professor Sir Bruce Keogh.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161482","161482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3139","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, by what criteria the pupil premium will be set under universal credit.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161483","161483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3140","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2013, Official Report, column 304W, on food banks, if he will take steps to record all referrals made by government agencies for people to receive emergency food aid or visit food banks.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161472","161472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3141","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the current political situation in Turkey is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161485","161485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3147","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2013, Official Report, column 1077W, on human trafficking, what the name is of each other member of the inter-ministerial team on human trafficking; and how many and what proportion of meetings each has attended since the team's establishment.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161452","161452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3148","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will issue guidance to decision-makers about the requirement to consider all relevant evidence in work capability assessments and to provide a copy of that evidence to tribunals.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161453","161453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3149","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department will commence the review to assess the feasibility of introducing a national choice offer for people who wish to die at home.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161457","161457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3150","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the role of cancer strategic clinical networks in promoting equality and reducing inequalities in cancer care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161458","161458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32","2013-06-24","Department for International Development","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the UK has taken to champion a strong EU budget and to hold other countries accountable for their aid promises.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161450","161450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38","2013-06-24","Department for International Development","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support the Government is providing to Syrian women and children in refugee camps.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161486","161486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5494","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many teenage pregnancies there have been in Cannock Chase constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161208","161208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5495","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many days were missed due to unauthorised absence from schools in (a) Cannock Chase constituency and (b) Staffordshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161258","161258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5496","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) small and (b) medium-sized businesses that were operating in (i) Cannock Chase constituency and (ii) Staffordshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161259","161259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5497","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children in (a) Staffordshire and (b) Cannock Chase constituency were eligible for free schools meals in (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161260","161260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5498","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many new companies were started  in (a) Cannock Chase constituency and (b) Staffordshire in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161261","161261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5499","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many homes in Cannock Chase constituency have received insulation under his Department's programmes in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161262","161262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5500","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff in Staffordshire were paid over (a) £50,000, (b) £65,738 and (c) £100,000 in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161277","161277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5569","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish the School Food Plan.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161203","161203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5642","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many claimants living in each constituency in Wales had to wait more than six weeks for their appeals to be heard against decisions on benefits entitlement made following work capability assessments carried out in the financial year 2012-13.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161211","161211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5644","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many claimants living in each parliamentary constituency in Wales had their appeals heard during the financial year 2012-13 against decisions on benefits entitlement made following work capability assessments.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161264","161264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5679","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what expenditure HM Revenue and Customs incurred on Government publicity campaigns to prevent tobacco smuggling in 2011-12 and 2012-13.","Biography information for Stephen Williams","Stephen Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161410","161410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5879","2013-06-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what guidance her Department issues to providers of fibre optic infrastructure to ensure that adequate internet speeds are available in all parts of the UK.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161213","161213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5880","2013-06-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her Department's definition is of the term economically unviable when applied to cabinets that enable fibre optic broadband.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161214","161214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5881","2013-06-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with providers of fibre optic broadband infrastructure on publishing information on economically unviable cabinets.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161215","161215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6171","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2013, Official Report, column 485W, on Colombia, what response he has received from the Colombian Attorney General; if he will place a copy of this response in the Library; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161328","161328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6172","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to reply to the Freedom of Information request from the hon. Member for Bridgend, reference MM/JH/29/04/2013 dated 29 April 2013.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161329","161329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6173","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 May 2013, Official Report, column 495W, on armed forces: sexual offences, what options are available to a commanding officer where they receive allegations relating to sexual offences not listed in schedule 2 to the Armed Forces Act 2006; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161386","161386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6174","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 May 2013, Official Report, column 495W, on armed forces: sexual offences, what forms of redress are available to armed forces personnel who make allegations of sexual offences not listed in schedule 2 to the Armed Forces Act 2006 if a commanding officer (a) decides not to investigate that allegation and (b) does not refer the allegation to the service police; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161387","161387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6175","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 May 2013, Official Report, column 495W, on armed forces: sexual offences, what sanctions against a perpetrator are available to a commanding officer following the conclusion of an investigation of a sexual offence listed in schedule 2 to the Armed Forces Act 2006 which they have undertaken; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161388","161388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6291","2013-06-25","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much has been received under the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002 from those convicted of human trafficking in the last three years; and how much has been paid out to the victims of human trafficking by way of compensation.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161236","161236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6347","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps have been taken to deliver the NHS Mandate objective of making rapid progress in the measuring of and acting upon the patient experience.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161460","161460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6348","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress cancer strategic clinical networks have made in developing their terms of reference; and if he will place in the Library copies of such terms of reference.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161461","161461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6349","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps (a) his Department and (b) NHS England plan to take to deliver improvements in the relational aspects of cancer care.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161462","161462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6350","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations he has received regarding potential amendments to the Hunting Act 2004 in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161463","161463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6351","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to bring forward proposals for a statutory instrument allowing more than two hounds to pursue a fox towards guns under the Hunting Act 2004.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161464","161464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6410","2013-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people claiming (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) income support are problem drug users.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161487","161487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6411","2013-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate expenditure on benefit claimants who are problem drug users.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161488","161488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6412","2013-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who claim (a) employment and support allowance, (b) disability living allowance and (c) incapacity benefit have alcoholism or drug abuse as their main disabling condition.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161489","161489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6413","2013-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the likely number of (a) personal independence payment and (b) employment and support allowance claimants in 2017 with alcoholism or drug abuse as their main disabling condition.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161490","161490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6414","2013-06-25","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many workless lone parent and couple households with (a) six, (b) seven, (c) eight, (d) nine and (e) 10 children claim child tax credit.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161491","161491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6609","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to encourage research on medically unexplained symptoms as part of wider research on ME and chronic fatigue syndrome.","Biography information for Sandra Osborne","Sandra Osborne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161418","161418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6719","2013-06-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2013, Official Report, column 722W, on conditions of employment, if she will require her executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies to confirm whether any staff were retained on zero-hour contracts.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161479","161479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6720","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer to Question 159799, what estimate he has made of the number of new properties built in areas of risk between February 2010 and October 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161476","161476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6721","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer to Question 159799, how much funding he allocated for London's flood defences in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161477","161477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6722","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of tenants in each London borough; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161475","161475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6723","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many members of the board of the (a) Charity Commission and (b) Big Lottery Fund have declared membership of a political party; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161478","161478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6943","2013-06-24","Cabinet Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Big Society community organisers have been trained to date.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161286","161286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6944","2013-06-24","House of Commons Commission","2013-06-19","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross, representing the House of Commons Commission, which specialist advisers to select committees have declared relevant financial interests in the subject matter for which the committee they advise is responsible; and what those declarations were.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161389","161389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6945","2013-06-24","House of Commons Commission","2013-06-19","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross, representing the House of Commons Commission, what the name is of each person who acts in an official capacity as a specialist adviser to a select committee.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161390","161390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6946","2013-06-24","House of Commons Commission","2013-06-19","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross, representing the House of Commons Commission, which specialist advisers to the Defence Select Committee have been issued a photo parliamentary pass.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161391","161391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6947","2013-06-24","House of Commons Commission","2013-06-19","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross, representing the House of Commons Commission, which specialist advisers to the Energy and Climate Change Select Committee have been issued a photo parliamentary pass.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161392","161392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7025","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what reports he has received of pig products entering the UK from other European nations which have not been produced in accordance with the EU law on pig and animal welfare.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161443","161443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7026","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department works with the Home Office to allocate resources to prevent pig products produced to animal welfare standards which do not comply with European law from entering the UK.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161468","161468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7027","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with European Commissioners on welfare and husbandry conditions for pigs in other EU member states.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161437","161437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7129","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to replace the seasonal agricultural workers scheme.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161332","161332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7223","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the future franchising arrangements for South West Trains will be subject to open consultation.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161302","161302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7224","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the criteria are for determing whether a train operating company (a) pays a premium and (b) receives subsidy for running services on the rail network.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161303","161303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7225","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the franchising arrangements for South West Trains will be formally reviewed.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161217","161217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7254","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many suspected victims of trafficking were found in Scotland in each of the last three years; how many traffickers were prosecuted and convicted in Scotland in that period; and what assets belonging to such traffickers were then seized from the UK and overseas.","Biography information for Michael Connarty","Michael Connarty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161357","161357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7365","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the annual total paid out in tax credits is.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161204","161204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7366","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the annual cost is of administering the tax credit system; and how many civil servants are employed in its administration.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161205","161205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7367","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost of raising personal allowance in line with the minimum wage; and what the saving in tax credits payments would be as a result.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161206","161206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7368","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many adults in full-time employment are in receipt of tax credits.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161207","161207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7371","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been paid inaccurately in tax credits in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161416","161416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7559","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total expenditure on (a) equine DNA testing and (b) phenylbutazone testing by (i) local authorities, (ii) Government and (iii) industry has been in 2013.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161380","161380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7560","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2013, Official Report, columns 699-700W, on horses: France, from which country each horse imported from third (non EU) countries was imported from in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161403","161403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7561","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2013, Official Report, columns 782-4W, on agriculture: finance,  what the reasons are for the decrease in the level of funding for Central finance ongoing activity - CAP between 2009-10 and 2011-12.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161473","161473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7562","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2013, Official Report, columns 782-4W, on agriculture: finance,  what the reasons are for the increase in the level of funding to the Food and farming group business support between 2009-10 and 2011-12.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161474","161474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7713","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people employed at (a) Kettering General Hospital and (b) Northampton General Hospital are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161374","161374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7714","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many care assistants in the East Midlands are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161375","161375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7715","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people employed in hospitals in England are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161376","161376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7716","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are employed by her Department on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161407","161407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7717","2013-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on how many people are employed on zero-hours contracts in each local authority in England.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161438","161438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7718","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance or policies his Department issues on the use of zero hours contracts in the NHS.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161469","161469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7954","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his most recent assessment is of the quality of work capability assessments undertaken on behalf of his Department.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161212","161212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7955","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was withheld as a result of benefit sanctions in 2012-13.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161312","161312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7956","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average amount withheld per benefit sanction was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161313","161313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7957","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how he monitors the quality of the work capability assessments carried out on behalf of his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161316","161316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7959","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what performance indicators are included in the contract between his Department and Atos Healthcare for undertaking work capability assessments; and what recent assessment he has made of the performance of Atos under that contract.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161372","161372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8127","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many licence applications the Security Industry Authority refused (a) in total and (b) due to unspent convictions in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011 and (iii) 2012.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161454","161454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8128","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many licence applications the Security Industry Authority granted in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161455","161455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8129","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for licences the Security Industry Authority received in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161456","161456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8161","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2013, Official Report, column 413W, on the Green Deal Scheme, when the second update on the number of Green Deal plans be published.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161291","161291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8162","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2013, Official Report, column 413W, on the Green Deal Scheme, how many staff hours have been spent on producing the first quarterly Official Statistics on Green Deal and Energy Companies Obligation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161292","161292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8163","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2013, Official Report, column 413W, on the Green Deal Scheme, how much the first quarterly Official Statistics on Green Deal and Energy Companies Obligation cost his Department to produce.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161293","161293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8164","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2013, Official Report, column 413W, on the Green Deal Scheme, how many staff have worked to produce the first quarterly Official Statistics on Green Deal and Energy Companies Obligation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161294","161294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8165","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2013, Official Report, column 413W, on the Green Deal Scheme, for what reason the report will only cover the period up to 31 March 2013.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161295","161295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8290","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the suitability for development of the Ashchurch military site and the possible presence of asbestos and unexploded ordnance; what the likely cost of clean-up of the site would be before it could be sold for development; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161406","161406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8291","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the potential sale value of the military site at Ashchurch; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161377","161377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8292","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support is available through the NHS for people suffering from Huntingdon's Disease; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161378","161378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8293","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the available space at Salisbury to potentially accommodate operations currently carried out at Ashchurch military site following the drawdown of forces from Afghanistan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161379","161379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8294","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of people convicted of burglary offences were given custodial sentences in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161484","161484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8399","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much has been gathered under the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002 from those convicted of human trafficking in each of the last three years; and how much has been paid out in compensation to victims of trafficking.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161270","161270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8482","2013-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much of the Coalfield Regeneration Fund has been used to assist companies developing new flood protection technologies; and in which coalfield regions such funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161289","161289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8483","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding his Department has made available for the development of new flood protection technologies in each of the last three years; which specific new technologies have been granted such funding; and which parts of the UK have benefited from that funding.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161318","161318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8494","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding his Department has made available in grants to businesses developing new flood protection technologies in each of the last three years; and in which part of the country businesses in receipt of such grants were based.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161327","161327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8910","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to hire outside consultants to undertake a root and branch analysis to establish the extent of shortcomings in the current UK Trade and Investment structure.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161399","161399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8911","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to replace civil servants at UK Trade and Investment with experienced private sector professionals with commercial experience.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161400","161400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8912","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to provide that UK Trade and Investment in future does not report to the Department of Business, Innovation and Skills and the Foreign and Commonwealth Office but is a standalone body along the lines of the Technology Strategy Board.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161401","161401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9263","2013-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if his Department will report emissions indicators on a consumption, rather than just a production, basis.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161307","161307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9264","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many apprentices are currently employed by his Department; and how many such apprentices are aged (a) under 19, (b) 19 to 25, (c) 26 to 30, (d) 31 to 59 and (e) more than 60.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161308","161308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9265","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to promote easier and cheaper (a) bus use and (b) interchange between bus, metro and train.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161309","161309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9266","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to improve surface connections to major airports.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161310","161310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9268","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of High Speed 2 on UK air travel.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161471","161471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9465","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of public confidence in the legal aid system.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161369","161369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9466","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timetable is for the rollout of universal credit in the London Borough of Brent.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161371","161371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9467","2013-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on the future of HM Prison The Verne; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161315","161315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9534","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what arrangements his Department has made to ensure that the work of its obstructive sleep apnoea working group, established in July 2012, is being continued following the recent NHS reforms.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161266","161266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9572","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dog attacks have been reported to police in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161279","161279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9573","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to tackle dog on dog attacks.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161281","161281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9574","2013-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many reported dog attacks have led to a successful prosecution in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161417","161417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9705","2013-06-24","Wales Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the effect on Wales of Government policies on shale gas extraction.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161284","161284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9746","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many limited liability partnerships (LLPs) have been created since 2000; how many partners have been created in such LLPs in that period; and what their average income is.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161345","161345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9747","2013-06-24","Department for Transport","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to investigate whether BRB (Residuary) Ltd land can be used for cycling routes.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161432","161432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9748","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has set up a national register of girls at risk of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161465","161465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10068","2013-06-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to allow parish councils to make payments by electronic banking; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mel Stride","Mel Stride","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160992","160992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10095","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the recommendations of the report on Children in Israeli Military Detention, published by UNICEF in March 2013.","Biography information for Angie Bray","Angie Bray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161155","161155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10146","2013-06-20","HM Treasury","2013-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the comparative competitiveness of the UK's air passenger duty regime; and what assessment he has made of claims by the British Air Transport Association that the UK's regime ranks 139th globally on this measure.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161070","161070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10266","2013-06-20","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons his Department decided to award a clasp rather than a medal to those who served in Bomber Command.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161080","161080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10267","2013-06-20","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of those who are eligible have applied for the Bomber Command clasp to date; how many of those applications have been (a) rejected and (b) accepted; and what estimate he has made of the number of members of Bomber Command who are ineligible for the clasp.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161077","161077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10331","2013-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the effect of population density on the cost of delivering local government services.","Biography information for Dan Rogerson","Dan Rogerson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161170","161170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10332","2013-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which specific services in the environmental, cultural and protective services block have given rise to additional funding because of the effect of population density in the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Rogerson","Dan Rogerson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161171","161171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10350","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the rise in non-compliance with the minimum wage for apprentices as highlighted in the 2013 Low Pay Commission report into the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161040","161040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10351","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take to tackle non-compliance with the minimum wage for apprentices.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161041","161041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10352","2013-06-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when his Department intends to extend its traineeship programme to young people aged between 20 and 24; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161042","161042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10387","2013-06-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what consideration he has made of the introduction of minimum standards in the provision of natural light in new homes.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160928","160928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10388","2013-06-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what consideration he has made of the introduction of national minimum space standards for all new homes in England.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160929","160929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10389","2013-06-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the size of new homes being built in England.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160927","160927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10561","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has held (a) with his ministerial colleagues and (b) between his Department and the Charity Commission and related bodies about (i) the future of the National Fund and (ii) the possibility of its early application to reduce the national debt.","Biography information for Lord Bruce of Bennachie","Sir Malcolm Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161044","161044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10562","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that deaf people have the opportunity to communicate in British Sign Language with (a) tax, VAT and other officials and  (b) the agencies and public bodies that support his Department.","Biography information for Lord Bruce of Bennachie","Sir Malcolm Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161045","161045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10563","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the US Department of the Treasury webpage that enables US citizens to donate online to reduce the US national debt; and if he will consider introducing a similar page on gov.uk.","Biography information for Lord Bruce of Bennachie","Sir Malcolm Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161047","161047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10564","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, by what means members of the public can make gifts for the reduction of the national debt.","Biography information for Lord Bruce of Bennachie","Sir Malcolm Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161048","161048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10565","2013-06-24","HM Treasury","2013-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many gifts from members of the public were made for the purposes of reducing the national debt in each of the last 10 years; what the (a) nature and (b) value of each gift was; and if he will list the non-monetary gifts.","Biography information for Lord Bruce of Bennachie","Sir Malcolm Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161049","161049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11175","2013-06-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what research his Department has undertaken on the effect of the living wage on employment.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161018","161018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11176","2013-06-20","HM Treasury","2013-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what research his Department has undertaken on the impact of combining increases in the employment allowance and payment of the living wage on (a) small businesses, (b) government receipts, (c) employment and (d) income for the lowest decile and quintile of employed households.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161019","161019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11177","2013-06-20","Department of Health","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the number of employees of East of England Ambulance Trust was whose total remuneration (including pension commitments) was (a) greater than £100,000, (b) between £75,000 and £99,999 and (c) between £50,000 and £74,999 in each of the last three years; and what the total cost of remunerating such employees in each year was.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161020","161020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11178","2013-06-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimates his Department has made of the number of employees who currently earn less than the living wage in (a) Bedford constituency, (b) Greater London and (c) England and Wales other than Greater London.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161021","161021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11179","2013-06-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what research his Department has undertaken on the effect of the living wage on small businesses.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160998","160998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11413","2013-06-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the equality impact of his Department's spending reductions since 2010; whether this assessment has been used to inform his planning ahead of the 2013 Comprehensive Spending Review and with what result; what plans he has to publish the equality impact assessments undertaken by his Department as a result of the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161172","161172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11414","2013-06-20","Cabinet Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the equality impact of his Department's spending reductions since 2010; whether this assessment has been used to inform his planning ahead of the 2013 Comprehensive Spending Review and with what result; what plans he has to publish the equality impact assessments undertaken by his Department as a result of the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161173","161173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11415","2013-06-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the equality impact of his Department's spending reductions since 2010; whether this assessment has been used to inform his planning ahead of the 2013 Comprehensive Spending Review and with what result; what plans he has to publish the equality impact assessments undertaken by his Department as a result of the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161174","161174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11416","2013-06-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the equality impact of her Department's spending reductions since 2010; whether this assessment has been used to inform her planning ahead of the 2013 Comprehensive Spending Review and with what result; what plans she has to publish the equality impact assessments undertaken by her Department as a result of the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161175","161175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11417","2013-06-20","Department for Education","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the equality impact of his Department's spending reductions since 2010; whether this assessment has been used to inform his planning ahead of the 2013 Comprehensive Spending Review and with what result; what plans he has to publish the equality impact assessments undertaken by his Department as a result of the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161176","161176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11418","2013-06-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the equality impact of his Department's spending reductions since 2010; whether this assessment has been used to inform his planning ahead of the 2013 Comprehensive Spending Review and with what result; what plans he has to publish the equality impact assessments undertaken by his Department as a result of the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161177","161177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11419","2013-06-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the equality impact of his Department's spending reductions since 2010; whether this assessment has been used to inform his planning ahead of the 2013 Comprehensive Spending Review and with what result; what plans he has to publish the equality impact assessments undertaken by his Department as a result of the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161178","161178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11420","2013-06-20","Women and Equalities","2013-06-18","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the equality impact of the Government Equalities Office spending reductions since 2010; whether this assessment has been used to inform her planning ahead of the 2013 Comprehensive Spending Review and with what result; what plans she has to publish the equality impact assessments undertaken by her Department as a result of the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161179","161179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11421","2013-06-20","Department of Health","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the equality impact of his Department's spending reductions since 2010; whether this assessment has been used to inform his planning ahead of the 2013 Comprehensive Spending Review and with what result; what plans he has to publish the equality impact assessments undertaken by his Department as a result of the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161180","161180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11422","2013-06-20","Home Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the equality impact of her Department's spending reductions since 2010; whether this assessment has been used to inform her planning ahead of the 2013 Comprehensive Spending Review and with what result; what plans she has to publish the equality impact assessments undertaken by her Department as a result of the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161181","161181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11423","2013-06-20","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the equality impact of his Department's spending reductions since 2010; whether this assessment has been used to inform his planning ahead of the 2013 Comprehensive Spending Review and with what result; what plans he has to publish the equality impact assessments undertaken by his Department as a result of the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161182","161182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11424","2013-06-20","Department for Transport","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the equality impact of his Department's spending reductions since 2010; whether this assessment has been used to inform his planning ahead of the 2013 Comprehensive Spending Review and with what result; what plans he has to publish the equality impact assessments undertaken by his Department as a result of the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161183","161183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11425","2013-06-20","HM Treasury","2013-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the equality impact of his Department's spending reductions since 2010; whether this assessment has been used to inform his planning ahead of the 2013 Comprehensive Spending Review and with what result; what plans he has to publish the equality impact assessments undertaken by his Department as a result of the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161184","161184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11426","2013-06-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the equality impact of his Department's spending reductions since 2010; whether this assessment has been used to inform his planning ahead of the 2013 Comprehensive Spending Review and with what result; what plans he has to publish the equality impact assessments undertaken by his Department as a result of the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161185","161185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11766","2013-06-20","Department for Transport","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish his Department's health impact assessment for the New Lower Thames Crossing proposed option C.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Mr Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161143","161143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/169","2013-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the rate and amount of emissions of refrigerant hydrofluocarbons from (a) gas absorption heat pumps and (b) ground source heat pumps and air source heat pumps powered by electricity.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161113","161113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2032","2013-06-24","Department for Education","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps his Department has taken to protect children from sexual abuse.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160870","160870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2050","2013-06-20","Department for Education","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has identified a shortfall in available (a) education and training places and (b) education places in (i) Yorkshire and (ii) England.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160958","160958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2773","2013-06-20","Home Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what protocols are in place to improve data collection across Europe on human trafficking.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160981","160981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2794","2013-06-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the continuation of the role of the Office of the High Representative for Bosnia-Herzegovina.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161003","161003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2851","2013-06-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the prospects for long-term stability in Bosnia-Herzegovina; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160999","160999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2852","2013-06-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the role of EUFOR in Bosnia-Herzegovina; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161000","161000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2853","2013-06-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which Minister will represent the Government at the 11 July Commemoration of the Srebrenica massacre.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161001","161001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2854","2013-06-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to support Bosnia's Euro - Atlantic Agreement aspirations since 2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 161002","161002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2857","2013-06-20","Department of Health","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) provision and (b) support is in place to enable NHS staff access to physiotherapy services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160839","160839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2858","2013-06-24","Department of Health","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many vending machines in his Department's premises contain snack foods that are high in calories and low in nutritional value.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160846","160846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2859","2013-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the closure of stores and warehouses belonging to members of the Bahá'i community in Hamadan, Iran by government officials; what assessment he has made of the implications of those actions for the 1958 Convention on Discrimination in Respect of Employment and Occupation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160847","160847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2860","2013-06-20","Department of Health","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department provides to women with obstetric fistula.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160930","160930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2861","2013-06-20","Home Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent meetings (a) she and (b) her ministerial colleagues have had with their foreign counterparts on improving international co-operation in tackling human trafficking.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160931","160931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2862","2013-06-20","Home Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the right hon. Member for Berwick-upon-Tweed will receive a reply from the Minister for Immigration to her letters of 4 February 2013 and 15 April 2013 concerning the sponsor's minimum income figure being determined on a national basis.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160949","160949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2863","2013-06-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many small and medium-sized enterprises there were in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) the East Midlands in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160950","160950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2864","2013-06-20","Home Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many domestic violence arrests have been made in Ashfield constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160951","160951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2865","2013-06-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claims were submitted for each benefit in each of the last 12 months for which figures are available; how many claimants applied for such benefits; and what estimate he has made of the number of claimants who applied for more than one benefit in that period.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160939","160939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2866","2013-06-20","Department of Health","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are on waiting lists to receive an organ transplant in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160952","160952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2867","2013-06-20","Cabinet Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the employment rate was in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) the UK in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160953","160953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2868","2013-06-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what amount has been spent and in what categories of expenditure by her Department in Ashfield constituency in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160954","160954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2869","2013-06-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many households in Ashfield constituency are unable to receive a broadband internet connection.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160955","160955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2870","2013-06-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints he has received relating to the performance of Jobcentre Plus offices (a) in Ashfield constituency, (b) in Nottinghamshire and (c) nationally in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160956","160956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2871","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) effectiveness of the Defence Infrastructure Organisation's new competency based application process and (b) the effect of such a process on existing employees in the Organisation.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160962","160962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2872","2013-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the total cost of the redundancy programme at the Defence Infrastructure Organisation in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160963","160963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2873","2013-06-20","Department of Health","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the health hazard or otherwise of secondary smoke inhalation from people using electronic cigarettes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160957","160957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2874","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what consideration she has given to enabling the registration of births in children's centres.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160970","160970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2875","2013-06-24","Home Office","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of registrars who have outsourced their registration of births to other places in the community due to high demand.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160971","160971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2876","2013-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average duration is of a claimant on jobseeker's allowance, by age group.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 160972","160972"
