"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4992","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has had with the Kenyan government in relation to the operation of UK unmanned aerial vehicles within its territory.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155037","155037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4993","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library  a map indicating those areas within the UK where his Department may operate unmanned aerial vehicles.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155038","155038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4994","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on public opinion in (a) Afghanistan and (b) Pakistan of unmanned aerial vehicle strikes.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155039","155039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4995","2013-05-14","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he first asked the Radiotherapy Clinical Reference Group to put in place a review process for NHS patients excluded from the Cancer Drugs Fund national list from 1 April 2013.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154950","154950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4996","2013-05-14","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the review process is for NHS patients for cancer treatments excluded from the Cancer Drugs Fund national list from April 2013.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154952","154952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4997","2013-05-14","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding mechanism has been available from 1 April 2013 to allow NHS patient access to selective internal radiation therapy prior to the outcomes of the review by the Radiotherapy Clinical Reference Group.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154953","154953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4998","2013-05-14","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of newly presenting NHS patients who will not receive cancer treatment from 1 April 2013 as a consequence of the transition of the Cancer Drugs Fund to the national list.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154954","154954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4999","2013-05-14","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the review process by the Radiotherapy Clinical Reference Group into selective internal radiation therapy will be conducted; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154955","154955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5000","2013-05-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to implement the Low Pay Commission's recommendation in its 2013 report to publish on gov.uk effective, clear and accessible guidance on all aspects of the minimum wage.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154958","154958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5001","2013-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what mental health treatment options are available to prisoners; whether there is proven-cost-effectiveness for those treatments; and what the average cost is of prison-based mental health treatment per prisoner.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154959","154959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5002","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions a Reaper UAV has launched a weapon in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154982","154982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5003","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what external legal advice he has commissioned to ensure that the provision of locational intelligence to facilitate unmanned aerial vehicle strikes by third parties is consistent with customary international law.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154983","154983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5004","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what external legal advice he has commissioned to ensure that UK ummanned aerial vehicle operations are consistent with the law of armed conflict.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154984","154984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5005","2013-05-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make a statement on the current position of negotiations with EDF for a contract for electricity from Hinkley Point C.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154985","154985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5006","2013-05-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the support of UK arts in the running of the 2012 Olympic and Paralympic Games.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155025","155025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5007","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent changes have been made to national guidance on the charges levied for the policing of (a) festivals with up to 5,000 attendees, (b) festivals with between 5,000 and 12,000 attendees and (c) festivals with more than 12,000 attendees.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155026","155026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5008","2013-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Harbours, Docks and Piers Clauses Act 1847 in order to give higher regard to the welfare of animals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155027","155027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5009","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the operation of the Court of Protection in respect of individuals suffering from Alzheimer's; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155028","155028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5010","2013-05-13","Department for Transport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of seafarer (a) ratings and (b) officers working on vessels registered under the (i) UK and (ii) Red Ensign Group flag were (A) UK nations, (B) non-UK nationals and (C) non-EU nationals in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155029","155029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5012","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what guidance his Department issues on the actions that would result in the suspension or removal of a bonus payment to an official in his Department; what the process is for clawing back such bonuses; and on how many occasions this has happened in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154998","154998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5013","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues on the actions that would result in the suspension or removal of a bonus payment to an official in his Department; what the process is for clawing back such bonuses; and on how many occasions this has happened in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154999","154999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5014","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department issues on the actions that would result in the suspension or removal of a bonus payment to an official in her Department; what the process is for clawing back such bonuses; and on how many occasions this has happened in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155000","155000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5015","2013-05-13","Department for International Development","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what guidance her Department issues on the actions that would result in the suspension or removal of a bonus payment to an official in her Department; what the process is for clawing back such bonuses; and on how many occasions this has happened in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155001","155001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5030","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will introduce tougher sentences in cases of extreme cruelty to animals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155030","155030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5036","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department issues on the actions that would result in the suspension or removal of a bonus payment to an official in his Department; what the process is for clawing back such bonuses; and on how many occasions this has happened in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155002","155002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5037","2013-05-13","Northern Ireland Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what guidance her Department issues on the actions that would result in the suspension or removal of a bonus payment to an official in her Department; what the process is for clawing back such bonuses; and on how many occasions this has happened in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155003","155003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5038","2013-05-13","Scotland Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what guidance his Department issues on the actions that would result in the suspension or removal of a bonus payment to an official in his Department; what the process is for clawing back such bonuses; and on how many occasions this has happened in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155004","155004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5039","2013-05-13","Department for Transport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department issues on the actions that would result in the suspension or removal of a bonus payment to an official in his Department; what the process is for clawing back such bonuses; and on how many occasions this has happened in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155005","155005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5040","2013-05-13","HM Treasury","2013-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance his Department issues on the actions that would result in the suspension or removal of a bonus payment to an official in his Department; what the process is for clawing back such bonuses; and on how many occasions this has happened in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155006","155006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5041","2013-05-13","Wales Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what guidance his Department issues on the actions that would result in the suspension or removal of a bonus payment to an official in his Department; what the process is for clawing back such bonuses; and on how many occasions this has happened in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155007","155007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5042","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department issues on the actions that would result in the suspension or removal of a bonus payment to an official in his Department; what the process is for clawing back such bonuses; and on how many occasions this has happened in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155008","155008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5043","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours of counselling are paid for annually from the public purse for prisoners.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155055","155055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5044","2013-05-13","Department for Transport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many new training roles for UK seafarers were created under the approved core training commitments submitted by company groups that qualified for the tonnage tax scheme for 2012-13.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155056","155056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5046","2013-05-13","Department for International Development","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she discussed increasing resources for nutrition-specific programmes at the World Bank Spring meeting in Washington, USA.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155042","155042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5047","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether prisoners are required to buy their own (a) televisions, (b) games consoles and (c) other entertainment devices.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155044","155044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5048","2013-05-13","Department for Transport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 11 March 2013, Official Report, column 20W, on high speed 2 railway line, when he plans to publish the draft environmental statement.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155046","155046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5049","2013-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the costings contained in the Bread and Flour Regulations 1998 Consultation Impact Assessment, what the costs would be to the (a) quarrying, (b) manufacture and (c) distribution industries of his proposals.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155047","155047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5059","2013-05-13","Department for Transport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of the ships over 500 gross tonnage working on commercial routes to and from UK ports were registered under (a) non-UK and (b) non-EU flags in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155065","155065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5060","2013-05-13","Department for Transport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the total number of commercial vessels over 500 gross tonnage working on routes to and from UK ports that will not be covered by laws implementing the Maritime Labour Convention 2006 after the Convention comes into force.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155066","155066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5061","2013-05-13","Department for Transport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vessels with valid licences to operate in the UK ferry sector are registered under (a) non-UK and (b) non-EU flags.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155067","155067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5062","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what timetable he has set for the development of his Department's policy framework for the Arctic.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155069","155069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5063","2013-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made by the EU task force established to implement the Rio+20 decision on the conservation and sustainable use of marine biodiversity in high seas marine protected areas.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155070","155070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5064","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the importance of zoos and aquariums to the UK economy.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154854","154854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5065","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to promote the economic potential of zoos, aquariums and allied wildlife sites to local enterprise partnerships.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154856","154856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5066","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to stimulate economic growth in the zoo and aquarium sector.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154857","154857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5067","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service family accommodation properties have had a Green Deal assessment to date.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154858","154858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5068","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what fishing and marine protection patrols have been undertaken in (a) Tristan da Cunha, (b) Bermuda and (c) Pitcairn Island in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154859","154859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5069","2013-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what additional work he has recently commissioned into the effects of the neonicotinoids pesticides (a) clothianidin, (b) imidacloprid and (c) thiametoxam on honeybees.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154860","154860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5070","2013-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the number of deaths per 100,000 due to fire in (a) the UK and (b) countries that have introduced compulsory fire sprinkers in domestic properties.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154861","154861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5071","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent changes have been introduced in relation to the recruitment of police officers; and what assessment she plans to make of recruitment levels of officers from (a) black and minority ethnic communities and (b) deprived communities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154862","154862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5072","2013-05-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the statutory or other parliamentary authority is on which he will rely to incur expenditure or other financial liability pursuant to any investment contract he enters into, or strike price agreed, prior to the Energy Bill gaining Royal Assent.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154892","154892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5073","2013-05-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent estimates she has made of the effect of small festivals with fewer than 5,000 attendees on the (a) national and (b) local economy.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154898","154898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5074","2013-05-14","Department for Education","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to enhance the professionalism of teachers.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155086","155086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5075","2013-05-14","Department for Education","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of proposals for the establishment of a Royal College of Teaching.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155087","155087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5076","2013-05-14","Department for Education","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage continuing professional development for teachers.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155088","155088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5077","2013-05-14","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Board of NHS England to publish all minutes of its meetings that do not pertain to commercial confidentiality.","Biography information for Dr Thérèse  Coffey","Dr Thérèse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155091","155091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5078","2013-05-14","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish all calculations undertaken in the process of allocating resources to clinical commissioning groups for 2013-14; and what (a) formulae and (b) criteria were used in each such calculation.","Biography information for Dr Thérèse  Coffey","Dr Thérèse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155092","155092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5132","2013-05-14","Prime Minister","2013-05-09","To ask the Prime Minister, which (a) women's sector organisations and (b) women's interest groups Councillor Laura Trott has met in her role as Special Adviser to the Prime Minister since February 2012.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155080","155080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5133","2013-05-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funds from his Department have been received by the University of Sussex in each of the last five years; and to what use such funds have been put.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155107","155107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5134","2013-05-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will review the regulatory and accountability regime of the University of Sussex.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155108","155108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5135","2013-05-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will conduct a financial and academic audit of the University of Sussex.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155109","155109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5136","2013-05-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will arrange an urgent review of the financial situation of the Central Sussex College.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155110","155110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5147","2013-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy that the Probation Service should not use door-to-door selling as part of the rehabilitation of young offenders.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155099","155099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5148","2013-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether there are any statutory requirements for probation officers to offer training to offenders as door-to-door salesmen as part of their rehabilitation programme.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155100","155100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5492","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what meetings have been held between the (a) Cabinet Secretary, (b) Head of the Civil Service or (c) Cabinet Office Permanent Secretary and any newspaper journalist or editor in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155083","155083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5493","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if the Permanent Secretary of his Department has held any (a) briefing sessions, (b) private meetings and (c) lunches or dinners with journalists and newspaper editors when he or Ministers in his Department were not present in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155082","155082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5697","2013-05-14","Cabinet Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of households in Barrow and Furness constituency which do not have access to the internet.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155089","155089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5698","2013-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff are employed by Forest Enterprise England in Cumbria; and what proportion of such staff are paid (a) at and (b) above the relevant level of the living wage.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155090","155090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5862","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department had with patient groups and care organisations before its decision to set a cap on the cost of social care.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155164","155164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5874","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment of the potential effects on (a) insurers and (b) policy holders of the proposed cap on social care costs.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155040","155040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5875","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department had with insurance providers before the Government's decision to set a cap on the cost of social care was taken.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155041","155041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6013","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has recently received representations from NHS Berkshire about (a) the future of Heatherwood Hospital, Ascot and (b) the strategic priorities for healthcare services in East Berkshire.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154904","154904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6321","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what reasons were recorded for the transfer of prisoners out of each prison establishment in England and Wales in each year from 2008 to 2012.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154927","154927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6323","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many defendants were remanded into custody in England and Wales in each month between January 2008 and April 2012.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154866","154866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6324","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost was of transferring prisoners between prison establishments in England and Wales in each year from 2010 to 2012.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154940","154940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6325","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of transfers was between prisons establishments per inmate serving a sentence of (a) six months or under, (b) between six and 12 months, (c) between one and four years, (d) between four and 10 years and (e) over 10 years in each year from 2010 to 2012.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154941","154941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6326","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offences have been committed by individuals remanded on bail in each month from April 2010 to April 2012.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154897","154897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6551","2013-05-14","Home Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with Ministers in the devolved administrations of her Department's proposals for the new Police Remuneration Review Body.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154883","154883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6552","2013-05-14","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to include measures regarding reservists in the Defence Reform Bill announced in the Queen's Speech.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154884","154884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6553","2013-05-14","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to publish the Reserves White Paper before introducing the Defence Reform Bill to Parliament.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154885","154885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6573","2013-05-14","Cabinet Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times the Security Vetting Appeals Panel has met since May 2010.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155177","155177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6574","2013-05-14","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contingency plans his Department has to respond to the potential spread of a human variant of the H7N9 influenza virus; and which Ministers have responsibility for civil contingency planning relating to an influenza pandemic.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155178","155178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6575","2013-05-14","Cabinet Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many special advisers have used the appeals process to challenge an adverse vetting decision since May 2010.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155182","155182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6578","2013-05-14","Cabinet Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many current Government special advisers have been subject to (a) all forms of personnel security control, (b) a counter terrorism check, (c) a security check and (d) developed vetting.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155094","155094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6920","2013-05-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many L1 examiners at each location are employed by the Insolvency Service; and how many such examiners (a) were employed at each location before implementation of restructuring under the Delivery Strategy and (b) will be employed at each location after that restructuring is complete.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155093","155093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7138","2013-05-14","HM Treasury","2013-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what formula his Department will use to adjust the block grant to Scotland to reflect the implementation of the new taxation powers contained in the Scotland Act 2012.","Biography information for Mr David Hamilton","Mr David Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155174","155174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7139","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the number of children expected to be living in (a) relative and (b) absolute poverty in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Mr David Hamilton","Mr David Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155170","155170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7140","2013-05-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of the size of the black market in online gambling (a) hosted in the UK and (b) used by UK consumers.","Biography information for Mr David Hamilton","Mr David Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155171","155171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7141","2013-05-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that there is adequate research on the extent of problem gambling to inform policy-making.","Biography information for Mr David Hamilton","Mr David Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155172","155172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7174","2013-05-13","Department for International Development","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which middle income countries receive official development assistance from the Government; what proportion of this assistance is in the form of (a) bilateral programmes and (b) support via multilateral organisations; how much each such country receives; how many such countries have received increased allocations since May 2010; and how much increase any such country has received.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154871","154871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7175","2013-05-13","Department for International Development","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many middle income countries receive overseas development assistance through (a) bilateral programmes and (b) multilateral organisations.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154872","154872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7176","2013-05-14","Department for International Development","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if there is a written record confirming the South African government's agreement to the UK ending its bilateral aid programme to South Africa in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154875","154875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7177","2013-05-14","Department for International Development","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she reached agreement with the South African government to end the UK's bilateral aid programme to South Africa in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154879","154879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7179","2013-05-14","Department for International Development","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with which South African government department it was agreed that the UK's bilateral aid programme to South Africa should end in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154964","154964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7180","2013-05-13","Department for International Development","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department's contracts for the provision of aid programmes by private contractors include provisions relating to the awarding of bonuses by those contractors to individual consultants.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154946","154946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7320","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what advice his Department has issued to the Aerospace Growth Partnership's working group examining the location of the proposed Aerospace Technology Institute.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154893","154893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7321","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects to announce the location of the proposed Aerospace Technology Institute.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154894","154894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7322","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received on the location of the proposed Aerospace Technology Institute.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154895","154895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7762","2013-05-14","Prime Minister","2013-05-09","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he discussed his possible attendance at the upcoming Commonwealth Heads of Government meeting in Colombo during his recent bilateral meeting with Prime Minister Harper of Canada.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155074","155074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7858","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer from the Leader of the House of 18 April 2013, Official Report, column 503, when she expects her Department's inspectors to make recommendations relating to allegations of cruelty and bad practice at Imperial College, London; and if she will place the findings of this inspection in the Library.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155043","155043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7859","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what level of risk rating was assigned to Imperial College London by her Department's Animals in Science Regulation Unit during 2012; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155045","155045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7860","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will increase the number of inspectors employed within her Department's Animals in Science Regulation Unit; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155068","155068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7946","2013-05-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the government of China on refugees from North Korea in China and on arrangements for such refugees to be resettled in third countries.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154910","154910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7947","2013-05-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that the commission of inquiry to investigate crimes against humanity in North Korea, mandated by the UN Human Rights Council in March 2013, is adequately resourced to conduct an investigation and make recommendations by March 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154911","154911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7948","2013-05-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people he expects to be in receipt of universal credit by April 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154956","154956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7949","2013-05-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the earliest date on which one million people will be in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154957","154957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7958","2013-05-14","HM Treasury","2013-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households in receipt of the childcare element of working tax credit claimed for the maximum eligible childcare costs for (a) one child and (b) two or more children; and how many such households incurred childcare costs in excess of these limits in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155079","155079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8153","2013-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress the Behavioural Insights Team has made in advising  his Department on how to encourage consumer take-up of the Green Deal.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155105","155105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8166","2013-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether (a) fuel cells and (b) hydrogen are being considered as suitable for a feed-in tariff by April 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155106","155106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8167","2013-05-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the revenue to be accrued to the Government through the sale of its shares in Urenco.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155102","155102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8168","2013-05-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects the sale of the Government's shares in Urenco to be completed.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155103","155103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8169","2013-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many staff from the Behavioural Insights Team have advised his Department on consumer take-up of the Green Deal to date.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155104","155104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8396","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of savings to his Department's budget in 2013-14 as a result of the abolition of strategic health authories and primary care trusts.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154899","154899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8397","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of savings accrued to his Department as a result  of the reduction in size of strategic health authorities and primary care trusts in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154900","154900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8398","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's administrative budget in 2013-14 is for (a) Monitor, (b) Healthwatch England, (c) Healthwatch Staffordshire, (d) Independent Complaints Advocacy Service, (e) health and wellbeing boards, (f) quality surveillance groups, (g) Care Quality Commission, (h) NHS England and (i) clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154901","154901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8406","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much the recent refurbishment of Hyde Park barracks married accommodation cost.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155136","155136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8407","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the level is of his Department's research budget; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155137","155137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8408","2013-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the bagder cull programme in Ireland and of lessons to be learned in relation to the proposed badger cull in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155141","155141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8409","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that clinical commissioning groups do not have conflicting interests when purchasing services on behalf of patients.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155134","155134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8410","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has for the future basing of the Queen Elizabeth Class aircraft carrier when overseas.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155135","155135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8412","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding her Department provided for the police pension top-up grant in 2011-12 and 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154948","154948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8413","2013-05-13","Department for International Development","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what programmes her Department supports to assist poorer countries in North Africa and the Gulf in water management.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154949","154949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8579","2013-05-14","Prime Minister","2013-05-09","To ask the Prime Minister, what relationships the hon. Members appointed by him serve on the Conservative Policy Board have with the Downing Street Policy Unit; whether they (a) have access to government papers, (b) are required to make a declaration of interests in the same manner as Ministers of the Crown and (c) are bound by government collective responsibility.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155187","155187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8580","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154966","154966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8581","2013-05-13","Wales Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154967","154967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8582","2013-05-13","HM Treasury","2013-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154968","154968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8583","2013-05-13","Department for Transport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154969","154969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8584","2013-05-13","Scotland Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154970","154970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8585","2013-05-13","Northern Ireland Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will list the purposes for which her Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154971","154971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8586","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154972","154972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8587","2013-05-13","Department for International Development","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will list the purposes for which her Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154973","154973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8588","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will list the purposes for which her Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154974","154974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8589","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154975","154975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8590","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154976","154976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8591","2013-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154977","154977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8592","2013-05-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154978","154978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8593","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154979","154979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8594","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154980","154980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8595","2013-05-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will list the purposes for which her Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154981","154981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8596","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will ask the Office for National Statistics to provide a list of all known official uses of (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155048","155048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8597","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155049","155049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8598","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155050","155050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8599","2013-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will list the purposes for which his Department uses (a) the retail price index measure of inflation, (b) the consumer price index measure of inflation and (c) any alternative measure of inflation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155051","155051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8600","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government intends to publish its response to the Public Administration Select Committee's sixth report of Session 2012-13 on the report, Special advisers in the thick of it.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155052","155052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8601","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government intends to publish its response to the Public Administration Select Committee's third report of session 2012-13 on Business appointment rules.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155053","155053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8715","2013-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to his reply to Question 37 at the sitting of 15 January 2013 of the Public Bill Committee on the Energy Bill, when he plans to publish the consultation paper on a community energy strategy.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155183","155183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8869","2013-05-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend clause 103 of the Local Democracy, Economic Development and Construction Act 2009 to allow York to be part of the Leeds City Region combined authority.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155184","155184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8870","2013-05-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will list (a) the total amount of European Regional Development Fund funding by English region committed to projects to date and (b) what percentage of the total allocation this represents.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155185","155185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8871","2013-05-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to remove the barriers to social tenants running a business from  home.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155186","155186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9177","2013-05-20","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) nationality and (b) gender was of each suspected victim of trafficking referred to the Trafficking Victim Support Scheme operated by the Salvation Army in March 2013; in which (i) region and (ii) local authority area each of the suspected victims was found; and which agency referred each case to this scheme.","Biography information for Margot James","Margot James","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155114","155114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9195","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many firms received criminal legal aid payments in (a) Alyn and Deeside constituency and (b) North Wales in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155157","155157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9196","2013-05-13","HM Treasury","2013-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of how many £5 notes (a) are curently in circulation and (b) were in circulation in each of the previous four years.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155158","155158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9197","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was paid in criminal legal aid costs to solicitors' firms in (a) Alyn and Deeside constituency and (b) North Wales in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155159","155159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9255","2013-05-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the recommendations of the Independent Review of E-lending in Public Libraries in England, published in March 2013, when lending rights will be extended to (a) e-books and audiobooks lent on library premises and (b) e-books lent remotely.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154886","154886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9256","2013-05-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many apprenticeships have been created in (a) the tourism sector and (b) libraries in (i) Barnsley Central constituency, (ii) South Yorkshire and (iii) England in (A) 2010, (B) 2011 and (C) 2012.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154888","154888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9257","2013-05-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many apprenticeships were created by her Department in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154889","154889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9258","2013-05-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will take steps to prevent the closure of local theatres as a result of local authority spending reductions.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154890","154890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9259","2013-05-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to maintain access to the arts in rural communities.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154891","154891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9738","2013-05-14","Home Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the salary bands of any staff who (a) are employed in and (b) otherwise contribute to the work of the Relationships and Communications Team of the Communications Capabilities Development Programme; what the total salary cost of all staff employed in this team is; and how many people the team employs.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154876","154876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9739","2013-05-14","Home Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 25 April 2013, Official Report, columns 1365-6W, on UK Border Agency, on which dates the Independent Chief Inspector of Borders and Immigration was formally (a) consulted about and (b) given final confirmation of the abolition of the UK Border Agency and the return of its functions to her Department.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154877","154877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9740","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average cost of recruitment was per armed forces recruit; and what the total cost to the public purse was of recruitment for all new personnel into the (a) Royal Air Force, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Army in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154863","154863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9741","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many minors have been deployed to (a) Afghanistan and (b) Iraq since the start of British military operations in those countries.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154864","154864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9742","2013-05-14","Department for Transport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will commission a study to outline the feasibility and initial cost of introducing a half-hourly train service between Cambridge and Stansted Airport.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155075","155075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9743","2013-05-14","Department for Transport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the cost to the public purse of introducing a half-hourly train service between Cambridge and Stansted Airport.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155076","155076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9744","2013-05-14","Home Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of the money spent on the Communications Capabilities Development Programme has been paid to service providers under the cost recovery system to date.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155077","155077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9745","2013-05-14","Department for Transport","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential gross value added to the economy of the East of England by improving rail links between Cambridge and Stansted Airport.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155078","155078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9811","2013-05-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, columns 702-3W, on Jobcentre Plus, which of his ministerial colleagues visited each of the Jobcentre Plus centres listed in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154880","154880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9812","2013-05-14","Prime Minister","2013-05-09","To ask the Prime Minister, what criteria were used to select which backbench hon. Members would accompany him on his recent trip to India; and what the cost was of travel and board for those hon. Members.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154881","154881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9813","2013-05-14","Cabinet Office","2013-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much No. 10 Downing Street spent on newspapers and periodicals in 2011-12.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154882","154882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9857","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the time taken in publication of assessment criteria on the development of learning resources.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155031","155031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9858","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Government plans to publish a revised impact assessment on the proposed changes to the National Curriculum.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155032","155032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9859","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish draft programmes of study for Key Stage 4.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155033","155033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9860","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish the final programmes for study for Key Stage 1 to 3.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155034","155034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9861","2013-05-14","Department for Education","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Skills Funding Agency will produce its property data survey.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155096","155096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9862","2013-05-14","Department for Education","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has put in place to monitor School Direct trainees' subsequent employment within their training school or group of schools; and whether their employment will be on a permanent or temporary basis.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155095","155095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9863","2013-05-14","Department for Education","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he expects to announce the first batch of the priority school building programme.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155097","155097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9864","2013-05-14","Department for Education","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 16 April 2013, Official Report, column 360W, on academies, if he will publish anonymised details of the complaints concerning the conduct of academy brokers and the outcome of any investigations by his Department.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155098","155098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9865","2013-05-14","Department for Education","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the stop lists of policy activity referred to in his Department's recent Infrastructure and Funding Division newsletter.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155101","155101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9972","2013-05-13","Department for International Development","2013-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of disparities in maternal mortality rates between indigenous women and national populations in Latin America.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 155024","155024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10","2013-05-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-05-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what recent assessment he has made of using private credit reference agencies in helping to improve electoral registration rates.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154455","154455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10017","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the number of people who will earn no more than the national minimum wage over the course of their working lives.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154712","154712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10018","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the take-up rate of pensions credit by those reaching retirement age in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154713","154713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10020","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effects of bringing forward the introduction of the proposed new single tier state pension on women born between April 1951 and April 1953.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154642","154642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10021","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential risk of losses to the public purse arising from applying the current accounting officer conventions in the period leading up to the referendum on Scottish independence in 2014.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154017","154017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10022","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with officials in his Department on how the accounting officers' conventions would apply to investment in Scotland in advance of the referendum on Scottish independence in 2014.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154018","154018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10023","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of setting the new single tier state pension at (a) £160 per week and (b) £180 per week.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154272","154272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10035","2013-05-10","Northern Ireland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the contribution of the Minister of State for the Northern Ireland Office of 21 November 2012, Official Report, column 637, what progress she has made on holding a round-table discussion with all interested people on a prison service memorial garden.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154223","154223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10078","2013-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when his Department will publish its written response to the Coroner's report into the Lakanal House fire that took place on 3 July 2009 in Southwark.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154025","154025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10103","2013-05-13","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to protect whistleblowers; and if he will place in the Library a copy of his Department's whistleblowing policy.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154048","154048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10104","2013-05-13","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which Minister in his Department is responsible for overseeing his Department's whistleblowing policy.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154044","154044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10134","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many strategic clinical networks have been fully established to date.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154627","154627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10135","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to support clinical commissioning groups to improve the experience of cancer patients in their area.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154628","154628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10136","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to address variations of care reported in the National Cancer Patient Experience survey.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154629","154629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10147","2013-05-10","Northern Ireland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with what external (a) organisations and (b) individuals her Department has engaged as part of the Scotland Analysis Programme; and what was discussed at such consultations.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154811","154811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10148","2013-05-10","Northern Ireland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many officials in her Department have been allocated to work on the Scotland Analysis Programme; and at what cost to the public purse.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154812","154812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10149","2013-05-10","Northern Ireland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what meetings she and officials in her Department have had with the right hon. Member for Edinburgh South West as part of the Scotland Analysis Programme; and what was discussed at those meetings.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154813","154813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10150","2013-05-10","Northern Ireland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what work her Department has commissioned from external consultants in relation to work on the Scotland Analysis Programme; which consultants were used; and at what cost to the public purse.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154814","154814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10151","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, if he will place in the Library copies of the contracts with Work Programme providers in Na h-Eileanan an Iar constituency.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153982","153982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10152","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, if he will publish full costings in respect of the operation of the Work Programme in Na h-Eileanan an Iar constituency.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153983","153983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10153","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, on what date he intends to release financial data below the national level; what consideration will determine the timing of that release; and whether the data will be published by (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) local authority area.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153984","153984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10172","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions has he had with the South African government concerning the re-introduction of a teaching inspectorate in that country.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154834","154834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10173","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions has he had with the Secretary of State for International Department on the decision to increase support on HIV and AIDS from 0 per cent in 2011-12 to 50 per cent in 2012-13.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154835","154835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10174","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the work of human rights officials in the new UN Office in Mali, which began deploying in January 2013; and what assessment he has made of that work.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154836","154836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10181","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the UN High Commissioner for Human Rights concerning the monitoring and investigating of allegations of human rights violations and abuses in Mali.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154846","154846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10298","2013-05-10","Scotland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many bilateral meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department have had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions or other Ministers in that department to discuss the effects of welfare reform in Scotland since 1 June 2010.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154630","154630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10299","2013-05-10","Scotland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many bilateral meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department have had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions or other Ministers in that department to discuss the effects of the introduction of size-criteria for the housing benefit of people renting in the social rented sector since 1 June 2010.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154631","154631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10300","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the contribution of the abolition of advanced corporation tax to the reduction in the value of pension funds.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154632","154632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10301","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been raised by the withdrawal of advance corporation tax credit on pensions.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154633","154633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10302","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, if he will place in the Library copies of the contracts with Work Programme providers in Banff and Buchan constituency.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153988","153988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10303","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, if he will publish full costings in respect of the operation of the Work Programme in Banff and Buchan constituency.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153989","153989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10304","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, on what date he intends to release financial data below the national level; what considerations will determine the timing of that release; and whether the data will be published by (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) local authority area.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153990","153990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10305","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether any changes have been made to the designated date for the introduction of universal credit in Scotland; and whether he anticipates any future changes to the timetable for the introduction of that programme.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154299","154299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10306","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons acceptance of claims for universal credit in pathfinder project areas of Wigan, Warrington and Oldham has been deferred.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154300","154300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10307","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of (a) the financial implications and (b) the administrative cost of the deferral of acceptance of claims for universal credit in the pathfinder project areas of Wigan, Warrington and Oldham.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154301","154301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10308","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the number of claimants who are affected by the deferral of acceptance of claims for universal credit in the pathfinder project areas of Wigan, Warrington and Oldham.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154302","154302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10342","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what budget his Department has allocated to the Traineeships programme; and what information his Department holds on funding for that programme from other sources.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154371","154371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10353","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when his Department will confirm its final proposals for traineeships.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154638","154638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10354","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when his Department will publish its response to its consultation on traineeships.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154639","154639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10355","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference the Queen's Speech on 8 May 2013, what measures relating to (a) apprenticeships and (b) traineeships he intends to introduce as part of the proposed Deregulation Bill.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154640","154640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10424","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many veterans of the UK armed forces receive concessionary (a) bus fares and (b) train fares.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154085","154085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10430","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost to the public purse is of the HM Forces Railcard.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154082","154082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10431","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many individuals have received an HM Forces Railcard to date.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154083","154083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10432","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost is of providing veterans of the UK Armed Forces with concessionary (a) bus fares and (b) train fares.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154084","154084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10478","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Maidstone and Tunbridge Wells NHS Trust has met the four key tests referred to in his letter of 13 December 2012 to the right hon. Member for Tonbridge and Malling.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154644","154644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10479","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the deficit of the Maidstone and Tunbridge Wells NHS Trust will be funded in (a) 2013-14 and (b) subsequent financial years.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154645","154645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10495","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the annual cost or benefit to the public purse will be of reducing the additional rate of income tax to 45 per cent.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154079","154079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10496","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK will benefit from the reduced additional rate of income tax from 50 per cent to 45 per cent.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154080","154080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10497","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK earn at least £1 million a year.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154081","154081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10546","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on equality of access for deaf people whose first language is British Sign Language in terms of communicating with (a) businesses and (b) his Department's agencies and non-departmental public bodies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Bruce of Bennachie","Sir Malcolm Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154691","154691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10547","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that deaf people have the opportunity to communicate in British Sign Language with (a) businesses and (b) his Department's agencies and non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Lord Bruce of Bennachie","Sir Malcolm Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154692","154692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10548","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on equality of access for deaf people whose first language is British Sign Language in terms of communicating with (a) benefit officers and Jobcentre Plus staff and (b) his Department's agencies and non-departmental public bodies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Bruce of Bennachie","Sir Malcolm Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154693","154693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10549","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that deaf people have the opportunity to communicate in British Sign Language with (a) benefit officers and Jobcentre Plus staff and (b) his Department's agencies and non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Lord Bruce of Bennachie","Sir Malcolm Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154694","154694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10550","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that deaf people for whom British Sign Language is a language of necessity are able to access employment on an equal basis to other people.","Biography information for Lord Bruce of Bennachie","Sir Malcolm Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154695","154695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10598","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make it illegal to strip copyright metadata and other information which identifies the copyright holder of a piece of work.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154678","154678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10644","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Speech by the Prime Minister of 25 October 2010, on what projects the funds to support the establishment of offshore wind manufacturing at port sites in assisted areas of England have been used; and how much funding has been allocated to each such project.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154436","154436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10743","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether vessels registered with members of the Red Ensign Group are considered to be registered under the UK flag for the purposes of applying the obligations of the Maritime Labour Convention 2006; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154398","154398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10744","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the provisions of the Maritime Labour Convention on (a) minimum age, (b) recruitment and placement services, (c) seafarers' employment agreements, (d) wages, (e) entitlement to leave, (f) repatriation, (g) seafarer compensation for ship's loss or foundering, (h) crew accommodation, (i) food and catering, (j) medical care, (k) shipowners' liability, (l) health and safety and (m) flag state and port state survey and certification to come into effect in the UK.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154399","154399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10745","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to extend the provisions of the Maritime Labour Convention on (a) minimum age, (b) recruitment and placement services, (c) seafarers' employment agreements, (d) wages, (e) entitlement to leave, (f) repatriation, (g) seafarer compensation for ship's loss or foundering, (h) crew accommodation, (i) food and catering, (j) medical care, (k) shipowners' liability, (l) health and safety and (m) flag state and port state survey and certification to all members of the Red Ensign Group.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154400","154400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10746","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of seafarer (a) ratings and (b) officers working on vessels currently registered under the flags of Category 1 members of the Red Ensign Group are (i) UK, (ii) EU and (iii) non-EEA nationals.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154401","154401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10747","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Maritime and Coastguard Agency last audited the shipping register operated by each member of the Red Ensign group; what the outcome was in each instance; and when the next such audit is scheduled.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154402","154402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10748","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many of the qualifying vessels for the tonnage tax scheme were registered under flags of members of the Red Ensign Group in each year since 2001-02.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154403","154403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10749","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the deadline is for completing negotiations with the incumbent franchisee for an extended rail passenger service contract on the (a) Essex Thameside, (b) Thameslink, (c) Inter City West Coast, (d) Great Western, (e) Greater Anglia, (f) Northern, (g) London Midland, (h) East Midlands and (i) South Eastern line; and what the (i) projected cost and (ii) cost to date is of the negotiations in each instance.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154404","154404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10750","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to protect the existing (a) collective bargaining rights and (b) contracts of employment for staff during negotiations with the incumbent franchisee for an extended rail passenger service contract on the (i) Essex Thameside, (ii) Thameslink, (iii) Inter City West Coast, (iv) Great Western, (v) Greater Anglia, (vi) Northern, (vii) London Midland, (viii) East Midlands and (ix) South Eastern line; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154405","154405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10751","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff from (a) his Department and (b) other government departments are involved in negotiations with the incumbent franchisee for an extended rail passenger service contract on the (i) Essex Thameside, (ii) Thameslink, (iii) Inter City West Coast, (iv) Great Western, (v) Greater Anglia, (vi) Northern, (vii) London Midland, (viii) East Midlands and (ix) South Eastern line.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154406","154406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10752","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total value of concessions given by HM Revenue and Customs to shipping companies in respect of the tonnage tax scheme was in 2012-13.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154407","154407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10753","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many vessels qualified for the tonnage tax scheme in 2012-13; and how many have qualified to date for the scheme in 2013-14.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154408","154408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10754","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Network Rail is permitted to submit bids to operate rail passenger services.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154461","154461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10755","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Network Rail's current licences allow it to submit bids to operate rail passenger services; and what changes are needed to the licensing process that would be required to permit Network Rail to submit such bids.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154462","154462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10756","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what safeguards are in place to ensure that members of the Rail Franchise Advisory Panel are not subject to conflicts of interest.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154463","154463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10757","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the annual rate of pay will be for each member of the Rail Franchise Advisory Panel.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154464","154464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10758","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what input the Rail Franchise Advisory Panel will have on the content of contracts to be tendered by his Department for rail passenger services on the (a) East Coast Main, (b) Essex Thameside and (c) Thameslink lines.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154465","154465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10759","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of (a) girls and (b) boys of each ethnic group achieved A* to E grades in (i) any and (ii) three or more A levels in each local authority area in each of the last 15 years.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153928","153928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10769","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils of each ethnicity who were eligible for free school meals achieved five A* to C grades including English and mathematics excluding equivalents by (a) local authority and (b) ward in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154819","154819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10770","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils in each free school were eligible for free school meals in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153917","153917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10771","2013-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the total value of (a) public service contracts and (b) grants that have been awarded by local authorities to voluntary sector organisations in each financial year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153924","153924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10772","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children receive free school meals in each (a) free school and (b) local authority area where a free school has been established.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153926","153926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10773","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils of each ethnic group achieved (a) five A* to C grades at GCSE including English and mathematics and (b) A* to C grades at GCSE in both English and mathematics but excluding equivalents in each local authority in each of the last 15 years.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153954","153954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10851","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Independent Reconfiguration Panel's advice on the review of children's heart surgery will be made public.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153911","153911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10971","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost per prison place was in (a) publicly run prisons, (b) privately run prisons, (c) the whole prison estate and (d) each individual prison in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154434","154434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10972","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost per prisoner was in (a) publicly run prisons, (b) privately run prisons, (c) the whole prison estate and (d) each individual prison in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154380","154380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10973","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent staff were employed in (a) publicly run prisons and (b) privately run prisons on 1 April in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154381","154381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10974","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent staff were employed in the Prisons Service in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154382","154382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10975","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employees of (a) his Department and (b) the agencies and non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible have an annual salary before tax of over £142,000.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154391","154391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10976","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what sentences were received by each employee of the Prison Service found guilty of criminal activity in the workplace in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154392","154392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10977","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the occupancy rate as a proportion of population to in-use certified normal accommodation was in (a) the whole of the Prison Service and (b) each public and privately-run prison in England and Wales on 1 April (i) 2009, (ii) 2010, (iii) 2011, (iv) 2012 and (v) 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154417","154417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10978","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases the Parole Board dealt with in (a) 2008, (b) 2009, (c) 2010, (d) 2011 and (e) 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154418","154418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10979","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the Parole Board case load was on 1 April (a) 2008, (b) 2009, (c) 2010, (d) 2011 and (e) 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154419","154419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10980","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the Parole Board's funding was in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154420","154420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10981","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the Parole Board's budget is for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154421","154421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10982","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full time equivalent staff were employed by the Parole Board in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154432","154432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10983","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many licence breaches there were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154433","154433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10989","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent on (a) televisions, (b) games consoles, (c) subscription television channels and (d) DVD players in publicly-run prisons.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154314","154314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10990","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employees of (a) his Department and (b) its agencies and non-departmental public bodies have an annual salary of (i) £100,000 to £150,000, (ii) £150,001 to £200,000, (iii) £200,001 to £250,000, (iv) £250,001 to £300,000, (v) £300,001 to £350,000 and (vi) over £350,000.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154315","154315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10991","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employees of (a) his Department and (b) its agencies and non-departmental public bodies have an annual salary before tax of over £142,000.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154316","154316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10992","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what sentences were handed down to employees of the Prison Service found guilty of criminal activity in the workplace in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154022","154022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10993","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times employees of the Prison Service have been found guilty of criminal activity in the workplace in each year since 2003, by category of offence.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154023","154023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10994","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total running costs, including salaries, of his Department's press office were in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154024","154024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10996","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many allegations of criminal activity in the workplace have been made in the Prison Service in each year since 2003, by category of offence.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154284","154284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10997","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times employees of the Prison Service have been charged with criminal activity in the workplace in each year since 2003, by category of offence.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154285","154285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10998","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department expects to publish an impact assessment for the proposals contained in the consultation paper, Transforming Rehabilitation, published in January 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154141","154141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10999","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the direct resource outturn expenditure was for each public sector prison in each financial year from 2009-10 to 2012-13.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154063","154063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11004","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cautions were issued for (a) triable either way offences and (b) indictable-only offences in each year from 2002 to 2012 in (i) total and (ii) each police authority area.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153938","153938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11005","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent on installing the nDelius system to date; and how much it expects to spend on the system in total.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153941","153941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11006","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department undertook a risk assessment of the installation of the nDelius system.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153942","153942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11007","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what offences were committed by offenders released on licence and classified as high risk during their licence period between 1997 and 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153943","153943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11008","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on pension entitlements for transpeople; whether the Government intends to bring forward amendments on this matter to the Marriage (Same Sex Couples) Bill 2012-13 at Report Stage; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153949","153949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11009","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on (a) external legal advice from Queen's Counsel and (b) other external legal advice (i) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (ii) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154137","154137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11010","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by his Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such payments were made; and for what reasons such legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154138","154138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11011","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154139","154139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11012","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by his Department was since 7 May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154140","154140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11013","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many escapes there were during prisoner transit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154388","154388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11014","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many allegations of criminal activity against employees in the Prison Service were (a) referred and (b) not referred to the police by category of offence in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154360","154360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11015","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many allegations of each category of criminal activity against employees in the Prison Service were (a) referred and (b) not referred to the police in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154383","154383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11016","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many allegations of each category of criminal activity in the workplace have been made in the Prison Service in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154384","154384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11017","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners who escaped during transit in the last five years are still to be re-captured; and of what offence each escapee had been convicted.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154387","154387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11018","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times employees of the Prison Service have been charged with each category of criminal activity in the workplace in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154393","154393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11019","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions employees of the Prison Service have been found guilty of each category of criminal activity in the workplace in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154394","154394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11020","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total running cost of his Department's press office was in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154389","154389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11021","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employees of (a) his Department and (b) the agencies and non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible have an annual salary of (a) between £100,000 and £150,000, (b) between £150,001 and £200,000, (c) between £200,001 and £250,000, (d) between £250,001 and £300,000, (e) between £300,001 and £350,000 and (f) over £350,001.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154390","154390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11330","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 2 July 2012, Official Report, column 520W, on health services: social enterprise, whether permission was given for the funds allocated to Cleveland Fire Brigade from the Social Enterprise Investment Fund to be used to explore the possibility of spinning that Fire Brigade out as a public service mutual.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154718","154718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11336","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the potential damage to (a) pupils' education and (b) efforts to combat climate change that might be caused by the proposed removal of climate change from the national curriculum guidelines for key stages one to three.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154369","154369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11337","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether he has made an assessment of the proposal by the Department for Education to remove climate change from the national curriculum guidelines for key stages one to three.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154370","154370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11339","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with trades unions about proposals to spin off elements of the Civil Service as public service mutuals.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154041","154041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11340","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the Information Commissioner on his Department's compliance with the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154620","154620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11341","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 25 April 2013, Official Report, column 1072W, on transport: livestock, what discussions he has had with his European counterparts on the compatibility of port authorities being unable to utilise their discretion to refuse the export of live animals through their ports and Article 13 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union 2009.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154202","154202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11342","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much Sodexo distributed through the Azure card in (a) 2011-12 and (b) 2012-13; and how much was allocated to Sodexo for the administration of the Azure card scheme in each such year.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154203","154203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11343","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the (a) potential merits and (b) practicability of permitting the use of Azure cards for bus travel.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154204","154204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11344","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to ascertain the views of fire brigade staff about his proposals to permit the spinning out of fire brigades as public service mutuals.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154363","154363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11349","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners absconded from each prison in the (a) North East and (b) Yorkshire and Humber region in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153968","153968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11350","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of off-gas grid households in (a) Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland constituency, (b) the Tees Valley and (c) the North East of England.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154362","154362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11351","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the potential benefits of providing initial training with universities.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154075","154075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11352","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of Freedom of Information requests submitted to his Department since May 2010 remained unanswered after (a) 20, (b) 40 and (c) 60 working days of their receipt.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154076","154076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11353","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will discuss with Atos (a) making transportdirect.info more accessible for smartphones and (b) creating smartphone apps to access transportdirect.info.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154078","154078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11354","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate the Office for National Statistics has made of the proportion of young people who have been unemployed for more than 12 months in each parliamentary constituency within Tees Valley.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154074","154074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11355","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Afghan government about (a) fully implementing the Elimination of Violence Against Woman Law, (b) increasing support for family responses units, (c) increasing the recruitment and retention of women in Afghan police forces, (d) increasing support for Afghan women human rights' defenders and (e) ensuring the meaningful representation of Afghan women in any peace negotiations.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154368","154368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11387","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with the International Maritime Organisation regarding the classification of polyisobutene.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154100","154100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11428","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 26 of the equality impact assessment of the income-related benefits change to the non-dependant deduction rates published in February 2011, if he will commission research to update the conclusions of that paragraph; if he will (a) make and (b) place in the Library an assessment of the (i) potential increase in the number of non-dependants between the ages of 16 and 24 leaving the parental home and claiming housing benefit in their own right following the reduction of their parents' housing benefit through increases in non-dependant deductions and (ii) cost to the public purse of any such increase in (A) Brighton and Hove local authority area and (B) total; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154110","154110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11699","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were employed in the (a) retail sector, (b) e-commerce and online retail sector and (c) wholesale and distribution sector on (i) 1 March 2010 and (ii) 1 March 2013.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154435","154435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11700","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) overall and (b) unit cost is of providing free bus travel to pensioners in (i) Worcester, (ii) Worcestershire and (iii) England.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154431","154431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11826","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will change inheritance rules so that an individual can transfer any extra state pension entitlement they have earned to a family member of pension age who is not a spouse or civil partner at the time of their death.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154450","154450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11827","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will review the amount which an estate of an individual who has earned extra state pension can claim at the time of their death.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154410","154410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11828","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the diagnosis of coeliac disease.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154411","154411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11829","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to mark Coeliac Awareness Week.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154412","154412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11840","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether alternatives to depleted uranium can be fired to test the propellant charge of CHARM3.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154612","154612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11841","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of shifts were staffed at below risk-assessed levels across all maritime rescue co-ordination centres in April 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154282","154282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11842","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions the Maritime Recue Co-ordination Centre, Belfast was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in April 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154283","154283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11843","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Stornoway was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in April 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154205","154205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11844","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the detention of Nafeesa Al Asfoor and Rayhana Al Mosawa in Bahrain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154367","154367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11845","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether Richard Paniguian, Head, UKTI Defence and Security Organisation, discussed the sale of military equipment to Bahrain during his recent visit to that country.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154066","154066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11846","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on the sale of military equipment to Bahrain.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154067","154067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11892","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff are employed by Natural England; and how many such staff are designated as managers.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154229","154229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11895","2013-05-14","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to consult on eligibility for free school meals ahead of the introduction of universal credit.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153906","153906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11896","2013-05-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities failed to identify and work with 75 per cent or more of their target families in 2012-13; which such authorities will have their funding cut in 2013-14 because of such failure; which other local authorities will receive less than 100 per cent of their provisional maximum funding for 2013-14; and for what reasons each such reduction in funding will occur.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153898","153898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11934","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 24 April 2013, Official Report, columns 905-6W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, what the reason was for the time taken to reveal the information contained in that answer.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154571","154571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11935","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he has any plans to review his policy on what information relating to unmanned aerial vehicles is held centrally.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154574","154574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11936","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether unmanned aerial vehicles have ever been flown by a team made up of both British and US forces.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154575","154575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11937","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on accountability of US unmanned aerial vehicles flown by UK personnel.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154576","154576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11938","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how long it takes to train an RAF pilot to become an unmanned aerial vehicles specific pilot; and how much such training costs.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154577","154577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11939","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how long an unmanned aerial vehicle pilot is allowed to fly before being required to take a break.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154578","154578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11940","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when a member of the UK Royal Air Force last flew an (a) US unmanned aerial vehicle and (b) UK unmanned aerial vehicle in Iraq.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154579","154579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11941","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether a member of the UK Royal Air Force has flown a US (a) armed and (b) unarmed unmanned aerial vehicle in Iraq to date.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154580","154580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11942","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in which years UK forces embedded with the US Air Force have flown unmanned aerial vehicles in Iraq.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154581","154581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11943","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the US about (a) armed unmanned aerial vehicle use in Pakistan and (b) the sharing of unmanned aerial vehicles between the UK and US.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154582","154582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11944","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will hold discussions with his Pakistani counterparts on the use of unmanned aerial vehicles in that country.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154583","154583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11945","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in which countries US forces have flown UK unmanned aerial vehicles to date.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154584","154584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11981","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to designate community pharmacies as buildings for the provision of healthcare for the purpose of determining business rates.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154675","154675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11982","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of designating pharmacies as buildings for the provision of healthcare for the purpose of determining business rates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154676","154676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/130","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential increase in carbon emissions if the motorway speed limit were raised to eighty miles per hour.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154123","154123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/139","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Office is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154529","154529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/140","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps No. 10 Downing Street is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154538","154538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/162","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many local authorities have received funding to train apprentices in each of the last three years; and how much funding each such local authority has received.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154087","154087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/196","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which educational courses are available to prisoners; what the uptake rate is of each such course; and what proportion of prisoner students see their course through to completion.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153961","153961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/203","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to review sentencing for those convicted of animal abuse; and whether he plans to increase punishments for those convicted of offences connected with animal fighting.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154785","154785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36","2013-05-13","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the expected percentage reduction in welfare expenditure that will be achieved through changes to the benefits system.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154838","154838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4121","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many residents of each constituency in England and Wales were born in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154791","154791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4122","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many trials were ineffective because of prosecution error in (a) 2012-13 and (b) each of the preceding 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154664","154664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4123","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, what the cost to the Crown Prosecution Service was of delays caused by trials that were ineffective because of prosecution error in (a) 2012-13 and (b) each of the preceding 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154665","154665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4124","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, what the cost to the Crown Prosecution Service was of trials that were cracked because of prosecution error in (a) 2012-13 and (b) each of the preceding 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154666","154666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4125","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which external (a) organisations and (b) individuals his Department has engaged as part of the Scotland Analysis Programme; and what was discussed at such consultations.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154729","154729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4126","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many officials in his Department have been allocated to work on the Scotland Analysis Programme; and at what cost to the public purse.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154730","154730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4127","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what meetings he and officials in his Department have had with the right hon. Member for Edinburgh South West as part of the Scotland Analysis Programme; and what was discussed at those meetings.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154731","154731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4128","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what work his Department has commissioned from external consultants in relation to work on the Scotland Analysis Programme; which consultants were used; and at what cost to the public purse.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154732","154732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4129","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to his Answer of 24 April 2013, Official Report, column 926W, on Crown Prosecution Service: training, for what reason there were no places on the Crown Prosecution Service in-house advocacy course in 2011-12 and 2012-13.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154647","154647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4130","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment (a) he and (b) the Land Registry has made of the (i) Ysciefiog and Nannerch Inclosure Act 1800 and (ii) Whitford Inclosure Act 1800; and whether he has any plans to bring forward proposals repeal or amend either Act.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154650","154650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4131","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many notification of interest letters relating to the Land Registry Act 2002 have been sent to (a) Flintshire residents, (b) Delyn constituency residents and (c) residents of the parishes of (i) Cilcain, (ii) Ysciefiog and (iii) Nannerch in 2013 to date.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154651","154651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4132","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions were dropped in the Crown Court because the court held that the charge should lie on the file in (a) 2012-13 and (b) the preceding 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154652","154652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4133","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations (a) he and (b) the UK Embassy in Bahrain has received in response to the publication of articles from Bahraini journalists and commentators on that Embassy's blog marking World Press Freedom Day.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154683","154683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4134","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which Bahraini journalists and commentators were invited by the UK Embassy in Bahrain to write an article for that Embassy's blog on freedom of expression in Bahrain on World Press Freedom Day; what criteria were used to decide which journalists and commentators were invited to do so; and what efforts were made to ensure balance in the selection of articles to be published.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154684","154684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4135","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has for commercialisation of HM Courts and Tribunal Services.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154685","154685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4136","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the quantity of coal gas off the coast of North Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154437","154437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4137","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which providers have been chosen to deliver the (a) Standard Crime, (b) Standard Civil, (c) Family and (d) Community Legal Advice legal aid contract in Cornwall; what the value is of each such contract; and what estimate he has made of the number of people assisted through each such contract.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154441","154441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4138","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on casualties amongst UN peacekeeping forces or others during the reported assassination of Kwol Deng, the Paramount Chief of Abyei.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154442","154442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4139","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy that there should be a full UN investigation into the reported assassination of Kwol Deng, the Paramount Chief of Abyei, including what is known of the perpetrators and from whom they received orders.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154443","154443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4140","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many former service personnel who have served in either Iraq or Afghanistan are in receipt of work-related benefits.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154572","154572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4141","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many former service personnel who have served in either Iraq or Afghanistan are in receipt of disability-related benefits.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154573","154573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4142","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the reported assasination of Kwol Deng, the Paramount Chief of Abyei; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154444","154444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4143","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what public consultation has taken place concerning the exploration and extraction of coal gas off the coast of North Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154445","154445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4144","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what licences have been issued for the purpose of coal gas exploration and extraction off the coast of North Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154446","154446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4145","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the potential environmental effect of coal gas exploration off the North Wales coast.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154447","154447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4146","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of health and safety procedures used for the flooding of the Point of Ayr colliery pit; what information his Department holds on any proposed gas and mineral extraction from the (a) onshore and (b) offshore areas near to the pit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154448","154448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4147","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what licences have been issued for the purpose of mineral and gas extraction in North Wales in each of the last 10 years; what the name was of each company to whom a licence was granted; and in which year each such licence was issued.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154449","154449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4148","2013-05-10","Church Commissioners","2013-05-08","To ask the Honourable Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what recent discussions the Church of England has had with (a) Government departments and (b) private sector energy exploration companies on mineral extraction rights on Church land.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154451","154451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4149","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on public health if fortification of bread and flour with key nutrients were no longer mandatory.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154452","154452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4150","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on low income groups if fortification of bread and flour with key nutrients is no longer mandatory.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154453","154453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4151","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what evaluation and due diligence has been carried out by his Department of the ability of Electricité de France to capitalise the construction of any new nuclear power plant in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154466","154466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4152","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the likely price per megawatt-hour of electricity generated by offshore wind in each year between 2014 to 2030.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154467","154467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4153","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress his Department has made towards the launch of the critical resources dashboard.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154468","154468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4154","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the critical resources dashboard will be launched.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154469","154469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4155","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to announce the Government's decision on the outcome of its consultation on the Bread and Flour Regulations 1998.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154470","154470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4156","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of benefits to (a) the milling industry and (b) other businesses of the Bread and Flour Regulations 1998.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154471","154471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4157","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Bread and Flour Regulations 1998 will be affected by the Government's Red Tape Challenge.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154472","154472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4158","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether to revoke the Bread and Flour Regulations as part of the Government's Red Tape Challenge.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154456","154456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4159","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effects of the mandatory fortification of bread and flour with key nutrients on individuals' health.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154457","154457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4160","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effects of the fortification of bread and flour with key nutrients on the health of low income groups.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154458","154458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4161","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions were dropped in the Crown Court because the indictment was stayed in (a) 2012-13 and (b) the preceding 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154653","154653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4162","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions were discontinued in the magistrates' court because the summons was withdrawn in (a) 2012-13 and (b) each of the preceding 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154654","154654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4163","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions were discontinued in the magistrates' court by way of a written notice under section 23 of the Prosecution of Offences Act 1985 in (a) 2012-13 and (b) each of the preceding 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154655","154655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4164","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions were discontinued in the magistrates' court because the defence successfully applied for the prosecution to be stayed in (a) 2012-13 and (b) each of the preceding 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154656","154656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4165","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the Answer of 23 April 2013, Official Report, columns 825-6W, on criminal proceedings, if he provide a breakdown by offence of the cases in which the prosecution offered no evidence in the Crown Court and Magistrates' Court in (a) 2012-13 and (b) the five preceding years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154740","154740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4166","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Turkish authorities regarding allegations that Syrian refugees were forcibly returned to Syria from the Akcakale refugee camp.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154751","154751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4167","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Egyptian authorities regarding the alleged kidnapping of refugees from East Sudan who are being held captive in the Sinai peninsula in Egypt.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154752","154752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4168","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Sudanese authorities regarding the alleged kidnapping of refugees from East Sudan.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154753","154753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4169","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Eritrean authorities regarding the alleged kidnapping of refugees from East Sudan.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154754","154754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4170","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with international aid organisations in Syria and the surrounding countries on reports of the selling of young women refugees.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154755","154755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4171","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that requirements on health and safety in the workplace are taken into account in the conduct of trade with Bangladesh.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154756","154756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4172","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) his European counterparts and (b) the European Commission on plans to use preferential trade access to encourage better health and safety regulations in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154757","154757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4173","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has for the minimum wage over the remainder of this Parliament.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154758","154758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4174","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the findings of the International Consortium of Investigative Journalists on money held in the British Virgin Islands.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154759","154759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4175","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with his European counterpart on the financial transaction tax.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154760","154760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4176","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of a tax on bonuses of bank employees in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154761","154761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4177","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Federation of Master Builders in Scotland on (a) falling workloads and rising costs and (b) the effects of these factors on unemployment.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154762","154762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4178","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effects of falling workloads and rising costs in the domestic repair, maintenance and improvement market on unemployment in (a) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154763","154763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4179","2013-05-10","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with the Global Fund to Fight Aids, Tuberculosis and Malaria on that organisation's funding.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154764","154764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4180","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with UNICEF on the UK being 16th in its ranking of overall wellbeing amongst developed countries.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154765","154765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4181","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the potential number of future universal credit claimants in (a) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154766","154766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4182","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with his Scottish counterparts on strategies to (a) prevent and (b) alleviate mental health issues among veterans.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154767","154767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4183","2013-05-10","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 608W, on EU aid, what the relationship is between Europeaid and the European Development Fund; whether there are any plans to combine those two funding streams; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154790","154790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4184","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of the residents of each constituency in England and Wales were classified by the 2011 census as working in (a) public administration and (b) the defence industry.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154792","154792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4185","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of police officers were in each NRS social grade in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154793","154793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4186","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of the population (a) in total and (b) who are (i) English, (ii) Welsh, (iii) Scottish and (iv) Northern Irish own a passport; and what assessment she has made of the reasons for differences in the ownership of passports between the constituent parts of the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154795","154795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4187","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of the residents of each constituency in England and Wales were born in (a) England and (b) Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154796","154796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4188","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what funding and support he plans to make available for the reserve projects in the Carbon Capture and Storage Commercialisation Competition.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154797","154797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4189","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the likely price per megawatt-hour of electricity generated by offshore wind in each year from 2014 to 2030 if a decarbonisation target for electricity generation in 2030 of between 40 and 60 grams per kilowatt-hour is set in 2014.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154802","154802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4190","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effects of tax and benefit reforms implemented since 2010 on levels of child poverty.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154782","154782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4191","2013-05-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the percentage change has been in her Department's funding for each of its sponsored organisations since May 2010.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154783","154783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4192","2013-05-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the percentage change is in her Department's funding for S4C over the next two years.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154784","154784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4193","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make the teaching of cardio pulmonary resuscitation skills a mandatory part of the national curriculum.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154786","154786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4194","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of ambulance vehicles were equipped with defibrillators in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154787","154787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4195","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK Border Agency staff in Scotland have been re-employed  by that Agency having previously been made redundant in each of the last 3 years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154788","154788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4196","2013-05-10","Prime Minister","2013-05-08","To ask the Prime Minister, with which external (a) organisations and (b) individuals he has engaged as part of the Scotland Analysis Programme; and what was discussed at such consultations.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154798","154798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4197","2013-05-10","Prime Minister","2013-05-08","To ask the Prime Minister, how many members of his staff have been allocated to work on the Scotland Analysis Programme; and at what cost to the public purse.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154799","154799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4198","2013-05-10","Prime Minister","2013-05-08","To ask the Prime Minister, what meetings he and members of his staff have had with the right hon. Member for Edinburgh South West as part of the Scotland Analysis Programme; and what was discussed at those meetings.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154800","154800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4199","2013-05-10","Prime Minister","2013-05-08","To ask the Prime Minister, what work he has commissioned from external consultants in relation to work on the Scotland Analysis Programme; which consultants were used; and at what cost to the public purse.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154801","154801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4200","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the Scientific Advisory Committee on Nutrition's report on the nutritional implications of repealing the Bread and Flour Regulations 1998.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154743","154743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4201","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government plans to announce its decision on the Bread and Flour Regulations 1998 consultation.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154744","154744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4202","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on (a) public health and (b) the cost of health services arising from revocation of the Bread and Flour Regulations 1998.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154745","154745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4203","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the milling industry and costs to other businesses of revocation of the Bread and Flour Regulations 1998.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154746","154746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4204","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on business certainty if the Bread and Flour Regulations 1998 are to be revoked in England but remain in place elsewhere in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154747","154747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4205","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the regulatory burden on business if the Bread and Flour Regulations 1998 are to be revoked.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154748","154748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4206","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what consideration he has given to the merits of the UK resuming its membership of the International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis (IIASA) in Vienna; and what assessment he has made of the benefits of UK academics taking up research partnerships at the IIASA.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154749","154749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4207","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the written ministerial statement of 15 April 2013, Official Report, columns 13-15WS, on horsemeat fraud, when he expects to announce the timing and details of the strategic review of the horsemeat fraud incident and its implications for the food chain and regulatory framework.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154750","154750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4208","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which organisations and stakeholder groups (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department have met as part of the review of nuclear waste management strategy following the decision of Cumbria County Council on the Managing Radioactive Waste Safely programme since 30 January 2013; and when the Geological Disposal Implementation Board last met to discuss the matter.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154473","154473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4209","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what definition of the precautionary principle is used by his Department.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154809","154809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4210","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when his Department plans to begin applying the findings of its new Biomass Emissions calculator.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154810","154810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4211","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, what meetings (a) he and (b) officials in the Law Officers' Departments have had with the right hon. Member of Edinburgh South West as part of the Scotland Analysis Programme.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154815","154815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4212","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps have been taken by HM Revenue and Customs to recover the interest owed by Goldman Sachs on the tax bill which it delayed paying.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154816","154816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4213","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, if he will set in train proceedings to prosecute Goldman Sachs for tax evasion.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154817","154817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4214","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 25 April 2013, Official Report, columns 1049-50W, on British nationals abroad: deaths, what the nature is of the assistance provided by his Department to families in such cases.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154313","154313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4215","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with disabilities in Coatbridge, Chryston and Bellshill constituency will be affected by the introduction of the under-occupancy penalty in housing benefit.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154317","154317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4216","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Coatbridge, Chryston and Bellshill constituency who are in full-time employment will be affected by the introduction of the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154318","154318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4217","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to adjust the rules on the under-occupancy penalty to take account of the circumstances of disabled persons.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154319","154319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4218","2013-05-10","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 608W, on EU aid, how decisions on funding to Europaid and to the European Development Fund are made; what the reasons are for differing amounts of funding being allocated to each; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154803","154803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4219","2013-05-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will (a) review the financial position of S4C and (b) institute a fixed funding formula for that channel to facilitate greater stability in financial planning.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154804","154804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4220","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many out-of-hospital cardiac arrests occurred in each of the last 30 years; and what the survival rates were of such cardiac arrests in (a) England and (b) each local authority area in England in each such year.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154805","154805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4221","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the availability and accessibility of defibrillators on survival rates for out-of-hospital cardiac arrests.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154806","154806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4222","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department has made available for the (a) purchase of defibrillators and (b) training of members of the public in their use.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154807","154807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4223","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his policy is on establishing a regional pilot scheme ban within the UK on the use of neonicotinoid pesticides.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154808","154808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4224","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Colombia about the death threat received by the Patriotic March member, Martha Cecilia Díaz Suárez and her two daughters from the paramilitary group Los Rastrojos in the form of two mutilated and red painted dolls.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154250","154250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4225","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what date he plans to publish his Department's guidance note on the use of pupil premium for learning outside the classroom.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154251","154251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4226","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 11 December 2012, Official Report, columns 257-8W, on flood control, what the planned spending on flood and coastal erosion risk management was in each year since 1996; and in each case what the actual spending was as a proportion of the planned spending.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154252","154252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4227","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding his Department has allocated for flood defences in each of the next four years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154253","154253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4228","2013-05-10","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of her Department's funding was committed to nutrition-specific programmes in 2012.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154257","154257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4229","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he expects to publish the next stage of the Children's Home Reform Programme.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154258","154258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4230","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance he currently provides to schools to support pupils who might be young carers.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154259","154259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4231","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what changes there will be to the National Referral Mechanism for human trafficking victims after the UK Border Agency is abolished.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154260","154260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4232","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154506","154506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4233","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance he has given to his Department's executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154523","154523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4234","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the current level of expenditure by his Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154545","154545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4235","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the report of the Scientific Advisory Committee on Nutrition on the potential nutritional effects of repealing the Bread and Flour Regulations 1998.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154459","154459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4236","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of repealing the Bread and Flour Regulations 1998 on the National Health Service.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154460","154460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4237","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 719W, on public sector: procurement, what discussions he has had with the European Commission regarding the proposed changes.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154604","154604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4238","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 719W, on public sector: procurement, when he expects his Department to generate a policy on the proposed changes.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154605","154605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4239","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department has given in subsidies to E.ON in each of the last five years; and for which projects this money was earmarked.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154606","154606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4240","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department has given in subsidies to British Gas in each of the last five years; and to which projects such money was allocated.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154607","154607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4241","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department has given in subsidies to SSE in each of the last five years; and to which projects such money was allocated.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154608","154608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4242","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department has given in subsidies to Scottish Power in each of the last five years; and to which projects such money was allocated.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154609","154609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4243","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many cases were dropped because the Crown Prosecution Service considered that the cost of prosecution would not be warranted by the likely final sentence in (a) 2012-13 and (b) each of the preceding 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154657","154657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4244","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many (a) magistrates' court and and (b) Crown Court cases were dropped by the Crown Prosecution Service  (i) pre-charge and (ii) post-charge in (A) 2012-13 and (B) each of the preceding 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154658","154658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4245","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many cases were dropped on (a) evidential and (b) public interest grounds in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) each of the preceding 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154659","154659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4246","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions were dropped before the case was served because upon review in the Crown Court it was apparent that the trial could not proceed or there was a lack of evidence in (a) 2012-13 and (b) each of the preceding 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154660","154660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4247","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, what  the Crown Prosecution Service's conviction rate has been in cases where the defendant has pleaded not guilty in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154661","154661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4248","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, what  the Crown Prosecution Service's conviction rate has been in cases in which the defendant has pleaded not guilty of (a) rape, (b) murder, (c) murder where the case was prosecuted by a single counsel and (d) murder where there were multiple defendants and a single prosecution counsel in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154662","154662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4249","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many judge-ordered acquittals there were in (a) 2012-13 and (b) each of the preceding 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154663","154663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4250","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department has given in subsidy to RWE Npower in each of the last five years; and to what projects such money was allocated.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154591","154591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4251","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department has given in subsidies to EDF in each of the last five years; and to what projects such money was allocated.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154592","154592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4252","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding has been allocated to each of the principal seaside towns under the Working Neighbourhoods Fund to date.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154593","154593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4253","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to improve the meeting of energy efficiency targets by energy companies.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154594","154594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4254","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of jobseekers who lack skills to use the internet in (a) Glasgow North West constituency, (b) Glasgow, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154595","154595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4255","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with JobCentre Plus staff about whether jobseekers do not accurately portray their internet and IT skills.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154596","154596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4256","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what research his Department has done into the accuracy of self-assessment of internet and IT skills by jobseekers.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154597","154597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4257","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Saudi Arabian counterpart regarding the rights of women in that country.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154598","154598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4258","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with Ofgem regarding energy efficiency targets for energy companies.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154599","154599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4259","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the unemployment level is in each of the principal seaside towns in England.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154585","154585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4260","2013-05-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much Heritage Lottery funding was allocated to each of the principal seaside towns in England in each of the last 15 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154586","154586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4261","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which coastal towns have benefited from flood defences under the Coastal Change Pathfinders Scheme; and how much has been spent on coastal defences in each such community since the termination of that scheme.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154587","154587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4262","2013-05-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much was spent in the principal seaside towns under the Sea Change Programme.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154588","154588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4263","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what internal discussions his Department has had regarding the corporation tax payment of (a) RWE Npower, (b) SSE, (c) EDF, (d) E.ON, (e) British Gas and (f) Scottish Power.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154589","154589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4264","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had regarding corporation tax with (a) RWE Npower, (b) SSE, (c) EDF, (d) E.ON, (e) British Gas and (f) Scottish Power.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154590","154590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4265","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had with Carnegie UK regarding its report, Across the Divide: Tackling digital exclusion in Glasgow.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154610","154610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4266","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had with members of the Scottish Government regarding digital exclusion in (a) Glasgow North West constituency, (b) Glasgow and (c) Scotland.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154611","154611"
