"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222852","2015-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices employed by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225059","225059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222854","2015-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what value of Small Business Research Initiative contracts has been awarded in 2014-15 (a) in total, (b) by the Ministry of Defence, (c) by the Department of Health, (d) by NHS England, (e) by the Department for Energy and Climate Change, (f) by the Department for Transport, (g) by the Home Office, (h) by the Department for the Environment and Rural Affairs, (i) directly by Innovate UK, (j) by research councils, (k) by other parts of his Department and (l) by other government departments and agencies to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225032","225032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222856","2015-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much Innovate UK funding has been used in 2014-15 to date to co-fund Small Business Research Initiative competitions by other departments or agencies.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225033","225033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222857","2015-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what value of Small Business Research Initiative Phase 1 contracts have been awarded in 2014-15 (a) in total, (b) by the Ministry of Defence, (c) by the Department of Health, (d) by NHS England, (e) by the Department for Energy and Climate Change, (f) by the Department for Transport, (g) by the Home Office, (h) by the Department for the Environment and Rural Affairs, (i) directly by Innovate UK, (j) by research councils, (k) by other parts of his Department and (l) by other government departments and agencies to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225034","225034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222859","2015-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what total amount of funds has been allocated via intermediaries in each bidding round of the Regional Growth Fund; and what proportion of such funds has not yet been drawn down.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225008","225008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222860","2015-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the total value is of all bids made in each region to each round of the Regional Growth Fund including the Exceptional Regional Growth Fund; how much has been allocated to winning bidders in each region in each round; and how much such funding has not yet been drawn down in each bidding round.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225009","225009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222862","2015-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many commitments have been agreed under the Export Refinancing Facility Scheme to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225010","225010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222863","2015-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many potential commitments under the Export Refinancing Facility Scheme are under discussion.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225011","225011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222865","2015-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) men and (b) women in further education received funding for childcare through the (i) Discretionary Learner Support scheme and (ii) Care to Learn scheme in the last academic year; and what the total amount spent on such support was in that period.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224914","224914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222866","2015-02-25","Cabinet Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many employees were on zero-hours contracts in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley local authority area, (c) South Yorkshire, (d) Yorkshire and the Humber and (e) England in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224937","224937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222868","2015-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been allocated for the impairment of student loans included in the Department Expenditure Limit for his Department.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224957","224957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222869","2015-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many young people living in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley local authority area and (c) South Yorkshire entered higher education in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224940","224940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222870","2015-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to resolve the mis-selling of Enterprise Finance Guarantee loans to small business by the Royal Bank of Scotland.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224964","224964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222874","2015-03-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, to state the date or dates on which export licence approval was given for the export of Saxon armoured vehicles to Ukraine, the number of Saxon armoured vehicles for which export approval was given and their stated value.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224887","224887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222875","2015-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage employers to keep on staff initially hired on a temporary basis.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224884","224884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222876","2015-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what value of Small Business Research Initiative Phase 2 contracts have been awarded in 2014-15 (a) in total, (b) by the Ministry of Defence, (c) by the Department of Health, (d) by NHS England, (e) by the Department for Energy and Climate Change, (f) by the Department for Transport, (g) by the Home Office, (h) by the Department for the Environment and Rural Affairs, (i) directly by Innovate UK, (j) by research councils, (k) by other parts of his Department and (l) by other government departments and agencies to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225035","225035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222877","2015-02-25","Cabinet Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of families in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) Merseyside have one stay-at-home parent.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224911","224911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222878","2015-02-26","Cabinet Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government plans to publish results of its trial of open book accounting; and what plans the Government has to mandate open book accounting for contracts.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224971","224971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222879","2015-02-26","Cabinet Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will assess the extent to which departments take account of past performance when re-tendering or contracting for new services.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224972","224972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222880","2015-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress has been made in publishing a new Code of Practice for Freedom of Information which apply to services delivered by external providers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224973","224973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222881","2015-02-25","Cabinet Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) live births and (b) stillbirths have been recorded in England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224926","224926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222882","2015-02-26","Cabinet Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the rate of unemployment among people aged (a) 16 to 24 and (b) 25 and above has been in each quarter since January 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224995","224995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222883","2015-02-25","Cabinet Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many apprentices employed by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225061","225061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222884","2015-02-26","HM Treasury","2015-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the proportion of an average-priced bottle of wine which is paid in tax.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225013","225013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222885","2015-02-25","HM Treasury","2015-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many apprentices employed by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225077","225077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222886","2015-02-26","HM Treasury","2015-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the proportion of total taxation revenue from wine paid across EU member states which is paid by UK consumers.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225014","225014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222887","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of adults in the UK who drink wine.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225015","225015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222888","2015-02-26","HM Treasury","2015-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the value of wine sales to pubs, bars and restaurants in the UK.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225016","225016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222889","2015-02-26","HM Treasury","2015-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much of HM Revenue and Customs' (HMRC) expenditure is allocated to preventing, detecting and handling cases of (a) tax evasion, (b) tax avoidance and (c) fraud and error in the tax credits system; and how many HMRC staff are working on each of those issues.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224907","224907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222890","2015-02-25","HM Treasury","2015-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average cost of providing childcare accounts for households in receipt of tax-free childcare will be per child; and how much has been set aside for the annual administration and running costs of the tax-free childcare system.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224912","224912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222891","2015-02-26","HM Treasury","2015-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to require RBS and Lloyds to disclose the activities of their subsidiary companies located in tax havens.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224902","224902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222892","2015-02-26","HM Treasury","2015-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the effect of alcohol excise duty rates on domestic consumption of Scotch whisky.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224922","224922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222893","2015-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department provides to local planning authorities on support for town and parish councils to initiate a neighbourhood plan when (a) there is no local plan, (b) a local plan is being considered by an inspection and (c) there is doubt about housing numbers.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224890","224890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222894","2015-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) statutory and (b) non-statutory homeless people there were in (i) Barnsley East constituency, (ii) Barnsley local authority area and (iii) South Yorkshire in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224918","224918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222895","2015-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reason his Answer of 23 February 2015 to Question 218656 did not provide the information requested in that Question; and if he will provide the information so requested.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225012","225012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222896","2015-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of funds under the 2007-13 European Regional Development Fund which were committed after May 2010 have not yet been drawn down.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225021","225021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222897","2015-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many apprentices employed by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225062","225062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222898","2015-02-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many apprentices employed by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225063","225063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222899","2015-02-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many fibre broadband hub stations there are in each local government area in Wales; how many such hubs are live; and what the expected roll-out date is for each station.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224961","224961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222900","2015-02-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of provision of broadband in the rural areas of Ashford constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224847","224847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222901","2015-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what additional funding his Department is making available to ensure that the remaining 10 per cent of premises get superfast broadband access.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224924","224924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222902","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have been recruited to work for his Department as a result of advertisements placed online in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224899","224899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222903","2015-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will ensure that women who worked in munitions factories during World War Two receive a medal to mark their contribution to the war effort.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224905","224905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222904","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have been recruited to work for his Department as a result of television advertising in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224898","224898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222905","2015-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent representations he has received on compensation for Christmas Island nuclear test veterans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224857","224857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222906","2015-03-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information he has as to whether Saxon armoured vehicles exported to Ukraine will have arms mounted on them by Ukroboronprom or any other Ukrainian organisation.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224886","224886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222907","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assets have been assigned to (a) Standing NATO Maritime Group 1, (b) Standing NATO Maritime Group 2, (c) Standing NATO Mine Countermeasures Group 1 and (d) Standing NATO Mine Countermeasures Group 2 since May 2014; and for how long each such asset has been so assigned.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224955","224955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222908","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the agreement in principle with BAE Systems for three offshore patrol vessels.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224956","224956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222909","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what deviations or exemptions from the Military Air Systems Certifications Process were made for the Airseeker aircraft; when those deviations or exemptions were made; and who authorised each such deviation or exemption.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224954","224954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222910","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when it is planned that the Capability Decision Point will be reached for the Type 26 Frigate programme.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224988","224988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222911","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the total cost to his Department of operations in Iraq since 30 September 2014.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224989","224989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222912","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to improve childcare infrastructure; and how much LIBOR funding has been used for that purpose.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224990","224990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222913","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assistance his Department is providing to the provincial government of Khyber Pakhtunkhwa, Pakistan for ensuring security.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224991","224991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222914","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many apprentices employed by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225064","225064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222915","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what total value of contracts was awarded under his Department's Small Business Research Initiative competitions advertised through the Innovate UK website in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225041","225041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222916","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what total value of contracts was awarded under his Department's Small Business Research Initiative competitions advertised through the Innovate UK website in 2014-15 to date; and for what total contract value his Department has budgeted for the full year.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225042","225042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222917","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what total value of new Phase 1 Small Business Research Initiative contracts were awarded by his Department in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225043","225043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222918","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what total value of new Phase 1 Small Business Research Initiative contracts were awarded by his Department in 2014-15 to date; and for how many contracts to what value his Department has budgeted for the full year.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225044","225044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222919","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what total value of new Phase 2 Small Business Research Initiative contracts have been awarded by his Department in 2014-15 to date; and for how many contracts to what value his Department has budgeted for the full year.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225046","225046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222920","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what total budget his Department has allocated for Small Business Research Initiative competitions to be advertised through the Innovate UK website in 2015-16.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225047","225047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222921","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what value of new Phase 2 Small Business Research Initiative contracts his Department expects to award in 2015-16.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225049","225049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222922","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what value of new Phase 1 Small Business Research Initiative contracts his Department expects to award in 2015-16.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225048","225048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222923","2015-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what total value of new Phase 2 Small Business Research Initiative contracts were awarded by his Department in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225045","225045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222924","2015-02-26","Department for Education","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential implications for her policy on early years interventions of the study by Professor James Heckman on the economics of human potential.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225019","225019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222925","2015-02-25","Department for Education","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprentices employed by (a) her Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225065","225065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222926","2015-02-25","Department for Education","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the pilot allowing approved adopters to search the Adoption Register is now working.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224958","224958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222927","2015-02-25","HM Treasury","2015-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have used the childcare calculator since it was launched.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224916","224916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222928","2015-02-25","Department for Education","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many disabled two-year-olds have been (a) eligible for and (b) received free early years entitlement since September 2014.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224917","224917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222929","2015-02-25","Department for Education","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average pay for teachers was in York unitary authority area in 2008-09 and in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224859","224859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222930","2015-02-25","Department for Education","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many nursery places have been available in Wirral South constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224913","224913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222931","2015-02-25","Department for Education","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people have used employer-supported childcare in (a) the North West and (b) Merseyside in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224910","224910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222932","2015-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the cost to the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority would have been of terminating its contract with Nuclear Management Partners at its break point.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224897","224897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222933","2015-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the projected number of years of active energy production available through the use of (a) nuclear power stations, (b) offshore wind turbines, (c) onshore wind turbines, (d) coal-powered power stations, (e) gas-powered power stations, (f) solar-powered farms, (g) tidal power lagoons, (h) biomass stations and (i) anaerobic digesters.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224892","224892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222934","2015-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many apprentices employed by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225066","225066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222935","2015-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many apprentices employed by (a) her Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225067","225067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222936","2015-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much was spent by her Department on flood prevention in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley local authority area and (c) South Yorkshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224936","224936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222937","2015-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the situation in Ukraine; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224860","224860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222938","2015-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his German counterpart about Eurozone negotiations with the Greek government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224861","224861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222939","2015-03-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he will be laying a Gifting Minute before the House in respect of Saxon armoured vehicles exported to Ukraine.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224888","224888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222940","2015-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to seek the release of Alaa Abdel Fattah.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224959","224959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222941","2015-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many apprentices employed by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225068","225068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222942","2015-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will appoint a special envoy with responsibility for promoting the rights of lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender and intersex people around the world.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225004","225004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222943","2015-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what effect the recent changes in the Yemeni government have had upon the case of Mr bin Haydara and the Bahá'í community in Yemen.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224993","224993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222944","2015-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the prosecution of Hamed Kamal bin Haydara in Yemen.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224992","224992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222945","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the BMA and other medical bodies on when treatment resistant prostate cancer drugs will be available in light of GPR158.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224994","224994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222946","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on why information about the timetable for the closure of Ealing Hospital Maternity Unit was communicated to three trainee doctors before it was communicated to the unit's midwives.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225005","225005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222947","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what rules determine who must sign the statement of manufacture that accompanies a custom-made dental device in the UK at initial and final inspection.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225022","225022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222948","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the statement of manufacture that accompanies a custom-made dental device in the UK must be signed at initial and final inspection by a person who has received recognised training to make a device of that type.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225023","225023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222949","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the statement of manufacture that accompanies a custom-made dental device in the UK must be signed at initial and final inspection by a General Dental Council registrant.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225024","225024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222950","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total (a) number and (b) value was of new Phase 3 Small Business Research Initiative contracts awarded by NHS England in 2014-15 to date; and what the total (i) number and (ii) value is of such contracts it has budgeted to award in 2014-15.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225050","225050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222951","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the statement of manufacture that accompanies a custom-made dental device in the UK must be signed at initial and final inspection by a person qualified to authorise that statement.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225025","225025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222952","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the value of new Phase 1 Small Business Research Initiative contracts which NHS England plans to award in 2015-16.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225051","225051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222953","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the value of new Phase 2 Small Business Research Initiative contracts which NHS England plans to award in 2015-16.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225052","225052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222954","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the practice of the General Dental Council in reporting possible breaches of the law by its registrants to the appropriate authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225026","225026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222955","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the value of new Phase 3 Small Business Research Initiative contracts which NHS England plans to award in 2015-16.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225053","225053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222956","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total (a) number and (b) value was of new Phase 3 Small Business Research Initiative contracts awarded by his Department in 2014-15 to date; and what the total (i) number and (ii) value is of such contracts it has budgeted to award in 2014-15.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225027","225027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222957","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total (a) number and (b) value was of new Phase 1 Small Business Research Initiative contracts awarded by his Department in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225054","225054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222958","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the planned total budget is for his Department's Small Business Research Initiative projects in 2015-16.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225028","225028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222959","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total (a) number and (b) value was of new Phase 1 Small Business Research Initiative contracts awarded by his Department in 2014-15 to date; and what the total (i) number and (ii) value is of such contracts it has budgeted to award in 2014-15.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225055","225055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222960","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the value of new Phase 1 Small Business Research Initiative contracts his Department plans to award in 2015-16.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225029","225029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222961","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the value of new Phase 2 Small Business Research Initiative contracts his Department plans to award in 2015-16.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225030","225030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222962","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the value of new Phase 3 Small Business Research Initiative contracts his Department plans to award in 2015-16.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225031","225031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222963","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total (a) number and (b) value was of new Phase 2 Small Business Research Initiative contracts awarded by his Department in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225056","225056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222964","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospitals meet each star level of the Food Standards Agency hygiene standards.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225020","225020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222965","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on phasing out all block contracts for mental health services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225017","225017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222966","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects that the Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services Dataset will start publishing data; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225018","225018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222967","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total (a) number and (b) value was of new phase 2 Small Business Research Initiative contracts awarded by his Department in 2014-15 to date; and what the total (i) number and (ii) value is of such contracts it has budgeted to award in 2014-15.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225057","225057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222968","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total (a) number and (b) value was of new Phase 3 Small Business Research Initiative contracts awarded by his Department in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225058","225058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222969","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many apprentices employed by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225070","225070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222970","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many individual funding requests have been (a) made to NHS England and (b) considered by an individual funding request panel of NHS England for funding for (i) any treatment and (ii) Duodopa in each month since April 2014; and how many of those funding requests for funding for Duodopa were (A) successful and (b) unsuccessful in each month since April 2014.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224946","224946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222971","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many statutory consultees to each technology appraisal conducted by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence in each of the last three years were (a) patient organisations, (b) manufacturers, (c) professional organisations and (d) other organisations.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224947","224947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222972","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many serious incident investigations have been undertaken by the NHS into incidents involving stillbirths in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224930","224930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222973","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the ratio of midwives to patients in the NHS was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224931","224931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222974","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he (a) received and (b) plans to publish the report by Lord Rose on NHS Leadership.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224934","224934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222975","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent by the NHS on obstetrics litigation in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224925","224925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222976","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many sick days were taken by NHS (a) nurses, (b) midwives, (c) doctors and (d) ambulance staff in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224935","224935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222977","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many obstetrics litigation cases in each year since 2010 involving incidents at Northampton General Hospital are still pending.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224927","224927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222978","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on obstetrics litigation involving incidents at Northampton General Hospital in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224928","224928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222979","2015-02-25","Cabinet Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) live births and (b) stillbirths have been recorded at Northampton General Hospital in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224929","224929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222980","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made by (a) NICE, (b) Health Education England and (c) his Department of the additional number of full-time equivalent nurses needed for NHS trusts to meet NICE safe staffing guidance.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224932","224932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222981","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of NHS trusts that have implemented the car parking principles he published on 23 August 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224933","224933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222982","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will increase funding for eye care research to tackle eye-related health conditions.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224985","224985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222983","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce more specialised nursing staff for community hospitals to assist people with diabetes.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224987","224987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222984","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when Duodopa has been (a) routinely and (b) not routinely available for use on the NHS in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224951","224951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222985","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the NHS Commissioning Board Special Health Authority first issued a public consultation on funding for Duodopa; what the outcome of that consultation was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224952","224952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222986","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that patients have timely and direct access to (a) gastroenterologists and (b) other specialist clinicians.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224974","224974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222987","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what dates in the last five years NHS England or its predecessor organisations have taken a decision to consult on whether to make Duodopa available for routine use on the NHS (a) internally and (b) externally.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224953","224953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222988","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Serious Incident Investigations have been undertaken by Northampton General Hospital into incidents involving stillbirths in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224979","224979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222989","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the ratio of midwives to patients has been in the maternity unit of Northampton General Hospital in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224980","224980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222990","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the specialised services circular issued by NHS England on 30 September 2013, ID SSC1315, on Individual Funding Requests for Clinically Urgent Treatment Outside Established Policy, remains in force; whether individual requests for treatments for which a cohort policy is in development will not be funded without evidence of clinical exceptionality; how many individual funding requests for (a) all treatment and (b) Duodopa were (i) approved and (ii) not approved under the (A) critical clinically urgent criteria and (B) urgent non-clinical criteria in each month in which that circular has been in force; if all requests made under the urgent non-clinical criteria received expert opinion from the Chair of the relevant clinical reference group within two weeks; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224981","224981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222991","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information NHS England collects on the status of individual funding requests for treatment.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224944","224944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222992","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that there are sufficient (a) specialist clinician trainees and (b) gastroenterologist trainees in the health education and training system.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224978","224978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222993","2015-02-26","Cabinet Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many incidences of gastrointestinal (GI) cancer were diagnosed in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14; and what proportion of cancer deaths were attributable to GI cancer in those years.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224975","224975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222994","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average legal costs to the NHS of bringing legal proceedings against doctors who have been excluded from their hospitals were in each of the last three years.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224968","224968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222995","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what treatments are currently due for consideration through NHS England's specialised commissioning prioritisation process; what communications his Department has received on each treatment from (a) hon Members and (b) other interested parties; whether each treatment is (i) routinely and (ii) not routinely available on the NHS in England pending the outcome of the prioritisation process; what the estimated annual eligible population is for each such treatment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224950","224950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222996","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase targeted screening for gastrointestinal cancers to better target those most at risk.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224976","224976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222997","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England is continuing to consider whether to publish the minutes of meetings of the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group; what factors it is taking into consideration before making that decision; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224943","224943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222998","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many gastrointestinal cancers were diagnosed in emergency and urgent care settings in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224977","224977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222999","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to introduce a national immunisation programme for meningitis B.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224901","224901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223000","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons NHS England has established screening groups to consider individual funding requests (IFRs) before a formal review by an IFR panel can take place; what information IFR screening groups require before making a decision on whether to submit a request to an IFR panel; whether decisions made by IFR screening groups can be appealed; how many IFR screening groups are in operation; what information is collected on decisions taken by IFR screening groups; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224945","224945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223001","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what basis NHS England's Clinical Priorities Advisory Group has recommended that Duodopa should not be routinely commissioned by NHS England; what factors NHS England's Clinical Priorities Advisory Group took into consideration in reaching that recommendation; what advice NHS England's Clinical Priorities Advisory Group sought from patient representatives in reaching that decision; what process NHS England follows to allow interested parties to appeal recommendations by the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224941","224941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223002","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the existence of the draft NHS England commissioning policy on Duodopa for a cohort of patients with Parkinson's disease means that any successful individual funding requests for Duodopa must demonstrate exceptionality against that cohort.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224942","224942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223003","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many attendees at each National Institute for Health and Care Excellence appraisal committee meeting convened in each of the last three years were (a) industry representatives, (b) doctors, (c) other health professionals, (d) health economists, (e) researchers, (f) patient representatives, (g) lay representatives and (h) other.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224948","224948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223004","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request that NHS England review its policy on individual funding requests.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224949","224949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223005","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of applications for NHS Continuing Healthcare funding has been successful in each year in which that funding has been available.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224855","224855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223006","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advance warning was given to patients who were previously entitled to free prescriptions before 2002 when the NHS Business Services Authority started checking eligibility for free prescriptions.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224858","224858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223007","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of graduating medical students opted for general practice in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224874","224874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223008","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to reduce the reliance on locum clinical staff at North Cumbria University Hospitals Trust.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224872","224872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223009","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many fines have been issued for claiming free prescriptions without a valid exemption certificate since the NHS Business Services Authority began checking eligibility for free prescriptions.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224848","224848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223010","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many fines have been issued for claiming free prescriptions without a valid maternity exemption certificate since the NHS Business Services Authority began checking eligibility for free prescriptions.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224849","224849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223011","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of diabetic patients fined by the NHS Business Services Authority since that authority started checking eligbility for free prescriptions.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224850","224850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223012","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the relationship between the allocation of funding for children's heart disease services and (a) current and (b) forecast patient numbers.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224851","224851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223013","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) measures and (b) guidelines NHS England has in place to ensure quality care for children with autism in the hospital system; and when those measures and guidelines were last updated.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224852","224852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223014","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to his Department has been of implementing the Friends and Family Test.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224853","224853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223015","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the NICE guidelines on safe staffing for nursing in A&E departments, published on 16 January 2015, what assessment (a) the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence, (b) Health Education England and (c) his Department has made of the (i) performance of A&E departments in meeting these ratios and (ii) number of full-time equivalent nurses required to meet the ratios across the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224875","224875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223016","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase cervical screening rates.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224882","224882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223017","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in England currently hold a medical exemption certificate.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224919","224919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223018","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential savings to the NHS of increasing cervical screening rates.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224881","224881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223019","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people in England who are eligible for a medical exemption certificate.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224920","224920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223020","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether patient uptake of insulin pumps has reached the levels set by the NICE technology appraisal 151 benchmarking tool issued in July 2008; how many people have taken up the use of such pumps; and if he will make  a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224921","224921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223021","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the patient experience of people with diabetes.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224909","224909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223022","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total (a) number and (b) value was of new Phase 2 Small Business Research Initiative contracts awarded by NHS England in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225038","225038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223023","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total (a) number and (b) value was of new Phase 2 Small Business Research Initiative contracts awarded by NHS England in 2014-15 to date; and what the total (i) number and (ii) value is of such contracts it has budgeted to award in 2014-15.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225039","225039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223024","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total (a) number and (b) value of new Phase 3 Small Business Research Initiative contracts awarded by NHS England was in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225040","225040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223026","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total (a) number and (b) value of new Phase 1 Small Business Research Initiative contracts awarded by NHS England was in 2014-15 to date; and what the total (i) number and (ii) value is of such contracts it has budgeted to award in 2014-15.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225037","225037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223027","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total (a) number and (b) value was of new Phase 1 Small Business Research Initiative contracts awarded by NHS England in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225036","225036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223028","2015-02-25","Home Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-UK citizens attempting to enter the UK illegally were apprehended by UK border control agencies at the ports of (a) Dover and (b) Calais in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224870","224870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223029","2015-02-26","Home Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to implement the ruling pertaining to the immigration case of the hon. Member for Sheffield, Brightside and Hillsborough, Home Office Reference Number SI733366.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224873","224873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223030","2015-02-25","Home Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in what locations non-UK citizens attempting to enter the UK illegally were apprehended in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224869","224869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223031","2015-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that all victims of historical child sexual abuse will be assessed for and offered the use of a registered intermediary in the court system.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224856","224856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223032","2015-02-25","Home Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the minimum income threshold of £18,600 set for migrants will apply to parts of the UK for which the average wage is below that level.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224983","224983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223033","2015-02-25","Home Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure that international students and graduates are exempted from targets to reduce net migration.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224984","224984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223034","2015-02-25","Home Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many apprentices employed by (a) her Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225071","225071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223035","2015-02-26","Home Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February to Question 223721, if she plans to respond to the recommendations of the Council of Europe Experts on Action Against Trafficking Report on the Implementation of the Council of Europe Convention on Action Against Trafficking in Human Beings by the UK before Parliament dissolves.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224996","224996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223036","2015-02-26","Home Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the annual cost of the National Police Air Service has been since 2012.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224997","224997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223037","2015-02-25","Department for International Development","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many apprentices employed by (a) her Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225072","225072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223038","2015-02-26","Department for International Development","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has issued in additional support to Malawi following the recent floods in that country; what activities this additional finance has been used to fund; and what proportion of such funding has been provided to the Malawian government for redistribution.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224967","224967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223039","2015-02-25","Department for International Development","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what contributions her Department has made to rehabilitating former combatants in the civil war in Sierra Leone; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224871","224871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223040","2015-02-25","Department for International Development","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent reports she has received on the Ebola outbreak in West Africa; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224862","224862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223041","2015-02-25","Department for International Development","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to promote the achievements of the Commonwealth Local Government Forum, Commonwealth of Learning and Commonwealth Scholarships and Fellowships programme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224891","224891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223042","2015-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) matched and (b) unmatched registered intermediaries requests there were for each group of vulnerable witnesses in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224878","224878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223043","2015-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many registered intermediaries were requested and matched for children in cases involving (a) sexual offences and (b) other offences at (i) pre-police interview, (ii) pre-trial and (iii) trial for each (A) age group, (B) geographical area and (C) impairment group in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224879","224879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223044","2015-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the average annual cost of court cases involving children that collapse due to insufficient or unreliable evidence.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224876","224876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223045","2015-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the Government's annual budget is for registered intermediaries; and what steps he is taking to ensure that this reflects need.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224877","224877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223046","2015-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the likely effect of the proposed increase in court fees for bringing money claims over the value of £10,000 on the ability of people on low incomes to make such claims.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224889","224889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223047","2015-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many apprentices employed by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225073","225073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223048","2015-02-25","Northern Ireland Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many apprentices employed by (a) her Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225074","225074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223049","2015-02-25","Scotland Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many apprentices employed by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225075","225075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223050","2015-02-25","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-23","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, whether the Electoral Commission will increase its target for voter increase.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224986","224986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223051","2015-02-25","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-23","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2014 to Question 216723, which local electoral registration officers in England and Wales will not publish registers until after 1 December 2015.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224960","224960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223052","2015-02-25","Department for Transport","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many apprentices employed by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225076","225076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223053","2015-02-25","Department for Transport","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many heavy rail vehicles built before 1999 have not been refurbished to comply with (a) RVAR 10 and (b) PRM TSI regulations.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224854","224854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223054","2015-02-26","Department for Transport","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to publish the invitations to tender for the Northern and TransPennine franchises.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224903","224903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223055","2015-02-26","Department for Transport","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was paid or is outstanding in premiums in (a) constant and (b) current prices by East Coast Main Line Company Ltd (i) since November 2009 and (ii) in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224904","224904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223056","2015-02-26","Department for Transport","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent by East Coast Main Line Company Ltd on stations enhancements (a) in total and (b) in each station since November 2009.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224906","224906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223057","2015-02-25","Wales Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many apprentices employed by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225078","225078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223058","2015-02-25","Women and Equalities","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many apprentices employed by (a) the Government Equalities Office and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225069","225069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223059","2015-02-25","Women and Equalities","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many companies have been required to carry out equal pay audits after they have been found to be discriminating on the basis of gender since 1 October 2014.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225003","225003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223060","2015-02-26","Women and Equalities","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, in which professions and sectors are (a) women and (b) men most over-represented; and what steps she is taking to encourage more equal gender representation in such areas.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224923","224923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223061","2015-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of housing benefit in Glasgow South West constituency are in part-time work.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224880","224880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223062","2015-02-26","Cabinet Office","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to Table 10 (1) of the Office of National Statistics' Labour Market Statistics release, when the Indicative Representation of the Claimant Count adjusting for Universal Credit caseload will become an official statistic.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224900","224900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223063","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants with alcohol or drug addictions have been sanctioned in (a) Dudley, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224895","224895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223064","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to support benefit claimants with alcohol or drug problems.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224896","224896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223065","2015-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of housing benefit in Glasgow South West constituency are in full-time work.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224885","224885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223066","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department issues to jobcentre staff on dealing with benefit claimants suffering from drug or alcohol addictions.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224893","224893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223067","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of benefit claimants in (a) Dudley, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England were receiving treatment for drug or alcohol addiction in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224894","224894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223068","2015-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the target time is from the point of application for people with (a) cancer and (b) motor neurone disease to receive their benefit entitlement under the special rules for terminal illness.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224883","224883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223069","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of the child maintenance arrears owed in respect of Child Support Agency cases where a child could still benefit is owed by a parent who is self-employed or a director of a private company.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224863","224863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223070","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of Child Support Agency cases with a child who could benefit are known to concern a non-resident parent who is self-employed or a director of a private company.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224864","224864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223071","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in how many and what proportion of Child Support Agency arrears cases where there is a child who could still benefit was a contribution made to arrears in the last (a) quarter, (b) year and (c) two years.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224865","224865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223072","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much of the Child Support Agency arrears owed in respect of a child who could still benefit are regarded as (a) temporarily and (b) permanently collectable.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224866","224866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223073","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what (a) number and (b) proportion of Child Support Agency cases are known to concern a non-resident parent who is (i) self-employed and (ii) a director of a private company.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224867","224867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223074","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what proportion of Child Support Agency arrears cases where there is a child who could still benefit are there arrears which have been (a) temporarily and (b) permanently suspended.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224868","224868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223075","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people received hardship payments in Scotland in the last 12 months; and how many such payments were made as a result of a benefit sanction.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225000","225000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223076","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what total cash value of jobseeker's allowance was withheld as a result of sanctions in Scotland in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225001","225001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223077","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 222884, whether his Department plans to publish statistics on the number of hardship applications and awards before the General Election.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225002","225002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223078","2015-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people on the Work Programme have been indentified as having mental health problems; and what the employment outcomes have been for those people since the beginning of that programme.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224998","224998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223079","2015-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to respond to the second report from the Work and Pensions Committee, Improving access to work for disabled people, HC481.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224999","224999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223080","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many apprentices employed by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225079","225079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223081","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people on the Work Programme who have been subject to benefit sanctions have been identified as suffering from mental health problems.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225007","225007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223082","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2015 to Question 223811, whether the next release of experimental statistics on the 2012 child maintenance scheme will include data on (a) the extent to which cases are fully, partially or nil compliant and (b) the amount of child maintenance arrears currently outstanding on Child Maintenance Service cases.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224962","224962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223083","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people received jobseeker's allowance (a) within three weeks of applying and (b) three weeks or longer after applying in (i) Barnsley East constituency, (ii) Barnsley local authority area and (iii) South Yorkshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224939","224939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223084","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the value was of benefit sanctions applied to claimants in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley local authority area and (c) South Yorkshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224938","224938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223085","2015-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much of his Department's expenditure is allocated to preventing, detecting and handling cases of fraud and error in the benefits system; and how many staff in his Department work on those issues.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224908","224908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223086","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will provide guidance to families with variable incomes on how best to choose between universal credit and the tax-free childcare scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224915","224915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223087","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment he has made of job outcomes of those people transferred from incapacity benefit to the fit to work groups who have (a) mental health and (b) other health issues.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224982","224982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223088","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on which dates a Minister in his Department last met a former Remploy employee; and when the next such meetings are planned.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224963","224963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223089","2015-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what means are available to his Department to validate claimant earnings data used in Universal Credit calculations which do not require employees to contact their employer.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224965","224965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223090","2015-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what research he has commissioned into the mental health needs of people claiming jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224969","224969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223091","2015-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the recorded primary medical condition was of each incapacity benefit reassessment claimant, where the outcome of the assessment was fit for work, since September 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224970","224970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223092","2015-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the caseload onflow onto local housing authority housing benefit was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224966","224966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223225","2015-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the Safe Bet Alliance on betting shop staff safety.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907754","907754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223226","2015-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps he has taken to support community football teams.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907756","907756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223227","2015-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the combined effect of poor mobile phone signal and poor broadband provision on rural communities and businesses.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907740","907740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223394","2015-02-26","Women and Equalities","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent progress she has made on encouraging girls to consider a range of careers.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907730","907730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223396","2015-02-26","Women and Equalities","2015-02-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent progress has been made on reducing violence against women.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907732","907732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223570","2015-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to uphold media freedoms.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907750","907750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222377","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many individuals and companies have been prosecuted for tax evasion in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224576","224576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222378","2015-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with (a) trade unions representing the offshore workforce and (b) industry representatives on the effect of recent reductions in oil prices on the steps required to achieve revising the oil and gas Industrial Strategy for (i) safety, (ii) skills, (iii) the supply chain, (iv) decommissioning and (v) the fiscal regime.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224573","224573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222379","2015-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the recent fall in the price of oil on (a) projects, (b) employment prospects and (c) long-term competitiveness and capacity in the offshore sector supply chain in the North East of England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224602","224602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222380","2015-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the total value of contracts his Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224652","224652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222381","2015-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people aged 16 to 24 of each ethnic group applied for an apprenticeship in each employment sector in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224670","224670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222382","2015-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people aged between 18 and 24 accessed the National Careers Service through each method of interaction in each of the last three years service user; and what the (a) gender and (b) home region was of each such applicant.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224729","224729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222383","2015-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people aged 16 to 24 of each ethnic group started an apprenticeship in each of the last five years; and in what sector subject area each of those starts were for each of those ethnic groups.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224745","224745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222384","2015-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) men and (b) women aged 16 to 24 started an apprenticeship in each sector subject area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224752","224752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222385","2015-02-24","Cabinet Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to stop websites charging for (a) the European Health Insurance Card and (b) other services provided for free by the Government.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224820","224820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222386","2015-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the European Structural and Investment Funds (ESIF) Operational Programmes for 2014-20 have been (a) agreed with and (b) authorised by the European Commission for (i) England, (ii) Wales, (iii) Scotland and (iv) Northern Ireland; and when he expects ESIF for 2014-20 to be released to local enterprise partnerships in each of these areas.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224798","224798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222387","2015-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the European Commission about the capacity of local enterprise partnerships to deliver the European Structural and Investment Funds Operational Programmes for 2014-20 in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224801","224801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222388","2015-02-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with Ofcom on simplification and clarification of tariffs charged by private providers for directory inquiries; and what information his Department holds on whether mobile telephone inquirers have been overcharged by directory inquiry providers.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224844","224844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222389","2015-02-25","Cabinet Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many individuals of each ethnic group were on zero-hour contracts in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224751","224751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222390","2015-02-24","Cabinet Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total value of contracts his Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224653","224653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222391","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total value of contracts his Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224668","224668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222392","2015-02-25","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans for payments of tax credits to cease as a result of their inclusion in universal credit.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224639","224639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222393","2015-02-25","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.203 of the Autumn Statement 2014, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of replacing Pacer trains under the Northern rail franchise due to start in February 2016.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224645","224645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222394","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2015 to Question 222787, what constitutes appropriate training for HM Revenue and Customs' staff dealing with accelerated payment notices; and what qualifications and training are required of the specialised team responsible for such notices.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224605","224605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222395","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many applications for 65+ Guaranteed Growth Bonds his Department estimated it would receive; how many applications for such bonds have been received; what estimate he made of how much time it would take to process each application for such bonds; and how long it is taking to process each such application.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224606","224606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222396","2015-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much from Right to Buy sales has been returned to the Treasury by each London borough in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224607","224607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222397","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 221932, whether it is his policy that licensed drilling contractors operating in the UK Continental Shelf are eligible for the investment allowance.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224574","224574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222398","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 17 February 2015 to Question 223222, how many staff made up the specialist inheritance tax compliance teams in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224585","224585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222399","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 17 February 2015 to Question 223222, how many staff were employed at HM Revenue and Customs offices in (a) Belfast, (b) Edinburgh and (c) Nottingham in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224586","224586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222400","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 17 February 2015 to Question 223223, how many of the notifications received by HM Revenue and Customs resulted in (a) court proceedings and (b) a conviction in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224587","224587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222401","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have been (a) under investigation and (b) taken to trial for tax evasion in (i) the UK, (ii) Scotland, (iii) Wales, (iv) Northern Ireland and (v) England in each year since April 2010.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224588","224588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222402","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the legal costs and fines recovered from (a) PricewaterhouseCoopers, (b) KPMG, (c) Ernst & Young and (d) Deloitte after tax courts and tribunals have rejected tax avoidance schemes designed by those firms in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224572","224572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222403","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of raising the basic state pension by (a) 10, (b) 15 and (c) 20 per cent.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224566","224566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222404","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff in HM Revenue and Customs have been assigned to deal with (a) pursuing cases of tax evasion and (b) investigating tax avoidance schemes in each of the last four financial years.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224575","224575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222405","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of raising personal tax allowances by 10 per cent.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224567","224567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222406","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are liable to pay income tax at the rates of (a) 10, (b) 20, (c) 40 and (d) 45 per cent.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224568","224568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222407","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from (a) the EU Commission and (b) other EU Member States on the patent box legislation.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224569","224569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222408","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will appoint an independent commission to investigate claims about the roles of PricewaterhouseCoopers, KPMG, Ernst & Young and Deloitte in designing, selling and implementing tax avoidance schemes.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224570","224570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222409","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will introduce legislation to make partners from accountancy firms ineligible for HM Treasury appointments if a tax tribunal or court finds that tax avoidance schemes marketed by such firms are unlawful.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224571","224571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222410","2015-02-25","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2015 to Question 220731, how many of the 94 investigations in the care sector have resulted in (a) prosecutions for non-payment of the national minimum wage, (b) recovery of fines following conviction for non-payment of the national minimum wage and (c) repayment of unpaid wages to workers affected by non-payment of the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224740","224740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222411","2015-02-25","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Big Six energy companies about community energy co-operatives in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224728","224728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222412","2015-02-25","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when existing community energy co-operatives will lose their entitlement to Enterprise Investment Scheme tax relief.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224725","224725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222413","2015-02-25","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority on the (a) regulatory approach and (b) registration criteria for co-operatives in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224727","224727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222414","2015-02-25","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on amending or abolishing the import/export tax regime.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224721","224721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222415","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will assess the effect on revenues to the Exchequer of buy-to-let landlords (a) being able to offset their bank interest against taxable income, (b) claiming the 10 per cent wear and tear allowance and (c) minimising their exposure to capital gains tax on the sale of properties by use of allowances or reliefs in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224674","224674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222416","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Prime Minister on HSBC and tax evasion since May 2010.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224675","224675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222417","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many notices of underpayment of national minimum wage were issued in respect of employers with (a) zero to nine, (b) 10 to 49, (c) 50 to 249 and (d) more than 250 employees in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224692","224692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222418","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effects on the number of community energy co-operatives of the removal of entitlement to Enterprise Investment Scheme tax relief.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224705","224705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222419","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to provide a two year transition period for community energy co-operatives to move from Enterprise Investment Scheme tax relief to social investment tax relief eligibility.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224706","224706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222420","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason the entitlement to Enterprise Investment Scheme tax relief is being removed from existing community energy co-operatives.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224707","224707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222421","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of removing community energy co-operatives' entitlement to Enterprise Investment Scheme tax relief on (a) the energy market and (b) the choice of energy providers available to consumers.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224774","224774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222422","2015-02-25","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 17 February 2015 to Question 223480, which stated that some complaints may not lead to the commencement of an investigation, for what reason the Answer of 28 November 2014 to Question 215561 stated that HM Revenue and Customs investigate all complaints.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224802","224802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222423","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was raised in revenue from employers of apprentices under the age of 25 in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales, (d) Northern Ireland and (e) England who were required to pay secondary Class 1 employer national insurance contributions on earnings up to the upper earnings limit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224788","224788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222424","2015-02-25","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) purchase and (b) installation cost was of the banner used at his speaking engagement at the Tate Modern on 20 February 2015.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224839","224839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222425","2015-02-25","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the contribution of Edward Troup in oral evidence to the Committee of Public Accounts on 5 November 2012, HC716, Question 60, what progress has been made on the further dozen pending criminal prosecutions for cases related to HSBC and tax evasion.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224808","224808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222426","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any Minister in his Department discussed the issue of HSBC and tax evasion with Lord Green during his time as Minister for Trade and Investment.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224797","224797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222427","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which parties have been given access by his Department to the Sandstorm Report associated with the closure of The Bank of Credit and Commerce International.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224763","224763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222428","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the agreement concluded with the Swiss Confederation in 2012 on co-operation in the area of taxation included a declaration that the UK will not actively seek to acquire customer data stolen from Swiss banks.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224764","224764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222429","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employers of apprentices under the age of 25 who are required to pay secondary Class 1 (employer) national insurance contributions on earnings up to the upper earnings limit there were in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales (d) Northern Ireland and (e) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224789","224789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222430","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any Minister in his Department discussed the declaration concerning the acquistion of customer data stolen from Swiss banks with Lord Green during his time as Minister for Trade and Investment.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224794","224794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222431","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which Government minister was first made aware of files relating to HSBC and tax evasion.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224786","224786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222432","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any Ministers in his Department discussed allegations of money laundering at HSBC with Lord Green during his time as Minister for Trade and Investment.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224795","224795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222433","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when Ministers in his Department were first made aware of the findings of the US Senate Homeland Security Sub-Committee that led to HSBC being fined $1.9bn in December 2012.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224796","224796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222434","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what action was taken immediately after Government ministers were made aware of the files relating to HSBC and tax evasion.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224787","224787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222435","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has held with the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) on its forthcoming investigation into allegations that British-headquartered banks have assisted clients to evade UK taxes by use of secret bank accounts in foreign jurisdictions; and what powers the FCA has to require employees of foreign-based subsidiaries of British-registered banks to assist such inquiries.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224843","224843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222436","2015-02-25","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to comments  by a senior HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) official to The Times, quoted in an article of 2 November 2012, what discussions Ministers of his Department had with HMRC officials on whether to pursue a selective prosecution policy on tax cases relating to HSBC in Switzerland.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224809","224809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222437","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what (a) discussions he had and (b) decisions were taken on tackling (i) money laundering and (ii) tax evasion at the meeting of G20 finance ministers in Istanbul in February 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224846","224846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222438","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when a Government minister was first made aware of files relating to HSBC and tax evasion.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224812","224812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222439","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, under what conditions the Government was provided with files related to HSBC and tax evasion.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224813","224813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222440","2015-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much the London Borough of Croydon received in total government grant in the last year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Richard Ottaway","Sir Richard Ottaway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224783","224783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222441","2015-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish all responses to the consultation on the proposal to amend the constitution of the Greater Manchester Combined Authority.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224756","224756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222442","2015-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish a list of respondees to the consultation on the proposal to amend the constitution of the Greater Manchester Combined Authority.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224757","224757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222443","2015-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many responses to the consultation on the proposal to amend the constitution of the Greater Manchester Combined Authority there have been.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224758","224758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222444","2015-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the European Regional Fund Operational Programme for 2014-20 has been agreed with the European Commission; and when he expects funding from that programme to be released to local enterprise partnerships.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224800","224800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222445","2015-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he intends to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Hyndburn dated 14 October 2014 on Hyndburn Homes.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224720","224720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222446","2015-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that advance public notice is given to the planned changes to the income eligibility thresholds for shared ownership.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224734","224734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222447","2015-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much (a) Derbyshire County, (b) South Derbyshire District and (c) Derby City Council received in total from government grants in (i) 2012-13, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Heather Wheeler","Heather Wheeler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224582","224582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222448","2015-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much (a) Derbyshire County, (b) South Derbyshire District and (c) Derby City Council have budgeted to spend in 2014-15.","Biography information for Mrs Heather Wheeler","Heather Wheeler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224583","224583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222449","2015-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what number and proportion of planning applications to build on sites in (a) Dudley, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England involved building on designated green belt land in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224590","224590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222450","2015-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to protect (a) green belt and (b) open green spaces in (i) Dudley, (ii) the Black Country and (iii) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224591","224591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222451","2015-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with the Royal Borough of Greenwich on a memorial to Drummer Lee Rigby.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224604","224604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222452","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the powers available to local authorities to intervene on privately-owned land to (a) monitor and (b) protect the welfare of horses; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224601","224601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222453","2015-02-25","Department for Education","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will undertake an assessment of the costs and benefits to the community in Nottingham of re-establishing a motor project on the Wheelbase site in Sneinton.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224634","224634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222454","2015-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release Pickles cuts stealth taxes on new homes and boosts small builders, published on 28 November 2014, if he will publish the business cases for each element of the initiatives announced in that press release.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224643","224643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222455","2015-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the total value of contracts his Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224654","224654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222456","2015-02-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the total value of contracts his Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224655","224655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222457","2015-02-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress he has made on delivering broadband to rural areas.","Biography information for Mrs Heather Wheeler","Heather Wheeler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224580","224580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222458","2015-02-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress he has made on delivering (a) broadband and (b) wifi to church halls.","Biography information for Mrs Heather Wheeler","Heather Wheeler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224581","224581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222459","2015-02-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to commemorate the tercentenary of the Battle of Preston in 1715.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224738","224738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222460","2015-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to help people protect their personal data.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224683","224683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222461","2015-02-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of Devon has access to superfast broadband; and what estimate he has made of what proportion of Devon will be covered by superfast broadband by the end of (a) 2015 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224827","224827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222462","2015-02-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of superfast broadband in Devon has been implemented by (a) BDUK and (b) BT commercially; and what estimate he has made of such figures at the end of (i) 2015 and (ii) 2017.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224826","224826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222464","2015-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total value of contracts his Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224656","224656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222465","2015-02-24","Department for Education","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total value of contracts her Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224657","224657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222466","2015-02-25","Department for Education","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to ensure that recent findings of the Local Government Ombudsman relating to grandparents and their grandchildren following family breakup are acted on by local authorities.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224631","224631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222467","2015-02-25","Department for Education","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2015 to Question 223692, if she will extend all bursaries to all students focusing on core curriculum on the Initial Teacher Training programme.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224632","224632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222468","2015-02-25","Home Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to amend Schedule 3 of the Nationality, Immigration and Asylum Act 2002 in order to ensure that there is no discrimination against care leavers who were taken into care as unaccompanied asylum-seeking children.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224649","224649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222469","2015-02-24","Department for Education","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons the salary sacrifice scheme available to teachers does not cover the purchase of cars.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224613","224613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222470","2015-02-24","Department for Education","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 February 2015 to Question 223512, how many students attend the (a) three free schools in Lancashire local authority area, (b) seven free schools in the county of Lancashire and (c) 41 free schools in the North West.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224584","224584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222471","2015-02-24","Department for Education","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on extending the VAT refund scheme used by other schools to sixth form colleges.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224684","224684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222472","2015-02-24","Department for Education","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations she has received from charities, schools, lobby groups and educationalists on the Drop the Learning Tax campaign.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224685","224685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222473","2015-02-24","Department for Education","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which schools in England and Wales have a dementia strategy.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224673","224673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222474","2015-02-25","Department for Education","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children of Chinese origin have been adopted by people resident in the UK in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Tim Yeo","Mr Tim Yeo","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224642","224642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222475","2015-02-24","Department for Education","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Sure Start children's centres there are in (a) Preston and (b) Lancashire.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224694","224694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222476","2015-02-24","Department for Education","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2014 to Question 207080, what information her Department collects on the use of the pupil premium allocated to children with special educational needs.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224793","224793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222477","2015-02-25","Department for Education","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total (a) capital and (b) revenue expenditure has been to date on free schools opened in districts which did not have a forecast need for extra school places.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224823","224823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222478","2015-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, for what reasons community energy schemes are not permitted to supply to local markets; and if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on such schemes' ability to reduce energy bills of them being permitted to supply to such markets.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224811","224811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222479","2015-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of units that secured a capacity agreement in the first auctions of the capacity market were based in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) England; and how many units of what capacity were so secured.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224815","224815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222480","2015-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the Rate of Return on Equity for each of the Distribution Network Operators under Distribution Price Control Review 5.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224816","224816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222481","2015-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much the Office of Unconventional Gas and Oil has spent on legal advice to date.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224817","224817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222482","2015-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress his Department has made on its investigation into the practice of de-rating wind turbines for the purposes of the feed-in tariff; and when he expects to publish the conclusions of that investigation.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224762","224762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222483","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent research his Department has conducted, funded or commissioned into the transmission of antimicrobial resistance from animal pathogens to human pathogens.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224784","224784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222484","2015-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department has taken with Ofgem to achieve a Price Average Reference (PAR) of 1MWh in future Capacity Market auctions; and when he expects that PAR to be implemented.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224768","224768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222485","2015-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on consumers' electricity bills of reducing the Price Average Reference to 1MWh by 2018.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224766","224766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222486","2015-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of reducing the Price Average Reference to 1MWh by 2018 on the cost of running future Capacity Market auctions.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224767","224767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222487","2015-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the cost to energy bill payers of all subsidies to wind turbines in the (a) >100 to 500kW and (b) >500kW to 1.5MW feed-in tariff bands in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224759","224759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222488","2015-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will estimate the additional cost to energy bill payers of the feed-in tariff scheme arising from the practice of de-rating wind turbines.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224760","224760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222489","2015-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the average cost to domestic consumers per kWh of gas in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) each English region in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224754","224754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222490","2015-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the average cost to domestic consumers per kWh of electricity in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) each English region in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224755","224755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222491","2015-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households have received support through the Green Deal in (a) Bradford East constituency and (b) Bradford to date.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224733","224733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222492","2015-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many wind turbines have been installed in the Yorkshire and Humber region between (a) 2005-10 and (b) 2010-15.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224731","224731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222493","2015-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the ability of community energy co-operatives to deliver reduced energy prices in the UK and in comparable countries.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224726","224726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222494","2015-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households have received support through the Energy Companies Obligation in (a) Bradford East constituency and (b) Bradford to date.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224732","224732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222495","2015-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that families with children which fall behind with their energy bills receive the Warm Home Discount.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224563","224563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222496","2015-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the UK's progress towards meeting its 2020 targets established under the Climate Change Act 2008.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224648","224648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222497","2015-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the total value of contracts his Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224658","224658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222498","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the total value of contracts her Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224659","224659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222499","2015-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, under what criteria she evaluates the humaneness of badger culls.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224633","224633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222500","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many times the Thames Barrier has to close in a single year to breach Tier 1 of the Thames Estuary 2100 Plan.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224680","224680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222501","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Summary of badger control monitoring during 2014 published by her Department on 18 December 2014, on what scientific evidence and advice the Chief Veterinary Officer based his conclusion that the pilot badger culls in Somerset show that culling can deliver the level of effectiveness required to be confident of achieving disease control benefits.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224612","224612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222502","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of how many hectares of peat bog were burned by owners of grouse moors in the last full year for which figures are available; and what estimate she has made of the amount of carbon released as a result of such burning.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224555","224555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222503","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the number of endangered and protected birds of prey which have been killed by owners of grouse moors or their employees in the most recent year for which figures are available; and how many of those incidents resulted in a prosecution.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224556","224556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222504","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the prevalence of poisoning of wild animals on grouse moors with (a) carofuran and (b) other substances for which this use is not permitted.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224557","224557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222505","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will require people shooting grouse for sport to have gained basic shooting skills, so birds are killed quickly rather than dying slowly of their injuries.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224558","224558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222506","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will ban the use of lead shot in grouse shooting in order to protect other wildlife.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224559","224559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222507","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effects of intensive, monocultural grouse production on biodiversity.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224560","224560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222508","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the environmental impact of lead discharged during game bird shooting.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224550","224550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222509","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) pheasants and (b) partridges were imported into the UK for the purposes of game shooting in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224551","224551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222510","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of (a) foxes, (b) badgers and (c) domestic pets killed by snare traps since the introduction of the Code of Practice on the use of snares in 2005.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224552","224552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222511","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the total cost to the public purse of subsidies provided to owners and operators of grouse moors was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224553","224553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222512","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much has been spent on maintaining flood defences on the River Ribble in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224693","224693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222513","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what reviews are being conducted into the Thames Barrier or Thames flood defences.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224681","224681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222514","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many times the Thames Barrier has been closed in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224682","224682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222515","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations she has received from farmers affected by the ban on grass cutting and oil seed rape in August seeking a derogation from hedge cutting provisions.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224782","224782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222516","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of farm registrations have been made (a) online and (b) by telephone to date; and what the average cost has been of each such transaction.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224781","224781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222517","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has received on the time taken to process the registration of basic farm payments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224779","224779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222518","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many farmers who have no digital history have been in contact with the Rural Payments Agency.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224777","224777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222519","2015-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what contingency plans the Rural Payments Agency has put in place to process late applications before the window for claims closes in mid-May 2015.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224778","224778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222520","2015-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 104 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, HC 17, what the amount spent was on each instance of business hospitality expenditure totalling more than £500.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224840","224840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222521","2015-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 104 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, HC 17, what the reasons are for the £8.74 million expenditure listed under other expenditure.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224841","224841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222522","2015-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 104 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, HC 17, what the amount spent was on each instance of property rental expenditure totalling more than £5,000.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224842","224842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222523","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 107 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, HC17, what the value is of each piece of residential land worth more than £250,000.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224837","224837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222524","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 107 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, HC17, what the value is of each dwelling worth more than £250,000.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224835","224835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222525","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 107 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, HC17, what the value is of each antique and work of art worth more than £1,000.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224836","224836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222526","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 107 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, HC17, what the value is of each building (excluding dwellings) worth more than £250,000.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224833","224833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222527","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 107 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, HC17, what the value is of each piece of non-residential land worth more than £250,000.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224834","224834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222528","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 104 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, HC17, what the amount spent was on each instance of travel expenditure totalling more than £1,000.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224831","224831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222529","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 105 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, HC17, what the reasons are for the £1.397m expenditure listed under other subscriptions.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224832","224832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222530","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Bangladeshi counterpart on threats to the leader of the Bangladesh National Party and other opposition leaders in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224780","224780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222531","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 104 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, HC17, what the amount spent was on each instance of contractor, consultancy and fee-based services expenditure totalling more than £1,000.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224829","224829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222532","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 104 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, HC17, what the reasons are for the £3.2m expenditure listed under consular.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224830","224830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222533","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance his Department is providing for security in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa province, Pakistan.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224676","224676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222534","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the state of the Israeli-Palestinian peace process.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224686","224686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222535","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent conversations he has had with his international counterparts on the Israeli-Palestinian conflict.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224687","224687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222536","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received on introducing a resolution condemning Bahrain's human rights record at the UN Human Rights Council; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224610","224610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222537","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the Israeli government on the construction of settlements on occupied Palestinian land.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224611","224611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222538","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Malaysia on the conviction on 9 February 2015 of Anwar Ibrahim; when he next plans to visit that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224603","224603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222539","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the total value of contracts his Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224660","224660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222540","2015-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 77 of the British Council's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, what the value is of each tangible fixed asset worth more than £250,000.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224838","224838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222541","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the annual cost of Meningitis B to (a) the NHS and (b) social care.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224825","224825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222542","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Clinical Commissioning groups are wholly compliant with NICE guidance on the provision of fertility treatment.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224824","224824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222543","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many IVF cycles have been provided on the NHS in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224828","224828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222544","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many of the pilots in the Prime Minister's Challenge Fund are not yet fully operational.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224814","224814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222545","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total value of contracts his Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224661","224661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222546","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that local authorities commission adult social care services at an hourly rate which provides for staff to receive the national minimum wage and includes travel time between clients.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224647","224647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222547","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve patient care for people with idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224671","224671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222548","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many registered nurses (a) left and (b) joined NHS employment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224599","224599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222549","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the oral evidence to the Health Committee of Dame Fiona Caldicott, 21 January 2015 to Question 705, what assessment he has made of whether patients who opt out of the care.data scheme will be excluded from NHS services such as bowel screening and e-referrals.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224564","224564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222550","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of income received by commissioning support units from clinical commissioning groups is spent supporting clinical commissioning groups in outsourcing NHS services.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224600","224600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222551","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that patients deemed to have critical need are not affected by the time taken by NHS England to draft a new commissioning policy for ultra-rare treatments.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224644","224644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222552","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what public health grant was awarded to Tower Hamlets in each year from 2005-06 to 2013-14.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224630","224630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222553","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Barts' Trust has paid for locum staff in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224629","224629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222554","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve diagnosis of hepatic encephalopathy.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224619","224619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222555","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the strategy for combating liver disease referred to by the Prime Minister on the 10 Downing Street website on 28 July 2011 has not been published.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224620","224620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222556","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to implement the recommendations of the Lancet Commission report on liver disease, published on 27 November 2014.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224621","224621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222557","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has made an estimate of the change in the number of donor eggs that will be required by the authorisation of mitochondrial donation.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224622","224622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222558","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2015 to Question HL4441, whether the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority imposed sanctions on clinics that had administered reagents to permitted gametes or permitted embryos that are then introduced into patients when the reagents concerned had not been CE marked; and when the Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency was notified of such instances documented in inspection reports.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224623","224623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222559","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, by what mechanisms the care.data programme board will be accountable to (a) Parliament and (b) patients.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224547","224547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222560","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's leaflet Better information means better care, published January 2014, and the oral evidence to the Health Committee of Dame Fiona Caldicott, 21 January 2015 to Question 705, what steps he is taking to ensure that if patients choose to opt out of care.data this will not have any adverse effect on (a) bowel screening, (b) e-referrals and (c) other services.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224561","224561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222561","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that patients who opt-out of the care.data programme are not excluded from certain NHS services before that programme is fully implemented.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224565","224565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222562","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that patients who have opted out of the care.data scheme with a type 2 objection will not be excluded from NHS services such as bowel screening and e-referrals.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224562","224562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222563","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the UK National Screening Committee's policy on screening people over 65 for atrial fibrillation.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224596","224596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222564","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to Freedom to speak up?, the report by Sir Robert Francis QC, published on 11 February 2015, what timetable he has set for the creation of a new support scheme to help NHS whistleblowers who have found themselves out of a job as a result of raising concerns.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224592","224592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222565","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to Freedom to speak up?, the report by Sir Robert Francis QC, published on 11 February 2015, what timescale he has set for NHS trusts to appoint whistleblowing guardians.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224593","224593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222566","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding NHS walk-in centres in (a) Preston, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West received from Government in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013 and (v) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224598","224598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222567","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to Freedom to speak up?, the report by Sir Robert Francis QC, published on 11 February 2015, when he plans to take steps to ensure that NHS whistleblowers are not discriminated against when they apply for other jobs.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224594","224594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222568","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) patients and (b) patients with life-limiting conditions have (i) been assessed by each specialised augmentative and alternative communication (AAC) provider and (ii) had equipment provided by each specialised AAC provider since 5 December 2014.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224700","224700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222569","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) patients and (b) patients with life-limiting conditions have (i) been assessed by each specialised augmentative and alternative communication (AAC) provider and (ii) had equipment provided by each specialised AAC provider in each month since 1 October 2014.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224701","224701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222570","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in Blyth Valley constituency were on methadone maintenance treatment in the last three years; and what proportion of all NHS spending on methadone maintenance treatment was spent in Blyth Valley constituency in that time.","Biography information for Mr Ronnie Campbell","Mr Ronnie Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224698","224698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222571","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many agency nurses were employed by Northumbria Healthcare between 2011 and 2013.","Biography information for Mr Ronnie Campbell","Mr Ronnie Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224699","224699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222572","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2015 to Question 221865, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on future cancer patient outcomes of using alternative cancer drugs fund drugs and conventional treatments instead of any of the treatments due to be delisted.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224723","224723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222573","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made towards full roll-out of the bowel scope screening programme by the end of 2016.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224722","224722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222574","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department is providing to research into the treatment of Crohn's disease.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224718","224718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222575","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the provision of counselling and support to those with Crohn's disease.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224719","224719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222576","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the number of patients (a) on waiting lists and (b) with motor neurone disease on waiting lists at each specialised augmentative and alternative communication provider.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224741","224741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222577","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the waiting times for (a) all patients and (b) patients with motor neurone disease have been at each specialised augmentative and alternative communication provider for (i) the assessment and (ii) the provision of equipment in each month since October 2013.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224742","224742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222578","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2014 to Question 218494, what the reasons were for the reduction in the number of flexible sigmoidoscopy tests carried out in 2013-14 compared to 2012-13.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224743","224743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222579","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 December 2014 to Question 218419 on radiotherapy, how many individual funding requests were (a) received and (b) declined for stereotactic radiosurgery/radiotherapy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224744","224744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222580","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 April 2014, Official Report, columns 261-3W, on psoriasis, what the conclusions were of the NICE Clinical Commissioning Group Outcomes Indicator Set Advisory Committee's review of potential indicators for psoriasis derived from the NICE Psoriasis Quality Standard.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224746","224746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222581","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2014 to Question 216131, what processes will be used to promote specialised commissioning expenditure against nominal clinical commissioning groups budgets; and how the present central NHS England budget for commissioning dialysis services will be transferred to clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224747","224747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222582","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 April 2014, Official Report, columns 261-3W, on psoriasis, what indicators have been proposed to the NICE Clinical Commissioning Group Outcomes Indicator Set Advisory Committee for psoriasis.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224748","224748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222583","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 April 2014, Official Report, columns 261-3W, on psoriasis, what development to Read codes was found to be necessary by the Health and Social Care Information Centre to support the indicators proposed for psoriasis.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224749","224749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222584","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the transfer of kidney dialysis commissioning to local clinical commissioning groups on future capital funding for maintenance and renewal of dialysis facilities and equipment.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224750","224750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222585","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings Ministers in his Department have had with the North West Amublance Service on ambulance cover and ambulance waiting times in (a) Preston and (b) the North West in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224790","224790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222586","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the meningitis B vaccine to be made available on the NHS; and what steps he is taking to make progress on price negotiations with Novartis for that vaccine.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224761","224761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222587","2015-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that the disability benefits regime takes into account the symptoms of multiple sclerosis which are sometimes hidden.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224772","224772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222588","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent research his Department has conducted, funded or commissioned into the transmission of antimicrobial resistance from animal pathogens to human pathogens.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224785","224785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222589","2015-02-24","Cabinet Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many teenage girls and women died in each of the last five years from toxic shock syndrome caused by tampon use.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224770","224770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222590","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that multiple sclerosis is detected at the earliest possible stage.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224771","224771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222591","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2015 to Question 223644, how many children who (a) were admitted to a hospital bed because of a psychiatric condition and (b) attended A&E with a diagnosis of psychiatric conditions were not attending for the first time.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224821","224821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222592","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with multiple sclerosis receive adequate treatment, care and support.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224773","224773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222593","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to provide additional support for girls with autism.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224806","224806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222594","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the incidence of Crohn's disease.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224776","224776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222595","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that sufficient numbers of clinicians capable of diagnosing and treating autism are being trained in (a) Hull and (b) England.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224803","224803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222596","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Children and Young People's Mental Health and Wellbeing Taskforce will examine the specific issue of challenges accessing a diagnostic assessment for children with suspected autism.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224804","224804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222597","2015-02-25","Department of Health","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Children and Young People's Mental Health and Wellbeing Taskforce will examine local commissioning of autism services.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224805","224805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222598","2015-02-25","Home Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which police stations in each constabulary in the North West have been (a) closed and (b) reduced to part time status since June 2010.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224739","224739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222599","2015-02-25","Home Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many newly qualified police officers have been employed in (a) Preston and (b) each constabulary in the North West of England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224737","224737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222600","2015-02-24","Cabinet Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many incidents of domestic violence were reported in (a) Preston, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224696","224696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222601","2015-02-24","Cabinet Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many knife crimes were reported in (a) Preston, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224697","224697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222602","2015-02-24","Cabinet Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many drug-related crimes were reported in (a) Preston, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224695","224695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222603","2015-02-24","Home Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons the cost of a gun licence has been set at £50 since 2001; and what the net cost to the public purse of the gun licensing system was, including the cost of background checks, in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224554","224554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222604","2015-02-24","Home Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the UK's capacity to provide further resettlement opportunities to Syrian refugees whose individual medical or humanitarian needs cannot be met in refugee camps in Syria's neighbouring countries.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224549","224549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222605","2015-02-24","Home Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been referred to her Department by the United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees for resettlement in the UK through the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Relocation scheme to date.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224609","224609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222606","2015-02-25","Home Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people granted discretionary leave to remain between October 2011 and September 2014 who have subsequently made an application for further leave are awaiting a decision on the subsequent application.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224640","224640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222607","2015-02-24","Home Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total value of contracts her Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224662","224662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222608","2015-02-25","Home Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what account she took of the recommendations of (a) the Report of the Modern Slavery Bill Evidence Review presented to her on 16 December 2013 and (b) the report from the Joint Committee on the Draft Modern Slavery Bill published on 3 April 2014, HC 1019, when establishing the review of migrant domestic worker arrangements.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224810","224810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222609","2015-02-24","Department for International Development","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the total value of contracts her Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224663","224663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222610","2015-02-25","Department for International Development","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what financial contribution the Government plans to make to the United Nations Relief and Works Agency for Palestine Refugees in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224636","224636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222611","2015-02-24","Department for International Development","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to work with the government of Malawi to enhance financial controls and transparency in that country, with a view to restoring bilateral support by the UK.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224577","224577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222612","2015-02-24","Department for International Development","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding has been allocated to NGOs and other non-state actors since bilateral support to Malawi was suspended in November 2013; and what the expected outcomes of that funding are.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224579","224579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222613","2015-02-24","Department for International Development","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations her Department has made to the Malawian government on the introduction of user fees for health and education services in that country.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224578","224578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222614","2015-02-24","Department for International Development","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department is providing for security in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa province, Pakistan.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224677","224677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222615","2015-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer on 12 February 2015 to Question 223311, what calculations were made to determine that to answer the original question would incur disproportionate costs.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224672","224672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222616","2015-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many domestic violence courts sat at each magistrates' court in Lancashire in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224736","224736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222617","2015-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the contribution by the hon. Member for North West Cambridgeshire of 18 March 2014, Official Report, column 625 and pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 217723, how many (a) ex-parte non-molestation orders were given to (i) women and (ii) men, (b) with notice non-molestation orders were given to (i) women and (ii) men, (c) non-molestation orders were applied for by each firm of solicitors, (d) non-molestation orders were given to (i) women and (ii) men by each judge, (e) ex-parte occupancy orders were given to (i) women and (ii) men, (f) with notice occupancy orders were given to (i) women and (ii) men, (g) occupancy orders were applied for by each firm of solicitors, (h) occupancy orders were given to (i) women and (ii) men by each judge in each quarter from the first quarter of 2011 to the third quarter of 2014 in courts in (A) Sussex and (B) the West Midlands.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224775","224775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222618","2015-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the letter sent on 2 February 2015 to the hon. Member for Birmingham, Yardley by HM Courts and Tribunals Service's Performance, Analysis and Reporting Team, what the (a) name of the judge, (b) date and (c) period of committal was of each court order issued by (i) Birmingham County Court, (ii) Birmingham High Court and (iii) Birmingham Family Court for contempt of court since November 2014.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224769","224769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222619","2015-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers have been dismissed (a) in total and (b) through lack of capacity following an employment tribunal hearing in the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224545","224545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222620","2015-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted of causing death by dangerous driving have not been subject to automatic release in the last three years.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224635","224635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222621","2015-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total value of contracts his Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224664","224664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222622","2015-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of local magistrate advisory boards were (a) women, (b) men, (c) of BAME origin and (d) aged over 65 on 1 April (i) 1989, (ii) 1994, (iii) 2000, (iv) 2005, (v) 2010 and (vi) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224616","224616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222623","2015-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who the members are of each local magistrate advisory board.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224614","224614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222624","2015-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of local magistrate advisory boards are (a) sitting magistrates and (b) non-magistrates.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224615","224615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222625","2015-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's press release Damian Green: new rehabilitation powers for magistrates, published on 25 March 2014, when he plans to publish a White Paper on magistrates' reform.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224617","224617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222626","2015-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of the total work undertaken in magistrates' courts was presided over by (a) lay magistrates and (b) district judges on 1 April (i) 1989, (ii) 1994, (iii) 2000, (iv) 2005, (v) 2010 and (vi) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224618","224618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222627","2015-02-24","Northern Ireland Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the total value of contracts her Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224665","224665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222628","2015-02-25","Prime Minister","2015-02-20","To ask the Prime Minister, when and how he was first made aware of files relating to HSBC and tax evasion.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224819","224819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222629","2015-02-24","Scotland Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the total value of contracts his Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224666","224666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222630","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total value of contracts his Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224667","224667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222631","2015-02-25","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the cost of replacing Pacer trains in the Northern rail franchise due to start in February 2016.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224646","224646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222632","2015-02-25","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the breakdown of Fareham Maritime Operations Centre's VHF radio network on 2 February 2015, how long the breakdown lasted; which body of water was affected by the breakdown; which communications systems were affected by the breakdown; and what information his Department holds on attempts by vessels on the waters affected during the period of the breakdown to make contact with the Coastguard Service using the affected communications networks.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224650","224650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222633","2015-02-25","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of whether the Coastguard Service's VHF radio systems are fit for purpose (a) generally and (b) in relation to the work of the Maritime Operations Centre at Fareham.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224651","224651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222634","2015-02-25","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish evidence held by his Department supporting the conclusion that passengers on Great Western services do not wish to have buffet cars on the new Intercity Express Programme trains.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224624","224624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222635","2015-02-25","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to sign off the Great Western direct award.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224625","224625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222636","2015-02-25","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what total amount his Department has spent on consultant fees for the Great Western direct award to date.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224626","224626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222637","2015-02-25","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what total amount his Department has spent on consultant fees relating to the Intercity Express Programme to date.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224627","224627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222638","2015-02-25","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Great Western direct award will specify that guards will be responsible for the opening and closing of doors on the new Intercity Express Programme trains.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224628","224628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222639","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Hitachi and Agility Trains on future maintenance depots for the new Intercity Express Programme trains in use for (a) Great Western and (b) East Coast services.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224608","224608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222640","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the performance of Govia in operating the Thameslink franchise.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224595","224595"
