"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765306","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the efficacy of the apprenticeship levy on funding police training in Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105684","105684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765307","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2017 to Question 10312, how many UK Border Force officers were deployed in each month between August 2016 and August 2017.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105685","105685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765308","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to (a) include harm reduction within the remit of the Recovery Champion and (b) appoint a bespoke harm reduction champion as part of the Government's new drugs strategy.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105686","105686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765309","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the lack of paid leave on the take-up of the Employer Supported Policing scheme.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105664","105664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765310","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will take steps to introduce paid leave for special constables to access training through the Employer Supported Policing scheme.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105665","105665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765311","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, whether it is her policy to extend visa entitlement to the spouses and dependents of EU academics who can work in the UK after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105612","105612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765312","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications from unaccompanied children her Department is considering under the Dublin III Regulation.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105617","105617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765313","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions fire service response times have been extended as a result of new build housing developments not being included in GPS navigation systems in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105547","105547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765314","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions the police response has been delayed as a result of new build housing developments not being included in GPS navigation systems in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105548","105548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765315","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what representations she has received from universities and national academies on the potential effect of changes to freedom of movement on the UK's ability to attract and retain high quality researchers.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105594","105594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765316","2017-10-11","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2017 to Question 6357, which police forces have seen their budgets (a) decrease and (b) increase in real terms since 2015.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105689","105689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765317","2017-10-11","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2017 to Question 6345, how much each police force has received through the Police Transformation Fund.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105690","105690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765318","2017-10-11","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether allegations made under the Prevention of Terrorism Act 2005 are held by police on a person's record.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105696","105696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765319","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an assessment of the potential effect of no longer having access to the second generation Schengen Information System on her Department's ability speedily to secure the arrest and extradition of suspects who flee to the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105757","105757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765320","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library data on the average waiting times for case resolution for asylum seekers in cases involving torture for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105758","105758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765321","2017-10-10","Wales Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much the Government has spent from the public purse on undertaking legal cases against the Government of Wales since 2011.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105759","105759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765322","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that funding to support the electoral process is effectively disbursed to help stabilise the political climate in the Democratic Republic of Congo; and whether she will take steps to increase funding for civic education and the training of independent electoral observers.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105560","105560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765323","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answers of 18 July 2017 to Questions 4979 and 4980, for what reasons there was a reduction in ICS (a) expenditure in financial year 2016-17 and (b) participants in 2016.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105621","105621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765324","2017-10-11","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8642, on Palestinians: schools, what criteria her Department applied in its assessment of the findings and recommendations of the IMPACT-se report on the Palestinian Elementary School Curriculum 2016-17, published in April 2017.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105565","105565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765325","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the UK's international aid budget is managed by the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105629","105629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765326","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what information her Department holds of instances when the work of organisations in receipt of its funding or other support has been materially affected by the enforcement by the Government of Israel of Amendment 27 to the Entry into Israel law of 1952.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105646","105646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765327","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the potential implications for the development of the Palestinian Territories of Amendment 27 to the Entry into Israel law of 1952.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105643","105643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765328","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 7998, on secondments, what assessment she has made of the reasons for the rise in applications in 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105436","105436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765329","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of progress towards the amount the Government pledged for education in Syria at the London donor conference in February 2016.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105487","105487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765330","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many child victims of sexual abuse have been denied compensation by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority (CICA) since 1996 on the grounds that (a) they had unspent convictions, (b) they had not falsely given consent as a result of being groomed and (c) made an application to CICA more than two years after (i) the date of the assault and (ii) the time they reported it to the police and (iii) if they were under 18 at the time of the incident, failed to make the complaint by their 20th birthday.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105485","105485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765331","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much additional funding he plans for each community rehabilitation company to receive in 2017.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105460","105460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765332","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much each community rehabilitation company received in additional funding in 2016.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105461","105461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765333","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which community rehabilitation companies have requested additional funding in 2016.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105459","105459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765334","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department's budget is sufficient to provide additional funding to community rehabilitation companies.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105456","105456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765335","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the business cases for requests for additional funding by community rehabilitation companies.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105457","105457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765336","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which community rehabilitation companies have requested additional funding in 2017.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105458","105458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765337","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8042, on Ministry of Justice: cybercrime, whether his Department requires contractors to have obtained a certificate from the Government Cyber Essentials scheme; and how many and what proportion of contractors doing work for his Department have obtained such a certificate.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105666","105666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765338","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress has been made on plans to tackle bogus holiday sickness claims.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105672","105672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765339","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what meetings (a) he and (b) his predecessor has had with community rehabilitation companies in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017 to date.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105569","105569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765340","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to extend provision of problem-solving courts.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105570","105570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765341","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to enhance joint-working between probation services and sentencers.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105571","105571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765342","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure the continuing professional development of existing prison officers.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105572","105572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765343","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to improve the training of new prison officers.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105573","105573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765344","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to extend statutory status to the office of the Prisons and Probation Ombudsman.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105574","105574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765345","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department's budget is sufficient to fund the 1.7 per cent pay rise for prison officers without decreasing spending on other departmental responsibilities.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105575","105575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765346","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has allocated to improve prison buildings in England and Wales.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105576","105576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765347","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mental health staff are deployed at each prison in England and Wales.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105577","105577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765348","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the Scottish Government's plans to restrict sentences of less than 12 months on (a) overcrowding, (b) safety and (c) reoffending.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105578","105578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765349","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of days is for which offenders are incarcerated in each prison in England and Wales.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105579","105579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765350","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that it achieves value for money when it sells former prison sites.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105580","105580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765351","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what valuations his Department has received of prisons selected for closure.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105581","105581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765352","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to introduce statutory purposes for prisons.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105582","105582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765353","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners were in prison due to licence recalls in each year since 1990.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105583","105583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765354","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners recalled on licence were (a) men and (b) women in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105584","105584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765355","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to improve oversight of licence recalls.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105585","105585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765356","2017-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Youth Justice of 25 April 2017, Official Report, column 993, on Cammell Laird, what steps he has taken following that contribution to look at that case further.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105692","105692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765357","2017-10-16","Northern Ireland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the provision of children's services across the border for young people in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105502","105502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765358","2017-10-10","Northern Ireland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which non-governmental organisations (a) he, (b) Ministers and (c) Officials of his Department have met since January 2017.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105488","105488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765359","2017-10-10","Scotland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will publish the Memorandum of Terms of Occupation for each building that his Department occupies.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105440","105440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765360","2017-10-10","Scotland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2017 to Question 1974, on social media, how much of that spend was (a) through Carat Ltd and (b) on the departmental procurement card.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105441","105441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765361","2017-10-10","Scotland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8783, on Scotland Office: buildings, (a) for what buildings and (b) to who those fees have been paid.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105528","105528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765362","2017-10-10","Scotland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2017 to Question 5447, on Scotland Office: social media, if he will make the advertisements available in an alternative format accessible to people who lack access to online facilities and social media.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105631","105631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765363","2017-10-10","Scotland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the devolution of powers over research and innovation to Scotland.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105613","105613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765364","2017-10-10","Scotland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the devolution of powers over research and innovation to Scotland.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105614","105614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765365","2017-10-10","Scotland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what discussions he has had with Scottish universities and the Royal Society of Edinburgh on the devolution of powers over research and innovation to Scotland.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105615","105615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765366","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to review the decision to cancel the electrification of the TransPennine Express route between Leeds and Manchester.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105678","105678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765367","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 September 2017 to Question 10187, on High Speed 2: redundancy, what the planned salaries are for (a) the HR Director, (b) Finance Managers, (c) Senior HR Business Managers, (d) the Head of Employee Relations and (e) the Interim Director of Organisational Development.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105524","105524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765368","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to reduce passenger fares on trains between Hull and (a) Liverpool and (b) Leeds; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105539","105539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765369","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to improve rail services in the North East of England.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105468","105468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765370","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to fund increases in line speed on the railway between Plymouth and Exeter.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105471","105471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765371","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9220, what services his Department has received in connection with High Speed 2; and how much was paid for each such service.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105527","105527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765372","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8043, how many and what proportion of firms have a Cyber Essentials qualification; and whether that qualification is a requirement for delivering work procured by his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105520","105520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765373","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve road safety on the A19.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105661","105661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765374","2017-10-11","Wales Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with reference to the Answer of 26 April 2017 to Question 71604, on EU grants and loans: Wales, whether the Shared Prosperity Fund will disburse to the Government of Wales sums at least equal to the amounts for European Structural and Investments funds as set out in that Answer.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105961","105961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765375","2017-10-11","Wales Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the establishment of the Shared Prosperity Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105962","105962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765376","2017-10-11","Wales Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 7156, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on specific recommendations as to which EU programmes operating in Wales the Government should contribute towards to continue to access after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105963","105963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765377","2017-10-10","Women and Equalities","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 14 September 2017 to Question 9679, on Government Equalities Office: Behavioural Insights Team, how many projects the Behavioural Insights Team worked on; and what the goals of each such project were.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105504","105504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765378","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures are currently in place to combat sex trafficking in the Swansea area.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105478","105478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765379","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what process is in place to identify people who are unable to make applications online for universal credit as a result of a disability.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105495","105495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765380","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether new claimants receive an email acknowledgement of their submission of an online claim for universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105496","105496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765381","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 September 2017 to Question 9688, on Department for Work and Pensions: Behavioural Insights Team, what projects the Behavioural Insights Team worked on; and what estimate he has made of the value of each such project to the public purse.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105503","105503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765382","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department made of alternatives to closing Tilehead Jobcentre; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105501","105501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765383","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, by when he plans to extend the universal credit landlord portal to all social sector landlords operating in Wirral.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105446","105446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765384","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of jobseekers' interviews with work coaches lasted (a) 10 minutes or less, (b) 20 minutes or less and (c) more than 20 minutes, in the most recent 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105447","105447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765385","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's policy is on the setting of time limits for jobseekers' interviews with their work coaches.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105448","105448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765386","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department has issued to Jobcentre Plus managers on setting time limits for jobseeker's interviews with work coaches.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105449","105449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765387","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations his Department has received on the effect of the closure of jobcentre plus offices on local communities.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105681","105681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765388","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Hartlepool have appealed against his Department's decision not to grant them personal independence payments in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105660","105660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765389","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it remains his policy to double relationship support funding to £70 million during the course of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105652","105652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765390","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when tenders for the new £30 million inter-parental conflict programme announced in April 2017 will be published.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105653","105653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765391","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial provision there is for people in need of family counselling services who are unable to pay for such services.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105654","105654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765392","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve support for early intervention family counselling.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105655","105655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765393","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish the full report of his Department's yellow card early warning trial evaluation pilot conducted in Scotland in 2016 benefit sanctions.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105566","105566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765394","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 7125, on jobcentres: staff, if he will publish a list of the (a) intervention types identified by his Department and (b) average length of time his Department allocates to each such intervention type.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105567","105567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765395","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what impact assessment his Department carried out before raising the pension age to 68 for prison officers.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105698","105698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765396","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department had with trade unions in (a) Scotland and (b) the rest of the UK before raising the pension age to 68 for prison officers.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105699","105699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765397","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department had with the Scottish Government before raising the pension age to 68 for prison officers.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105700","105700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765398","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2017 to Question 6180, what the level of allowance was for the plan to enrol and adopt SMETS1 meters into the Data and Communications Company in the 2016 cost-benefit analysis.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105622","105622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765399","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2017 to Question 6168, whether an assessment has been made of the potential effect of the interoperability of SMETS1 on the expected benefits of the Smart Meter Roll-out Scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105620","105620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765400","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of domestic regulatory options through the National Grid and Ofgem on allowing merchant gas assets to remain competitive until changes to EU law are implemented.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105637","105637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765401","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what energy contingencies the UK will rely on after the recent closure of the Rough gas storage facility.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105638","105638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765402","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on gas security of supply in the event that Interconnector UK closes after the end of its contract in October 2018.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105639","105639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765403","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the UK's merchant gas interconnectors of the EU network codes governing gas transmission operators.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105640","105640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765404","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what alternative regulatory frameworks his Department has considered following the cessation of storage at the Rough gas storage facility to ensure that Interconnector UK is able to continue to operate.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105641","105641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765405","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the closure of Interconnector UK on the security of UK gas supplies, market volatility and consumer household gas prices.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105642","105642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765406","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to meet senior representatives from the Civil Nuclear Police Federation to discuss a realistic retirement age for its members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105679","105679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765407","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has in place to monitor and review the benefits of the minimum energy standards post-implementation in 2018; and what assessment his Department has made of the scope for strengthening those plans.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105669","105669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765408","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the future of the Centre for Applied Photonics at the University of Strathclyde.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105588","105588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765409","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Scotland on the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the future of the Centre for Applied Photonics at the University of Strathclyde.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105589","105589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765410","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what assessment the Government has made on the potential effect on the UK research and innovation sector of the UK no longer being able to continue working through EUREKA, CERN, ESA or EBI after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105590","105590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765411","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what assessment the Government has made on the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on its targets of UK research and development spending reaching 2.4 per cent of GDP by 2027; and what steps he plans to take to ensure that that target is reached.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105591","105591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765412","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, whether the seven EU Reference Laboratories based in the UK will be relocated after the UK leaves the EU; whether an economic assessment has been carried out on the potential effects of such relocation; and whether an assessment has been carried out on the potential effect of such relocation on the future of UK research.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105595","105595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765413","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, how much funding the UK has received in each of the last five years from the Horizon 2020 programme; and what those amounts were as a proportion of the total EU-wide funding in each of those years.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105596","105596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765414","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the space sector in Scotland.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105597","105597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765415","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what discussions he has had with representatives of the Glasgow-based space sector on the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the future of that sector.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105598","105598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765416","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Scotland on retaining the UK's place in EU space programmes.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105599","105599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765417","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the amount of electricity was in (a) megawatts and (b) as a proportion of the overall total, produced by coal fired power stations in the UK in (i) the fourth quarter of 2016, (ii) the first quarter of 2017 and (iii) the second quarter of 2017.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105444","105444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765418","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what financial support is available for pensioners living in park homes to assist with the costs of implementing energy efficiency measures.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105531","105531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765419","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to improve energy efficiency for pensioners living in park homes.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105532","105532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765420","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support manufacturers in the North West.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105533","105533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765421","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support job creation schemes in (a) the North West and (b) Blackburn with Darwen.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105534","105534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765422","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support business growth schemes in (a) the North West and (b) Blackburn with Darwen.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105535","105535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765423","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on employment of the introduction of autonomous vehicles.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105482","105482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765424","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to introduce an energy price cap.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105467","105467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765425","2017-10-10","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 19 September 2017 to Question 10040, how much of the amount paid in exit schemes in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17 was paid to (i) men and (ii) women.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105523","105523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765426","2017-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8561, what the evidential basis is for his statement that Parliament has agreed that the Government need not publish anything that would undermine its ability to negotiate the best deal for the UK.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105500","105500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765427","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps he is taking during negotiations on the UK leaving the EU to establish recognition in EU countries of UK degrees completed by (a) UK and (b) EU students after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105492","105492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765428","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish a timeline for the registration process for non-UK EU citizens applying to remain in the UK following March 2019.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105483","105483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765429","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what representations he has made to other EU member states on UK collaboration with EU research programmes after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105600","105600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765430","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what representations the Government has received from UK nationals who work as researchers in other EU countries on UK collaboration with EU research programmes after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105601","105601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765431","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what representations the Government has received from researchers from other EU countries on UK collaboration with EU research programmes after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105602","105602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765432","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what role he plans for the devolved administrations to have in negotiations on UK collaboration with EU research programmes after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105603","105603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765433","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what role he plans for UK universities and national academies to have in negotiations on UK collaboration with EU research programmes after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105604","105604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765434","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what discussions he has had with Scottish universities and the Royal Society of Edinburgh on a future UK-EU science research framework.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105605","105605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765435","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on a future UK-EU science research framework.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105606","105606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765436","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on continued participation in EU and Euratom research programmes.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105607","105607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765437","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on continued participation in EU and Euratom research programmes.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105608","105608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765438","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, whether it is his policy that the UK should remain a participant in Horizon 2020 throughout any transitional period.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105609","105609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765439","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: A Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what discussions the Government has had with UK universities and national academies on the content of that paper.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105610","105610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765440","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, what discussions he has had with non-EU participants in EU science programmes on the UK adopting similar association frameworks to those which such non-EU participants have with the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105592","105592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765441","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Government's policy paper, Collaboration on Science and Innovation: Future Partnership Paper, published on 6 September 2017, whether it is his policy to request UK membership of the European Strategy Forum on Research Infrastructures after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105593","105593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765442","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many UK citizens are in receipt of a pension from another EU member state.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105635","105635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765443","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support has been provided to British nationals affected by recent events in Catalonia.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106299","106299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765444","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to implement the recommendations of the Lammy Review, an independent review into the treatment of, and outcomes for, Black, Asian and Minority Ethnic individuals in the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106360","106360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765445","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government plans to halt the roll-out of universal credit.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106361","106361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765446","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to Question 9514, tabled on 7 September 2017 by the hon. Member for Denton and Reddish.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106035","106035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765447","2017-10-11","Prime Minister","2017-10-06","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions she had on the case of Raif Badawi during her meeting with the Saudi Arabian Minister for Foreign Affairs in September 2017; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106251","106251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765448","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support the Government plans to provide to children and young adults affected by valproate after their birth (a) now and (b) over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106362","106362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765449","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will meet people who have been harmed by sodium valproate during pregnancy; and what steps he has to provide compensation to such people.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106363","106363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765450","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will meet the Chair of the All-Party Parliamentary Group on anti-epileptic drugs in pregnancy to discuss the effect of people harmed by sodium valproate prescribed during pregnancy.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106364","106364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765451","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the number of babies harmed by  valproate prescribed during pregnancy.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106365","106365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765452","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his Department's policy to introduce a care compensation plan similar to plans already introduced in other EU states for people harmed by valproate prescribed during pregnancy since 1973.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106366","106366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765453","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions (a) he, (b) Ministers and (c) officials of his Department have had with their counterparts in the EU regarding valproate.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106367","106367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765454","2017-10-11","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 15 September 2017 to Question 9154, whether he discussed the Bombardier-Boeing dispute with Commerce Secretary Wilbur Ross during his visit to the US in July 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106245","106245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765455","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether mental health will be included on the agenda for the Commonwealth Summit 2018.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106082","106082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765456","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to raise the issue of mental health and discrimination against people with mental illness at the Commonwealth Summit 2018.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106083","106083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765457","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of UK Border Force officers were absent on each day of August 2017.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105916","105916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765458","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to assist dependents of British citizens who live in Venezuela.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105793","105793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765459","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will visit the National Museum of the Royal Navy in Hartlepool.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105810","105810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765460","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the capital spend on transport per head of population in (a) the North Eastand (b) Hartlepool constituency in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105744","105744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765461","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of 14 to 24-year olds who have been diagnosed with a mental illness in Hartlepool.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105723","105723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765462","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to reply to the letter of 23 June 2017 from the hon. Member for Weston-super-Mare on funding for apprenticeships.","Biography information for John Penrose","John Penrose","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105743","105743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765463","2017-10-11","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many days of operational capacity have been lost at New Brighton Lifeboat Station in Wallasey as a result of the RNLI's decision of July 2016 to reduce the number of volunteers it uses.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106172","106172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765464","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the recent trends in the number of successful personal independence payment tribunal appeals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106173","106173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765465","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to establish an approved list of regulated pension schemes with regulated underlying investments that are deemed safe; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106439","106439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765466","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8352, on personal independence payment (PIP): hearing impairment, what estimate he has made of the cost of developing a joined-up digital journey for PIP claimants with health and disability needs.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106301","106301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765467","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on charges by the Child Maintenance Service when claimants are required to transfer their cases from the Child Support Agency.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106369","106369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765468","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to compel employers to inform departing employees of their pension options.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106150","106150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765469","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support the Government has offered to the Commonwealth of Dominica in the wake of Hurricane Maria and other recent extreme weather events.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106057","106057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765470","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of reports of arrests of people who are (a) perceived or (b) identify as LGBT in Azerbaijan.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106097","106097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765471","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations her Department has received from childcare providers on the effect of the level of central government funding to local authorities for their expanded statutory responsibility to provide free childcare from September 2017 on the (a) pay levels they are able to offer their employees and (b) the experience and qualification levels of the employees they are able to recruit.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106079","106079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765472","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to update his Office's publication entitled List of Ministerial Responsibilities.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106078","106078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765473","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the need for disaster relief and reconstruction funding for the Commonwealth of Dominica in the wake of Hurricane Maria and other recent extreme weather events.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106058","106058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765474","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2017 to Question 10205, whether the choice of the 40th percentile as a cut off point for comparing workless families with families with work on low incomes was based on prior research on (a) similarities in equivalised total household net income and (b) other similarities between these groups.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106087","106087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765475","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2017 to Question 10204, what proportion of children with (a) at least one parent reporting having a longstanding limiting illness or disability, (b) at least one parent reporting having poor mental health, (c) the household reports signs of problem debt and (d) all parents having low or no qualifications are in (i) workless families, (ii) families with work from the bottom 40 per cent of the income distribution and (iii) families with work from the top 60 per cent of the income distribution.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106088","106088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765476","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the UK policy on Yemen is in the (a) short, (b) medium and (c) long-term.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105724","105724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765477","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding the West Yorkshire Combined Authority has received from the public purse for public transport provision in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105739","105739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765478","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of daily smoking levels in the UK each year for the next 15 years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106212","106212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765479","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the scientific evidence upon which the Government based its ban on snus.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106405","106405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765480","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people over 100-years old receive the UK state pension in each country outside the UK.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105738","105738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765481","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) children and (b) unaccompanied children the Government estimates will be resettled under the Vulnerable Children's Resettlement Scheme during the course of the 2017 Parliament.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106207","106207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765482","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many bodies were in receipt of funding from the Regional Development Fund in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) St Helens local authority area, (c) Liverpool City Region, (d) the North West and (e) England in each year for which that fund operated; and how much each such body received in each such year.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105864","105864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765483","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2017 to Question 8037, on Foreign and Commonwealth Office: cybercrime, whether his Department requires contractors to have obtained a certificate from the Government Cyber Essentials scheme; and how many and what proportion of contractors working for his Department have obtained such a certificate.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105823","105823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765484","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many fast stream civil servants work abroad after completing their five-month European placements.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106068","106068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765485","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8714, on Government Property Unit: staff, from which firm the one employee seconded from outside Government was; and to where the four government secondees went outside Government.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105938","105938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765486","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 7039, on senior civil servants: recruitment, if he will provide those figures by (a) Department, (b) profession, (c) function and (d) grade.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106358","106358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765487","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8517, on government departments: email, when the mail check service was introduced; and what proportion of total relevant domains those figures represent.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105936","105936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765488","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8513, on electronic government: proof of identity, what plans he has to roll out Verify to the private sector; and what estimate he has made of the potential receipts to the taxpayer from that roll out.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105941","105941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765489","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8509, on electronic government: proof of identity, what the average success rate for users has been in each month since May 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105942","105942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765490","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8257, on Government Property Unit: staff, how many and what proportion of unit staff are interim staff; and how many such staff are seconded from outside the Government.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105943","105943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765491","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 9192, on electronic government: proof of identity, how many users of the Government Verify Scheme there have been in each (a) Department and (b) year since 2013.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105814","105814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765492","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8508, on the Government Property Unit, what the 13 applications were which were granted with conditions attached to the approval; and what conditions were attached to each of those applications.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105820","105820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765493","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2017 to Question 8361, what the five most common conditions attached to agreements to extend or renew lets with Government Departments are; and to how many agreements each such condition is applied to.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105821","105821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765494","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8718, on the Government Communication Service, what the five projects were that were completed by the Government Communications Service International.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105830","105830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765495","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2017 to Question 8732, from whom that money came; and for the renting of which parts of the estate those sums were charged.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105946","105946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765496","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 October 2017 to Question 7507 on cyber skills, with which organisation and representatives her officials have (a) met and (b) sought advice from.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106069","106069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765497","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8734, on Ministry of Defence: buildings, from whom at what values and in order to rent which parts of the estate that money was collected.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105945","105945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765498","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8834, on civil servants: reserve forces, how many reservists have volunteered from each of those Departments.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105815","105815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765499","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8834, on civil servants: reserve forces, how many reservists have volunteered in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105816","105816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765500","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8765, on Department for Transport: procurement, what the contracts were that took more than (a) two years and (b) one year to procure; and what the values were of those contracts.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105817","105817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765501","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how long on average it has taken to fill a vacant GP post in (a) West Yorkshire, (b) Yorkshire and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106347","106347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765502","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many leave to remain applications on the basis of family and private life were received in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106345","106345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765503","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many leave to remain applications on the basis of family and private life were submitted for a child's right to remain in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106346","106346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765504","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the decision to close the Corner House, Rotherham on the provision of mental health support in Yorkshire.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106359","106359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765505","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average time taken to rehouse an adult male in-patient with complex needs has been following the closure of services in (a) Yorkshire and (b) the UK, in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106354","106354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765506","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many in-patient beds there are for patients with complex needs in (a) West Yorkshire and (b) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106355","106355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765507","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on locum doctors in (a) West Yorkshire, (b) Yorkshire and (c) the UK in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106348","106348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765508","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding the Government has provided to ensure that there are adequate specialist gender identity clinics for people undergoing treatment relating to their identity to be referred to by their GP.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106349","106349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765509","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) funding and (b) training has been provided to GPs to ensure that they and their staff are adequately equipped to support people undergoing treatment relating to their gender identity.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106350","106350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765510","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding has been provided to GPs and technicians to support the prescribing and monitoring of hormone treatments for people undergoing gender transition.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106351","106351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765511","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the decision to close The Corner House, Rotherham on (a) service users, (b) the local population and (c) the landscape of the country's mental health provision.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106038","106038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765512","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 September 2017 to Question 10152, on Department for Transport: redundancy pay, how much of the £6,307,274 awarded in exit payments to core department staff and the £17,011,102 awarded to departmental group staff in 2016 and of the £5,848,495 awarded to core department staff and £17,987,001 awarded to departmental staff in 2015 was awarded to (a) men and (b) women.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105947","105947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765513","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8827, on personal independence payments: complaints, how many of those cases were closed in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106356","106356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765514","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8827, on personal independence payments: complaints, how many cases are waiting to be heard; and how many of those cases have been referred by hon. Members.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106357","106357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765515","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many meetings have taken place between HS2 Ltd and campaign groups from Crofton in Hemsworth constituency.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106352","106352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765516","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many meetings High Speed 2 engagement officers have cancelled in (a) Hemsworth constituency and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106353","106353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765517","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 9648, on Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy: Behavioural Insights Team, what workshops the Behavioural Insights Team provided; and on how many occasions those workshops were provided.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105828","105828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765518","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 9648, on Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy: Behavioural Insights Team, for what purpose the Department undertook randomised control trials.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105826","105826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765519","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 9648, what policy advice the Behavioural Insights Team provided to his Department or former constituent Departments.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105824","105824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765520","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 9648, how much his Department paid the Behavioural Insights Team for each of the services provided.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105825","105825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765521","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 7994, on Department for Exiting the European Union: secondment, from which departments the 350 staff have been seconded from; and how many such staff were seconded from each Department; and on which civil service payscale level such staff are.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105829","105829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765522","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2017 to Question 10041, how many secondments from outside the Government into his Department occurred in the first 12 months of his Department's existence.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105822","105822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765523","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8768, on Department for Work and Pensions: procurement, when his Department will make such detailed reporting available.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105819","105819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765524","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8750, on Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy: procurement, what the contract was that took more than one year to procure.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105818","105818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765525","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 9648, on Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy: Behavioural Insights Team, for what purposes the (a) qualitative and (b) quantitative research were done.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105827","105827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765526","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8787, on Department for Work and Pensions: buildings, whether his Department receives any benefit from the sub-let of surrendered space to Telereal Trillium.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105940","105940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765527","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8833, on HM Revenue and Customs: staff, what pay scales the staff referred to are on.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105937","105937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765528","2017-10-10","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8761, on Department for International Trade: procurement, which two contracts took over three months to procure; which contract took over six months to procure; and which contract took over one year to procure.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105944","105944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765529","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8511, on civil service: secondments, which other departments sent staff to Brussels in any round of negotiations with the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105939","105939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765530","2017-10-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that severely mentally impaired people receive the council tax reductions or exemptions they are legally entitled to.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106163","106163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765531","2017-10-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of severely mentally impaired people who (a) were eligible for and (b) received council tax reductions or exemptions in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106162","106162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765532","2017-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 8695, on consumers, which consumer groups have been invited to the planned roundtable event; when the event is due to be held; and on which dates representatives of his Department met (a) Which?, (b) Money Saving Expert, (c) the British Retail Consortium and (d) Citizens Advice.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106304","106304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765533","2017-10-11","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 28 June 2017 to Question 986, aluminium: USA, what progress he has made in determining the implications of the US Section 232 investigation on the effects of imports of aluminium for the UK steel industry in the talks held with the US Commerce Secretary and US Trade Representative on 19 to 20 June 2017.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106164","106164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765534","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on establishing an industrial energy efficiency scheme to help large companies install measures to reduce their energy use and bills.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105969","105969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765535","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the forthcoming Green Paper on consumer law will include measures to tackle the challenges disabled people face as consumers.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106246","106246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765536","2017-10-11","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of climate change on the geographic range and incidence of malaria.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105987","105987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765537","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to respond to the Murray review of community pharmacy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Sir Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105880","105880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765538","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons methodology used by the Government to calculate the funding formula for 30 hours free childcare for three and four-year olds with working parents did not draw upon data from HM Revenue and Customs or the General Register Office to help calculate how many children would be eligible for that scheme.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105747","105747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765539","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much Early Years Pupil Premium funding remains unclaimed in (a) the Liverpool City Region and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105862","105862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765540","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the take-up rate for the early years pupil premium is in the (a) Liverpool City Region and (b) UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105852","105852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765541","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been allocated to each North West local education authority in round one of the strategic school improvement fund.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105886","105886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765542","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of children who will be (a) eligible for and (b) registered to receive free school meals in each year since 2022 as a result of a parent or guardian being in receipt of (i) universal credit or (ii) legacy benefits.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105955","105955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765543","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the difference between the average rate of take-up for free school meals for eligible families in receipt of (a) universal credit and (b) legacy benefits.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105764","105764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765544","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many working families in receipt of universal credit are (a) eligible and (b) registered for free school meals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105765","105765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765545","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children qualify for free school meals on account of their parent or guardian's receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105766","105766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765546","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many young people in England completed a Level 1 award in construction followed by an on-site NVQ in the most recent 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106120","106120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765547","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of (a) the amount of time children under the age of three spend in front of screens and (b) the effect of that screen time on their development.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106200","106200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765548","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the success rate of appeals against decisions taken by local authorities' licensing committees to limit the supply of cheap, super-strength alcohol has been in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106050","106050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765549","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to make company directors personally liable for tax liabilities and associated legal costs where their company's tax avoidance scheme has been declared unlawful.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105928","105928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765550","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the potential effect on council tax revenue of revaluing properties to their current levels.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105929","105929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765551","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to counter the abuse of non-domicile status for tax purposes.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105930","105930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765552","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the potential effect on tax revenue of abolishing non-domicile status.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105931","105931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765553","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many criminal investigations have been initiated by HM Revenue and Customs against individuals suspected of being involved with tax evasion and aggressive tax avoidance in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105925","105925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765554","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many individuals have been prosecuted for offshore tax evasion in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105926","105926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765555","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on how many occasions the online payment system for anti-money laundering supervision has broken down in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105796","105796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765556","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to prevent the breakdown of the anti-money laundering supervision online payment system.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105797","105797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765557","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of businesses' ability to report to HM Revenue and Customs faults on the anti-money laundering supervision online system.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105798","105798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765558","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many companies supplying goods and services to the Government have been identified as avoiding their tax liabilities in the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105927","105927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765559","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to sections 13 to 16 of the Pension Schemes (Transfers, Reorganisations and Winding Up) (Transitional Provisions) Order 2006, whether he plans to extend this provision to (a) members of the British Steel Pension Scheme and (b) other schemes where a regulated apportionment arrangement has been approved but which have not yet entered Pension Protection Fund assessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106122","106122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765560","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse of tax relief on private pension contributions was in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106090","106090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765561","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many individuals have been registered as non-domicile for tax purposes in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106045","106045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765562","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners gained level 1 qualifications in construction-related skills in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105866","105866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765563","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Chair of the Sentencing Council on linking the length of custodial sentences to the acquisition of specified skills in prison.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106123","106123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765564","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish guidance for local and regional transport authorities on the implementation of the Bus Services Act 2017.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105843","105843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765565","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons families with babies and young children migrating onto universal credit are required to make a new claim for Healthy Start scheme vouchers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106336","106336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765566","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of cognitive behavioural therapy and graded exercise therapy treatment administered by the NHS on the health and wellbeing of people suffering with (a) myalgic encephalomyelitis and (b) chronic fatigue syndrome.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106121","106121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765567","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of eligible families who claim universal credit are registered for healthy start vouchers and vitamins.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105849","105849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765568","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the take-up rate for Healthy Start vouchers is in the (a) Liverpool City Region and (b) local authority areas of (i) Halton, (ii) Knowsley, (iii) Liverpool, (iv) Sefton, (v) St Helens and (vi) the Wirral.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105842","105842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765569","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment he has made of the number and rate of sanctions applied to (a) universal credit and (b) legacy benefit claimants.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105877","105877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765570","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which terminal conditions mean that repeat assessments for employment and support allowance are not required.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105895","105895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765571","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how pensioners in receipt of universal credit in mixed-couple households where one partner is over pensionable age and the other is below will be affected by the under-occupation penalty.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106048","106048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765572","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the two-child limit will apply to existing tax credit claimants when they are migrated onto universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106047","106047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765573","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what arrangements are in place to enable people applying for universal credit who have no fixed address and no access to computers to receive notifications of their appointments with work coaches.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106049","106049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765574","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether tax credit claimants with three children or more will be classified as new claimants when they are migrated to universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106046","106046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765575","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many families with babies and young children have had to reapply for Healthy Start following their migration to universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106044","106044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765576","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many work coaches have been employed in jobcentres in each of the last three years; and what the ratio of work coaches to claimants has been in each of those years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106225","106225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765577","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people repaying a universal credit advance are asked to repay within (a) three and (b) six months; how many of those people have other sums deducted from their monthly payment; and in how many of those cases that total deduction exceeds the maximum recommended amount.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105949","105949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765578","2017-10-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2017 to Question 6312, on carbon emissions, whether his review of the minimum energy performance requirements in the building regulations for new homes will be complete before the publication of the Clean Growth Strategy.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106154","106154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765579","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 July 2017 to Question 724, on high rise flats, when he plans to publish the list of buildings tested.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106063","106063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765580","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if the Government will ensure that all newly built properties designated by local authorities as low-cost housing are sold on a freehold basis.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106399","106399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765581","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether English schools designated with a religious character are able to give preference in connection  with the appointment of a teacher to a person whose religious opinions are in accordance with the tenets of the religion of the school even in cases where a genuine professional or occupational requirement on the basis of religion does not apply to the post in question.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106059","106059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765582","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations officials of her Department have made to the Open University on its policy of not accepting students from Cuba, Syria and Iran.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106060","106060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765583","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the Environment Agency's capacity to maintain those navigable waterways for which it is responsible.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105767","105767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765584","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will provide an update on proposals to transfer waterways run by the Environment Agency to the Canal and River Trust.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105954","105954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765585","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to reduce the number of clinical commissioning groups that have entirely decommissioned IVF services.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106061","106061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765586","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to ensure that patients in England have equal access to comprehensive NHS IVF services.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106062","106062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765587","2017-10-11","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2017 to Question 6358, on police finance, whether the £5 rise has decreased the average difference in precept bills between the lower and higher quartile since it was introduced.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106153","106153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765588","2017-10-11","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of trends in the level of public satisfaction with the 101 police non-emergency number.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106152","106152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765589","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many road traffic accidents in the UK involved in left-hand-drive vehicles in the last two years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106400","106400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765590","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps his Department has taken to reduce the number of road traffic accidents involving left-hand-drive vehicles in the UK.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106401","106401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765591","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will respond to the recommendations in the report by the Sutton Trust, entitled Closing Gaps Early, published in September 2017, on awarding early years teachers with Qualified Teacher Status.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106012","106012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765592","2017-10-11","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 52463, how (a) much of the £40 million available to the Early Years Capital Fund was allocated on conclusion of the bidding process, (b) many projects were approved in December in 2016 and (c) many of those projects were completed by August 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106148","106148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765593","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 8 March 2016 to Question 29036, how much funding her Department has provided to the Association of Independent Local Safeguarding Children's Board Chairs in 2016-17.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106145","106145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765594","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which early years settings the Early Years Minister has visited since taking up her ministerial role.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106141","106141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765595","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of business rates of increases on the (a) number and (b) quality of early years settings in England.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106210","106210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765596","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many child minders were listed on Ofsted's Early Years register in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106144","106144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765597","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which early years settings she has visited in 2016-17.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106142","106142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765598","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on adjusting the total budget allocation for the early years national funding formula to take account of inflation in 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106143","106143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765599","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many tenancies there have been in supported housing in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106204","106204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765600","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much earmarked for the Shared Ownership and Affordable Homes Programme has been spent since the scheme was announced in the Spending Review 2015.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106205","106205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765601","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) local authority and (b) housing association homes in each of London's local authority areas have not met the decent homes standard in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105845","105845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765602","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people who moved into supported housing in 2016-17 are eligible for housing benefit.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106203","106203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765603","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS operational standards have not been met during the period from May 2015 to date.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106201","106201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765604","2017-10-11","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 3 August 2017 to Question 2332, how many people directly affected by the Grenfell Tower fire have been granted 12 months limited leave to remain.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106438","106438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765605","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training posts for nurses were commissioned in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105853","105853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765606","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many general practice speciality training posts were (a) commissioned and (b) filled in (i) 2014-15, (ii) 2015-16 and (iii) 2016-17.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105854","105854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765607","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average number of hours spent on administrative tasks each week by GPs in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105848","105848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765608","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which hospitals he has visited in an official capacity since 9 June 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105847","105847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765609","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2017 to Question 3971 on Down's syndrome: screening, whether NHS England's plans to go live with new genomic laboratory infrastructure remains on course.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106199","106199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765610","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the financial sustainability of NHS services in north west London.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106202","106202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765611","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses have (a) participated in the Return to Practice programme and (b) subsequently returned to practice within the NHS in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106194","106194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765612","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department provides to local authorities on administration of discretionary housing benefit; and what steps his Department is taking to monitor the effectiveness of delivery of that benefit to those most in need.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106250","106250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765613","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will respond to the recommendations of the report by the Sutton Trust entitled Closing Gaps Early, published in September 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106011","106011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765614","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time was for a decision being reached on a claim for employment and support allowance in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105970","105970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765615","2017-10-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which Government departments and agencies have achieved the Food for Life catering award.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106155","106155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765616","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, why Open University students do not qualify for council tax discounts; and whether he plans to review this policy.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106139","106139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765617","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, why the Child Maintenance Service allows non-resident parents £2,500 of unearned income that is not factored into payment plans; and whether he plans to review this policy.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106137","106137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765618","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the (a) effect on living standards and (b) equity of Open University students being ineligible for council tax discounts.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106129","106129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765619","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what role the Small Business Commissioner plays in the formation and delivery of UK industrial strategy.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106138","106138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765620","2017-10-11","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of his Department's policy on employment allowance on (a) employment and (b) small and medium-sized enterprises; and whether he plans to amend the employment allowance policy.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106157","106157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765621","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what action the Government is taking to ensure timely payments to small and medium-sized enterprises; and whether he plans to introduce legislation to ensure that payments to small and medium-sized enterprises are timely.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106156","106156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765622","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of late payments on small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106158","106158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765623","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to revise the process for awarding contracts to private companies for the provision of accommodation for asylum seekers.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106322","106322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765624","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures are in place to ensure that private subcontractors providing accommodation for asylum seekers are meeting the standards of the Housing Act and that such measures are enforced and complaints acted on.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106323","106323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765625","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what undertakings has G4S made to improve service in relation to accommodation for asylum seekers.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106324","106324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765626","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in how many of the last 12 months G4S has met its KPIs for providing accommodation for asylum seekers.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106325","106325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765627","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints have been made against G4S in the last year on its service to asylum seekers.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106326","106326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765628","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have been moved more than four times in a year by (a) G4S and (b) other providers of accommodation for asylum seekers.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106327","106327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765629","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his officials have had with EDF Energy and CGN Energy (a) before 29 July 2016 and (b) after 15 September 2016 on the potential financial consequences for those companies of the decision to delay approval of Hinkley Point C.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106160","106160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765630","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will provide a breakdown of the estimate of the total whole life costs for Hinkley Point C in the major project portfolio data published in September 2016.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106161","106161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765631","2017-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department accepts health visitors as suitable professionals to complete and sign the letter Response from health professional to request for evidence of injuries/condition consistent with domestic violence in pursuit of the granting of legal aid.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106305","106305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765632","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what notice period his Department gave to the industry before the Renewable Heat Incentive Scheme and Domestic Renewable Heat Incentive Scheme (Amendment) (No. 2) Regulations 2017 came into force.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105813","105813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765633","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non molestation orders and prohibited steps orders were issued by the Sussex family courts of (a) Brighton, (b) Chichester, (c) Eastbourne, (d) Hastings, (e) Horsham and (f) Worthing for the first and second quarters of 2017.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105808","105808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765634","2017-10-10","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to make it easier for small and medium-sized enterprises to access UK Export Finance resources.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105737","105737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765635","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission research into the care plan for people harmed by Valproate during pregnancy in France in order to identify potential benefits that such a plan could bring to the UK.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106219","106219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765636","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will meet with INFACT to discuss a care plan compensation package for people harmed by Valproate in pregnancy since 1973.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106222","106222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765637","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of babies harmed by Valproate in pregnancy.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106221","106221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765638","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures the Government is taking to support children with birth defects as a result of valproate taken during pregnancy.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106272","106272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765639","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what projects jointly funded by the private sector Network Rail has completed in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106099","106099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765640","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of regulations introduced earlier in 2017 to restrict access to personal independence payments (PIP) for some groups on take-up of PIP.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106381","106381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765641","2017-10-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his policy is on improving protection for ancient woodland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105971","105971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765642","2017-10-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress his Department is making on implementing the housing white paper of February 2017, Fixing our broken housing market; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105972","105972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765643","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the capped expenditure process on funding for NHS trusts.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106086","106086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765644","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applicants have documents recorded as lost by UK Visas and Immigration in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105855","105855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765645","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much compensation has been paid to applicants for documents recorded as lost by UK Visas and Immigration in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105856","105856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765646","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) non-UK EU and (b) other seasonal agricultural workers who have come to the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106264","106264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765647","2017-10-11","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the report entitled Study of early education and development: the potential value for money of early education, published in July 2017, what the median hourly delivery cost was in early years funding for a three-four-year old place in the east of England.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105968","105968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765648","2017-10-11","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the report entitled Study of early education and development: the potential value for money of early education, published in July 2017, what the modal hourly delivery cost was in early years funding for a three-four-year old place in the east of England.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105967","105967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765649","2017-10-11","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of NHS doctors have completed foundation training and progressed into speciality training in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105988","105988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765650","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times Section 135 of the Mental Health Act 1983 has been used (a) in total, (b) by region and (c) by ethnic group in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106432","106432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765651","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has to introduce new regulations under section 136 of the Mental Health Act 1983 in relation to amendments to that Act brought in under the Policing and Crime Act 2017.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106409","106409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765652","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times the Mental Health Act 1983 has been used for the purposes of detention by ethnic group in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106431","106431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765653","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times Section 136 of the Mental Health Act 1983 has been used (a) in total, (b) by region and (c) by ethnic group in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106433","106433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765654","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times Section 3 of the Mental Health Act 1983 has been used (a) in total, (b) by region and (c) by ethnic group in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106434","106434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765655","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times Section 2 of the Mental Health Act 1983 has been used (a) in total, (b) by region and (c) by ethnic group in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106435","106435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765656","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people presented as homeless in each local authority area in England and Wales in each month from January 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106128","106128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765657","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information her Department holds on the number of council-funded library sites in the South East which have closed in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106053","106053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765658","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information her Department holds on the number of council-funded library sites across England in each local authority which have closed in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106052","106052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765659","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of replacing the work capability assessment with separate assessments for employment support and for financial support; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106211","106211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765660","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will collect and publish quarterly data on the number and proportion of universal credit claimants who fall into rental arrears each month.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106208","106208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765661","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to allow local authorities to implement mandatory licensing for landlords; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105736","105736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765662","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government has made an estimate of the number of work hours for which people cannot work on account of free childcare not being available for a full week of 37.5 hours and during school holidays.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105734","105734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765663","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the letter she received from the Chief Constable of Avon and Somerset Police dated 18 September 2017, what resources she plans to provide to prevent that force reaching breaking point.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106040","106040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765664","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Government plans for funding relative to burden of disease to reach parity across mental and physical health.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105735","105735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765665","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy of 12 July 2017, Official Report, columns 108-10WH, what progress has been made on delivering an alternative body to Euratom ahead of the UK's proposed withdrawal from Euratom in May 2019.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106337","106337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765666","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans the Government has to leave the European Economic Area.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106039","106039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765667","2017-10-11","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to address the unmet social care needs of working-age disabled people.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105977","105977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765668","2017-10-11","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his planned consultation on social care will include working-age disabled people's social care.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105978","105978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765669","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of ending free school transport at 16-years old on the number of students continuing to study to age 18; and what estimate she has made of the quantum of costs per student for people aged over 16 not able to use free school transport.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105725","105725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765670","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of claims that song-birds are being illegally trapped on land forming part of the UK Sovereign Base Territory in Cyprus.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106224","106224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765671","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of prison-based de-radicalisation programmes; and what improvements have been made to such programmes in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106223","106223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765672","2017-10-11","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Memorandum of Understanding between her Department and the Palestinian Authority (PA), what discussions she has had with the PA on the Electronic Crimes Law adopted in July 2017.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106170","106170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765673","2017-10-11","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Memorandum of Understanding between her Department and the Palestinian Authority (PA), what discussions she has had with the PA on proposed legislation allowing the executive branch to dismiss judges.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106171","106171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765674","2017-10-11","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Memorandum of Understanding between the Palestinian Authority (PA) and her Department, what discussions she has had with the PA on its funding of summer camps named after Dalal Mughrabi.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106169","106169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765675","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) doctors, (b) midwives and (c) nurses and health visitors were employed by the North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust in each year between 2014 and 2017.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106009","106009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765676","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) doctors, (b) midwives and (c) nurses and health visitors were employed by the Royal Free London NHS Trust in each year between 2014 and 2017.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106010","106010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765677","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Work and Pensions of 17 January 2017, Official Report, column 279WH, what assessment he has made of the cost of index-linking pension rights acquired before 1997 for members of the Digital Equipment Ltd pension scheme.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105966","105966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765678","2017-10-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much each branch of the armed forces spent on advertising and marketing for recruitment purposes in each year from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106165","106165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765679","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the potential benefits to the Welsh economy of basing Welsh regiments in Wales when those regiments are not on active service.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105859","105859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765680","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of potential locations in Wales that could be used to base Welsh regiments when those regiments are not on active service.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105857","105857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765681","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of age-gaming applications that replicate gambling activities in order to stop children accessing such applications.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105794","105794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765682","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of publishing advice for parents and carers on the potential dangers of young people playing online games that encourage them to gamble.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105795","105795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765683","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to uprate the annual Christmas bonus for recipients of benefits.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106176","106176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765684","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the annual cost for the Christmas bonus for recipients of benefits was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106177","106177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765685","2017-10-10","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2017 to Question 8328, what assessment his Department made of the human rights records of those countries his Department invited to attend the Defence and Security Equipment International Exhibition that was held in London in September 2017 prior to those invitations being sent.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105858","105858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765686","2017-10-10","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2017 to Question 8328, what factors his Department took into account when deciding which countries to invite to the Defence and Security Equipment International Exhibition that was held in London in September 2017.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105860","105860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765687","2017-10-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funds are provided for the maintenance of national trails for each year to 2021; and what sum has been allocated to maintain the Pennine Way.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106302","106302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765688","2017-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Saudi Arabia on support for UK nationals traveling to Saudi Arabia for the Hajj pilgrimage in the event they encounter any difficulties with their tour operators; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105986","105986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765689","2017-10-11","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of applicants for premium service visas wait more than one month to be allocated a caseworker.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105973","105973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765690","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that all operators and travel agents offering tours to Mecca and the Hajj pilgrimage are meeting the standards set out in consumer protection legislation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105984","105984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765691","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that those making the Hajj pilgrimage are aware of their consumer and travel rights when booking tours; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105985","105985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765692","2017-10-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many buildings owned by his Department and its agencies are currently empty in (a) Norfolk and (b) North Norfolk; if he will provide a list of those buildings; and what plans he has for the future use of those buildings.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106373","106373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765693","2017-10-11","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many buildings owned by Government Departments are currently empty in (a) Norfolk and (b) North Norfolk; and if he will provide a list of those buildings, the Departments to which they belong and the plans he has for their future use.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106375","106375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765694","2017-10-10","Northern Ireland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many meetings he has had with the Government's Chief Scientific Adviser in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106330","106330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765695","2017-10-11","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many buildings owned by his Department and its agencies are currently empty in (a) Norfolk and (b) North Norfolk; if he will provide a list of those buildings; and what plans he has for the future use of those buildings.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106374","106374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765696","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will consider introducing a national 24-hour helpline to support people affected by prescribed drug dependence.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106319","106319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765697","2017-10-11","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many buildings owned by his Department and its agencies are currently empty in (a) Norfolk and (b) North Norfolk; if he will provide a list of those buildings; and what plans he has for the future use of those buildings.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106372","106372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765698","2017-10-11","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many buildings owned by her Department and its agencies are currently empty in (a) Norfolk and (b) North Norfolk; if she will provide a list of those buildings; and what plans she has for the future use of those buildings.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106371","106371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765699","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effects of plans to downgrade South Tyneside District Hospital by moving acute services to Sunderland.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105721","105721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765700","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the NHS in the North East receives the funding it requires to (a) improve care, (b) train and (c) retain adequate numbers of medical professionals.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105722","105722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765701","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the (a) system and (b) running costs of tax-free childcare; and whether that estimate exceeds the original budget for such childcare.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105727","105727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765702","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will postpone the deadline for closing childcare vouchers in April 2018 in the event that the Childcare Service IT system is not yet fully operational.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105726","105726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765703","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she plans to take to help protect vulnerable adults and children from illegal gambling, in-game gambling and loot boxes within computer games.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106043","106043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765704","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment the Government has made of the effectiveness of the Isle of Man's enhanced protections against illegal and in-game gambling and loot boxes; and what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on adopting such protections in the UK.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106042","106042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765706","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what talks he has had with the EU Commission to ensure that the Community Plant Variety Office continues commissioning variety testing contracts to the National Institute of Agricultural Botany after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106328","106328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765707","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on competition of the decision by Betfred to close on-site bookmakers at UK racecourses.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106037","106037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765708","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are in receipt of childcare vouchers in England.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106406","106406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765709","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are in receipt of childcare vouchers in Wales.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106407","106407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765710","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are in receipt of childcare vouchers in Scotland.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106408","106408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765711","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken is to process new claims for employment and support allowance in Northern Ireland in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105800","105800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765712","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average time taken is to process joint claims for tax credit from the day of application to the day of payment in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105801","105801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765713","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average time taken is to process child benefit claims from the day of application to the day of payment in Northern Ireland in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105802","105802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765714","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken is to process new claims for jobseeker's allowance across the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105803","105803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765715","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many families in Northern Ireland have moved from a single tax credit claim to a joint tax credit claim in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105806","105806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765716","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are in receipt of childcare vouchers in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105844","105844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765717","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken is to process new claims for jobseeker's allowance in Northern Ireland in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105804","105804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765718","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken is to process new claims for employment and support allowance across the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105805","105805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765719","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students aged between 11 and 18 are studying in fee-paying schools in England.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106425","106425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765720","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of students aged between 11 and 18 who are studying in fee-paying schools in Scotland.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106428","106428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765721","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of students aged between 11 and 18 who are studying in fee-paying schools in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106429","106429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765722","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of students aged between 11 and 18 who are studying in fee-paying schools in Wales.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106427","106427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765723","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of a one per cent pay increase for public sector staff in the NHS.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105834","105834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765724","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of a three per cent pay increase for public sector staff in the NHS.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105832","105832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765725","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of a two per cent pay increase for public sector staff in the NHS.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105833","105833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765726","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of reducing the pension age of women by one year back to the age of 66 from the 2017-18 tax year.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105835","105835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765727","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of reducing the pension age of women by two years back to the age of 65 from the 2017-18 tax year.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105836","105836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765728","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of reducing the pension age of women by seven years back to the age of 60 from the 2017-18 tax year.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105841","105841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765729","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of reducing the pension age of women by five years back to the age of 62 from the 2017-18 tax year.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105839","105839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765730","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of reducing the pension age of women by six years back to the age of 61 from the 2017-18 tax year.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105840","105840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765731","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of reducing the pension age of women by three years back to the age of 64 from the 2017-18 tax year.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105837","105837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765732","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of reducing the pension age of women by fours years back to the age of 63 from the 2017-18 tax year.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105838","105838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765733","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people declaring incorrect incomes to avoid child support payments in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105878","105878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765734","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding from the public purse will be disbursed for each post on the UN Junior Professional Officer programme by location and UN organisation in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105728","105728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765735","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to ensure that complete and accurate data is provided to Companies House when a UK entity, such as a Scottish Limited Partnership, is formed.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Dame Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106292","106292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765736","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will bring forward proposals to prevent public relations companies based in the UK undertaking work that aims to misrepresent the human rights record of a person or government.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Dame Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106291","106291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765737","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 7777, what performance indicators he has agreed with National Savings and Investments for the delivery of tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106404","106404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765738","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many jobs have been created as a result of Government investment in military research and development in west Wales in the last five years.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105850","105850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765739","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much the Government has invested in military research and development in west Wales in the last five years.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105851","105851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765740","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recorded accidents involving RAF pilotless drones have occured at Aberporth Airport.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105846","105846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765741","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, at which locations the Armed Forces' pilot-less drones are flown for training purposes.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106051","106051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765742","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what mechanism will beused to ensure that UK domestic legislation captures changes to CITES when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106378","106378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765743","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what provision there is for sign language interpreters to be available for people registered as deaf who are involved in court trials.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105732","105732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765744","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of people registered as deaf who are called for jury service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105733","105733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765745","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with charities for the deaf on the service received by people registered as deaf in the justice system.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105731","105731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765746","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward proposals to amend the Juries Act 1974 to allow for a sign language interpreter not to be considered as an extra juror.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105730","105730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765747","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what measures the Government plans to introduce to ensure that small charities are not treated less favourably than other small businesses in relation to their liability for non-domestic rates.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106218","106218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765748","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish all responses received by the current inquiry into infected blood.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106270","106270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765749","2017-10-11","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average payment per unit of dental activity for dental practices is in (a) Stockton on Tees, (b) the North East and (c) England.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106309","106309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765750","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many secondary victims claims have been made against his Department in each of the last 10 years; how many of those claims were successful; how many claimants have undergone psychiatric assessment as part of that process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106016","106016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765751","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many awards have been made for claims of punitive damages in cases of death of military personnel in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106017","106017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765752","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many places on Volunteer Gliding Squadron courses will be available in 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106130","106130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765753","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to remove invasive Australian acacia trees from the Sovereign Base Areas of (a) Akrotiri and (b) Dhekelia in (i) the remaining months of 2017 and (ii) thereafter; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105742","105742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765754","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the use of silver-coated catheters in hospitals on (a) infection rates and (b) costs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106131","106131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765755","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will detail the steps his Department is taking to ensure the close monitoring of ships registered to the Democratic People's Republic of Korea which change their (a) ship names, (b) flag, (c) company name and (d) reported beneficial owner; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106019","106019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765756","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking proactively to monitor Democratic People's Republic of Korea foreign-flagged ships in order to ensure enforcement of the mandate to inspect their cargo; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106018","106018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765757","2017-10-10","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he is having with (a) South Africa and (b) other countries that have an existing Free Trade Agreement with the EU on rules of origin or originating content issues arising from the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106338","106338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765758","2017-10-10","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will take steps for the UK to have third-party membership of existing EU Free Trade Agreements to comply with rules of origin requirements.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106339","106339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765759","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with clinical commissioning groups that have reportedly commissioned their own reviews of fertility services to inform commissioning practice.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106093","106093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765760","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the potential increase in the number of people seeking IVF treatment abroad and the consequences of this for multiple birth rates.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106091","106091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765761","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ask NICE's implementation team to look at methods by which access to NHS tertiary infertility services can be improved in England.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106092","106092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765762","2017-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what date he first received communication from the Welsh Government identifying potential sites for a new prison in South Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106167","106167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765763","2017-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what date he first received communication from the Welsh Government identifying the Port Talbot site for potential development as a new prison.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106166","106166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765764","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to review his Department's policy towards Saudi Arabia as a result of alleged war crimes in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105885","105885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765765","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Saudi counterpart on the challenges faced by humanitarian agencies delivering aid to Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106067","106067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765766","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he will conduct a new Strategic Defence and Security Review when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105935","105935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765767","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to protect public services against cyber attacks.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105883","105883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765768","2017-10-10","Cabinet Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the size of the Civil Service workforce.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105884","105884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765769","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to use contracts it has with G4S to improve the tagging performance of that company; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106430","106430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765770","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passport applications were received by HM Passport Office in (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106335","106335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765771","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time is for a visa to be issued for a visitor to the UK from a non-EU country in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106331","106331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765772","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many e-gates there are at each UK airport; and how many such gates were operational on 21 July 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106332","106332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765773","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the country of origin was of EU citizens applying for passports in (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106333","106333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765774","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passport applicants were EU citizens in (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106334","106334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765775","2017-10-10","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many meetings he has had with representatives of UK arms manufacturers on the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105933","105933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765776","2017-10-10","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will review his Department's policy on arms sales to Saudi Arabia following alleged human rights violations in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105881","105881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765777","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to protect the UK aerospace sector.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105882","105882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765778","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to support the UK space industry during the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105934","105934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765779","2017-10-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many fines have been levied on letting agents in England for breaches of the Consumer Rights Act 2015 since it came into force.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106248","106248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765780","2017-10-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many letting agents have been fined for breaching the Consumer Rights Act 2015 since it came into force.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106249","106249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765781","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure the commemoration of Workers' Memorial Day in the UK.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105982","105982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765782","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve delivery of primary care health services for people with coeliac disease; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105924","105924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765783","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much of the Home Building Fund has been allocated; and what proportion of that amount has been allocated to small and medium-sized house builders.","Biography information for Robert Courts","Robert Courts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106267","106267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765784","2017-10-11","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate she has made of the number of 30 hours of free childcare codes which have been validated by providers and local authorities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106146","106146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765785","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9980, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress her Department has made on delivering greater UK steel content in line with the public procurement guidelines published by the Government in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105707","105707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765786","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9980, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress his Department has made on delivering greater UK steel content in line with the public procurement guidelines published by the Government in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105708","105708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765787","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9980, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress his Department has made on delivering greater UK steel content in line with the public procurement guidelines published by the Government in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105704","105704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765788","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9980, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress his Department has made on delivering greater UK steel content in line with the public procurement guidelines published by the Government in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105706","105706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765789","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9980, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress her Department has made on delivering greater UK steel content in line with the public procurement guidelines published by the Government in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105705","105705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765790","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9980, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress his Department has made on delivering greater UK steel content in line with the public procurement guidelines published by the Government in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105709","105709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765791","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9980, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress her Department has made on delivering greater UK steel content in line with the public procurement guidelines published by the Government in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105710","105710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765792","2017-10-10","Wales Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9980, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress his Department has made on delivering greater UK steel content in line with the public procurement guidelines published by the Government in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105715","105715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765793","2017-10-10","Northern Ireland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9980, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress his Department has made on delivering greater UK steel content in line with the public procurement guidelines published by the Government in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105712","105712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765794","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9980, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress his Department has made on delivering greater UK steel content in line with the public procurement guidelines published by the Government in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105711","105711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765795","2017-10-10","Scotland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9980, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress his Department has made on delivering greater UK steel content in line with the public procurement guidelines published by the Government in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105713","105713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765796","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9980, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress his Department has made on delivering greater UK steel content in line with the public procurement guidelines published by the Government in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105714","105714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765797","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9980, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress his Department has made on delivering greater UK steel content in line with the public procurement guidelines published by the Government in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105703","105703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765798","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9980, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress his Department has made on delivering greater UK steel content in line with the public procurement guidelines published by the Government in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105716","105716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765799","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of introducing charges for non-UK citizens accessing non-life threatening treatment on the NHS on the accessibility of such treatments for such citizens who are classed as vulnerable.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106029","106029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765800","2017-10-11","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the free national teacher vacancy website announced in the March 2016 White Paper Educational Excellence Everywhere will be operational.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106159","106159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765801","2017-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many civil law proceedings involving alleged domestic violence or child abuse one or more of the parties has chosen to represent themselves.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106436","106436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765802","2017-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of law centres dispensing legal aid which have closed in the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106437","106437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765803","2017-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time between the commencement of an employment and support allowance appeal and a decision was in (a) Ashfield, (b) Mansfield, (c) Nottinghamshire and (d) the UK in the most recent 12-month period for which data is available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106312","106312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765804","2017-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time between the commencement of a personal independence payment appeal and a decision was in (a) Ashfield, (b) Mansfield, (c) Nottinghamshire and (d) the UK in the most recent 12-month period for which data is available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106313","106313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765805","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of adults who are (a) Black, Asian and minority ethnic, (b) with a special educational need or disability or (c) from disadvantaged backgrounds do not participate in any adult education or training.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106415","106415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765806","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how the adult education budget is calculated in London.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106379","106379"
