"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802128","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the jurisdiction of the European Court of Justice in relation UK patents before the Unified Patent Court after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117815","117815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802129","2017-12-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the proportion of businesses that will be in a state of readiness for the General Data Protection Regulation compliance by May 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117816","117816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802130","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of businesses in the chemical industry considering relocating from the UK to the EU in the event that the UK does not remain part of the REACH system for authorising chemicals after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117817","117817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802131","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what changes there have been in the (a) assessment and (b) management of motor neurone disease in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117818","117818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802132","2017-12-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to help the local newspaper sector in the face of reducing sales and increasing online news content.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117819","117819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802133","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the findings of the Disability Benefits Consortium Survey, published in September 2017, that over 71 per cent of respondents found the Personal Independence Payments form hard or very hard to complete.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117820","117820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802134","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the protection of ancient woodland in England.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117821","117821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802135","2017-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations he has received on the effect on jobcentre staff of outsourcing jobcentre telephony work to Capita","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117822","117822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802136","2017-12-11","Cabinet Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 16 November 2017, HCWS 258, on social care, what the timetable is to (a) publish recommendations and (b) bring forward legislative proposals as a result of the Green Paper.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117823","117823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802137","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 9826, at which grades of staffing are Crown Prosecution Service staff selected to review the sample of case files to assess the frequency and outcome of applications seeking to introduce into rape proceedings evidence of the complainant's sexual history.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117824","117824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802138","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 9826 on rape: trials, in which Crown Courts those applications were made; and in how many case files from each of those Crown Courts were put into the sample of case files selected by the Crown Prosecution Service to assess the frequency and outcome of applications seeking to introduce into rape proceedings evidence of the complainant's sexual history under section 41 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117825","117825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802139","2017-12-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the reliance of the UK creative industry sector on non-UK EU citizens in the (a) visual effects artists, (b) video game designers and (c) arts officers occupations.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117826","117826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802140","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2017 to Question 115972, what proportion of the £243 million allocated to Greater Manchester, from the Transforming Cities Fund, Leigh constituency will benefit from.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117827","117827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802141","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if the Government will review its policy on military training for Saudi Arabia as a result of the allegations that 2nd Battalion the Royal Regiment of Scotland undertook irregular warfare training for the Royal Saudi Land Forces Infantry Institute.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117828","117828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802142","2017-12-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has held with social media platform providers on tackling online bullying against young people.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117829","117829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802143","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department has issued on the provision and supervision of prisoners' family contact.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117830","117830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802144","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of number of adults annually giving up smoking as a result of vaping; and whether there has been an increase in the number of adults giving up smoking since vaping became more common practice.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117831","117831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802145","2017-12-11","Wales Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the criteria was for the removal of certain redactions from the Macur Review,published on 5 December 2017.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117832","117832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802146","2017-12-11","Cabinet Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what data is held by his Department's Foxhound data service by each Government department and data category.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117833","117833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802147","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to promote awareness of counterfeit standardised tobacco.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117834","117834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802148","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received on companies using funding from the public purse to install sub-standard and faulty cavity wall insulation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117835","117835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802149","2017-12-11","Cabinet Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many assets are classified at which level of risk by the Government Security Classifications system.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117836","117836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802150","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the average length time it takes from a new applicant for universal credit beginning their application and the point at which the six week period wait for that credit is triggered.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117837","117837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802151","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been paid out by NHS clinical commissioning groups in compensation for deficiencies in the contract tendering procedure.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117838","117838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802152","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of potential universal credit claimants failed to complete their registration in the first seven days after registering their account.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117839","117839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802153","2017-12-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much was disbursed by the Heritage Lottery Fund in each year since 2012","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117840","117840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802154","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of potential universal credit claimants failed to complete their registration in the 28 days after account verification.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117841","117841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802155","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2017 to Question 116801, how much Virgin Trains East Coast paid in premium payments (a) from the commencement of the franchise in 2015 to date and (b) will pay in each year until 2023-2024.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117842","117842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802156","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Parent Company Guarantee provided by Virgin Trains East Coast for the InterCity East Coast Franchise amounts to; and whether any of that amount will be retained by his Department.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117843","117843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802157","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the number of (a) hospitals, (b) wards and (c) beds in the mental health sector that have closed in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117844","117844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802158","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the list of hospitals that are rated by the Care Quality Commission as requires improvement overall.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117845","117845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802159","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many inpatient mental health beds there are that are suitable for children; and where those beds are situated.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117846","117846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802160","2017-12-11","Scotland Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he plans to visit a food bank in December 2017.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117847","117847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802161","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients underwent an interventional radiology (image-guided surgery) procedure in each region in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117848","117848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802162","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the NHS’ capacity to deliver 24-hour interventional radiology (image-guided surgery) services in each region.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117849","117849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802163","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of regional variation in patient access to interventional radiology procedures (image-guided surgery).","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117850","117850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802164","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential efficiency savings that could be generated through the use of minimally invasive procedures supported by interventional radiology (Image-guided surgery).","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117851","117851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802165","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many 24-hour interventional radiology centres there are in each region.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117852","117852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802166","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of full-time equivalent interventional radiologists; and what assessment he has made of whether there are adequate numbers of interventional radiologists to deliver 24-hour services.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117853","117853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802167","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of day beds available to interventional radiology patients.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117854","117854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802168","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on the mutual recognition of seafarer qualifications with EU member states after 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117855","117855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802169","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times officials from the Maritime and Coastguard Agency have visited another country to advise on seafarer training standards since May 2010; and what the dates and destinations were of each such visit.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117856","117856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802170","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress is being made on his Department's review of the Maritime Growth Study.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117857","117857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802171","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of primary school children have daily reading lessons in (a) England and (b) Northamptonshire.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117858","117858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802172","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many UK seafarer (a) Ratings and (b) Officers held jobs on vessels which have joined the UK Ship Register since 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117859","117859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802173","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vessels on the UK Ship Register are (a) beneficially owned and (b) managed outside the UK.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117860","117860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802174","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to encourage UK ship owners to register merchant vessels on the UK Ship Register.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117861","117861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802175","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the (a) minimum and (b) maximum cost to industry of legislation prohibiting nationality-based pay discrimination in the UK shipping industry.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117862","117862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802176","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that farmers know the method of proposed slaughter for their animals before they agree to sell them.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117863","117863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802177","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of crops on which neonicotinoids have been used; and if he will list those crops.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117864","117864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802178","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that farmers have access to a sufficient number of workers to work in the horticultural industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117865","117865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802179","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on reducing the incidence of rural crime.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117866","117866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802180","2017-12-11","Department for International Trade","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2017 to Question 116918 on energy intensive industries: trade agreements, if he will list the 19 organisations from which he received representations on the implementation of trade remedy measures; and what plans he has to publish the details of those representations.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117867","117867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802181","2017-12-11","Department for International Trade","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2017 to Question 116660 on trade promotion, what estimate he has made of the total employment cost per annum of the nine Her Britannic Majesty's Trade Commissioners.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117868","117868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802182","2017-12-11","Cabinet Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many members of staff have left his Department since 1 January 2015; and how many of those members of staff were nationals of non-UK EU countries.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117869","117869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802183","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Government Ministers have used RAF aircraft on official business for what purposes on what dates since July 2016.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117870","117870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802184","2017-12-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-06","To ask the secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer 28 November to Question 113183, how her Department plans to monitor uptake and observance of the code of practice for social media companies provided for in the Digital Economy Act 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117871","117871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802185","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will instruct NHS trusts and Clinical Commissioning Groups to start compiling data on the numbers of children with incontinence problems.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117872","117872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802186","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the US Administration on its decision to recognise Jerusalem as the capital of Israel.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117873","117873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802187","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the National Grid on its investment portfolio and its plans for future investment in the UK.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117874","117874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802188","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 110602, on Midland Main Railway Line: Electrification, how the estimate of the environmental benefits included in Table 8 – 5 were calculated.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117875","117875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802189","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to review and enhance local authorities' compulsory purchase powers.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117876","117876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802190","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 110602, what assessment he has made of the environmental effect of using bi-mode trains on the Midland Mainline on the basis that the line beyond Kettering will not be electrified.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117877","117877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802191","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress has been made on establishing the Strike Experimentation Group.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117878","117878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802192","2017-12-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and which local authorities he estimates will receive a negative revenue support grant in the financial year 2018-19.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117879","117879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802193","2017-12-11","Women and Equalities","2017-12-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many times she has (a) met, (b) spoken to and (c) communicated with (i) directly with or (ii) through (A) officials, (B) Ministerial advisers and (B) other contacts, the Chair of the Equality and Human Rights Commission in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117880","117880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802194","2017-12-11","Women and Equalities","2017-12-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, on what dates she (a) met, (b) spoken to and (c) communicated with (i) directly with or (ii) through (A) officials, (B) Ministerial advisers and (B) other contacts, the Chair of the Equality and Human Rights Commission in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117881","117881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802195","2017-12-11","Department for International Development","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that UK development assistance does not end up in the hands of terrorist groups or regimes that persecute LGBT people, religious minorities or minority ethnic groups.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117882","117882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802196","2017-12-11","Women and Equalities","2017-12-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, on what dates between (a) 20 March and 21 April 2017 and (b) since 21 April 2017 (i) she, (ii) Officials of her Department, (iii) Ministerial advisers or (iv) others (A) met with, (B) spoke to or (C) communicated with the Chair of the Equality and Human Rights Commission; and on which of those dates contact with the Chair of the Equality and Human Rights Commission included communication about (I) the position of Disability Commissioner on the Equality and Human Rights Commission or (II) Lord Shinkwin.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117883","117883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802197","2017-12-11","Women and Equalities","2017-12-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will publish communications relating or referring to (a) the position of Disability Commissioner on the Equality and Human Rights Commission and (b) Lord Shinkwin between (i) herself, (ii) Officials of her Department, (iii) Ministerial advisers, (iv) the Government Equalities Office, (v) the Equality and Human Rights Commission and (vi) David Isaac between (A) 20 March and 21 April 2017 and (B) since 21 April 2017; and if she will place copies in the Library.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117884","117884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802198","2017-12-11","Department for International Trade","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to increase the amount of foreign direct investment in the North of England.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117885","117885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802199","2017-12-11","Department for International Trade","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how his Department is working with the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy to attract foreign direct investment into the Industrial Strategy.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117886","117886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802202","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if a (a) local planning authority, and (b) planning inspector, is able to consider as a material planning consideration, the likelihood of a local planning authority making up a shortfall identified in its five year supply of deliverable housing sites in later years in an (i) existing Local Plan; and (ii) emerging Local Plan, when determining planning application.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117889","117889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802203","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2017 to Question 116496, whether the Mechanised Infantry Vehicle program is in the assessment phase.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117890","117890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802204","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether a local planning authority not able to demonstrate a five-year supply of deliverable housing sites can deliver the shortfall in future years in the Local Plan period.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117891","117891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802205","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Mechanised Infantry Vehicles his Department plans to procure.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117892","117892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802206","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reasons the Punjabi authorities have given to his Department for the denial of private and unfettered access to British consular services to Jagtar Singh Johal for over a month.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117893","117893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802207","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether a (a) local planning authority and (b) planning inspector has a duty to consider as a material planning consideration (i) the delivery of new housing during the course of a Local Plan period of fifteen years and (ii) each five-year period of the supply of housing sites for new housing when considering the impact and weighting of a local authority's position in relation to their delivery of a five-year supply of housing sites.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117894","117894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802208","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to issue new guidance in relation to the protection of sites located in the countryside outside of settlement boundaries from new housing in instances where a local authority (a) can and (b) cannot demonstrate a five-year supply of deliverable sites.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117895","117895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802209","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether people who moved to the UK before the Immigration Act 1971 came into force are considered to be illegal immigrants.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117896","117896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802210","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what consideration (a) local planning authorities and (b) planning inspectors should give to the scheduled building of new infrastructure beyond the five-year period for the supply of deliverable housing sites when determining planning applications in circumstances where a local planning authority (a) can and (b) cannot demonstrate a five-year supply of deliverable sites.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117897","117897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802211","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who moved legally to the UK prior to the Immigration Act 1971 have received deportation notices in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117898","117898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802212","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what policies are in place to support the protection of sites located in the countryside outside of settlement boundaries from new housing in instances where a local authority (a) can and (b) cannot demonstrate a five-year supply of deliverable sites.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117899","117899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802213","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued to people who have indefinite leave to remain under the Immigration Act 1971 on their citizenship status.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117900","117900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802214","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued to people who have indefinite leave to remain under the Immigration Act 1971 who have lost their documentation.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117901","117901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802215","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential role of garden communities in addressing shortfalls in (a) local housing need, (b) a local authority's five-year supply of deliverable housing sites by facilitating increased development in the later years of a Local Plan period.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117902","117902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802216","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether (a) local planning authorities and (b) planning inspectors considering planning applications have a duty to consider as a material planning consideration (i) future housing deliverability throughout the Local Plan period of 15 years or more, (ii) future infrastructure delivery necessary to support new housing and (iii) reasonable efforts and best endeavours of local planning authorities to secure a five-year supply of deliverable housing sites in circumstances where a local planning authority is not able to demonstrate a five-year supply of deliverable housing.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117903","117903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802217","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential for generation of (a) electricity and (b) gas by anaerobic digestion by 2030.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117904","117904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802218","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to increase penalties for animal antibiotic or drug abuse for animals destined for food.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117905","117905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802219","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what comparative assessment he has made of available evidence on the efficiency of disposing food waste by (a) anaerobic digestion and (b) incineration.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117906","117906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802220","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that early years education is sufficiently funded.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117907","117907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802221","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the pledge in the Industrial Strategy to protect and enhance all aspects of Natural Capital will also apply to Natural Capital in other countries that will be potentially affected by UK decisions.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117908","117908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802222","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will rule out co-firing and conversion as an abatement option in the coal phaseout.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117909","117909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802223","2017-12-11","Scotland Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will meet with the National Farmers Union Scotland to discuss a specific Agricultural Labour Scheme to meet labour shortages in the agricultural sector in Scotland.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117910","117910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802224","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 9826 on rape: trials, over what time period  the Crown Prosecution Service selected the court cases which constituted the sample of case files to assess the frequency and outcome of applications seeking to introduce into rape proceedings evidence of the complainant's sexual history under section 41 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117911","117911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802225","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 9826, what the total number of rape and sexual assault trials heard in the Crown Courts was during the same time period over which the sample of case files was selected by the Crown Prosecution Service to assess the frequency and outcome of applications seeking to introduce into rape proceedings evidence of the complainant's sexual history under section 41 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117912","117912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802226","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 9826 on rape: trials, what national and local data on applications under section 41 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999 was being recorded by the Crown Prosecution Service at the time when the sample cases were selected.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117913","117913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802227","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Government Departments owe money to the Ministry of Defence for the use of RAF aircraft by Ministers.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117914","117914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802228","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28  November 2017 to Question 115103 on Electricity Generation: Waste, what steps he is taking to ensure that greater levels of biodegradable waste is disposed of through (a) composting and (b) anaerobic digestion.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117915","117915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802229","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many tenants of Service Family Accommodation properties allocated under a civilian licence are (a) civil servants and (b) reservists.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117916","117916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802230","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to Answer of 6 December 2917 to Question 116209 on GP at Hand, whether the evaluation of financial impact will include an impact assessment on local GP surgeries who may be affected by a reduction in the number of their patients.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117917","117917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802231","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Sudan on the activities of the Rapid Support Forces in Darfur.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117918","117918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802232","2017-12-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2017 Question 2584 on business: Scotland, if he will publish the (a) correspondence and (b) minutes of the meetings referred to in that answer","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117919","117919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802233","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Police and Crime Commissioners are developing proposals to take on governance of fire and rescue services.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117920","117920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802234","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that all schools teach awareness of violence against women and girls.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117921","117921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802235","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the privatisation of Royal Mail on employment standards in the postal industry.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117922","117922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802236","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps is he taking to encourage the car industry to tackle air pollution.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117923","117923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802237","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2017 to Question 115500, for what reasons a new consultation is being undertaken on the designation of the third tranche of marine conservation zones; what aspect of the designation is under consultation and which (a) individuals and (b) organisations are being consulted.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117924","117924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802238","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2017 to Question 115500, whether he plans for the designation of the third tranche of marine conservation zones to be completed by the end of 2018.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117925","117925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802239","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2017 to Question 115500, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of the Scottish Government on Marine Protected Areas which remain outstanding and the Government of Wales on that government's plans for a separate Marine Conservation Zone process.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117926","117926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802240","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the Israeli Government on President Trump's decision to recognise Jerusalem as the capital of Israel.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117927","117927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802241","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the level of home overcrowding in social rented sector.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117928","117928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802242","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he has taken to ensure that all homes meet efficiency band C by 2035?","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117929","117929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802243","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many homes have been insulated under national government schemes in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117930","117930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802244","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of (a) the total monies outstanding from other Departments and (b) the length of time payment has been outstanding for the use of his Department's RAF jets and helicopters.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117931","117931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802245","2017-12-11","Cabinet Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of workers with a disability in each Government Department declared that were treated fairly at work in each Civil Service People Survey since 2014.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117932","117932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802246","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to incentivise the installation of household insulation by private landlords and housing associations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117933","117933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802247","2017-12-13","Department for International Trade","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff currently work for his Department's Defence and Security Organisation; and what the budget of that organisation was for 2016-17.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117934","117934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802248","2017-12-13","Department for International Trade","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what representations his Department has made to overseas governments, police and law enforcement agencies and their respective procurement agents or representatives on the promotion of and invitation to the Security and Policing event to be held in March 2018.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117935","117935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802249","2017-12-11","Department for International Trade","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the value of (a) imports from and (b) exports to the EU was for each region and constituent part of the UK in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117936","117936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802250","2017-12-13","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations her Department has made to overseas governments, police and law enforcement agencies and their respective procurement agents or representatives on the promotion of and invitation to the Security and Policing event in March 2018.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117937","117937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802251","2017-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will place a copy of any correspondence between his Department and Adam Smith International since 2014 on the risk of money in his Department's Official Development Assistance budget earmarked for the access to the justice and community security scheme being used for corrupt or fraudulent practices or being diverted to armed groups inside Syria in the Library.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117938","117938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802252","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2017 to Question 107168 on housing: insulation, if his Department will provide a breakdown of those figures for (a) owner-occupied, (b) private-rented and (c) social sector housing.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117939","117939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802253","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time was for a final decision on an asylum application in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117940","117940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802254","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answers of 4 December 2017 to Question 115274 and 2 December 2016 to Question 55490, what progress she has made on the implementation of her policy to include mothers' names on marriage certificates since 2 December 2016.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117941","117941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802255","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December to Question 116362 on Asylum: Sanitary Protection, if he will make a specific fund available for for asylum seekers who would otherwise be destitute to apply for an allowance to be able to pay for sanitary products.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117942","117942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802256","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations her Department has received on the ability of asylum seekers to afford sanitary products.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117943","117943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802257","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2017 to  Question 115264 on Railways: Freight, when he expects the air quality impact study undertaken by the Rail Delivery Group's freight air quality group to be published.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117944","117944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802258","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2017 to Question 1033 on Nitrous Oxide: EU Law, how much the Government has spent on legal fees to defend litigation brought by ClientEarth in respect of air quality compliance.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117945","117945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802259","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence what the ages of the submarines awaiting recycling in Devonport and Rosyth are.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117946","117946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802260","2017-12-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will take steps to ensure that national collections and other recipients of public funding make digital images of works of art held in public collections and which are outside of copyright, free of charge to non-commercial causes and for educational purposes.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117947","117947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802261","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans a public consultation on the defence aspects of the National Security and Capability review.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117948","117948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802262","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence how much funding he has allocated to the submarine recycling demonstrator project in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117949","117949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802263","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations her Department has received on the potential benefits to looked-after children of extending the 30 hours of free childcare entitlement to those children.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117950","117950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802264","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 115266 on companies: ownership, when (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department last held discussions with representatives of the Governments of (i) Anguilla, (ii) Turks and Caicos Islands and (iii) Montserrat on the establishment of a central register or similar arrangement; and what the outcome was of those discussions.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117951","117951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802265","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 115266 on companies: ownership, when he expects the Legislative Assembly of Montserrat to (a) introduce and (b) pass legislation to implement a central register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117952","117952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802266","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 to Question 115266 on companies: ownership, how many times UK law enforcement authorities have accessed beneficial ownership information held on companies incorporated in British Overseas Territories since 2016.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117953","117953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802267","2017-12-11","Cabinet Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he expects the review of the National Security Strategy to be published.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117954","117954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802268","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many badgers have been culled in the south west of England in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117955","117955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802269","2017-12-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps his Department is taking to engage with the governments of other EU member states to agree future cooperation on security policy after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117956","117956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802270","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure Cornish pasties retain European Protected Status.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117957","117957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802271","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to increase the frequency of train services on the South Fylde railway line.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117958","117958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802272","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2017 to Question 115775, what guidance his Department has issued to users of dynamic risk assessments to decide whether to (a) continue, (b) pause and (c) stop an activity where one or more participants have been assessed as having a heat injury.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117959","117959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802273","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the net contribution foreign students studying in the UK made to the economy in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Simon Hoare","Simon Hoare","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117960","117960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802274","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with Public Health England on updating its report of 2014 on the effect of shale gas on public health.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117961","117961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802275","2017-12-11","Department for International Trade","2017-12-06","To ask Secretary of State for International Trade, what value of bonds the Government holds in Burntisland Fabrications.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117962","117962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802276","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what funds have been made available for support services in Sheffield for women who have left prison in the last 12 months; and what funds she plans to make available for that purpose in the next 12 months?","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117963","117963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802277","2017-12-11","Cabinet Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 106358 on Senior Civil Servants: Recruitment, when he plans for the information on those functions to become available.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117964","117964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802278","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of tableware used in British embassies is supplied by manufacturers in the UK","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117965","117965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802279","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the proportion of women who have been homeless after leaving prison in the last three years.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117966","117966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802280","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, from which suppliers his Department acquires its tableware.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117967","117967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802281","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of self-harm incidents by prisoners per prison has been in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117968","117968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802282","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department owes to the Ministry of Defence on 6 December 2017 in respect of his use of RAF aircraft and helicopters.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117969","117969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802283","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the total amount owed by the Treasury to the Ministry of Defence for the Chancellor's use of RAF aircraft and helicopters to date.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117970","117970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802284","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2017 to Question 116297 when he plans to publish the amended drill manual (a) online and (b) in hard copy; and where hard copies will be made available.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117971","117971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802285","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has had discussions with any bus services franchising authorities which are not a mayoral combined authority on the use of the Bus Services franchising powers.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117972","117972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802286","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department plans to give to bus service franchising authorities which are considering applying for franchising powers under the Bus Services Act 2017.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117973","117973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802287","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria his Department plans to use to determine whether to grant consent to franchising authorities which make an application for franchising powers under the Bus Services Act 2017.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117974","117974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802288","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December, 2017 to Question 116658, if he will list the legitimate grievances of direct suppliers of reporting potential breaches of the Grocery Code to the Grocery Code Adjudicator to which he refers in that answer.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117975","117975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802289","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing discounted rail and coach travel for single veterans.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117976","117976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802290","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will extend the provision of 15 additional hours of free childcare under the Childcare Act 2016 to foster children in England.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117977","117977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802291","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to increase the national minimum fostering allowance to take into account the cost of childcare.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117978","117978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802292","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce waiting times for people seeking treatment for eating disorders.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117979","117979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802293","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what she is doing to remove barriers for people who want to combine work outside the home with fostering.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117980","117980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802294","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, her Department is taking to reduce the number of dangerous journeys taken by unaccompanied child refugees with family in the UK.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117981","117981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802295","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to assess the benefit to fostering families of the increase from 15 to 30 hours of free childcare provision.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117982","117982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802296","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much solar energy has been deployed subsidy-free by (a) capacity and (b) project numbers since the closure of the Renewables Obligation in March 2017.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117983","117983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802297","2017-12-11","Department for International Trade","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December to Question 115256, what plans he has to publish the economic research on the design and implementation of the future trade remedies framework.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117984","117984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802298","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, (a) by what date he expects the Greyhound Board of Great Britain to begin publishing aggregate injury and euthanasia figures and (b) what period that data will cover.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117985","117985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802299","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, (a) by what date he expects the Greyhound Board of Great Britain to begin publishing summary statistics for the number of dogs that leave the industry each year and (b) what details those statistics will include.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117986","117986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802300","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will set out the evidence base and analysis underpinning his Department's position that solar energy no longer requires public support and can be deployed without subsidy.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117987","117987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802301","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, by what criteria requests for access to anonymised track injury and euthanasia data for research purposes will be assessed.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117988","117988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802302","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he expects the Greyhound Board of Great Britain to fulfil its agreement to develop a Publicly Available Specification for trainers’ kennels and to extend its UK Accreditation Service to include the enforcement of those new standards.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117989","117989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802303","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress his Department has made on a non-regulatory agreement with independent greyhound racing tracks to allow anonymised, aggregate injury and euthanasia statistics from those tracks to be published.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117990","117990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802304","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy what are the eligibility criteria for technologies entering competitive contracts for difference auctions.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117991","117991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802305","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2017 to Question 116097 on solar power, what information his Department holds on the project financing of the subsidy-free solar farm referred to in that answer.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117992","117992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802306","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on what date he plans to publish the 2017 Feed-in Tariff consultation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117993","117993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802307","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of the 36 per cent increase in the use of bioenergy envisaged in the Clean Growth Strategy the Government plans will come from woody biomass.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117994","117994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802308","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to introduce proposals for a cap on the amount of money senior council officials are entitled to receive in payments when leaving the employment of local authorities.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117995","117995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802309","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of unsuccessful attempts made by (a) patients and (b) GPs when attempting to book an appointment at a hospital directly through the online choose and book system.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117996","117996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802310","2017-12-11","Department for International Trade","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what support is available to SMEs in Fylde constituency that wish to export abroad.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117997","117997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802311","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the consumer green paper; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117998","117998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802312","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of bringing non-asylum immigration claims for children back into scope of legal aid.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117999","117999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802313","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, by what method his Department requires CCGs to show they have regard for NICE guidelines.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118000","118000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802314","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the availability of support offered to patients diagnosed with Spondyloarthritis.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118001","118001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802315","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who is responsible for monitoring the legal duty of CCGs to have regard for NICE guidelines.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118002","118002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802316","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education,  with reference to the publication of the Government's Careers Strategy on 4 December 2017, how her Department plans communicate the introduction of T Levels; and how much her Department plans to spend on marketing.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118003","118003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802317","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with Spondyloarthritis in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118004","118004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802318","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to encourage UK researchers to continue to make bids for Horizon 2020 funding.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118005","118005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802319","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 34 of the Government's Careers Strategy, published on 4 December 2017, what discussions her Department has had with the Director of Fair Access to Education on the continuation of targeted career outreach interventions for disadvantaged pupils.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118006","118006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802320","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what budget is for the National Collaborative Outreach Programme.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118007","118007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802321","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Government's Careers Strategy, published on 4 December 2017, whether her Department has any plans to assess the breadth and effectiveness of careers provision in social sciences and the humanities in schools.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118008","118008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802322","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has plans to require Ofsted to comment in school inspection reports on the careers advice provided to students.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118009","118009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802323","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons work capability assessments are given greater weight than a GP's fit note when a Job Centre considers whether someone is able to search for work or undertake work-related activity.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118010","118010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802324","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with Blackpool Victoria Hospital to facilitate an increase in the recruitment of hospital consultants at that hospital.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118011","118011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802325","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times Jobcentre Plus staff have applied the discretion defined in regulation 99 of the Universal Credit Regulations 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118012","118012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802326","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons Jobcentre Plus implementation of regulation 99 of the Universal Credit Regulations 2013 defaults to a 14-day unfit period rather than the number of days specified in a fit note.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118013","118013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802327","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many homes bought in North Cornwall in 2016-17 were below the stamp duty threshold.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118014","118014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802328","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs,  what effect he expects the end of EU quotas on sugar beet production to have on domestic sugar prices.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118015","118015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802329","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his department maintains a list of all UK companies which have a global turnover of more than (a) £16 million (b) £26 million (c) £36 million and (d) £46 million.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118016","118016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802330","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) local authority maintained schools (b) academies and (c) free schools are currently in financial special measures; and of those how many have been in financial special measures for more than (i) 6 months (ii) 12 months (iii) 18 months (iv) 24 months.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118017","118017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802331","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding has been raised from the immigration skills charge since its introduction.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118018","118018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802332","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the suitability of the current visa sponsorship process for non-EU workers in small companies.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118019","118019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802333","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to have a public consultation on the functioning of the visa system for those coming to the UK to work before the publication of the Immigration Bill.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118020","118020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802334","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of the total amount spent on UK railways was raised through passenger fares for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118021","118021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802335","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place the HS2 route plans for the refined Meadowhall route at the time of the completion of the updating of standards stage in 2014 in the Library.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118022","118022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802336","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport,  if he will place the HS2 route plans for the refined Meadowhall route at the time of the conclusion of the Blackburn to Normanton refinement stage in March 2015 in the Library.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118023","118023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802337","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage international ship owners to register their merchant vessels on the UK Ship Register.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118024","118024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802338","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place the HS2 route plans for the refined Meadowhall route at the time of the Markham Vale and Staveley approach refinements stage March 2015 in the Library.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118025","118025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802339","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place the HS2 route plans for the refined Meadowhall route at the time of the conclusion of the Blackburn to Normanton further refinement stage in January 2016 in the Library.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118026","118026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802340","2017-12-12","HM Treasury","2017-12-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to replace European Investment Bank and European Investment Fund lending in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118027","118027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802341","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to increase funding for ESOL courses in areas with the highest proportion of refugees.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118028","118028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802342","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has adopted (a) the recommendation in the UN Committee on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities’ report, published in October 2016, on undertaking a cumulative impact assessment of the measures adopted since 2010 on the rights to independent living and to be included in the community, social protection and employment of persons with disabilities and (b) other recommendations of that report.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118029","118029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802343","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will review the Local Housing Allowance and the effect it has on tenants living in the private rented sector.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118030","118030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802344","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of first-time buyers who will benefit from the changes to stamp duty announced in Autumn Budget 2017 in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118031","118031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802345","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many first time buyers in (a) Great Grimsby constituency and (b) the UK he expects to benefit from the changes to stamp duty announced in Autumn Budget 2017 in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118032","118032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802346","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason the number of students enrolling on Early Years Initial Teacher Training courses is less than the target set by her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118033","118033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802347","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to respond to the recommendations of the Ofsted report entitled Bold beginnings: The Reception curriculum in a sample of good and outstanding primary schools, published in November 2017.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118034","118034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802348","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much victims of modern day slavery and human trafficking received in subsistence support in each week of 2016-2017.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118035","118035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802349","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department what her policy is on the amount  per week that victims of modern slavery and human trafficking will receive in subsistence support in 2018-2019.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118036","118036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802350","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Batley and Spen, dated 11 October 2017.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118037","118037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802351","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will place in the Library copies of all correspondence between her Department and the Advertising Standards Authority on the 30-hours of childcare policy.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118038","118038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802352","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for the stability of the region, including  the potential for destabilisation and violence, of the US Government recognising Jerusalem as the capital of Israel.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118039","118039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802353","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent representations he has received on introducing no-fault divorce.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118040","118040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802354","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he received reports that US President Donald Trump is set to recognise Jerusalem as the capital of Israel.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118041","118041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802355","2017-12-11","Prime Minister","2017-12-06","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions she has had with US President Donald Trump on (a) his proposal to move the US Embassy to Jerusalem and (b) US recognition of Jerusalem as the capital of Israel; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118042","118042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802356","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2017 to Question 116593, what proportion of self-employed people or who have a partner who is self-employed and have successfully applied for tax-free childcare have used that account to date.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118043","118043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802357","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Environment Agency is taking to prevent illegal angling in Lancashire.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118044","118044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802358","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on whether the UK’s Credit Reference Agencies have sent all the required demand letters to the banks requesting small business credit information.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118045","118045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802359","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential benefit to (a) small businesses seeking access to finance and (b) the alternative finance industry of implementing the Commercial Credit Data sharing scheme.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118046","118046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802360","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department’s timetable is for the implementation of the Commercial Credit Data Sharing scheme.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118047","118047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802361","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government has made an assessment of the extent to which the use of viability assessments could reduce affordable housing contributions.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118048","118048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802362","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps are being taken to prevent housing developers using loopholes in the Government's planning policy to reduce the number of affordable houses.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118049","118049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802363","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to tackle trafficking and sale of slaves in Libya.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118050","118050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802364","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to protect marine environments in (a) the UK and (b) the UK Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118051","118051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802365","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of access to mental health services for university students.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118052","118052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802366","2017-12-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what analysis her Department has undertaken to assess the viability of making Cambridge a joint Tech Nation cluster with Norwich?","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118053","118053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802367","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to encourage the start up and development of small businesses in (a) Kettering, (b) Northamptonshire and (c) England.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118054","118054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802368","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who is responsible for the provision of counselling and wellbeing services to university students in England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118055","118055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802369","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2017 to Question 114975 (a) which local authorities commissioned forensic hair strand tests for drug and alcohol use by Trimega Laboratories Limited during the period January 2010 to April 2014 and (b) how many such tests were conducted.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118056","118056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802370","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he made an assessment of the case for suspending the Access to Justice and Community Services programme in Syria before 4 December 2017?","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118057","118057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802371","2017-12-11","Department for International Development","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department has allocated to humanitarian operations to takle the famine in South Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118058","118058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802372","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) fines for school attendance orders were issued by courts in England, and of that number how many were unpaid and (b) prison sentences there were for non-payment of school attendance orders, and of those numbers how many were for Gypsy and Traveller children in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118059","118059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802373","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the Khartoum Process on tackling migration within the Horn of Africa.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118060","118060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802374","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to encourage greater private sector investment in research and development; and if he will make a statement","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118061","118061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802375","2017-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish the Government response to the Hendry Review on tidal lagoons before Christmas 2017.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118062","118062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802376","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Sudan to request that it end its use of torture?","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118063","118063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802377","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of the 30 hours free childcare policy on nursery school budgets.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118064","118064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802378","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the reasons for the fall in the number of apprenticeship starts between May to July 2017 compared to the same period in 2016.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118065","118065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802379","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the National or Regional Schools Commissioner first had discussions with the Education and Skills Funding Agency on concerns about the management by the Wakefield City Academies Trust of the schools in their multi-academy trust.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118066","118066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802380","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many 16 to 18 year old apprentices whose families had previously been in receipt of welfare payments there were in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118067","118067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802381","2017-12-11","Women and Equalities","2017-12-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of maternity leave on the gender wage gap?","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118068","118068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802382","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to increase the level of funding allocated by his Department to the Child and Adolescent Mental Health Service.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118069","118069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802383","2017-12-11","Women and Equalities","2017-12-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of proposing gender quotas for businesses.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118070","118070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802384","2017-12-11","Department for International Development","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what mechanisms her Department uses to ensure that UK aid does not fund radicalisation in the Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118071","118071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802385","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason school nurses are not permitted to pass on the names of children who they assess to be obese to their GPs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118072","118072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802468","2017-12-12","HM Treasury","2017-12-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the timetable is for proposed charges on single-use plastic items to come into effect; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902887","902887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798009","2017-12-05","Women and Equalities","2017-12-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities how funding announced in the Spring 2017 Budget to mark the centenary of the Representation of the People Act 1918 has been allocated.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116916","116916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800856","2017-12-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","What steps the Government plans to take to ensure the effective operation of the UK legal system after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902760","902760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800857","2017-12-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","What assessment he has made of trends in access to justice resulting from court and tribunal service closures in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902761","902761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800858","2017-12-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","Whether there are plans to review sentencing guidelines for rape committed by people under 18.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902762","902762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800860","2017-12-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","What steps he is taking to reduce overcrowding in prisons.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902750","902750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800864","2017-12-07","Church Commissioners","2017-12-05","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what assessment has been made of the merits of the Church of England's recent guidance to nursery and primary school teachers on transphobic bullying.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902815","902815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800888","2017-12-07","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2017 to Question 112826 on Nurses and Midwives: Registration, when he plans to publish the report on Workforce Information Review.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117447","117447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800889","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the assessment by UK National Recognition Information Centre that the International Certificate of Christian Education General Certificate is comparable to a Cambridge International Education O Level; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117448","117448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800890","2017-12-07","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the evidential basis was for the sum of £20 million allocated to the GovTech fund in Autumn Budget 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117449","117449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800891","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with Student Finance England on extending the eligibility for the adult dependency grant to include couples living together but who are not married or in a civil partnership.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117450","117450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800892","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the adequacy of the welfare standards of licensed sellers of puppies.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117451","117451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800893","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) timetable and (b) remit is for the independent review of funding and financing for Crossrail 2 announced in the Autumn Budget 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117452","117452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800894","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education,with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October 2017, how many civil servants her Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117453","117453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800895","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that toilet facilities accredited to the Changing Places standard are available in all motorway service stations in England.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117454","117454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800896","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the number of motorway service stations in the North West which provide toilet facilities to the Changing Places standard.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117455","117455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800897","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the number of motorway service stations in England that provide toilet facilities to the Changing Places standard.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117456","117456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800898","2017-12-07","Department for International Development","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to undertake a review of her Department’s role in the global response to HIV/AIDS; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117457","117457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800899","2017-12-07","Department for International Development","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, for what reasons her Department has not undertaken a cumulative impact assessment of its work on the global response to HIV/AIDS since 2013.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117458","117458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800900","2017-12-07","Northern Ireland Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what representations Ministers of his Department have received from Bell Pottinger on behalf of (a) Atos IT Services UK Limited, (b) the British Horseracing Authority, (c) Centrica PLC, (d) DS Smith plc, (e) Ernst & Young, (f) Heads of the Valleys Development Company Limited, (g) Monarch Holdings Limited and (h) Waitrose Limited.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117459","117459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800901","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times in the past two years he has made representations to the Government of Israel on lifting the blockade of Gaza.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117460","117460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800902","2017-12-07","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to tackle opioid abuse in the homeless community.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117461","117461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800903","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the (a) Libyan Government and (b) relevant UN agencies on recent reports of human trafficking in Libya.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117462","117462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800904","2017-12-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what  assessment his Department has made of the effect on single homeless people in short-term accommodation of his Department's proposals for the reform of supported housing.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117463","117463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800905","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2017 to Question 114846, what information her Department holds on reasons for the time taken for Wakefield City Academies Trust to pass the resolution to rebroker its academies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117464","117464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800906","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the UN Security Council Resolutions and the UN Weapons Embargo against Iran in preventing Iran from exporting weapons and advancing its ballistic missile programme.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117465","117465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800907","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to increase procurement of pig products by Government institutions.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117466","117466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800908","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the National Farmers' Union on improving productivity in the pig sector after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117467","117467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800909","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to increase the export of pig products to Asia after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117468","117468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800910","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what advice his Department provides to other Government Departments and businesses on doing business in Iran.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117469","117469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800911","2017-12-07","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what full compliance with the standards and conditional on demonstrating convincing progress along the way means in relation to the continued provision of level 1 services by the Royal Brompton Hospital as announced by his Department on 30 November 2017.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117470","117470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800912","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to make it a requirement for future housing targets to take account of the effect of additional housing on local infrastructure planning and budgets.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117471","117471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800913","2017-12-07","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with NHS England on whether breast cancer patients who currently receive Herceptin (trastuzumab) in the subcutaneous formulation will be included in their ambition for 80 per cent of existing patients being on the best value biological medicine within 12 months.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117472","117472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800914","2017-12-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to increase competition in the (a) energy and (b) banking consumer markets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117473","117473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800915","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to encourage the establishment of greater numbers of housing co-operatives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117474","117474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800916","2017-12-07","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2017 to Question 115401 on Mental Health Services: Nurses, to which NHS Trusts will the first cohort of nursing associates be assigned, and what specialisms he expects that cohort to undertake.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117475","117475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800917","2017-12-07","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the answer of 30 November 2017 to Question 115246 on Mental Health Services: Children and Young People, if he will publish the letter sent by NHS England Directors on 27 February 2017 to CCGS and Trusts on using their budgets for the purposes intended.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117476","117476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800918","2017-12-07","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2017 to Question , what information his Department holds on the number of NHS  (a) frontline and (b) support staff who receive suicide awareness training.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117477","117477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800919","2017-12-07","Department for International Development","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2017 to Question 115249 on Refugees: Disability, what information her Department holds on  the number of referrals made to the disability programmes the UK Government is supporting in that region.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117478","117478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800921","2017-12-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to take into account the Regulation 28: Report to prevent future deaths by David Lewis, Assistant Coroner for the area of North Wales (East and Central) on the Llanrwst fire inquest when it responds to the report from the Working Group on Product Recalls and Safety.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117480","117480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800922","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations he has received on the effect on benefit claimants of outsourcing jobcentre telephony work to Capita.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117481","117481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800923","2017-12-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's response to the consultation, Work, health and disability: improving lives, what plans his Department has to improve mental health training for frontline staff in each region of the UK.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117482","117482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800924","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the contribution to growth and employment in the STEM sector made by the general aviation sector in the UK.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117483","117483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800925","2017-12-07","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued on the sharing of information between medical and educational professionals following a diagnosis of autism for a young person.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117484","117484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800926","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of (a) the detrimental impact on the countryside and (b) the additional pressures on public services in Hatfield Peverel caused by development proposals when he considers the planning applications APP/Z2610/V/17/3180725, APP/Z2610/V/17/3180729 and APP/Z1510/W/16/3162004, called in for him to determine","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117485","117485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800927","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Advisory Council on the Misuse of Drugs report Commissioning impact on drug treatment which published in September 2017, what assessment he has made of the effect of reductions in funding for local authorities on the availability of drug misuse treatment in England.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117486","117486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800928","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the role and remit of the Social Mobility Commission will be upon appointment of its new Board.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117487","117487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800929","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding was allocated to the Social Mobility Commission from the public purse in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, (c) 2017-18; and how much such funding is planned to be allocated in (i) 2018-19, (ii) 2019-20 and (iii) 2020-21.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117488","117488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800930","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which recommendations the Government adopted from the Social Mobility Commission's State of the Nation Report (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117489","117489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800931","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timetable is for (a) new Commissioners, (b) a new Chair and (c) a new Vice-Chair to be appointed to the Social Mobility Commission.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117490","117490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800932","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's proposals in its Green Paper on children and young people's mental health, published on 4 December 2017, if he will publish a breakdown of spending areas in each year to 2022-23 for the additional expenditure committed.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117491","117491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800933","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will assess the merits of implementing the Disability Benefits Consortium's recommendations on PIP assessors.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117492","117492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800934","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to allow Personal Independence Payment claimants to have their assessments recorded.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117493","117493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800935","2017-12-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2017 to Question 115913, if he will list the Government's programmes aimed at reducing regulation.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117494","117494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800936","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to decide whether protected geographical indicators will continue after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117495","117495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800937","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have been found (a) in possession and (b) under the influence of drugs in each of the last seven years in each region of England.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117496","117496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800938","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of occasions when, due to the loss or theft of keys, a prison has had to be relocked since March 2010; and what the cost to the public purse was of each such incident.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117497","117497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800939","2017-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much compensation has been paid to prisoners as a result of delays in parole hearings in each year since March 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117498","117498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800940","2017-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been paid in compensation to (a) prisoners, (b) prison staff and  (c) third parties as a result of injuries suffered in a violent attack on the prison estate in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117499","117499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800941","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on a Communique sent to the Anglophone population of Southern Cameroon on its being required to evacuate its villages.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117500","117500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800942","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Cameroon.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117501","117501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800943","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November 2017 to Question 110340, whether he plans to make further representations to the Prime Minister of Cameroon on reports of genocide in that country.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117502","117502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800945","2017-12-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that there is adequate private investment in shared ownership accommodation.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117504","117504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800946","2017-12-07","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the (a) potential for reduction in the cost of payments transactions and (b) effect of changes in that cost on financial inclusion.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117505","117505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800947","2017-12-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that local government pension funds can invest in areas such as new build shared ownership.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117506","117506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800948","2017-12-07","Department for International Development","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's science budget is allocated to (a) the UK,  (b) Africa and (c) Asia.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117507","117507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800949","2017-12-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the implications of third-party tracker in Android apps for the security and privacy of UK citizens.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117508","117508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800950","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of the grant for Kensington and Chelsea Council announced in Autumn Budget 2017 for people affected by the Grenfell Tower fire is allocated to (a) mental health services, (b) developing new community spaces and (c) regeneration projects.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117509","117509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800951","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with Ofwat on ensuring water and sewerage companies improve their response to leakages.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117510","117510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800952","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the rates of prostate cancer among men over 50 who are (a) white and (b) BAME during the last ten years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117511","117511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800953","2017-12-11","Department for International Development","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress her Department has made on eliminating female genital mutilation in Africa in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117512","117512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800954","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the change in number of financial advisors who offer advice on personal pensions arising from recent changes on accessibility to personal pensions.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117513","117513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800955","2017-12-11","Department for International Development","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the amount of funding allocated to the Global Polio Eradication Initiative which will not be spent by 2019.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117514","117514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800956","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has for regulation of the chemical industry in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117515","117515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800957","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the cost of REACH registration fees paid by UK chemicals industry companies in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117516","117516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800958","2017-12-07","Cabinet Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of possible changes required to the Civil Service nationality rules to address the provisions relating to freedom of movement after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117517","117517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800959","2017-12-07","Cabinet Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has made an assessment of the civil service functions across central government that have the highest reliance on non-UK EU nationals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117518","117518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800960","2017-12-07","Cabinet Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has made an estimate of the number non-UK EU nationals employed by each Government Department as a (a) civil servant and (b) contractor.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117519","117519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800961","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) men and (b) women hold a (a) full and (b) provisional UK driving licence.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117520","117520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800962","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health what assessment he has made of the potential merits of fully implementing the International Code of Marketing of Breastmilk Substitutes after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117521","117521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800963","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer what progress is being made on abolishing VAT on sanitary products.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117522","117522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800964","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the amount of (a) food waste and (b) total bio-degrable waste that goes to (i) incineration and (ii) landfill in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117523","117523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800965","2017-12-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the strength of Stoke-on-Trent's bid to be UK City of Culture 2021.","Biography information for Jack Brereton","Jack Brereton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117524","117524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800966","2017-12-07","Home Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether a Memorandum of Understanding or similar document is in place for the sharing of data obtained by the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority with her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117525","117525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800967","2017-12-07","Home Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have had their data shared by the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority with her Department for immigration enforcement purposes since that authority was established.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117526","117526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800968","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress is being made on the review of parents’ right to retract nationality and country of birth data submitted through the school census; and whether parents will still be able to retract this data by responding that they refused in the Spring census.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117527","117527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800969","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Memorandum of Understanding between her Department and the Home Office published in December 2015, whether nationality data is used in the data-matching process that matches her Department's records with Home Office records submitted to it.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117528","117528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800970","2017-12-07","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which Minister of his Department has responsibility for non-emergency patient transport.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117529","117529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800971","2017-12-07","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which Department will be allocated funds repatriated from the Common Fisheries Policy after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117530","117530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800972","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the level of WTO tariffs for (a) beef (b) poultry (c) sheep (d) pork exports from the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117531","117531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800973","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse to date has been of installing or subsidising (a) uni-directional and (b) bi-directional charge points for electric vehicles in the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117532","117532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800974","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) uni-directional and (b) bi-directional charge points for electric vehicles have been installed and are operational within the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117533","117533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800975","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions the RAF has cannibalised Typhoon aircraft due to lack of available spares in order to keep up with operations and training programmes over the last (a) three, (b) six and (c) 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117534","117534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800976","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding from the public purse is planned to be allocated on installing or subsidising (a) uni-directional and (b) bi-directional charge points for electric vehicles within the UK by 2025.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117535","117535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800977","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how may spare parts for RAF Typhoons have been used over the last (a) three, (b) six and (c) 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117536","117536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800978","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on support for a possible UN-mandated global arms embargo on Burma.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117537","117537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800979","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking in order to reduce cannibalism of equipment in the Armed Forces.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117538","117538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800980","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) uni- directional and (b) bi-directional charge points for electric vehicles which are planned to be installed within the UK by 2025.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117539","117539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800982","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to discuss with his EU counterparts an expansion of the current EU arms embargo to ban all EU companies from supplying any kind of equipment to the military in Burma.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117541","117541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800983","2017-12-07","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether there are plans to extend the cancer dashboard to include tumour-specific data for (a) ovarian and (b) other less common cancers.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117542","117542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800984","2017-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of self-harm incidents by prisoners has been per prison in England and Wales since March 2017.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117543","117543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800985","2017-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of incidents relating to Spice has been per prison in England and Wales since March 2017.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117544","117544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800986","2017-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average level of staff turnover has been per prison in England and Wales since March 2017.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117545","117545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800987","2017-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of incidents of seizures of drugs recorded per prison in England and Wales has been since since March 2017.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117546","117546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800988","2017-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of prisoner-on-prisoner assaults recorded has been per prison in England and Wales since March 2017.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117547","117547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800990","2017-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of times is the local Fire and Rescue service has been called to prisons in England and Wales per prison since March 2017.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117549","117549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800991","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the humanitarian effects of the proposed demolition of the village of Susiya in the South Hebron hills.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117550","117550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800992","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what evidence he has received on the potential of the voluntary agreement by lenders to effectively ensure that customers’ credit limits are not increased without their permission.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117551","117551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800993","2017-12-07","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average number of incidents of prisoners attending accident and emergency departments at local general hospitals has been per prison in England and Wales since March 2017.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117552","117552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800994","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on the voluntary agreement by lenders not to increase customers’ credit limits without their permission; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117553","117553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800995","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the National Audit Office has inspected the accounts of the office of the Director of Special Forces since its establishment in 1987; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117554","117554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800996","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the rates of uptake of the shingles vaccine","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117555","117555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800997","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of tree planting rates.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117556","117556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800998","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of times the website web.whatsapp.com was accessed from computers based in her Department during the period Feb 2017 to July 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117557","117557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800999","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs what support the Government is providing to the United Nations Special Rapporteur on the situation of human rights in Myanmar, and the United Nations Fact Finding Mission on Myanmar.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117558","117558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801000","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs what assessment he has been made of whether Niranjan Rasalingam, a British citizen jailed in Burma, has received a fair trial.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117559","117559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801001","2017-12-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of the £28 million funding for Housing First pilot schemes will be allocated to projects in the St Helens local authority area.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117560","117560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801002","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of the Pothole Action Fund will be allocated to St Helens Council.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117561","117561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801003","2017-12-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of rough sleepers in the St Helens local authority area in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117562","117562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801004","2017-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Government plans to publish its response to the recommendations made in the Insurance Fraud Taskforce report of January 2016; and what steps he is taking to reduce fraudulent personal injury claims while ensuring appropriate compensation for genuine claimants.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117563","117563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801005","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will (a) make an assessment of the equity of the tolling scheme and (b) investigate the operational problems with the administration of tolls on the Mersey Gateway Bridge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117564","117564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801006","2017-12-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of which EU assets the UK will be able to benefit from the use of or have recourse to during the period when the UK is contributing to the EU budget but is no longer an EU member state; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117565","117565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801007","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to remove the disparity in tolls on the Mersey Gateway Bridge between people who live within the local authority boundaries of Liverpool City Council and Knowsley Borough Council and those who have a Halton postcode.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117566","117566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801008","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what processes are in place to ensure that care provider CQC ratings are taken into account in advice issued by local authority social services to people seeking a care home.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117567","117567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801009","2017-12-07","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2017 to Question 113472, for what reasons the period from April 2010 to March 2013 was excluded from the total amount of money from the public purse spent on Talk to Frank since its creation.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117568","117568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801010","2017-12-11","Home Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people born on 3 May 2000 or earlier are in possession of a firearms licence registered in the (a) West Midlands and (b) Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117569","117569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801011","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the role of school education in improving social mobility; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117570","117570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801012","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of falling bio-ethanol prices on the (a) operation and (b) future of the UK bio-ethanol industry.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117571","117571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801013","2017-12-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to bring forward proposals to factor unearned income into child maintenance payment plans.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117572","117572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801014","2017-12-07","Home Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for the UK Government to ratify the Istanbul Convention.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117573","117573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801015","2017-12-07","Home Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the effect of closing custody suites on people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117574","117574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801016","2017-12-07","Home Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's policy paper entitled Ratification of the Council of Europe convention on combating violence against women and domestic violence, published on 1 November 2017, what discussions she has had with the devolved administrations on extra-territorial jurisdiction in respect of that convention.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117575","117575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801017","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for legislative proposals to be brought forward to provide for a 10 per cent bio-ethanol content in UK petrol supplies.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117576","117576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801018","2017-12-07","Home Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what meetings she had with Women’s Aid, IC Change and other women's organisations before publishing the Government's policy paper entitled Ratification of the Council of Europe convention on combating violence against women and domestic violence on 1 November 2017.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117577","117577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801019","2017-12-11","Cabinet Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of non-UK born EU citizens that have left the UK since 23 of June 2016.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117578","117578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801020","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing the use of E10 fuel into the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117579","117579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801021","2017-12-11","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the relocation of the European Medicines Agency on the future of the Novartis pharmaceutical (a) site and (b) production at that site.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117580","117580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801022","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether student loans are classed as complete income for the purposes of calculating universal credit eligibility.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117581","117581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801023","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when last he met his counterpart in the Government of Ethiopia, and what issues were discussed at that meeting","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117582","117582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801024","2017-12-07","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many demand notices for an overpayment of child tax credit have been sent out in the last financial year.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117583","117583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801025","2017-12-07","Home Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of number plate fraud have been recorded in England and Wales each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117584","117584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801026","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for Northern Rail to begin operating services between York and Scarborough.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117585","117585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801027","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage more young people to train in agriculture-based industries.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117586","117586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801028","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has for the development of specialist careers advice for people who are considering study and careers in agricultural technologies.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117587","117587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801029","2017-12-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that consumers who are victims of data breaches receive adequate service and compensation from the companies responsible.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117588","117588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801030","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential economic effect on the surrounding area of the opening of Carlisle Airport to domestic flights.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117589","117589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801031","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many kinship carers have been denied child tax credit for a baby to whom they or their partner have given birth since 6 April 2017.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117590","117590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801032","2017-12-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the potential cost to parish councils of complying with the General Data Protection Regulation.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117591","117591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801033","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of kinship carers who will be unable to claim child tax credit for their own baby as a result of the restriction of child tax credit to two children within the household in the financial years (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117592","117592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801034","2017-12-07","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing the time limit for complaints to be referred to the Financial Ombudsman Service from 6 months to 12 months in line with other ombudsman services.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117593","117593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801035","2017-12-07","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the savings that will accrue to the public purse in financial years (a) 2017-18,  (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20 as a result of kinship carers with two children in a household not being able to claim child tax credit for their own baby.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117594","117594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801036","2017-12-07","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the sustainability of the GP network.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117595","117595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801037","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the Cycle to Work scheme on supporting the uptake of electric bikes.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117596","117596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801038","2017-12-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much electricity was consumed by incinerators in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016; and how much (i) CO2 and (ii) CO2e was emitted as a result of that consumption in each of those years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117597","117597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801039","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) primary schools and (b) secondary schools are in financial special measures; and how many of those schools have been in financial special measures for more than (i) six months, (ii) 12 months, (iii) 18 months and (iv) 24 months.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117598","117598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801040","2017-12-07","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of annually indexing the contribution limits for Share Incentive Plans and Save As You Earn plans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kenneth Clarke","Mr Kenneth Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117599","117599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801041","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department or other Government departments or agencies have had access to a full copy of the US Senate Select Committee on Intelligence Committee Study of the Central Intelligence Agency's Detention and Interrogation Program.","Biography information for Mr Kenneth Clarke","Mr Kenneth Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117600","117600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801042","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department or other Government departments or agencies have requested a full copy of the US Senate Select Committee on Intelligence Committee Study of the Central Intelligence Agency's Detention and Interrogation Program.","Biography information for Mr Kenneth Clarke","Mr Kenneth Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117601","117601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801043","2017-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Justice, of 5 December 2017, Official Report, column 882, on Female Offender Management, when he plans to publish the strategy for women and justice.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117602","117602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801044","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the letter of 27 November 2017 from the hon. Member for Croydon North about cladding on the Citiscape building in Croydon.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117603","117603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801045","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2017 to Question 115795, if he will provide a breakdown of breaches of permits in each of the Environment Agency’s 14 operational areas in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117604","117604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801046","2017-12-11","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he will answer the hon. Member for Garston and Halewood's letter to him of 18 October 2017 about tolls on the Mersey Gateway Bridge.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117605","117605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801047","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 8 of the Government’s July 2016 Keep on Caring strategy, what review his Department has undertaken into extending the exemption from the Shared Accommodation rate of Local Housing Allowance from 22 to 25; and when he plans to publish the findings of that review.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117606","117606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801048","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of care leavers who are receive housing support through universal credit are in rent arrears.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117607","117607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801049","2017-12-07","Cabinet Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Written Statement of 16 November 2017, HCWS 258 on social care, whether the proposed green paper will specifically cover social care services received by working-age and non-working age people affected by dementia.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117608","117608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801050","2017-12-07","Cabinet Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Written Statement of 16 November 2017, HCWS 258 on social care, if he will ensure that the reasons for delayed transfers of care relating to people affected by dementia are included as part of the proposed green paper.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117609","117609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801051","2017-12-07","Cabinet Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 16 November 2017, HCWS 258 on social care, whether the Government plans to bring forward proposals on the future of children’s social care and services for children who need palliative care.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117610","117610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801052","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, by means of which operations, through which ships and in which theatres the Royal Navy projects its power strategically.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117611","117611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801053","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of schools in West Sussex are rated good or outstanding; and how that proportion compares with the national average and the equivalent proportion in other local authority areas.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117612","117612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801054","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 9826, what method the CPS used to select the sample of case files to assess the frequency and outcome of applications seeking to introduce into rape proceedings evidence of the complainant's sexual history under s.41 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117613","117613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801055","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 9826, what crimes were selected for the sample of case files selected by the CPS to assess the frequency and outcome of applications seeking to introduce into rape proceedings evidence of the complainant's sexual history.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117614","117614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801056","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 9826 how many case files were selected by the Crown Prosecution Service for the sample of case files selected to assess the frequency and outcome of applications seeking to introduce into rape proceedings evidence of the complainant's sexual history.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117615","117615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801057","2017-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the (a) two child limit element in child tax credits and(b) the equivalent element in universal credit on the use of food banks families over the next 5 years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117616","117616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801058","2017-12-11","Department for International Trade","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what account his Department took of outstanding indictments in the International Criminal Court before agreeing to the joint trade conference with Sudan set for 12 December 2017.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117617","117617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801059","2017-12-11","Department for International Trade","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2017 to Question 116341, whether his Department plans to replicate the 19 trade remedies currently in force against Chinese steel to which the UK adheres through its EU membership after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117618","117618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801060","2017-12-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will publish the travel costs incurred by (a) Ministers and (b) staff in his Department since his Department was established.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117619","117619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801061","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to increase parking provision at railway stations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117620","117620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801062","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Pakistani counterpart on that country's decision to supply Burma with military equipment.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117621","117621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801063","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with members of the UN Security Council on support for a UN-mandated arms embargo against Burma.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117622","117622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801064","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with EU counterparts on support for a UN-mandated arms embargo against Burma.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117623","117623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801065","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations on the case of Mai Cho Min Htwe with (a) Aung San Suu Kyi and (b) other members of the Burmese Government.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117624","117624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801066","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to commemorate those who gave their lives in Aden.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117625","117625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801067","2017-12-12","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take against Concordia as a result of the Competition and Markets Authority findings announced on 21 November 2017 that Concordia had overcharged the NHS for the provision of Liothyronine tablets.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117626","117626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801068","2017-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Land Registry's publication of offshore companies owning UK property, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the public purse of making the beneficial owners of those companies public.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117627","117627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801069","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of public spending on flood prevention in (a) Fylde constituency and (b) the UK in each of the (i) next and (ii) last five years.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117628","117628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801070","2017-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Office, what funds the Government has made available to Anguilla following Hurricane Irma.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117629","117629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801071","2017-12-12","Department for International Development","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State of International Development, what proportion of the package of recovery and reconstruction for British Overseas Territories affected by recent hurricanes announced by the Prime Minister on 28 November 2017 is classified as ODA; and whether any amount of ODA has been diverted from other intended recipients as a result of that classification.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117630","117630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801072","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prevent coastal flooding in Lancashire.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117631","117631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801073","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff were employed by the Environment Agency in (a) Cumbria and (b) Lancashire in each year since 1 January 2012.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117632","117632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801074","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment the Environment Agency has made of the effect of new housing developments on the risk of flooding in Fylde constituency.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117633","117633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801075","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has taken to ensure that tractors pulling trailers in a work capacity are not charged (a) tolls and (b) Penalty Charge Notices on the Mersey Gateway Bridge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117634","117634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801076","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations he has received on the liability of tractors to pay tolls on the Mersey Gateway Bridge.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117635","117635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801077","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children who are (a) eligible and (b) not eligible for free school meals have achieved school readiness standards at the end of the Early Years Foundation Stage in each year since 2010 in Lewisham Deptford constituency.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117636","117636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801078","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the uptake of funded childcare for (a) two-year-olds and (b) three-year-olds from (i) disadvantaged and (ii) non-disadvantaged households in Lewisham Deptford constituency.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117637","117637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801079","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings (a) ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with (i) HM Treasury and  (ii) the Department of Transport related to the liability of tractors to pay tolls on the Mersey Gateway Bridge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117638","117638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801080","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings (a) Ministers or (b) officials of his Department have had with (i) HM Treasury and (ii) the Department of Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the liability of tractors to pay tolls on the Mersey Gateway Bridge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117639","117639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801081","2017-12-07","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with the (i) Department of Environment Food and Rural Affairs and (ii) Department of Transport related to the liability of tractors to pay tolls on the Mersey Gateway Bridge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117640","117640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801082","2017-12-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that sporting bodies are sufficiently well-regulated to prevent abuse within those organisations.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117641","117641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801083","2017-12-07","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on the liability of tractors to pay tolls on the Mersey Gateway Bridge.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117642","117642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801084","2017-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if the Government will take steps to ensure the continued provision of quality assured chaplaincy services in prisons by maintaining the guidelines set out in PSI 5/2016 and incorporating them into any future policy framework.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117643","117643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801085","2017-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what support his Department provides to improve attendance at schools by children whose families are placed in temporary accommodation away from local schools.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117644","117644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801086","2017-12-07","Department of Health","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has increased the level of funding allocated to A&E departments, maternity units and GP surgeries in (a) England and (b) Kent in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117645","117645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801087","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers left the profession within three years of qualification in each region of England in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117646","117646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801088","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many women (a) applied for, (b) were accepted on and (c) completed the UK Officer Commissioning Course at Royal Military Academy Sandhurst for each course since the start of 2015.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117647","117647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801089","2017-12-07","Home Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to maintain police officer numbers in England in 2018-19; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117648","117648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801090","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the reasons for teachers leaving the profession; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117649","117649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801091","2017-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will include access to chaplaincy in its performance measures for prisons on time spent out of cells engaging in purposeful activity.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117650","117650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801092","2017-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times and on what dates the Government has raised the issue of slavery in Libya in discussion with the Libyan Government or has otherwise made representations to that government on that subject.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117651","117651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801093","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many women (a) applied for, (b) were accepted on and (c) completed the Initial Officer Training Course at RAF College Cranwell for each course since the start of 2015.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117652","117652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801094","2017-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many women (a) applied for, (b) were accepted on and (c) completed the Initial Naval Training (Officer) course at Britannia Royal Naval College for each course since the start of 2015.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117653","117653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801095","2017-12-11","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 102 of the Industrial Strategy, when she plans to introduce revised performance measures for school and colleges performance.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117654","117654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801096","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 103 of the Industrial Strategy,  when she plans to undertake a review into higher level technical education at levels 4 and 5.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117655","117655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801097","2017-12-07","Department for Education","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 110 of the Industrial Strategy, when she expects the National Centre for Computing Education to be in operation.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117656","117656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801098","2017-12-11","Cabinet Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to page 134 of the Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to improve procurement tools to make public sector contracts more accessible for SMEs.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117657","117657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801099","2017-12-11","Department for Transport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 137 of the Industrial Strategy, when he expects the Rebalancing Toolkit to be in operation.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117658","117658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801100","2017-12-07","HM Treasury","2017-12-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 145 of the Industrial Strategy, when he expects the Charging Infrastructure Investment Fund to be in operation.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117659","117659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801101","2017-12-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 148 of Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the Bioeconomy Strategy.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117660","117660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801102","2017-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 148 of the Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the new strategy for resources and waste.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117661","117661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801103","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Government has any plans to introduce a mandatory retirement age for prison officers.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117662","117662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801104","2017-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Government has plans to lower the pension age for prison officers from 67 to 60.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117663","117663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801105","2017-12-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to ensure that local authorities are regularly informed by his Department of households in their area in receipt of universal credit in which a child is or is about to be two years’ old to ensure that local authorities can promote free early years education entitlement for two-year-olds to qualifying households; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117664","117664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801106","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Infantry, (b) Royal Artillery, (c) Royal Corps of Signals, (d) Army Medical Services, (e) Adjutant General's Corps, (f) Royal Armoured Corps, (g) Army Air Corps, (h) Royal Engineers, (i) Royal Logistics Corps, (j) Royal Electrical and Mechanical Engineers and (k) Intelligence Corps overseas training exercises have been (i) held and (ii) cancelled in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117665","117665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801107","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on external website design consultants in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117666","117666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801108","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support his Department plans to offer to Babcock employees at Rosyth dockyard who are to be made redundant as a result of the completion of work on the UK’s Queen Elizabeth-class aircraft carrier programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117667","117667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801109","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to make representations to his Russian counterpart Russia’s veto of the UN Security Council draft resolution on extending the mandate of the Joint Investigative Mechanism investigating use of chemical weapons in Syria.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117668","117668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801110","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many British nationals travelling independently to North Korea have informed the British Embassy in Pyongyang of their visit in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117669","117669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801111","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his oral contribution of 27 November 2017, Official Report, column 2, if he will set out in more detail what the £1.5 billion of defence investment in Scotland is being spent on.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117670","117670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801112","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his oral contribution of 27 November 2017, Official Report, column 4, what the value of the real terms increase in defence spending on defence equipment has been over the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117671","117671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801113","2017-12-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many times the Information Commissioner's Office has fined central government departments in each year since it was created.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117672","117672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801114","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Defence of 27 November 2017, Official Report, column 14, what the value of successful applications to the Defence Innovation Fund has been during 2017.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117673","117673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801115","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2017 to Question 116529, on Ministry of Defence: Disclosure of information, whether his Department always notifies families of their right to seek redactions and the removal of names of family members prior to publication.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117674","117674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801116","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2017 to Question 116529, on Ministry of Defence: Disclosure of information, how many reports were compiled in the period 2014 to 2016; and what (a) the dates of completion, (b) the dates of publication and (c) the notification periods were that were given to the affected families for each of those reports.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117675","117675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801117","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2017 to Question 116530, on Ministry of Defence: Disclosure of information, whether his Department has received agreement from the other families involved to publish the report.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117676","117676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801118","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2017 to Question 116535, on Armed Forces: Compensation, what the considerations are which his Department makes before a payment will be made.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117677","117677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801119","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2017 to Question 116535, on Armed Forces: Compensation, what the exceptional circumstances are in which his Department delays payments in the case of an appeal before the Army Board.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117678","117678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801120","2017-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2017 to Question 116535, on Armed Forces: Compensation, for what reasons his Department cannot delay payment in the case of an uncompleted appeal.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117679","117679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801121","2017-12-07","Department for International Development","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government of Burma has informed the UK Government that aid agencies using the word Rohingya will face restrictions on their activities.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117680","117680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801122","2017-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the  Aung San Suu Kyi on releasing all political prisoners in Burma.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117681","117681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801123","2017-12-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much the Government spent on funding for cavity wall insulation schemes in the last ten years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117682","117682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801124","2017-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 30 November to Questions 114885 and 114886, how many of the reindeer imported into the UK in 2016 were (a) females, (b) intact males and (c) castrated males; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117683","117683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801125","2017-12-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will introduce an independent dispute mechanism for consumers related to companies which have installed defective or unsuitable cavity wall insulation.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117684","117684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801126","2017-12-07","Cabinet Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many incidents relating to cyber attacks have been dealt with by GCHQ in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117685","117685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801127","2017-12-07","Cabinet Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to introduce guidelines to ensure that reporting of security breaches to the Cabinet Office is consistent across all Departments.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117686","117686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801128","2017-12-07","Cabinet Office","2017-12-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many data incidents in central Government departments were (a) recorded and (b) reported to the Information Commissioner's Office in (i) 2015-16 and (ii) 2016-2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117687","117687"
