"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968208","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department has provided to local authorities on the elimination of foxes from urban areas.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170840","170840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968209","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many full-time equivalent staff are employed by his Department in (a) London and (b) each regions of England.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170841","170841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968210","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many parking penalty charge notices were issued under the Forestry Commission Byelaws 1982 in 2017.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170842","170842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968211","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many parking penalty charge notices were issued under the Forestry Commission Byelaws 1982 for (a) non-payment and (b) insufficient payment in 2017.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170843","170843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968212","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Coastal Protection Act 1949 on reducing the level of coastal erosion.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170844","170844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968213","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential productivity of the livestock industry over the next six months.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170845","170845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968214","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential productivity of the arable industry over the next six months.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170846","170846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968215","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the potato crop for England and Wales in 2018.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170847","170847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968216","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has estimated the number of trees in the (a) Hendon constituency and (b) Greater London area.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170848","170848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968217","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 April 2018 to Question 136869 on Wakefield City Academies Trust, whether the Mexborough Academy has been re-brokered.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170849","170849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968219","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Scotland over the age of 65 have been (a) invited to move from disability living allowance to personal independence payment and (b) referred to the assessment provider as part of that reassessment process.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170757","170757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968220","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Scotland over the age of 65 have been (a) successfully reassessed and (b) unsuccessfully reassessed after being invited to move from disability living allowance to personal independence payment; and how many of those people were referred to the assessment provider as part of that reassessment process.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170850","170850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968221","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of personal independence payment in Scotland over the age of 65 have been (a) sent an AR1 for a review of their award and (b) referred to the assessment provider as part of that review process.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170851","170851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968222","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment (PIP) claimants in Scotland over the age of 65 have had their award (a) increased, (b) reduced and (c) unchanged under the PIP review process.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170852","170852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968223","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect on humanitarian access after military operations in Saada in August 2018.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170678","170678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968224","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of Saudi-led Coalition military operations in Saada in August 2018 on civilian life.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170679","170679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968225","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's position is on the view of the UN Human Rights Council Group of Eminent Experts that individuals in the Government and the coalition, including Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates, may have conducted attacks in violation of the principles of distinction, proportionality and precaution that may amount to war crimes.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170680","170680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968226","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much money the Government has invested in wave and tidal stream technologies since 2010.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170853","170853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968227","2018-09-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will (a) update the 2011 lists of statutory duties placed on local authorities by legislation for which (i) his Department and (ii) other Departments are responsible; and (b) publish the additional potential duties placed on local authorities set out in (A) legislative proposals and (B) Government consultations.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170690","170690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968228","2018-09-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans the Government has to ensure the maintenance of rights of representation before the EU Intellectual Property Office for UK legal professionals when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170854","170854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968229","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which international election observation missions his Department provided financial support for the participation of UK observers in each year since 2010; how much such finance his Department provided in each such year; which international election observation missions his Department plans to provide financial support for the participation of UK observers in 2018-19; how much such finance his Department has committed for 2018-19; whether there have been any changes to his Department's policy for supporting and funding such missions in 2018-19; and whether his Department plans to make any such changes for future financial years.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170691","170691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968230","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure the transparency of the terms of state-supported nuclear power projects.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170855","170855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968232","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the welfare of livestock of balloons and Chinese lanterns.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170856","170856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968233","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing restrictions on the use of (a) balloons and (b) Chinese lanterns on animal welfare grounds.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170857","170857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968234","2018-09-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport's press release of 8 August 2018 entitled Government outlines vision to empower and invest in society on the launch of the innovation in democracy pilot scheme, whether there has been any change in departmental responsibilities that resulted in that Department issuing that press release.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170692","170692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968235","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the responsible use of (a) balloons and (b) Chinese lanterns in relation to their effect on livestock.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170858","170858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968236","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the role of local authorities will be in the establishment of innovation in democracy pilots.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170693","170693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968237","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that support payments are paid by the Rural Payments Agency in a timely manner, in light of the dry weather in summer 2018.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170859","170859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968238","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department provides for unmarried bereaved parents and their children who are ineligible for bereavement support payments.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170705","170705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968240","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the feasibility of a UK net emissions target of zero before 2050.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170860","170860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968241","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the UK meets its commitments under the Paris Climate Change Agreement.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170861","170861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968242","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of Northern services operating at weekends.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170862","170862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968243","2018-09-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether his Department has made a regional assessment of the effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170863","170863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968244","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the findings of the National Education Union and Child Poverty Action Group, Child poverty and education: A survey of the experiences of NEU members, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of school staff who are personally purchasing equipment for students.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170706","170706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968245","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations he has received from industry organisations and farmers requesting flexibility in the application of CAP schemes or agri-environment schemes, in light of the dry weather in summer 2018.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170864","170864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968246","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the change in the public health grant on the health outcomes of lower income households in (a) Blackburn and (b) England.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170865","170865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968247","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the economic effect of broadband blackspots in (a) the London Borough of Enfield and (b) the Enfield North constituency.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170662","170662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968248","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will increase the national living wage to the rate recommended by the Living Wage Commission.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170707","170707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968250","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what (a) representations her Department has made to and (b) what recent discussions his Department has held with the (i) EU and (ii) World Bank on funding for the United Nations Relief and Works Agency for Palestine Refugees in the Near East (UNRWA) in light of the decision of the US to withdraw its funding to that Agency.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170866","170866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968251","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress is being made on plans for electrification of the trans-pennine railway line.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170867","170867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968252","2018-09-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Written Statement of 24 July 2018 on Local Growth, HLWS898, what the timeframe is for the start of the consultation on the UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170708","170708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968253","2018-09-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of funding allocated to (a) Blackburn borough council (b) other local authorities in England.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170868","170868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968254","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to assess whether the first phase of managed migration to universal credit is being managed effectively for disabled claimants.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170657","170657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968255","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2018 to Question 167151 on Disability Living Allowance: Appeals, what the timeframe is for the reduction in the waiting times to be achieved; and what recent assessment she has made of the potential level of reduction in waiting times.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170701","170701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968256","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of the proposed rates of transitional payments for universal credit on the financial situation of individuals receiving severe disability premium; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170658","170658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968258","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the Government’s policy is on financial support for UK Fintech companies in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170663","170663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968259","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Explanatory Memorandum to the draft Universal Credit (Transitional Protection) (Managed Migration) Amendment Regulations 2018, what methodology her Department used to estimate the number of claimants that will move from legacy benefits to universal credit through managed migration.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170659","170659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968260","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an assessment of the experience of disabled people using the digital gateway for universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170660","170660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968261","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to identify (a) disabled people and (b) other vulnerable groups that will require additional support to make a new claim for universal credit during the managed migration.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170661","170661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968262","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the amount of the allocated radio spectrum that is unused.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170869","170869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968263","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department has allocated to local authorities for home to school travel in each financial year since 2014-15.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170870","170870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968264","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers currently serving at HMP Risley have (a) less than six months, (b) six to 12 months, (c) 12 months to five years and (iv) more than five years' service as prison officers.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170695","170695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968266","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of T-Levels with employers in advance of the 2020 start date for those qualifications.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170871","170871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968267","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the effect on local authority support services  of reclassifying HMP Risley as a prison for non-UK prisoners; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170696","170696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968268","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support employers to provide placements for T-level students.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170872","170872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968269","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with Warrington Borough Council on the effect on that council's (a) services and (b) budget of reclassifying HMP Risley as a prison for non-UK prisoners.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170697","170697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968270","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what social economic distributional analysis his Department has undertaken in relation to the effect on individual groups of the Enterprise Management Incentive Exemptions and Reliefs; and if he will place a copy of that analysis in the Library.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170666","170666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968271","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions (a) Ministers of his Department and (b) officials in his Department have had with the (i) CBI, (ii) Federation of Small Business and (iii) British Chamber of Commerce on employer-understanding of the recent changes to 9-1 grading for GCSEs.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170873","170873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968272","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate she has made of the number of women (a) receiving jobseeker's allowance and (b) in rent arrears as a result of changes to the state pension age.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170874","170874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968273","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2018 to Question 162589 on WASPI, whether she plans to meet with representatives of the WASPI campaign in the future.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170875","170875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968274","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations he has received from (a) Facebook, (b) Google, (c) YouTube, (d) Twitter, (e) WhatsApp, (f) Snapchat and (e) other social media companies on his Department’s social media hub to tackle gang-related online content; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170664","170664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968276","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure special protection measures are implemented for all victims of domestic abuse across all UK jurisdictions.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170876","170876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968277","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has plans for an independent statutory inquiry into the family courts’ handling of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170877","170877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968278","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses benefited from Enterprise Management Incentives exemptions and reliefs in each year since 2010.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170667","170667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968279","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that women are better represented in the UK judicial system.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170878","170878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968280","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse was of Enterprise Management Incentives exemptions and reliefs in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014, (f) 2015, (g) 2016 and (h) 2017.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170668","170668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968281","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his (a) US, (b) South Korean and (c) North Korean counterparts on peace and stability in the Korean peninsula.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170726","170726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968282","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Japanese counterpart following Typhoon Jebi.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170727","170727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968283","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with Chinese counterpart on the human rights of ethnic minorities.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170728","170728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968285","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Nicaraguan counterpart on human rights in that country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170729","170729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968286","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what equality impact assessment on gender and other protected characteristics under the Equality Act 2010 his Department has undertaken on the Enterprise Management Incentives exemptions and reliefs; and if he will place a copy of that equality impact assessment in the Library.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170669","170669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968287","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he had had with his Latin American counterparts on their response to Venezuelan refugees.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170730","170730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968288","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has identified a disproportionate effect of Enterprise Management Incentives exemptions and reliefs with regard to gender and other protected characteristics under the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170670","170670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968289","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the loss of tax revenue in the event of a GDP fall of 7.7 per cent over (a) five years, (b) 10 years and (c) 15 years; and if he will place a copy of the findings in the Library.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170671","170671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968290","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average amount of time is for a person to receive a response from HMRC caseworkers for queries on (a) inheritance tax payments and (b) other subjects; and whether his Department has any target times for such responses to be sent.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170734","170734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968291","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what equality impact assessment on gender and other protected characteristics under the Equality Act 2010 his Department has undertaken with regard to the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and if he will place a copy of that equality impact assessment in the Library.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170672","170672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968292","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has identified a disproportionate effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal with regard to gender and other protected characteristics under the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170673","170673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968294","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timescale is for removing the experimental status of quarterly Child Maintenance Service statistics.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170879","170879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968295","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the paper, Strategy for the publication of information about the 2012 scheme, updated 30 November 2016, whether the Data Warehouse has been replaced by the new Data and Analytics Platform.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170880","170880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968296","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the monthly receipts accrued to the public purse were from (a) the fee charged for applications to the Child Maintenance Service (CMS), (b) the collection fee for paying parents using the CMS Collect and Pay service, (c) the collection fee for receiving parents using the CMS Collect and Pay service and (d) enforcement fees levied on paying parents in each month since March 2017.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170881","170881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968297","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the money that will accrue to the public purse of the (a) fee charged for applications to the Child Maintenance Service (CMS), (b) collection fee for paying parents using the CMS Collect and Pay service, (c) collection fee for receiving parents using the CMS Collect and Pay service and (d) enforcement fees levied on paying parents in (i) 2019-20 and (ii) 2020-21.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170882","170882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968299","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority staff responsible for frontline inspection activity are female.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170883","170883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968300","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what training he Department has provided to Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority frontline inspection officials on the (a) identification of indicators of gender based violence and (b) harassment at work.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170884","170884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968301","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many external intelligence reports received by the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority from non-governmental organisations were (a) received and (b) acted upon in (i) 2015-16, (ii) 2016-17 and (ii) 2017-18.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170885","170885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968302","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much money has been accrued to the public purse as a result of Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority Tier 1 interventions in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170886","170886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968303","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the Government's response to the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse's report on Child Migrant Programmes, published on 1 March 2018.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170887","170887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968304","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Syrian refugees of each religious group his Department has (a) recommended to be resettled by the UN; and (b) agreed to resettle in the UK in each quarter of each of the last four years.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170888","170888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968305","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to improve mental health (a) care and (b) education in Africa.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170889","170889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968307","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on wages of the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and if he will place a copy of that assessment in the Library.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170674","170674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968308","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant the oral answer to the hon Member for Liverpool, West Derby on 4 September 2018, Official Report, column 5, what steps his Department are taking to enable the safe return of the Rohingya to their home.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170890","170890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968309","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the Government’s strategic shift on UK aid on poverty reduction in Africa.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170891","170891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968310","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of revenue required through (a) income tax or (b) corporation tax to offset the £80 billion of additional borrowing forecast in his letter to the Treasury Committee relating to Brexit analysis, dated 23 August 2018; and if he will place a copy of the findings in the Library.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170675","170675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968311","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect the 2019 Loan Charge on the NHS.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170892","170892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968312","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an estimate of the VAT loss to the public purse of the use of direct engagement models for agency health workers in the NHS.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170893","170893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968313","2018-09-10","Cabinet Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the access to elections working group is appropriately resourced to implement the actions set out in the Government's response to Call for evidence: access to elections, published in August 2018.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170894","170894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968314","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support the Government provides to Venezuelan refugees living in other Latin American countries.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170895","170895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968315","2018-09-10","Cabinet Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government plans to lay the Boundary Commission's recommendations before the House.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170709","170709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968317","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the establishment and command structure by rank of the Ministry of Defence Police is; and at what locations they are deployed.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170656","170656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968318","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many and what proportion of his Department's staff are based in his Department's Sheffield office at St Paul’s place.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170896","170896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968319","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help tackle the persecution of Christians in North Korea.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170717","170717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968320","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for Mental Health and Inequalities of 3 July 2018, Official Report, column 105WH, for what reason his Department did not publish before the summer parliamentary recess a formal response to the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse's report on Child Migrant Programmes, published on 1 March 2018.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170897","170897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968322","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is his policy for an application for settled status to be affected by the applicant being in receipt of a state retirement pension.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170898","170898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968323","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Departments plans for the rules on the five-year continuous residency test for settled status applications to be the same as the rules for permanent residency applications.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170899","170899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968324","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is his Department's policy that the five-year continuous residency requirement for settled status can be satisfied by reference to any such period of time during an applicant’s life in the UK rather than the most recent five years.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170900","170900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968325","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether people who have settled status will continue to be able to access the NHS after the UK leaves the EU on the same basis as EU citizens can today.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170901","170901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968326","2018-09-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he has had discussions with the leaders of the political parties in Northern Ireland on the Government’s plan for Northern Ireland in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170740","170740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968328","2018-09-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what progress he has made with his counterparts in the EU on the prevention of a hard border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland as a result of the UK leaving the EU without remaining in (a) a customs union or (b) the single market.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170741","170741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968329","2018-09-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many civil servants are working on his Department's papers to prepare for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170742","170742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968330","2018-09-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on travel requirements for EU and UK holiday-makers after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170743","170743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968331","2018-09-10","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate he has made of the number of schools in Northern Ireland that are in a financial deficit.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170744","170744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968332","2018-09-10","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she is taking to ensure that foreign investment in Northern Ireland continues.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170745","170745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968334","2018-09-10","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether her Department plans to commemorate in 2021 the centenary of the creation of Northern Ireland.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170746","170746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968335","2018-09-10","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with political leaders in Northern Ireland on implementing the recommendations of the Bengoa report.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170747","170747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968336","2018-09-10","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she plans to hold with the Northern Ireland administration on ensuring the adequacy of fire safety checks of listed buildings as a result of the fire at Bank Buildings in Belfast.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170748","170748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968337","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when his Department plans to publish the draft Agricultural Bill.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170749","170749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968338","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that British citizens receiving a UK pension while living elsewhere in the EU continue to receive that pension after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170750","170750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968339","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to reduce waiting times for payments of universal credit to help ensure that tenants do not fall into rent arrears.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170751","170751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968340","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of employers who have been identified as not providing a workplace pension scheme.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170752","170752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968341","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the planned timescale is for the transitional protection period for universal credit.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170753","170753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968342","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of personal independence payments assessments are home visits.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170754","170754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968344","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many lorry drivers were fined for driving over their allotted time limits in 2017.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170755","170755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968345","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what additional resources he is allocating to HMRC to assist parents in locating lost Child Trust Fund accounts.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170710","170710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968346","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage local authorities to use the powers available to them to seize vehicles used in fly-tipping activities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170711","170711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968347","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many vehicles have been seized because of their being used in fly-tipping activities since that power was introduced; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170712","170712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968348","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce the incidence of porcine reproductive respiratory syndrome; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170713","170713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968349","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of meat fraud whereby expensive meat is replaced with a cheaper product; and how many successful prosecutions there have been for such offences in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170714","170714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968350","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to alter or repeal the ban on farmers feeding human food waste to pigs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170715","170715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968351","2018-09-10","Scotland Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what progress the UK Government has made on an islands' deal; and when the Government plans to publish details on that deal.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170902","170902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968352","2018-09-10","Cabinet Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of returning officers spent in excess of their maximum recoverable amount at the 2017 general election.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170903","170903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968353","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many students entered training as a (a) nurse, (b) midwife and (c) GP in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170904","170904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968354","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department collects data on the number of (a) addiction services and centres and (b) detox beds which have closed since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170905","170905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968356","2018-09-10","Cabinet Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170906","170906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968357","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the funding required from the public purse to remove the backlog of maintenance work in the NHS in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, (c) 2017-18 and (d) the 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170907","170907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968358","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170908","170908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968359","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by NHS staff in each of the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170909","170909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968360","2018-09-10","Cabinet Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to improve the administration of (a) fees and (b) charges of Returning Officers for parliamentary elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170910","170910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968361","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170911","170911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968363","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) NHS trusts and (b) Foundation Trusts have been placed in (i) special measures and (ii) financial special measures in each year since 2012; how many of those Trusts remain in special measures.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170912","170912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968364","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170913","170913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968365","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many practising GPs there were in England per 100,000 population in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170914","170914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968366","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken was from request to response to carry out vetting under the disclosure and barring regulations in each police force in England and Wales in the last period for which figures are available; whether that vetting is undertaken in accordance with national requirements in each such force; and (a) what his policy is on and (b) how he measures the performance of the Disclosure and Barring Service.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170694","170694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968367","2018-09-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170915","170915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968368","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time to see a GP in England was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170916","170916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968369","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170917","170917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968370","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) NHS trusts and (b) NHS foundation trusts that will be in deficit at the end of the 2018-19 financial year; and whether he projects the NHS trust sector as a whole to be in deficit at the end of that year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170918","170918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968371","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170919","170919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968373","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170920","170920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968374","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the merits of banning the sale of energy drinks to children.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170921","170921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968375","2018-09-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether it is the Government's policy to enable local authorities to retain business rates collected.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170922","170922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968376","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170923","170923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968377","2018-09-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170924","170924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968378","2018-09-10","Department for International Trade","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170925","170925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968379","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170926","170926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968380","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170927","170927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968381","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans his Department has to prevent social media companies from enabling illicit drugs to be sold on their platforms.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170928","170928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968382","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170929","170929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968384","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) her Department and (ii) her Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170930","170930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968385","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of damage caused by potholes on the NHS estate in which year for which information is available; and what recent assessment he has made of trends in that level of cost.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170931","170931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968386","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170932","170932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968387","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what emergency support is in place for pregnant women affected by temporary closures of NHS maternity units throughout England.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170933","170933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968388","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) her Department and (ii) her Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170934","170934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968389","2018-09-10","Scotland Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170935","170935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968390","2018-09-10","Wales Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170936","170936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968391","2018-09-10","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many members of the House of Lords hold (a) paid and (b) unpaid roles within (i) his Department and (ii) his Department's agencies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170937","170937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968392","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many contracts the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency has secured with the European Medicines Agency to carry out authorisation processes in each of the past five years.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170938","170938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968394","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the income of the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency came from the European Medicines Agency in each of the past five years.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170939","170939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968395","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many contracts the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency bid for to carry out authorisation processes for the European Medicines Agency in each of the past five years; and how many of those bids were successful.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170940","170940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968396","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made since 2016 on the target of a 10% reduction in suicides by 2020-21.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170941","170941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968397","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of emergency service staff using emergency vehicles for private use that have been affected by the changes to taxable benefits: asset made available without transfer introduced in the Finance Act 2017.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170942","170942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968398","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the level job vacancies in the mental health workforce.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170943","170943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968399","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2018 to Question 124503 on Crime: Social Media, whether he has recently met with representatives of (a) Facebook, (b), Google, (c) YouTube, (d) Twitter, (e) Snapchat and (f) other social media platforms to discuss tackling the prevalence of videos and other social media content that glorifies gang and knife crime.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170665","170665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968401","2018-09-10","Cabinet Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Prime Minister on whether the Rt. hon. Member for Uxbridge and South Ruislip is compliant with the ministerial code by re-commencing secondary employment in addition to his parliamentary duties following his resignation as Foreign Secretary.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170944","170944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968402","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England operated consistently at a patient occupancy level of 98 per cent or higher in each year from 2010 to 2017.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170945","170945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968403","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many nurses were employed at the Princess Alexandra Hospital in Harlow in each year from 2010 to 2017.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170946","170946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968405","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many A&E Departments in NHS hospitals treated more than 300 patients per day in (a) Harlow, (b) Essex (c) the East of England and (d) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170947","170947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968406","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals were classified as being in special measures according to Care Quality Commission guidance in (a) Harlow, (b) Essex, (c) the East of England and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170948","170948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968407","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information he holds on the total number of qualified staff working in mental health services.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170949","170949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968408","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an assessment  of the dynamic effect on tax receipts of the New Enterprise Allowance.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170735","170735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968409","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps his Department has taken to simplify the system of National Insurance payments for self-employed people.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170736","170736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968410","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an assessment of trends in the level of self-employed people participating in a private pension scheme.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170737","170737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968412","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent steps her Department has taken to encourage self-employed individuals to participate in a private pension scheme.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170738","170738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968413","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an assessment of the progress of the delivery of the Pension Dashboard.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170739","170739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968414","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has identified a disproportionate effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on jobs and employment for the (a) UK as a whole, (b) devolved nations and (c) each region of the UK.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170676","170676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968415","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his Department's policy is on Law Centres.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170950","170950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968416","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has identified a disproportionate effect on levels of business investment of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on the (a) UK as a whole, (b) devolved nations and (c) each region of the UK.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170677","170677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968417","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2018 to Question 167999 on Social Mobility Commission: public appointments, how many applications have been received; and whether shortlisting has taken place for the recruitment of new commissioners to the Social Mobility Commission.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170951","170951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968418","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2018 to Question 168002, to what budget the £5 million fund for transport to selective schools for disadvantaged pupils has been reallocated.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170952","170952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968419","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff of his Department have been absent from work on full pay for more than twelve consecutive months.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170681","170681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968420","2018-09-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many staff of his Department have been absent from work on full pay for more than twelve consecutive months.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170682","170682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968421","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff of her Department have been absent from work on full pay for more than twelve consecutive months.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170683","170683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968423","2018-09-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July to Question 162973 on council tax: Dorset, whether representations have been received in response to the consultation; and on what date the Government plans to announce its decision.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170684","170684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968424","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to ensure that the Union flag is flown at British ports after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170720","170720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968425","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on securing international support for Antarctic marine protection.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170721","170721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968426","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether there are plans to add Merchant Navy day to the official list of dates for flag-flying on Government buildings.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170722","170722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968427","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether there are plans to extend the ancestral visa to include people whose great-grandparents were born in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170723","170723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968429","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that small businesses improve the safety standards of bouncy castles.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170724","170724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968431","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions initiated by private third parties were brought to trial in the last five years; and how many of those prosecutions resulted in a conviction.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170725","170725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947577","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage procurement at (a) schools, (b) colleges, (c) universities and (d) other educational establishments to be compliant with high animal welfare standards.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168178","168178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964602","2018-09-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the avenues available to bring the perpetrators of crimes against the Rohingya under international law to justice.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169556","169556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964604","2018-09-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help tackle religious and racial discrimination in Burma.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169558","169558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967117","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","What his policy is on global ocean conservation.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906723","906723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967118","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","What recent discussions he has had with his Colombian counterpart on the peace process in that country.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906724","906724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967119","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","What his policy is on global ocean conservation.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906728","906728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967120","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","What political and diplomatic steps he is taking to help resolve the conflict in Syria.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906731","906731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967121","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","What political and diplomatic steps he is taking to help resolve the conflict in Syria.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906732","906732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967734","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps are taken to ensure that damage is not done to public land as a result of hunts.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170398","170398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967735","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps are taken to ensure that the provisions of the Hunting Act 2004 are not violated on public land.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170399","170399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967736","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what comparative assessment he has made of the equity of legislation relating to (a) dogs and (b) dogs on hunts on public land.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170400","170400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967737","2018-09-06","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to enforce legislation relating to the blocking of public highways by hunt followers during a hunt; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170401","170401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967738","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make illegal the production and sale of fox urine for the purpose of hunting.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170402","170402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967739","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what role the Ministry of Defence Fire Services undertook during firefighting operations near Saddleworth Moor between June 2018 and July 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170379","170379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967740","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2018 to Question 147821, on Chronic Fatigue Syndrome, what plans he has and what recent steps he has taken to expand this funding in the future.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170278","170278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967741","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many times a monitor from Natural England visits a proposed culling site to assess whether the weather conditions are suitable for the badger cull in an area to proceed.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170251","170251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967742","2018-09-06","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect on the viability of private, voluntary and independent childcare providers of current levels of business rates paid by those providers.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170403","170403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967743","2018-09-06","Treasury","2018-09-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward a reduction in the duty on beer.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170404","170404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967744","2018-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received representations on the June 2016 resolution of the US Congress entitled Expressing concern regarding persistent and credible reports of systematic, state-sanctioned organ harvesting from non-consenting prisoners of conscience in the People's Republic of China; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170313","170313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967745","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse was for policing the summer visit of the US President.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170255","170255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967746","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the cost to the public purse was of housing the previous Foreign Secretary at his official ministerial residence.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170256","170256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967747","2018-09-10","Women and Equalities","2018-09-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she has held discussions with the Leader of the House on tackling the inequality in the number of males and females carrying out parliamentary assistant/researcher roles for Members of Parliament; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170257","170257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967748","2018-09-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the effect on the provision of services by East Sussex County Council of the imposition of a statutory minimum budget by that council.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170405","170405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967749","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-resident parents are in maintenance arrears through the Child Maintenance Service; how many of those non-resident parents are in the Glenrothes constituency; and how much money is outstanding in those arrears.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170374","170374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967750","2018-09-06","Cabinet Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an estimate of the number of government computers using the Windows XP operating system.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170448","170448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967751","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Windrush generation cases remain outstanding; and what the timeframe is for those cases to be concluded.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170380","170380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967752","2018-09-10","Department for International Trade","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to his oral contribution of 16 July 2018, Official Report, column 41 on Trade Policy, whether the Government plans to consult (a) the public, (b) business and (c) civil society including women’s rights organisations in the countries with which the UK seeks new trade agreements on those agreements.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170297","170297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967753","2018-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the increase in the small claims limit from £1,000 to £2,000 on the ability of victims of workplace accidents to bring forward a claim.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170449","170449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967754","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the levels of (a) lead and (b) phosphorus are in the water supply for each regional water authority.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170381","170381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967755","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Thames Valley Police made an application for special grant funding for the costs of policing the wedding between Princess Eugenie and Jack Brooksbank.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170370","170370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967756","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2018 to Question 154750 on Home Energy and Lifestyle Management: Kilmarnock and Loudoun, what the disclosure issues are that prevent the publication separately of statistics on loans with payback periods of 5-10 years and 10-15 years.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170376","170376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967757","2018-09-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to table 4a of the Right to Buy Sales in England: January to March 2017-18 document of 28 June 2018, what proportion of the 17,911 new start and acquisitions forming right to buy replacement are new builds.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170377","170377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967758","2018-09-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to table 4a of the Right to Buy Sales in England: January to March 2017-18 of 28 June 2018, whether he is taking steps to increase the number of new build homes in order to reduce the disparity between the 17,911 new starts and acquisitions forming right to buy replacements and the 19,445 additional sales between Q1 2012-13 and Q4 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170378","170378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967759","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many libraries have closed in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170382","170382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967760","2018-09-06","Treasury","2018-09-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a tobacco industry levy to fund smoking cessation services provided by local authorities.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170383","170383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967761","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the recent CQC inspection which established that University Hospital Coventry requires improvement, whether he plans to ensure that staff at that hospital receive an adequate level of mandatory training; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170258","170258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967762","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to support emergency departments in hospitals in Coventry that are experiencing a record number of unnecessary visits in the absence of GP appointments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170259","170259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967763","2018-09-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason public health provision was excluded from Fair Funding Review, published by his Department on 19 December 2017.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170384","170384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967764","2018-09-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what criteria his Department plans to use to calculate public health funding in relation to the roll-out of Business Rates Retention in 2020-21.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170385","170385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967765","2018-09-06","Cabinet Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has undertaken a review of the relationships between Ministers and the Institute of Economic Affairs.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170260","170260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967766","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timeframe is for the processing time for applications to NHS Pensions by NHS employees to revert to 30 calendar days.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170311","170311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967767","2018-09-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has undertaken an assessment of the changes to the planning system which would be required to tackle the rise of so-called trojan phone box applications.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170450","170450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967768","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, by what date the Government plans to respond to the recommendations in the 2018-19 strategy of the Director of Labour Market Enforcement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170267","170267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967769","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, by what date the Government plans to publish the outcome of its consultation on Employment status.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170268","170268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967770","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what date he approved the 2018-19 budget for the Access to Work programme.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170252","170252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967771","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with a disability have been denied an Access to Work grant at the point of contact.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170253","170253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967772","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many and what proportion of slaughterhouses in the UK are not compliant with the European Union regulation EC 1099/2009 Annex I on stunning poultry in electric water baths.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170283","170283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967773","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of electric waterbaths for stunning poultry that use frequencies outside of the parameters set out in Annex 1 of EC 1099/2009.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170284","170284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967774","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require post-cut stunning for animals that are slaughtered without being pre-stunned.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170285","170285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967775","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that the volume supply of non-stun meat meets only the domestic demand of the communities that want to eat it.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170286","170286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967776","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 20 April 2018 to Questions 133445, 133447 and 133449, on Ritual Slaughter, when his Department plans to publish the results of the Food Standards Authority survey of slaughterhouses and the Halal market; and whether survey includes the amount of non-stun meat exported from the UK.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170287","170287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967777","2018-09-10","Scotland Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on effect on the (a) environment and (b) animal welfare of Marine Biopolymer’s application for industrial scale wild kelp harvesting.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170288","170288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967778","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of people that attended A&E for self-harm received a psychosocial assessment in accordance with NICE guidelines in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170281","170281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967779","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect on the level of personal independence payment award of the amendments to the illustrative example in section 1.5.2. Part 2 of the personal independence payment assessment guide for assessment providers made on 16 July 2017.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170314","170314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967780","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the draft Universal Credit (Transitional Provisions) (Managed Migration) Regulations 2018, which criteria her Department used to calculate the proposed flat rate of £80 per month to cover the shortfall to claimants' income moving from Employment Support Allowance to universal credit.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170315","170315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967781","2018-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of claimants of (a) severe disability premium and (b) enhanced disability premium under employment support allowance have had a reduction in social security support as a result of moving from universal credit with the transitional provisions as outlined in the draft Universal Credit (Transitional Provisions) (Managed Migration) Regulations 2018.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170316","170316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967782","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average post-partum hospital stay was in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170271","170271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967783","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect on levels of homelessness of refugees granted discretionary leave to remain with no recourse to public funds.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170312","170312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967784","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any government contracts for the provision of housing to asylum seekers include options for the payment of a bonus to the provider if certain criteria are met.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170432","170432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967785","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any bonus payments have been paid by the Government to any companies currently providing asylum seeker accommodation.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170433","170433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967786","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) police officers, (b) police staff and (c) police community support officers were in post in Northumbria in each year from 2010 until the most recent period for which data is available.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170308","170308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967787","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in police officer numbers on the ability of police to respond to anti-social behaviour.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170309","170309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967788","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of the level of the 2018-2019 policing budget on police numbers in Northumbria for (a) 2019-20 and (b) 2020-21.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170310","170310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967789","2018-09-10","Cabinet Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Minister of the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the UK Joint Ministerial Committee being expanded to a full Council of Ministers with responsibility for regional policy after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170272","170272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967790","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to publish the Waste and Resources Strategy.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170273","170273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967791","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether provisions have been included in the draft asylum accommodation renewal contract for the future (a) amendment and (b) termination of the contract; and what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of enacting such provisions.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170434","170434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967792","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of his Departments policy on asylum accommodation since 2012.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170435","170435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967793","2018-09-11","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions his Department has had with (a) external experts and (b) asylum seekers on the design of the contract for asylum seeker housing from 2019.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170436","170436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967794","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money from the public purse has been spent commissioning IVF services in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170429","170429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967795","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 July 2018  to Question 164292, what the average waiting time was to process a DS1500 form in each (a) constituent part and (b) region of the UK in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170274","170274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967796","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of Official Development Assistance to be allocated by the (a) Foreign and Commonwealth Office, (b) Department for Business, Enterprise and Industrial Strategy, (c) Home Office, (d) Department of Health, (e) Ministry of Defence, (f) Prosperity Fund and (g) Conflict Stability and Security Fund in (i) 2018-19 and (ii) 2019-20.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170406","170406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967797","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the role of prosumers in the transition to a low carbon economy.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170375","170375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967798","2018-09-06","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what average spending per pupil was in (a) Middlesbrough and (b) Redcar and Cleveland in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Mr Simon Clarke","Mr Simon Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170438","170438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967799","2018-09-06","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of schools in (a) Middlesbrough and (b) Redcar and Cleveland are classified as Good or Outstanding by Ofsted.","Biography information for Mr Simon Clarke","Mr Simon Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170439","170439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967800","2018-09-06","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children in (a) Middlesbrough and (b) Redcar and Cleveland achieved the English Baccalaureate attainment measure in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Mr Simon Clarke","Mr Simon Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170440","170440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967801","2018-09-06","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) all pupils and (b) pupils from disadvantaged backgrounds in (i) Middlesbrough and (ii) Redcar and Cleveland entered university in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Mr Simon Clarke","Mr Simon Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170441","170441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967802","2018-09-06","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many young people in the Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland constituency started an apprenticeship in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Mr Simon Clarke","Mr Simon Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170442","170442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967803","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to respond to the email of 3 July 2018 from the hon. Member for Slough to her Department's Southern England Group Operations Correspondence Team, reference TD3826.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170430","170430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967804","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has held discussions with the Government of India on (a) the recent killing of five nomadic people in Maharashtra state which was filmed and shared on social media and (b) other so-called WhatsApp Lynchings.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170340","170340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967805","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on patient access to short-shelf life medicines.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170342","170342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967806","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the total value of rebates to be paid under the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme 2014.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170343","170343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967807","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on how money raised from rebates paid under the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme 2014 has been used; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170344","170344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967808","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons rebates paid by manufacturers under the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme 2014 are not ring-fenced for the use of medicines; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170345","170345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967809","2018-09-06","Department for Transport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to support the growth and development of the bikeshare sector.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170346","170346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967810","2018-09-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the level of staff turnover in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170261","170261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967811","2018-09-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff in his Department are classed as contingent labour.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170262","170262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967812","2018-09-06","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on which GCSE subjects that were available in the 2017-18 school year will no longer be available by 2020-21.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170443","170443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967813","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding was awarded to businesses in Nottinghamshire under the Government-backed start-up loans scheme; and how much of that money has been repaid to date.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170444","170444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967814","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the policy of the Icelandic government to permit the continued whaling of endangered Fin whales on the long-term survival of that species; if he will raise that policy and its effect on marine biodiversity with his Icelandic counterpart; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170298","170298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967815","2018-09-06","Treasury","2018-09-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives of Lloyds Bank on its closures of local bank branches.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170445","170445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967816","2018-09-06","Department for Transport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his answer of 22 November 2017 to Question 112924 on Bicycles: Hire Services, what progress he has made on developing a consistent national standard for bike-share schemes.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170347","170347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967817","2018-09-06","Department for Transport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the quality of service provided by bikeshare operators.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170348","170348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967818","2018-09-06","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many valid British national (overseas) passports were in issue on 31 December in each year since 1987.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170349","170349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967819","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to maintain the responsibilities and functions of the European Food Safety Authority when the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170350","170350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967820","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, published in July 2018, whether he has plans to replicate the provisions of Regulation (EC) No 178/2002 in the common rulebook.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170351","170351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967821","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on the UK beef sector of the European Commission’s proposal to allocate a larger share of its hormone-free beef quota to the US.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170248","170248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967822","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposed review of the EU hormone-free beef quota on the allocation of EU and UK tariff rate quotas.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170249","170249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967823","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the potential redistribution of the EU hormone-free beef quota on UK beef exports to the EU in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170250","170250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967824","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the REACH regulations will form part of the common rulebook proposed in the paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm 9593.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170352","170352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967825","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the proportion of late payments to SMEs.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170292","170292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967826","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the number of self-employed individuals.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170293","170293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967827","2018-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an assessment of recent trends in the number of individuals in receipt of the New Enterprise Allowance.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170294","170294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967828","2018-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse has been of the New Enterprise Allowance in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170295","170295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967829","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of students in each ethnic group studied Art and Design at GCSE Level in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170279","170279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967830","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) ethnicity of pupils who studied Art and Design at A-Level in 2017-18.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170280","170280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967831","2018-09-06","Department for Transport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans in place to repeal the provisions of EU regulation 2017/352 on port services once the UK leaves the European Union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170302","170302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967832","2018-09-06","Department for Transport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals for the mandatory 30-day retention of CCTV footage from train and bus services.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170422","170422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967833","2018-09-06","Department for Transport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department holds information on marine incidents involving alcohol and recreational boaters; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170303","170303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967834","2018-09-06","Department for Transport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many coach companies have had their operating licences revoked in the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170423","170423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967835","2018-09-06","Treasury","2018-09-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to compensate people who have sustained losses due to the mis-selling of Integrity Cash Maximiser products.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170388","170388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967836","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the rate of (a) age-standardised premature mortality from breast cancer and (b) uptake of screening for that cancer was in each clinical commissioning group area in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170447","170447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967837","2018-09-06","Treasury","2018-09-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support is available for people who sustained losses as a result of misleading selling of Integrity Cash Maximiser products.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170389","170389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967838","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring onshore windfarm developers to offer property owners within a set proximity to a windfarm the option of having their property purchased at market value by those developers.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170390","170390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967839","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for a new contractor to be appointed to complete the new Royal Liverpool University Hospital following the liquidation of Carillion.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170270","170270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967840","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the latest advice is that he has received from Public Health England on the risks of ingesting asbestos from drinking water which has been pumped through asbestos pipes.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170282","170282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967841","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the leadership at Wirral Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170269","170269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967842","2018-09-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many rough sleepers there were in each region of the UK in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170275","170275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967843","2018-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has classified Mr Hasan Mushaima as a prisoner of conscience.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170299","170299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967844","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of rough sleepers suffer with mental ill health.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170276","170276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967845","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to compensate people for their loss of property value arising from close proximity to wind farms.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170391","170391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967846","2018-09-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of rough sleepers who have spent time in foster care.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170277","170277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967847","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of whether the £40 million fund for Chagossians has addressed the needs of those citizens residing in the UK.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170339","170339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967848","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for International Trade on LGBT rights in (a) Botswana, (b) Namibia and (c) Swaziland.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170424","170424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967849","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterparts in (a) Swaziland, (b) Namibia and (c) Botswana on LGBT+ rights in those countries.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170425","170425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967850","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Myanmar government regarding the imprisonment of Reuters journalists Wa Lone and Kyaw Soe Oo.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170426","170426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967851","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the USA withdrawing funding to the United Nations Relief and Works Agency on the humanitarian situation in Gaza.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170427","170427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967852","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Chinese Government on reports of political re-education camps housing up to one million Uighur Muslims in that country.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170428","170428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967853","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the (a) potential value of bilateral research between the UK and India in 2022 and (b) value of that research in 2010.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170446","170446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967854","2018-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants there are in the Ayr, Carrick and Cumnock constituency.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170392","170392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967855","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Minister of State for Immigration plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Glasgow East of 2 August 2018, reference DL1598.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170431","170431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967856","2018-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what timetable he has in place for spending the £190 million allocated to the roll-out of full-fibre broadband.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170393","170393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967857","2018-09-06","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that Somali passport holders with the right to live in the UK are not refused entry as a result of the change from passport endorsement to a bio-metric residence permit system.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170296","170296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967858","2018-09-06","Scotland Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what progress has been made on the Ayrshire Growth Deal.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170394","170394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967859","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the recent dry weather on farmers and food producers.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170415","170415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967860","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans to make changes to the Rural Payments Agency as a result of the recent summer dry weather to ensure that support payments are paid in a timely manner.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170416","170416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967861","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the European Commission on introducing flexibility on greening and agri-environment schemes as a result of the 2018 summer’s dry weather.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170417","170417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967862","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what submissions he has received from (a) industry organisations and (b) farmers requesting flexibility in the application of (a) CAP and (b) agri-environment schemes because of the 2018 summer’s dry weather.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170418","170418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967863","2018-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he next plans to hold meetings with representatives of (a) the Scottish Government, (b) East Ayrshire Council and (c) South Ayrshire Council on promoting tourism in Ayrshire.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170395","170395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967864","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of levels of funding for autistic spectrum children in education.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170420","170420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967865","2018-09-06","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of education funding for sixth form students.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170289","170289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967866","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of funding for the support of autistic spectrum children in education.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170421","170421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967867","2018-09-06","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions his Department has had with HM Treasury on the adequacy of funding for the education of sixth form students.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170290","170290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967868","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Iranian counterpart on the death sentence imposed on Ramin Hossein Panahi.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170419","170419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967869","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department received when determining the length of time medicines will need to be stockpiled in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; if he will publish that guidance.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170317","170317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967870","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the NHS stockpiling medicines for six weeks in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and whether that cost will be borne from existing Department of Health budgets.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170318","170318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967871","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the recent dry weather on farmers and food producers.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170407","170407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967872","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the merits of the approach taken by the devolved administrations in supporting farmers and food producers during this summer’s dry weather.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170408","170408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967873","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking with the Rural Payments Agency to ensure that support payments to farmers are paid in a timely manner.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170409","170409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967874","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made representations to the European Commission on flexibility for greening and agri-enviroment schemes because of dry weather this summer.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170410","170410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967875","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations has he received from industry organisations and farmers requesting flexibility in the application of (a) CAP schemes and (b) agri-environment schemes because of dry weather conditions.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170411","170411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967876","2018-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for the price and supply of fodder in the UK of the Irish Government’s fodder transport scheme.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170412","170412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967877","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Saudi counterpart on the sentencing of human rights activist Israa al-Ghomgham.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170254","170254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967878","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to the NHS of drug addiction; and if his Department will publish an estimate of those annual costs in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170319","170319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967879","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to support the ageing profile of heroin users; and whether his Department has a written strategy to support ageing heroin users.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170320","170320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967880","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to publish a written strategy on tackling new psychoactive substances.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170321","170321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967881","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to promote dual diagnosis for patients with both addiction and mental health problems.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170322","170322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967882","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure equality of access to (a) alcohol and (b) drug treatments.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170323","170323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967883","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to tackle dependence on (a) illicit drugs and (b) alcohol among people from deprived backgrounds; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170324","170324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967884","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of young people dependent on (a) illicit drugs and (b) alcohol.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170325","170325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967885","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the incidence of foetal alcohol spectrum disorders.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170326","170326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967886","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what share of the UK's Official Development Assistance budget is planned to be delivered (a) through and (b) outside of the Department for International Development in (i) 2018-19 and (ii) 2019-20.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170413","170413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967887","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to increase the scope of local suicide prevention plans to include steps to tackle the links between alcohol misuse, deliberate self-harm and deaths by suicide.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170327","170327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967888","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of deaths arising from alcohol and drug dependency.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170328","170328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967889","2018-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress he is making in the development of the new women centres announced on 27 June 2018; and if he will ensure that such provision will be made available in Wales.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170386","170386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967890","2018-09-06","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with Devon and Cornwall Police on tackling the availability and use of synthetic cannabinoid substances.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170368","170368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967891","2018-09-06","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department plans to reclassify synthetic cannabinoid substances as class A drugs.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170369","170369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967892","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been in contact with drug and alcohol services since 2009-10; what assessment he has made of the reasons for changes in the number of people making contact during that time period; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people are able to make contact with drug and alcohol services.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170329","170329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967893","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have discontinued drug and alcohol treatment within (a) three months and (b) six months of starting such treatment in each of the last seven financial years; and what plans his Department has to reduce such discontinuation rates.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170330","170330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967894","2018-09-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the (a) planned and (b) current expenditure for drug and alcohol treatment services.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170331","170331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967895","2018-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Iranian counterpart on the sentencing of Ramin Hossein Panahi.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170414","170414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967896","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many clinical commissioning groups have an addiction workforce strategy; and what plans his Department has to increase the number of local commissioners with an addiction workforce strategy.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170332","170332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967897","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many addiction psychiatrists are employed in drug and alcohol addiction treatment services; how many psychiatrists have been employed in those services in each year since 2009-10; what plans his Department has to increase the number of addiction psychiatrists employed in those services; and what plans his Department has to increase the number of training posts in addiction psychiatry.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170333","170333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967898","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) share and (b) enforce best practice across the NHS.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170245","170245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967899","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the NHS England EU Transition Team has taken to prepare for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170353","170353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967900","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the annual budget is of the NHS England EU Transition Team; and what the remit of that team is.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170354","170354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967901","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hospital and community NHS trusts are rated as outstanding by the Care Quality Commission.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170246","170246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967902","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent representations he has received from NHS England on changing the four-hour accident and emergency waiting target.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170355","170355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967903","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent representations he has received from NHS trusts on workforce morale.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170356","170356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967904","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money NHS Trusts and Foundation Trusts received in car parking charges levied against blue badge holders in 2017-18.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170357","170357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967905","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment has he made of the effect of increasing the qualifying period for unfair dismissal claims to two years on job security.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170358","170358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967906","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what equality impact assessment the Government has made since the qualifying period for unfair dismissal claims was increased to two years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170359","170359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967907","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to Good work: the Taylor review of modern working practices, published in July 2017, what steps he has taken to increase the availability of good work as outlined in that review.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170360","170360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967908","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of staff on each agenda for change band who will have a net pay decrease this year.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170361","170361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967909","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to Good work: the Taylor review of modern working practices, published in July 2017, if he will make an estimate of the number of jobs which are classified as good work as outlined in that review.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170362","170362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967910","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 13 the Government's response to the Taylor review of modern working practices, published in February 2018, when the Government plans to publish the annual report on good work.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170363","170363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967911","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the variation in the quality of NHS services.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170247","170247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967912","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 15 of the Government response to the Taylor review of modern working practices, published in February 2018, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to improve transparency for agency workers.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170364","170364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967913","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent representations he has received on ending the Swedish derogation.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170365","170365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967914","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Director of Labour Market Enforcement on extending the scope and remit of the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170366","170366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967915","2018-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Low Pay Commission on introducing a higher rate of minimum wage for hours not guaranteed as part of a contract.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170367","170367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967916","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of the Foxhound in extreme heat.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170291","170291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967917","2018-09-06","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers in England and Wales have been (a) investigated for, (b) charged with and (c) convicted of careless or dangerous driving while pursuing suspects by vehicle in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170387","170387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967918","2018-09-06","Department for Transport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of Network Rail’s train planning resources for implementing the December 2018 timetable changes.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170334","170334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967919","2018-09-06","Department for Transport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to the valuation of the railway pension scheme on the viability of (a) train operating company finances and (b) the wider rail franchising model.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170335","170335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967920","2018-09-06","Department for Transport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the press release entitled Number of substandard bridges rises, published by the RAC Foundation on 19 January 2018, if he will make an assessment of the implication for his policies of the statement in that release that 3,441 road bridges with spans of more than 1.5 metres are substandard.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170336","170336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967921","2018-09-06","Department for Transport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has he made of the structural integrity of post-tensioned concrete bridges built before 1992; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170337","170337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967922","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total receipts collected from the apprenticeship levy were in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170266","170266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967923","2018-09-06","Department for Transport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to undertake a review of the regulations on the use of electric scooters on roads.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170338","170338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967924","2018-09-06","Department for Transport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will seek a change through the International Maritime Organisation to ban ships from using heavy fuel oil when travelling in the Arctic and Antarctic regions.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170300","170300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967925","2018-09-06","Cabinet Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment his Department has made of UK progress towards the sustainable development goals.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170301","170301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967926","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what performance standards he has set for (a) academies and (b) local authorities to conclude the transfer of a pupil to a new school as a result of a change of address; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170263","170263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967927","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what penalties are incurred by a school for a delay in returning forms required for a pupils to transfer to another school as a result of a house move.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170264","170264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967928","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trains (a) to and (b) from Warrington have been cancelled as a result of the recent disruption on the trans-Pennine line.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170265","170265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967929","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the number of mental health beds per 100,000 people in England; and what information his Department holds on the number of mental health beds per 100,000 people in each country in the EU.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170304","170304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967930","2018-09-10","Cabinet Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people with autism have died by suicide since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170305","170305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967931","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many Approved Mental Health Professionals have been employed in the public sector in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170306","170306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967932","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of people referred to consultant-led mental health treatment were seen within 18 weeks.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170307","170307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967933","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what budget is allocated to the Office of the Independent Anti-Slavery Commissioner; and how much of that budget has been spent in the current financial year.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170396","170396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967934","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the deadline is for applications for the position of Independent Anti-Slavery Commissioner; and whether that deadline has been changed since the position became vacant.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170397","170397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967935","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Social Mobility Commissioners have been appointed; and how many positions on that Commission remain vacant.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170341","170341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967936","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government receives legal advice on the legality of the sale of arms to Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170437","170437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967937","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions her Department has had with (a) Glasgow Housing Association, (b) Southside Housing Association, (c) Elderpark Housing Association, (d) Glenoaks Housing Association, (e) Govan Housing Association, (f) Linthouse Housing Association, (g) Rosehill Housing Association, (h) Sanctuary Scotland Housing Association, (i) Home Group Scotland and (j) Blackwood Housing on (i) service rollout of universal credit and (ii) access to the Landlord Portal; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170371","170371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967938","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions her Department has had with (a) Ofcom and (b) the Phone-paid Services Authority on call connection service access to the helplines her Department provides; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170372","170372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967939","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to publish its legislative proposals in response to the Taylor Review into Working Practices; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170373","170373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968130","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time is for veterans to receive (a) prothetics and (b) mobility aids for injuries caused as a result of their service in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170786","170786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968134","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has issued to schools on the pricing of school uniforms.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170789","170789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968153","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the discussion paper, Criminal Liability: Insanity and Automatism, published by the Law Commission in July 2013,  whether the Government has plans to reform the legislation on the defence of insanity.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170806","170806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963983","2018-09-05","Home Office","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that refugees are not excluded from the private rented sector as a result of the introduction of the right to rent scheme.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169467","169467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963984","2018-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of the reduction in magistrates' training costs from £110 per magistrate in 2008-09 to £36 in 2015 on (a) the consistent application of law in magistrates court trials, (b) defendants, (c) victims and (d) the justice system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169336","169336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963985","2018-09-05","Home Office","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what Key Performance Indicators his Department has put in place for the performance of commercial visa application centres in African countries.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169468","169468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963986","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to make it easier for people to receive a GP appointment.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169775","169775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963987","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to increase the number of GP's in more populated areas.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169776","169776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963988","2018-09-05","Department for Transport","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department collects information from alternative dispute resolutions in respect of complaints about compensation and assistance to passengers in the event of cancellation of flights.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169777","169777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963989","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the time taken for HMRC to notify people affected by the high-income child benefit charge of the money to be repaid.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169778","169778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963990","2018-09-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to end discrimination against housing benefit claimants by private sector landlords.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169779","169779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963991","2018-09-05","Home Office","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many leave to remain applications were rejected from applicants married to habitually resident British subjects in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169780","169780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963992","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 28 of the Government's 2017 Drug Strategy, published in July 2017, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) potential benefits and disbenefits of the proposals to use locally retained business rates for the funding of alcohol treatment services and (b) effect of those proposals on the provision of such services in deprived areas.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169387","169387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963993","2018-09-05","Department for Education","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what measures have been put in place for schools to deal with racist incidents.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169781","169781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963994","2018-09-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to protect people who have fled domestic violence and are homeless.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169782","169782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963995","2018-09-05","Department for Education","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to ensure that schools are adequately funded to deliver the Nisai learning programme.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169783","169783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963996","2018-09-05","Department for Education","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support existing programmes aimed at helping to ensure that the views of disadvantaged children in (a) London and (b) other parts of England are taken into consideration by decision-making organisations.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169167","169167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963997","2018-09-05","Department for Education","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department is taking steps to educate young people about the potential dangers of social media outside of formal education.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169652","169652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963998","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to  provide financial support for research to small and medium-sized enterprises developing new tools for the (a) prevention, (b) diagnosis and (c) treatment of drug-resistant TB.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169479","169479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963999","2018-09-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the framework for state pensions in respect of work carried out by non-UK EU citizens in the UK will remain in place after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169469","169469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964000","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the regulations that allow the transfer of a private pension scheme to a Qualifying Recognised Overseas Pension Scheme within the European Economic Area will be exempt from tax after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169470","169470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964001","2018-09-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has developed proposals for the free movement of capital with in relation to pensions for (a) UK citizens that  have accrued pensions in the European Union and (b) for non-UK EU citizens that have accrued pensions in the UK after the UK has left the EU; and will she make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169471","169471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964002","2018-09-06","Home Office","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied child refugees have been re-settled in Scotland in each of the last three years; and how many of those children were resettled with family already living in Scotland.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169822","169822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964003","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if the Government will adopt Macmillan Cancer Support's five recommendations as recently published on its website page entitled Support our vision for the future of the NHS.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169710","169710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964004","2018-09-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of establishing a publicly-owned not-for-profit energy company similar to that proposed by the Scottish Government.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169562","169562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964006","2018-09-05","Department for Education","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on the eligibility of survivors of modern slavery for publicly-funded education; what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on the application of the Immigration Rules to institutions which provide education for survivors of modern slavery; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169676","169676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964007","2018-09-05","Department for Education","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which ministerial visits he and Ministers of his Department have undertaken by region since his appointment.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169677","169677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964008","2018-09-05","Home Office","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of UKVI's communications with asylum claim applicants on the progress of their applications; and if he will take steps to ensure that those applicants receive adequate communications on the progress of their applications.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169183","169183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964009","2018-09-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the effect of clinical commissioning groups' commissioning of FreeStyle Libre glucose monitoring technology on patients' access to that technology throughout England.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169910","169910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964010","2018-09-06","Department for Transport","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve rail services (a) on the Southport to Manchester line and (b) to and from the West Lancashire constituency; and if he will make an assessment of the effect of recent national timetable changes on commuter services in those areas.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169912","169912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964011","2018-09-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will list all the changes made to universal credit since it was introduced.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169742","169742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964012","2018-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 130945 on civil proceedings, who holds the information referred to in that question.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169609","169609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964013","2018-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many civil restraining orders were (a) requested and (b) granted in Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169610","169610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964014","2018-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many civil restraining orders were (a) requested and (b) granted in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169611","169611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964015","2018-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 July 2018 to Question 166117 on defence: modernisation, whether all additional finance in the Modernising Defence Programme will be generated by greater efficiency through business modernisation.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169194","169194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964016","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department plans to complete the peer review of the systematic overview of reviews on the effective, safe and appropriate use of anticoagulation medicines undertaken by the Evidence for Policy and Practice Information and Co-ordinating Centre; and when that final report will be published.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169005","169005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964017","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which stakeholders were involved in (a) developing the protocol for and (b) conducting the systematic overview of reviews on the effective, safe and appropriate use of anticoagulation medicines undertaken by the Evidence for Policy and Practice Information and Co-ordinating Centre.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169006","169006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964018","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to hold a consultation on the findings of the systematic overview of reviews on the effective, safe and appropriate use of anticoagulation medicines undertaken by the Evidence for Policy and Practice Information and Co-ordinating Centre.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169007","169007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964019","2018-09-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the levelised cost of energy of new onshore wind projects.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169519","169519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964020","2018-09-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what comparative estimate his Department has made of (a) international auction prices and (b) UK auction clearing prices for onshore wind in each of the last two years; and what steps his Department is taking to support internationally competitive pricing in the UK auction clearing market.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169520","169520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964021","2018-09-05","Cabinet Office","2018-09-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the change in the number of people working in the public sector has been since 2010.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168949","168949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964022","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take to protect UK retailers from an increase in goods brought into the UK without the appropriate taxes being paid.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168950","168950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964023","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to prepare the UK for a potential situation whereby the UK loses access to the EU VAT information sharing system.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168951","168951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964024","2018-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2018 to Question 165463 on Pakistan: Conflict, Stability and Security Fund, what the independent third party is referred to in that answer.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168995","168995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964025","2018-09-05","Department for International Development","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support legislation in developing countries to help disabled people.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169300","169300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964026","2018-09-05","Department for International Development","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the promotion of democracy in developing countries.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169301","169301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964027","2018-09-05","Department for International Trade","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to further UK exports in the space sector.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169302","169302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964029","2018-09-06","Home Office","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to improve the English Language lessons service for refugees; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169080","169080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964030","2018-09-05","Department for International Development","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to assist countries with long coastlines such as Indonesia to tackle plastic pollution.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169304","169304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964031","2018-09-05","Department for Education","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason the Government has removed its target of increasing the number of early years teachers; and what assessment his Department has made of the effect of removing that target on the educational achievements of disadvantaged children.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168978","168978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964032","2018-09-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that any agreement reached on EU citizens' rights in the UK after the UK leaves the EU will be reciprocated for UK citizens in European countries.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169305","169305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964033","2018-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on the production of the Type (a) 26 and (b) 31e Frigates; and what plans he to export those frigates.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169306","169306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964034","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the proposed average payments to community pharmacies were in Sheffield Hallam constituency under the Pharmacy Access Scheme in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169826","169826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964035","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average payments to community pharmacies were in Sheffield Hallam in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169827","169827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964036","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to prevent the closure of community pharmacies.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169828","169828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964037","2018-09-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claimants undergoing a Work Capability Assessment for employment and support allowance have (a) failed their assessment and (b) failed their assessment and subsequently moved on to universal credit in each of the most recent 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169033","169033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964038","2018-09-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants attempting to make a claim for universal credit have not completed the process due to a failure to agree terms on a Claimant Commitment.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169034","169034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964039","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,what steps his Department is taking to increase funding for new mothers' postnatal checks.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169245","169245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964040","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has met with the representations of the National Childbirth Trust to discuss the findings of its  report, Hidden Half: bringing postnatal mental illness out of hiding, published in June 2017 and recommendations for tackling low rates of identification of perinatal mental illness.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169246","169246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964041","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the evidence of a link between perinatal mental illness and emotional and behavioural problems in children, what steps he is taking to ensure the adequate identification through primary care of (a) that illness and (b) those problems.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169247","169247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964042","2018-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish a list of those implementing organisations referred to as various on page one of the Conflict Security and Stability Fund (CSSF) Programme Summary document for the CSSF Great Lakes Programme for the programmes entitled (a) Human rights in DRC elections and (b) Monitoring and responding to conflict risks in Burundi.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168996","168996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964043","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the FinTech bridge agreement between the UK and Australia.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169237","169237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964044","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the FinTech bridge agreement between the UK and Hong Kong.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169238","169238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964045","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the FinTech bridge agreement between the UK and Singapore.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169239","169239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964046","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the FinTech bridge agreement between the UK and South Korea.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169240","169240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964047","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the FinTech bridge agreement between the UK and China.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169241","169241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964048","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has had discussions with the US Administration on establishing a FinTech bridge agreement between the UK and the USA.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169242","169242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964049","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has had discussions with his international counterparts on establishing new Fin Tech bridge agreements between their countries and the UK.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169243","169243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964050","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has had discussions with the Bank of England on the establishment of a state-backed digital currency.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169244","169244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964051","2018-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 15 of his Department’s Annual Report and Accounts 2017-18, how many (a) military and (b) civilian personnel in his Department perform an administrative role.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169195","169195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964052","2018-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 16 of his Department’s Annual Report and Accounts 2017-18, what the timetable is for the completion of Project Centurion.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169196","169196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964053","2018-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 16 of his Department’s Annual Report and Accounts 2017-18, what infrastructure work is being carried out at RAF Marham to support the arrival of the F-35s; what the timetable is for the completion of that work; and what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of that work.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169197","169197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964054","2018-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 22 of his Department’s Annual Report and Accounts 2017-18, what the (a) 30 operations and (b) 25 countries are in which UK armed forces personnel are deployed.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169198","169198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964055","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of take-up rates by levels of household income of recipients of the health check for children aged two years undertaken by health visitors.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169035","169035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964056","2018-09-06","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many NCC1, Support for a child conceived without your consent forms have been received by HMRC.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169454","169454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964057","2018-09-06","Cabinet Office","2018-09-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if his Department will provide a list of the third-party organisations that have received funding from the Prosperity Fund in the the last 12 months to design or implement projects overseas.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168997","168997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964058","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential causal link between respiratory diseases and deprivation and its effect on levels of (a) chronic obstructive pulmonary disease, (b) cancer, (c) tuberculosis, (d) pneumonia, (e) pulmonary fibrosis and (f) asthma; and what steps he is taking to reduce any such inequalities relating to respiratory diseases.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169538","169538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964059","2018-09-06","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 24 July 2018 to Question 165184 on Brexit, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of the Government's policies on the future relationship between the UK and the EU on (a) jobs in and (b) value of the broadcasting sector in the UK.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169859","169859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964060","2018-09-05","Department for Transport","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department agreed to the separation of the fleet maintenance and engineering functions relating to the West Coast Trains Limited franchise; whether his Department undertook at competitive tender relating to that separation of functions; and whether funds accrued to the public purse as a result of that separation of functions. .","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169784","169784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964061","2018-09-05","Department for Transport","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the separation of the fleet maintenance and engineering functions relating to the West Coast Trains Limited franchise, whether (a) assets were fully scrutinised and valued in relation to that separation of functions and (b) the pension funds of employees affected by that separation of functions received protections under the terms of the Railways Act 1993.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169785","169785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964062","2018-09-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timetable is for publishing the social housing green paper; and for what reasons that green paper was not published prior to the House rising for summer recess.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169518","169518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964063","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the estimated £70 billion in unpaid compensation for the mis-selling of payment protection insurance, if he will review the deadline for making a compensation claim.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169786","169786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964064","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-09-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the potential increase in demand on the court system as a result of the deadline for making PPI claims via the Financial Ombudsman; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169787","169787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964065","2018-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 24 July 2018 to Question 166155, to which budget headlines will the £825,000 of income for reinvestment in the Sunderland Magistrates’ court be allocated.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169321","169321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964066","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support biomedical research on myalgic encephalomyelitis.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169455","169455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964067","2018-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the HM Courts and Tribunals Service employ security personnel to assist with the processing of tribunal cases.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169517","169517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964068","2018-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department plans to spend on upgrading Sunderland Magistrates Court.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169322","169322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964069","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many training places for midwifery were (a) commissioned and (b) filled in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169176","169176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964070","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the total number of midwives in training was in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169177","169177"
