"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516182","2016-05-03","HM Treasury","2016-04-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of fruit juice a drink must contain to be considered a pure fruit juice for the purposes of the sugar levy.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35890","35890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516183","2016-05-03","HM Treasury","2016-04-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on the potential merits of exempting drivers between the ages of 17 and 25 who have telematics car insurance policies from insurance premium tax.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35932","35932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516184","2016-05-03","HM Treasury","2016-04-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on the potential merits of exempting telematics car insurance policies from insurance premium tax.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35930","35930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516185","2016-05-03","HM Treasury","2016-04-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on the potential merits of reducing the insurance premium tax paid by drivers between the ages of 17 and 25 who have telematics car insurance policies.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35931","35931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516186","2016-05-04","HM Treasury","2016-04-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 21 April 2016 to Question 34477, whether it is possible to correct errors in PAYE real-time data submitted by employers before the point at which such errors affect universal credit claimants.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35952","35952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516187","2016-05-04","HM Treasury","2016-04-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether sixth form colleges will be affected by VAT regulations if they convert to a 16 to 19 academy.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35964","35964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516188","2016-05-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people were homeless but did not qualify for priority access to social housing in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35955","35955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516189","2016-05-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the number of tenants in private housing who have only sufficient funds to cover one week's rent.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35914","35914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516190","2016-05-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will issue guidance to the private rented sector on the issuing of rental contracts that prohibit tenants from switching electricity suppliers.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35852","35852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516191","2016-05-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department is taking steps to ensure the sustainability of tenant management organisations.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35831","35831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516192","2016-05-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if it is her policy for the oil and gas industry to include employment costs in interpreting paragraph 29 of her Department's paper, Maximising Economic Recovery Strategy for the UK.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35853","35853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516193","2016-05-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects his Department to submit a final estimation of the damage caused by flooding in the South Lakes area to the European Commission as part of the UK's application to the EU Solidarity Fund.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35775","35775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516194","2016-05-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to encourage (a) the Royal Academy, the National Portrait Gallery and the Tate and (b) other national art galleries to loan works from their collections to art galleries in (i) Harrow and (ii) other parts of outer London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35779","35779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516195","2016-05-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to paragraph 1.330 of Budget 2016, how much of the £14.5 million in grants for extending the coverage of ultrafast broadband in the South West will be spent on tackling broadband blackspots in Cheltenham.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35939","35939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516196","2016-05-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the fairness of the (a) licence fee and (b) initial overcharge for those paying the licence fee by direct debit.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35887","35887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516197","2016-05-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has carried out an impact assessment of airstrikes in Yemen since 2012.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35920","35920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516198","2016-05-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any MOD personnel have been seconded to positions in Yemen since 2012.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35921","35921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516199","2016-05-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the findings of the Armed Forces continuous attitude survey 2015 on dissatisfaction of personnel with service life, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies on (a) reforming service pay and (b) service conditions of those findings.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35830","35830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516200","2016-05-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 14 December 2015 to Question 18992, on military bases: religious buildings, what recent steps his Department has taken to fully implement Parliament's sanction of same-sex marriages.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35843","35843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516201","2016-05-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's timetable is for the renewal of Trident.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35764","35764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516202","2016-05-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implication for his policies on a future nuclear deterrent of the development of the Boeing Echo Voyager and other new drone technology.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35821","35821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516203","2016-05-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release, A new pay model for the Armed Forces, published on 7 January 2016, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the reformed pay structure on the number of complaints about terms and conditions received through the service complaints process.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35825","35825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516204","2016-05-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what criteria his Department uses to determine links between cancer experienced by a current or former member of the armed forces and exposure to chemicals during periods of service.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35820","35820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516205","2016-05-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it is technically possible for Trident missiles to be used by the UK without US knowledge and agreement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35768","35768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516206","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish the interim findings of the Area Based Review of further education which includes Central Sussex College; what the geographical extent of that review is; and which other further education institutions are included in that review.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35772","35772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516207","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has undertaken an assessment of the potential effect of changes to employer national insurance and pension contributions on (a) primary and (b) secondary school budgets.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35774","35774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516208","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the provision of free school transport for children who receive the higher rate of the mobility component of disability living allowance.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35814","35814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516209","2016-05-03","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answers of 2 and 8 February 2016 to Questions 25202 and 23871, and the update provided by Ofqual, what further progress has been made on A levels in (a) French, (b) German, (c) Spanish, (d) Religious Studies and (e) Geography being approved ready for first teaching from September 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35752","35752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516210","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will instruct exam boards to offer GCSE and A-Level examinations in Persian after 2018; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35778","35778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516211","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will instruct Ofsted, when drawing up a report on a school, to consult parents who live locally but do not send their children to that school.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35796","35796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516212","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average time taken is for an academy school to be re-brokered to another academy sponsor.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35797","35797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516213","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy schools have been re-brokered to other academy sponsors in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35798","35798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516214","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy schools are (a) in the process of being re-brokered and (b) awaiting re-brokering.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35799","35799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516215","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy schools are not members of a multi-academy trust.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35800","35800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516216","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of times the Key Stage 1 spelling, punctuation and grammar test, which was due to be sat in May 2016 but was subsequently cancelled, was downloaded from the Standard and Testing Agency's website.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35801","35801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516217","2016-05-03","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department is providing to schools engaging in consultation processes on the Government's policy that all schools should become academies to allow maximum stakeholder participation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35844","35844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516218","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of consultation processes on the conversion of all schools to academies in the next 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35849","35849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516219","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the cost of Civil Service support for the Tile Hill Wood and Woodlands Academy consultation to date; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35850","35850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516220","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received from schools in Coventry on the Government's policy that all schools should become academies; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35851","35851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516221","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the Government's plan to make every school an academy on nursery school education.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35841","35841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516222","2016-05-03","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) introducing a Standardised Means Test for Residence Order Payments and (b) making the use of such a test a statutory requirement for local authorities.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35871","35871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516223","2016-05-03","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Key Stage 1 spelling, punctuation and grammar test which was to be sat in May 2016 and which was subsequently cancelled was uploaded to the Standard and Testing Agency's website; and when it was updated.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35882","35882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516224","2016-05-03","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues on the (a) role of health visitors operating in designated children's centres and (b) ratio of health visitors to children under five years old.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35883","35883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516225","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of requiring all schools to convert to academies; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35911","35911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516226","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of converting schools into academies in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35912","35912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516227","2016-05-03","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils in free schools have (a) statements of special educational needs and (b) Education, Health and Care plans.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35922","35922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516228","2016-05-03","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils in schools with academy status have (a) statements of special educational needs and (b) Education, Health and Care plans.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35923","35923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516229","2016-05-03","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 33991, what proportion of the 644 teachers and head teachers who responded to the 2013 consultation supported the principle of the assessment reforms.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35933","35933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516230","2016-05-03","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils in local authority maintained schools have (a) statements of special educational needs and (b) Education, Health and Care plans.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35924","35924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516231","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what training is provided to teachers on working with children who have autism spectrum disorder.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35957","35957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516232","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in (a) primary and (b) secondary non-specialist schools have autism spectrum disorder; how schools are required to identify those children;  and what support her Department gives to those children.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35958","35958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516233","2016-05-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to increase the installation of home insulation.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35949","35949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516234","2016-05-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33974, what regard she has given to to Section 14 of the Cabinet Office publication, Guide to making legislation, when determining the relative timing of issuing the impact assessment and the closure of the consultation on further reforms to the Capacity Market.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35892","35892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516235","2016-05-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many staff of her Department she expects to transfer into the Oil and Gas Authority.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35880","35880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516236","2016-05-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the remote Scottish islands projects will be eligible to compete in the forthcoming Contracts for Difference auction process.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35860","35860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516237","2016-05-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the potential economic benefits of the remote Scottish islands onshore wind projects for the (a) regional economies of the islands and (b) wider UK supply chain.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35861","35861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516238","2016-05-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions she has had with her Japanese counterpart on the involvement of Japanese companies in new nuclear power projects in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35895","35895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516239","2016-05-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the application for state aid clearance for the remote Scottish islands has been submitted to the European Commission.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35859","35859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516240","2016-05-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with British Crown Dependencies on the status of such territories for the purpose of awarding Contracts for Difference to projects that benefit the UK's electricity supply.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35855","35855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516241","2016-05-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she expects the regulatory approval processes, including the Generic Design Assessment, to be completed for proposed new nuclear reactors at Moorside in Cumbria.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35894","35894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516242","2016-05-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she plans to classify grass as a crop for the purpose of consideration of biogas options in the Renewable Heat Incentive consultation.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35854","35854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516243","2016-05-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will take steps to ensure that Ministers and officials of her Department meet trades unions comprising the offshore co-ordinating group to discuss industrial relations and associated features of the oil and gas industry.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35856","35856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516244","2016-05-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she expects the regulatory approval processes, including the Generic Design Assessment, to be completed for proposed new nuclear reactors at Wylfa in Wales.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35893","35893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516245","2016-05-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 22 April 2016 to Question 34372, whether Petroleum Exploration and Development Licence 189 was one of the licences included in the Deed of Variation dated 4 December 2013, allowing the drilling of 10 wells to a depth of 800 metres and three wells to 3,000 metres on 13 specified licences.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35785","35785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516246","2016-05-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions her Department has had with external organisations on the development of the new cyber security strategy.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35780","35780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516247","2016-05-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether coal is being stockpiled in any location in the UK.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35829","35829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516248","2016-05-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she is reviewing (a) the number of air quality zones expected to comply with nitrogen dioxide limits by 2020 and (b) her Department's Air Quality Plan to take account of the results of the Government's diesel emissions testing programme.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35807","35807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516249","2016-05-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether future grants awarded by her Department to (a) universities and (b) charities will be exempt from the anti-lobbying clause in government grant agreements.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35795","35795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516250","2016-05-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effects on wider biodiversity of commonly used pesticides; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35869","35869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516252","2016-05-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the dairy crisis on (a) jobs in the industry, (b) local economies, (c) supply chains and (d) the environment.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35872","35872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516253","2016-05-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure that the Rural Payments Agency learns the lessons of the introduction of the Basic Payment Scheme.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35906","35906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516255","2016-05-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to reduce (a) microbeads entering and (b) rubbish in marine environments.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35904","35904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516256","2016-05-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Rural Payments Agency will maintain the current level of resources until the 2016 applications are logged and the issues with the 2015 applications are resolved; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35907","35907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516257","2016-05-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to protect bees from (a) neonicotinoids and (b) other harmful pesticides.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35884","35884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516258","2016-05-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress the Government has made on Food Enterprise Zones.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35885","35885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516259","2016-05-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on provision of affordable housing in rural areas.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35886","35886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516260","2016-05-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to improve the Rural Payments Agency call centre service.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35950","35950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516261","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government is taking steps to encourage progress towards the holding of a referendum in Western Sahara.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35954","35954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516262","2016-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to discourage the commemoration of acts of violence against Israeli civilians in the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35944","35944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516263","2016-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the employment rights of staff members seconded to or working within international organisations are protected.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35875","35875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516264","2016-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support a UN implementing agreement for the establishment and management of marine protected areas in the high seas.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35878","35878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516265","2016-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number and area of marine protected areas established beyond national jurisdiction through regional seas agreements or other instruments.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35879","35879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516266","2016-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of areas beyond national jurisdiction is covered by (a) regional seas agreements (b) regional fisheries management organisations and (c) other relevant instruments which are legally mandated to establish marine protected areas where the most important environmental impacts are effectively addressed.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35876","35876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516267","2016-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to (a) promote the protection of marine biodiversity in areas beyond national jurisdiction and (b) ensure that the agreed commitment to establish marine protected areas in 10 per cent of the world's oceans by 2020 is effectively implemented in such areas.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35877","35877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516269","2016-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to (a) the Indian government and (b) other parties involved on the release to its owners of the vessel Seaman Guard Ohio.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35823","35823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516270","2016-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to impose financial sanctions on Russian individuals complicit in human rights abuses.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35833","35833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516271","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to engage with the Polisaria Front; and if he or Ministers of his Department will meet senior Polisario Front officials.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35803","35803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516272","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on recognition of the Polisario Front as the representative of the people of Western Sahara.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35804","35804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516273","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will place in the Library copies of all departmental documents relating to the lifting of EU sanctions from Suleiman Marouf in August 2013.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35817","35817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516274","2016-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will establish a treatment programme to support the rehabilitation of young Yazidi and other women.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35819","35819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516275","2016-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure British citizens employed on international marine vessels are not arrested for entering the territorial waters of a country with incorrect paperwork for arms held on the ship to combat pirates.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35824","35824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516276","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions the Government has had with the government of Morocco on the holding of a free and fair referendum on the governance of Western Sahara.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35811","35811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516277","2016-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what date and in which location his Department last met with AdvanFort, the operator of the Seaman Guard Ohio; and what subjects were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35822","35822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516278","2016-05-03","HM Treasury","2016-04-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with which countries the UK has negotiated bilateral tax conventions; and how many of those conventions contain tax evasion information-sharing agreements in a similar form to Article 26 of the Model Tax Convention on Income and on Capital, published by the OECD.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35754","35754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516279","2016-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Romanian government on the treatment of the Roma community in that country.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35784","35784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516280","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government is making to the UN on incorporating a human rights mandate into the renewal of the UN peacekeeping force in Western Sahara.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35802","35802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516282","2016-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the level of threat in the Maghreb region posed by extremist, terrorist and criminal factions.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35760","35760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516283","2016-05-03","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to include in the Government's public health and obesity strategies the recent proposal from the Local Government Association, announced in its press release, Restaurants should offer tap water to help fight child obesity, of 23 April 2016, on the free and proactive provision of tap water by restaurants.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35746","35746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516284","2016-05-03","Cabinet Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reasons progressive supranuclear palsy is not recorded as a cause of death on death certificates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35761","35761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516285","2016-05-03","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how he plans to ensure that an additional 20,000 patients a year will have their cancers genetically tested as part of the Government's Cancer Taskforce strategy; and what data he plans to collect on those people who are tested.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35747","35747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516286","2016-05-03","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funds the Government has allocated for research into progressive supranuclear palsy in each of the last three years; and what plans the Government has to allocate further funding for research to support early diagnosis of and effective treatments for that condition.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35762","35762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516288","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the progress that clinical commissioning groups have made on implementing NICE guidelines on fertility treatment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35765","35765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516289","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he plans to give to clinical commissioning groups on encouraging their move towards full implementation of NICE guidelines on fertility treatment.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35766","35766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516290","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2016 to Question 21676, whether the new junior doctors' contract would be an improvement on the pay structure previously developed without the addition of transition protection.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35805","35805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516291","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 88 of the Equality Analysis in the new contract for doctors and dentists in training in the NHS, published in March 2016, if he will implement the recommendation that flexible pay premia should apply where a doctor needs to change speciality because of a disability or the need to care for a person with a disability.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35777","35777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516292","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 57 of the Equality Analysis in the new contract for doctors and dentists in training in the NHS, published in March 2016, if he will implement the recommendation that a pro rata cash sum equivalent to a five per cent to 10 per cent pay enhancement should be paid to part-time doctors based on the proportion of full-time work for on-call that has been agreed in the work schedule.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35776","35776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516293","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department is taking steps to encourage clinical commissioning groups to develop a commissioning policy for requests for cough assist machines for patients with muscle-wasting conditions.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35834","35834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516294","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has held with patients affected by muscle-wasting conditions on the benefits of cough assist machines.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35835","35835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516295","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the range of prices charged by fertility units within the NHS in England is to provide (a) a cycle of IVF and (b) a cycle of intracytoplasmic sperm injection.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35810","35810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516296","2016-05-03","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that general practitioners are taught objective methods of assessing serious illness in babies.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35832","35832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516297","2016-05-03","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the socio-economic groups to which those deciding to have a termination of pregnancy after the 20 week scan of a neural tube defect-affected pregnancy belong.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35864","35864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516298","2016-05-03","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of pregnancies affected by neural tube defects are terminated after the 20 week scan.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35865","35865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516299","2016-05-03","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the establishment of a national emergency operations centre within Public Health England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35868","35868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516300","2016-05-03","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the emergency operations capability of  Public Health England.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35867","35867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516301","2016-05-03","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the infrastructure cost was of installing a national emergency operations centre at the head office of Public Health England in 2011.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35866","35866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516302","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, by what average proportion Care Quality Commission registration fees have changed in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35902","35902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516303","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people under the age of (a) 18 and (b) 16 reported to hospital having taken more than the recommended daily allowance of non-prescription painkillers in (i) the last 12 months and (ii) each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35916","35916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516304","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make it compulsory for people working in residential care homes to be trained in (a) mental health screening and (b) bereavement counselling.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35909","35909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516305","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the Care Quality Commission spent on hotels and accommodation for inspectors in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35903","35903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516306","2016-05-03","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 33989, on blood: contamination, when he plans to publish a response to the public consultation.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35936","35936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516307","2016-05-03","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 April 2016 to Question 32720, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the removal of quality and outcomes framework indicators EP002 and EP003 on the number of avoidable epilepsy deaths.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35934","35934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516308","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings Ministers in his Department has had with industry since publication of the blood folate results in the National Diet and Nutrition Survey on 20 March 2015.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35917","35917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516309","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential benefits for public health and the economy of introducing a birth defects prevention month and a folic acid awareness week similar to those operating in the United States of America.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35918","35918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516310","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on implementing the recommendations of the National Maternity Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35953","35953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516311","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of schools have a mental health specialist as a permanent member of staff.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35956","35956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516312","2016-05-03","Department of Health","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of pregnancies that are unplanned.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35937","35937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516313","2016-05-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the efficacy of sentencing guidelines for people convicted of using a mobile phone when driving.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35925","35925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516314","2016-05-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations his Department has received on strengthening sentencing guidelines for people using a mobile phone when driving.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35926","35926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516315","2016-05-04","Home Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of female genital mutilation have been reported in (a) London and (b) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35905","35905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516316","2016-05-03","Home Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the 35 individuals named under the US Sergei Magnitsky Rule of Law Accountability Act 2012 have been granted UK visas since the murder of Sergei Magnitsky in 2009.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35845","35845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516318","2016-05-03","Home Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will establish an asylum programme for young Yazidi and other women who wish to relocate to the UK.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35818","35818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516319","2016-05-03","Home Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the European Commissioner for Migration and Home Affairs on the applicability of the European Security Strategy to the UK since recent terrorist attacks in Paris and Brussels; and what assessment she has made of the potential merits of the wider use of the EU Radicalisation Awareness Network Centre of Excellence in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35782","35782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516320","2016-05-03","Home Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total value was of criminal assets laundered abroad identified by British law enforcement agencies in each year since 2009 by country; and how much of those assets in each such country (a) has been recovered and (b) is recoverable.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35790","35790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516321","2016-05-03","Home Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the (a) effect of the Criminal Justice and Data Protection Regulations 2014 have had in assisting enforcement agencies in EU member states to recover money laundered abroad and (b) potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the UK's ability to tackle money laundering internationally.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35791","35791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516322","2016-05-03","Home Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests for mutual legal assistance have been made to foreign jurisdictions to recover criminal assets laundered abroad in each year since 2009; and what the jurisdictions are to which those requests were made.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35786","35786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516323","2016-05-03","Home Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many suspicious activity reports the ELMER database was designed to be capable of processing on an annual basis.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35756","35756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516324","2016-05-03","Home Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the of the potential benefits of replacing the ELMER database as part of the implementation of the Government's Action Plan for anti-money laundering and counter-terrorist finance, published in April 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35757","35757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516325","2016-05-03","Home Office","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many suspicious activity reports the ELMER database processed in 2015.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35758","35758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516326","2016-05-04","Department for International Development","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department allocated to schemes that tackle female genital mutilation in (a) Egypt, (b) Sudan, (c) Mali, (d) Somalia, (e) Sierra Leone and (f) Guinea.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35842","35842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516327","2016-05-04","Department for International Development","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that programmes implemented are cost-effective.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35910","35910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516328","2016-05-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drivers who did not hold valid driving licences have been convicted of driving without insurance in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35900","35900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516329","2016-05-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children under 18 were convicted of driving without insurance in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35901","35901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516336","2016-05-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of driving with a driving licence that was fraudulently obtained in the last three years.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35862","35862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516337","2016-05-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drivers with full, provisional or no licences were convicted of driving without insurance in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35863","35863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516338","2016-05-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 4.53 of the report on an unannounced inspection of HM Prison and Young Offenders Institute Bronzefield by HM Inspector of Prisons, published in November 2015, what steps his Department is taking in response to the finding that people who were released from prison with nowhere to go had been given tents and sleeping bags by the prison and its chaplaincy.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35940","35940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516339","2016-05-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that people imprisoned for stalking offences receive psychiatric or psychological support to break the cycle of offending.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35888","35888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516340","2016-05-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions he has had with (a) G4S and (b) other bodies on the announcement that G4S is to sell its children's services businesses made on 26 February 2016.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35891","35891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516341","2016-05-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has accrued to the public purse from employment tribunal fees in each year since those fees were introduced.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35963","35963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516342","2016-05-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department plans to publish its review of the impact of tribunal fees.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35951","35951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516343","2016-05-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of people released from prison into homelessness.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35826","35826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516344","2016-05-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have been recalled to prison in each of the last 12 months; and what steps he is taking to reduce that number.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35827","35827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516345","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he made of the potential workload of the Construction Commissioner for High Speed 2 when setting an anticipated commitment of two days per week for that Commissioner.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35773","35773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516346","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Maritime and Coastguard Agency's Survey and Inspection Transformation Programme; when he expects that Programme to be completed; and if he will place a copy in the Library.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35808","35808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516347","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the report by the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs Committee on Air Quality and the recommendation to introduce a diesel scrappage scheme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35809","35809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516348","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on whether constructing Phase 1 of High Speed 2 would breach the requirements of Directive 2008/520/EC on ambient air quality and cleaner air for Europe.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35815","35815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516349","2016-05-03","Department for Transport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what work his Department is carrying out to follow up the International Maritime Organisation summit on shipping emissions in April 2016; and whether the UK will play an active role in the working group established at that summit.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35783","35783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516350","2016-05-03","Department for Transport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, by which body he plans that the Construction Commissioner for High Speed 2 will be paid; and to whom it is planned that that Commission will report.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35751","35751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516351","2016-05-03","Department for Transport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 33300, for what reason the objectives for walking contained in the draft Cycling and Walking Investment Strategy are not measurable.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35889","35889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516352","2016-05-03","Department for Transport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on the potential merits of exempting telematics car insurance policies from insurance premium tax.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35927","35927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516353","2016-05-03","Department for Transport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on the potential merits of exempting drivers between the ages of 17 and 25 who have telematics car insurance policies from insurance premium tax.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35929","35929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516354","2016-05-03","Department for Transport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on the potential merits of reducing the insurance premium tax paid by drivers between the ages of 17 and 25 who have telematics car insurance policies.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35928","35928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516355","2016-05-03","Department for Transport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of security measures implemented at Israeli airports in order to inform his Department's policies.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35874","35874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516356","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with motor vehicle insurance companies on reducing the number of uninsured drivers.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35899","35899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516357","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will abolishing work-focused interviews in work-related activity groups for disabled people who are under appeal from employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35908","35908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516358","2016-05-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in each parliamentary constituency who have been reassessed for personal independence payments or disability living allowance have lost the higher rate mobility allowance.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35873","35873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516359","2016-05-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the tender document for the Work and Health Programme to provide specialist support for long-term unemployed and claimants with health conditions and disabilities will be published; and when that programme will be operational.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35858","35858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516360","2016-05-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the specification for the Work and Health Programme to provide specialist support for long-term unemployed and claimants with health conditions and disabilities will require (a) autism and (b) other conditions of claimants to be recorded by both providers and Jobcentre Plus; and what discussions he has had about which conditions will be recorded.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35857","35857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516361","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people received payments from the Financial Assistance Scheme in each (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) government region in the last year; and how many of those recipients were former members of the Allied Steel and Wire pension scheme in that year.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35945","35945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516362","2016-05-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33625, when he plans to publish the policy review of the supported housing sector.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35935","35935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516363","2016-05-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 21220, what progress has been made on deciding whether to add Dupuytren's contracture condition to the list for industrial injuries disablement benefit.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35941","35941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516364","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department last met representatives of former members of the Allied Steel and Wire pension scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35947","35947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516365","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of reforming (a) pension protection arrangements and (b) corporate pension schemes.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35946","35946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516366","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average reduction in benefits was for claimants subject to the under-occupancy penalty in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35961","35961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516367","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average value was of payments made under the Financial Assistance Scheme to former members of Allied Steel and Wire pension scheme in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35948","35948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516368","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the savings to his Department arising from application of the under-occupancy penalty in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35962","35962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516369","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the Financial Assistance Scheme paid out in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35965","35965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516370","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure the randomised control trial his Department is conducting on in-work progression follows the code of ethics set by the British Psychological Society.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35959","35959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516371","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether participation in the randomised control trial his Department is conducting on in-work progression is mandatory for claimants; and what consequences there will be for claimants who do not wish to take part in that trial.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35960","35960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516372","2016-05-03","HM Treasury","2016-04-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of all disbursements for public sector pensions for all those in employment and currently entitled to such pensions.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35750","35750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516373","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average (a) waiting time and (b) total call time is for calls made to the 0345 numbers operated by his Department.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35806","35806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516922","2016-05-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for UK Erasmus students, lecturers and research fellows in the event of the UK voting to leave the EU.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904785","904785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516923","2016-05-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that customers who were sold cashback warranties by PowerPlan and who did not receive their cash deposits having not claimed against those warranties receive compensation.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904783","904783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516924","2016-05-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assistance his Department provides to prevent job losses in highly-skilled manufacturing businesses.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904786","904786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516925","2016-05-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to address skills shortages in the workforce.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904780","904780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516926","2016-05-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage businesses to take on apprentices.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904773","904773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516927","2016-05-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the privatisation of the Land Registry on the effectiveness of its service.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904781","904781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516928","2016-05-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to address skills shortages in the workforce.","Biography information for Seema Kennedy","Seema Kennedy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904779","904779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516929","2016-05-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of a UK withdrawal from the EU on the UK's digital industries.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904782","904782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515682","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33754, on World War 1, what constitutes the extensive efforts referred to which are made to try and identify any recovered remains.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35492","35492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515683","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many trainee teachers have carried out practical teaching experience at pupil referral units in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35510","35510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515684","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy alternative provision sponsor-led schools have been graded (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requires improvement and (d) inadequate in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35514","35514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515685","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupil referral units have been graded (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requires improvement and (d) inadequate in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35515","35515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515686","2016-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what guidance she plans to provide to the oil and gas industry on the definition of satisfactory commercial return used in her Department's report, Maximising economic recovery strategy for the UK, published in January 2016.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35504","35504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515687","2016-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will estimate the cost to the public purse of funding the Oil and Gas Authority in each year to 2021-22.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35503","35503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515688","2016-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent research her Department has conducted on the potential merits of wave-generated power.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35495","35495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515689","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to collect data on (a) the number of patients who are required to return to hospital for a review or follow-up out-patient appointment or procedure and (b) the length of time between such patients' initial appointment and that review or follow-up appointment.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35493","35493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515690","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many tonsillectomy operations were carried out in England in the last five years.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35501","35501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515691","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support the Government is providing to GPs to help them with the cost of insuring work carried out outside normal hours.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35502","35502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515692","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 April 2016 to Question 34277, on disability aids, if he will estimate the cost to the NHS of those delayed days in hospital due to patients waiting for community equipment and adaptions.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35508","35508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515693","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the advertisement on the Hays recruitment website by NHS England for a temporary Senior Deputy Head of Media Planning and Strategy on a daily rate of pay, whether the successful candidate for that post will be paid through (a) the NHS England payroll, (b) that agency or (c) a limited company.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35511","35511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515694","2016-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of potential steps to increase provision of (a) court time and (b) relevantly skilled members of the judiciary to ensure the timely management of legal proceedings on complex planning disputes.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35494","35494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515695","2016-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to page 31 of his Department's publication, Response to the proposal on the provision of court and tribunal services in the South East region, published in February 2016, what the evidential basis is for the statement that a small proportion of people would use public transport to reach court.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35505","35505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515696","2016-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what provision has been made for moving the First-tier Tribunal (Property Chamber) from Chichester Magistrates' Court when that Court is closed.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35498","35498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515697","2016-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of closing the Chichester Combined Court Centre and Chichester Magistrates' Court on the work of (a) Chichester constabulary, (b) Chichester District Council and (c) other local services.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35499","35499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515698","2016-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on demand for justice services of future growth in the population of Chichester.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35500","35500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515699","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce HGV testing waiting lists at Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency testing centres.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35509","35509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515700","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much Transport for London will pay to the British Transport Police's budget in 2016-17.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35512","35512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515701","2016-04-28","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many road traffic accidents have been recorded over the last five years on the area of the A417 in Gloucestershire for which an upgrade is planned in 2020.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35496","35496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515702","2016-04-28","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will extend the English national concessionary travel scheme for disabled people beyond off-peak times.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35497","35497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515703","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many accidents were reported involving mobility scooters in 2015.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35513","35513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515706","2016-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 20 April 2016 to Question 33501, on equal pay tribunals, how many (a) men and (b) women were involved in the two large multiple claims referred to in that answer; and against whom those claims were brought.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35507","35507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515707","2016-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 20 April 2016 to Question 33501, on equal pay tribunals, how many individual equal pay claims have been brought against employers by (a) men and (b) women in each year between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35506","35506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515708","2016-05-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 21 April 2016 to Question 33376, by what date his Department plans to decide on whether British Sign Language is an acceptable alternative to qualifications in English for the purposes of completing an apprenticeship.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35529","35529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515709","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he has plans to regulate the sale of black spot carbon monoxide detectors.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35533","35533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515710","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward regulations on the sale of black spot carbon monoxide detectors.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35534","35534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515711","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many organisations receive funding from the science budget to conduct research into the use of proton therapy for cancers.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35535","35535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515712","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the funding of research into the use of proton therapy for cancers from the science budget in the next five years.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35537","35537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515713","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the funding of research into the use of laser treatment for cancers from the science budget in the next five years.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35538","35538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515714","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the 10 largest grants to fund research into the use of laser treatment for cancers made from the science budget were in the last five years; and when the results of such research will be published.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35539","35539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515715","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the 10 largest grants to fund research into the use of proton therapy treatment for cancers made from the science budget were in the last five years; and when the results of such research will be published.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35540","35540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515716","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the funding of research into the use of proton therapy for cancers from the science budget in the last five years.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35536","35536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515717","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will take steps to support finding a new buyer for Austin Reed Group Ltd.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35555","35555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515718","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the funding provided for research into the use of laser treatment for cancers from the science budget in the last five years.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35562","35562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515719","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many organisations received funding from the science budget to conduct research into the use of laser treatment for cancers in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35563","35563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515720","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what involvement (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department had in the Security and Counter Terror Conference at Olympia on 19 and 20 April 2016.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35598","35598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515721","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has made to the World Trade Organisation to request that anti-dumping measures are taken against the People's Republic of China.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35630","35630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515722","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many metric tonnes of Chinese rebar steel have been imported into the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35631","35631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515723","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the UK could act unilaterally to take an equity stake greater than 25 per cent in Tata Steel while being a member of the EU.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35632","35632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515724","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the UK has taken to support increased tariffs on artificially cheap steel imports to the EU.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35633","35633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515725","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many nationals of other EU member states (a) have student loans outstanding to repay, (b) are currently making payments on those loans and (c) have completed their course of study and are not making student loan repayments.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35656","35656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515726","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many nationals of other EU member states have taken out student loans but have made no repayments to date; and if he will estimate the total financial value of such loans.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35657","35657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515727","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much was paid in student loans to students from each other EU member state in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35658","35658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515728","2016-05-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 April 2016, HCWS701, what estimate he has made of the number of students affected by the proposed changes to eligibility to student support for people with long residency in the UK.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35678","35678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515729","2016-05-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 April 2016, HCWS701, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the proposed changes to eligibility to student support for people with long residency in the UK.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35679","35679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515730","2016-05-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the oral contribution of 25 April 2016, Official Report, column 1131, which groups he (a) has met with and (b) plans to meet with to discuss the importance of apprenticeships and other technical education for young people with disabilities.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35680","35680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515731","2016-05-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to prevent the dumping of Chinese steel in the UK at below-market prices.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35681","35681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515732","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many nationals of other EU member states have defaulted on their student loans; and what amount of such loans is not recoverable.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35659","35659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515733","2016-05-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has made to the EU on the dumping of cheap Chinese steel in western European markets.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35682","35682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515734","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many nationals of other EU member states with loans outstanding are uncontactable; and what estimate he has made of the amount of outstanding loans owed by such people.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35660","35660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515735","2016-05-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make a comparative assessment of energy costs for heavy industry in the UK and in other EU countries.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35693","35693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515736","2016-05-04","Cabinet Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much UK public money has been used to purchase steel from loss-making state-owned Chinese steel making companies (a) through the Crown Commercial Service and (b) in total in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35702","35702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515737","2016-05-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish a summary of the findings of the Insolvency Service's inquiry into the collapse of Comet.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35719","35719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515738","2016-05-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many UK citizens living in other EU countries, excluding Ireland, derived incomes from UK sources in the most recent year for which statistics are available.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35721","35721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515739","2016-05-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure the protective award is made to employees made redundant who worked across several establishments within one business.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35710","35710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515740","2016-05-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been paid out by his Department in statutory entitlements as a result of the collapse of Comet; how many people have been so compensated to date; and what estimate he has made of the total cost to the Exchequer of meeting all arising liabilities in this case.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35720","35720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515741","2016-05-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward legislative proposals on redundancy to specify that the word establishment applies to a whole business rather than an individual working environment.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35709","35709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515742","2016-05-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of people taking degree apprenticeships by the 2019-20 academic year.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35714","35714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515744","2016-05-04","Cabinet Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Ministers will represent the Government at the Anti-Corruption Summit in May 2016.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35695","35695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515745","2016-05-04","Cabinet Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his policy is on the declaration and publication by civil servants of financial interests other than gifts and hospitality.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35726","35726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515746","2016-05-04","Cabinet Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reasons the exemption from the anti-lobbying clause is limited to Research Councils, National Academies and the Higher Education Funding Council for England; and if he will delay the implementation of that clause until a full consultation has taken place.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35701","35701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515747","2016-05-04","Cabinet Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many full-time equivalent staff currently work in (a) the Joint Intelligence Organisation's Assessments Staff and (b) the National Security Secretariat; and how many such staff have not previously been employed as civil servants.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35669","35669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515748","2016-04-28","Cabinet Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of (a) increasing the powers of the Parliamentary Commissioner for Administration  and (b) merging the office of that Commissioner with the office of the Health Service Commission for England.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35650","35650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515749","2016-05-04","Cabinet Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 21 April 2016 to Question 33817, what the Joint Intelligence Committee's current estimate is of the number of non-extremist opposition fighters in Syria.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35668","35668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515750","2016-05-04","Cabinet Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what spending will be incurred on the EU referendum for each of the proposed lines of expenditure.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35594","35594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515751","2016-05-04","Cabinet Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the budget available to the Government is to spend on the EU referendum for each expenditure line and expenditure type.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35595","35595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515752","2016-05-04","Cabinet Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people working for central government departments have been paid through a limited company in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35611","35611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515753","2016-04-28","Cabinet Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what involvement ministers or officials of his Department had in the Security and Counter Terror Conference at Olympia in London on 19 and 20 April 2016; and how the Civil Contingencies Secretariat of his Department undertakes outreach activities.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35575","35575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515754","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made a recent estimate of the annual cost to the public purse of exempting plant and machinery from the calculation of business rates.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35570","35570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515755","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total number of Individual Savings Account (ISA) subscriptions was in 2015-16; and what proportion of ISA subscribers contributed the maximum amount in 2015-16.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35571","35571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515756","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of extending real time data sharing to the whole consumer credit market on the level of consumer debt in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35568","35568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515757","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the extension of real-time data sharing to the whole consumer credit market.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35565","35565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515758","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the economic benefit of extending real-time data sharing to the whole consumer credit market.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35566","35566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515759","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to reduce the obstacles to first-time house-buyers due to their outstanding student loans.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35574","35574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515760","2016-05-04","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 12 April 2016 to Question 32664 and the Answer of 25 April 2016 to Question 33678, and with reference to paragraph 2.113 of the report, The best of both worlds: the UK's special status in a reformed EU, published in February 2016, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of child benefit payments paid to non-UK citizens in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35530","35530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515761","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data quality testing has been carried out on the effect on universal credit calculations of the timeliness and accuracy of employer PAYE reporting through real time information.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35526","35526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515762","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which (a) PFI contracts and (b) other large contracts between the Government and private bodies have been renegotiated since  May 2010.","Biography information for Mhairi Black","Mhairi Black","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35619","35619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515763","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse excluding the cost of the introduction of the Lifetime Individual Savings Account of increasing the annual Individual Savings Account savings limit for all adults to £20,000 from April 2017, in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20 and (d) 2020-21.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35586","35586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515764","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support will be provided to parents should they have difficulties accessing support through the tax-free childcare scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35627","35627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515765","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to pilot his policy on tax-free childcare before it is launched.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35624","35624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515766","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what he expects the take-up rate of tax-free childcare to be.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35625","35625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515767","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support the Government plans to provide to working parents who wish to claim tax-free childcare but who are unable to access the internet; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35626","35626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515768","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made in the renegotiation of the 1955 UK-Malawi taxation treaty and what matters have yet to be agreed during that renegotiation.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35635","35635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515769","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of parents with children who claimed tax credits in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35655","35655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515770","2016-05-04","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 25 April 2016 to Question 34917, if he will provide a breakdown of the £25 billion total receipts from asset sales in financial year 2015-16 by (a) individual asset, (b) the amount raised by each asset and (c) the buyer of that asset.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35697","35697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515771","2016-05-04","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the total amount of income paid to UK citizens living in other EU countries except Ireland which derived from UK sources in the most recent year for which statistics are available.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35722","35722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515772","2016-05-04","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the total amount remitted to non-UK citizens living in other EU countries except Ireland, by non-UK citizens from the EU working in the UK in the last year.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35723","35723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515773","2016-05-04","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of UK citizens living in other EU countries excluding Ireland, derived incomes from UK sources in the most recent year for which statistics are available.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35724","35724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515774","2016-05-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require private landlords to fit safety devices on blinds to ensure children's safety.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35606","35606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515775","2016-05-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much government funding has been allocated to Cornish language schemes in the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35518","35518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515776","2016-05-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support the learning of the Cornish language.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35516","35516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515777","2016-05-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many regional or minority languages are recognised by his Department; and how many of those languages receive funding for language programmes.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35522","35522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515778","2016-05-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has had discussions with the BBC on the decision to move the Chinese language BBC World News Service to Hong Kong.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35589","35589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515779","2016-04-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the (a) Secretary of State for Education and (b) Northern Ireland Executive on increasing the involvement of children and young people of school age in commemorative events for the First World War.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35603","35603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515780","2016-04-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with Tourism NI on increasing the level of tourism from the UK mainland to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35604","35604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515781","2016-05-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2015 to Question 20201; what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy on safe-standing facilities at higher tier sports stadia on the recent findings of the Hillsborough Inquest.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35713","35713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515782","2016-05-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the militerisation of the Arctic.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35725","35725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515783","2016-05-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Government's policy is on (a) including within Common Article 3 of the Geneva Conventions 1949 prohibition of the targeting of individuals based on actual or perceived sexual orientation and (b) whether the consequences under international law of targeting individuals on the ground of sexual orientation are the same as targeting on the grounds of race, colour, religion or faith, sex and birth or wealth.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35741","35741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515784","2016-05-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the scale of Russian military presence in the Arctic.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35696","35696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515785","2016-05-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the UK's contribution will be to the Very High Readiness Joint Task Force.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35698","35698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515786","2016-05-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 April 2016 to Question 34932, what the grades were of the civilian employees seconded by his Department to (a) the Joint Intelligence Organisation's Assessments Staff and (b) the National Security Secretariat within the Cabinet Office during 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35671","35671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515787","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of the Farnborough International Airshow due to take place in July 2016.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35617","35617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515788","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Defence Attaché and Loan Service Centre was established; how many staff that Centre employs; and what that Centre's budget is for 2016-17.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35618","35618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515789","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2015 to Question 12325, how many defence attachés at what rank were employed at each of those locations on 1 April 2016; and whether each of those attachés has civilian assistants.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35599","35599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515790","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on the Defence and Security Equipment International Conference held in September 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35583","35583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515791","2016-05-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the UK's commitment is to NATO's Standing Naval Forces for 2016-17.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35593","35593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515792","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Annual Report 2015 of the Service Complaints Ombudsmen for the Armed Forces, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the finding that (a) some complaints first processed by the Service Complaints Commissioner in 2008 remain open and (b) other referrals by the Service Complaints Commissioner have been outstanding for over a year.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35582","35582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515793","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25082, how many unauthorised entries were recorded in relation to each of the bases listed in the Answer; what form of unauthorised entries were recorded in each case; which cases were investigated by (a) the Ministry of Defence Police, (b) a military police force and (c) a local civilian police force; and which such investigations led to a prosecution.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35621","35621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515794","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 21 April 2016 to Question 33821, how many unauthorised entries were recorded in relation to each of the bases listed in that Answer; what form of unauthorised entries were recorded in each case; which cases were investigated by (a) the Ministry of Defence Police, (b) a military police force and (c) a local civilian police force; and which such investigations led to a prosecution.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35622","35622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515795","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the findings of the Annual Report 2015 of the Service Complaints Ombudsmen for the Armed Forces, what steps he is taking to reduce the reluctance of service personnel to raise complaints through the service complaints system.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35579","35579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515796","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the findings of the Annual Report 2015 of the Service Complaints Ombudsmen for the Armed Forces, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of the Service Complaints Commissioner among junior members of the armed forces.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35580","35580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515797","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the findings of the Annual Report 2015 of the Service Complaints Ombudsmen for the Armed Forces, what steps he is taking to reduce the reluctance of service personnel who claim to have experienced bullying, harassment or discrimination to make a formal complaint.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35578","35578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515798","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Annual Report 2015 of the Service Complaints Ombudsmen for the Armed Forces, what steps he is taking in response to the finding on page 2 of that Report that the most common reasons for not submitting a complaint given by service personnel who claim to have experienced bullying, harassment or discrimination were that nothing would be done and that complaining would adversely affect the career of the potential complainant.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35577","35577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515799","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Annual Report 2015 of the Service Complaints Ombudsmen for the Armed Forces, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the finding that female personnel in the armed forces are approximately 30 per cent more likely than their male counterparts to lodge a complaint with the Service Complaints Commissioner.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35581","35581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515800","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) Royal Air Force aircraft and (b) manpower establishment is of (i) airborne early warning and (ii) air to air refuelling.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35585","35585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515801","2016-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he last had discussions with the Chief of the Defence Staff on the need to improve response times to complaints from serving officers; and what was agreed in that discussion.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35541","35541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515802","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy alternative provision converter schools have been graded (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requires improvement and (d) inadequate in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35520","35520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515803","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many alternative provision free schools have been graded (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requires improvement and (d) inadequate in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35519","35519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515804","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department plans to take to ensure that the number of qualified teachers does not decrease proportionately or in real terms by 2022.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35596","35596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515805","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to section 2.28 of the White Paper, Educational excellence everywhere, published in March 2016, by what criteria her Department will assess which higher education institutions are assessed as the best universities for education and teacher training.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35605","35605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515806","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 2.29 of her Department's White Paper, Educational excellence everywhere, published in March 2016; what measure her Department plans to use to determine what constitutes a high quality trainee.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35609","35609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515807","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 2.12 of her Department's White Paper, Educational excellence everywhere, published in March 2016; how she plans to reform the National College of Teaching and Leadership so that it can ensure the national and regional supply of teachers.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35610","35610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515808","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect on delivery of initial teacher training of all schools becoming academies.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35608","35608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515809","2016-04-28","Department for Education","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of a vote to leave the EU in the forthcoming referendum on (a) the process for child adoption and (b) the number of children adopted.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35732","35732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515810","2016-04-28","Department for Education","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2015, to Question 31427, whether her Department plans to provide additional funding to enable 25 per cent of secondary schools to extend their school day in the event that less than £285 million is available from the soft drinks industry levy.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35735","35735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515811","2016-05-04","Department for Education","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the observations from the Minister for Children and Families of 1 February 2016, Official Report, volume 605, column 8P, when the consultation on mandatory reporting of child abuse will commence.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35743","35743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515812","2016-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government is taking to support international electricity connectors.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35661","35661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515813","2016-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to keep coal plants open.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35662","35662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515814","2016-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to ensure that the closure of coal-powered stations does not lead to electricity shortages.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35663","35663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515815","2016-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will take steps to ensure that gas smart meter installers (a) take steps if they have safety concerns about a gas appliance and carbon monoxide poisoning and (b) are given the power to make such appliances safe.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35561","35561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515816","2016-05-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to ensure consumers are placed on the cheapest tariff available by their energy supplier.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35666","35666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515817","2016-05-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to reduce consumer energy prices.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35667","35667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515818","2016-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will take steps to ensure that gas smart meter installers check for carbon monoxide after fitting the meter and the appliance has been relit.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35560","35560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515819","2016-05-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of recent trends in the prevalence of myxomatosis in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35551","35551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515820","2016-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Deer Act 1991 in 2015.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35643","35643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515821","2016-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Wild Animals (Protection) Act 1996 in each police force area in 2015.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35637","35637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515822","2016-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will assess the merits of introducing a deposit return system for single-use drinks containers in England.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35646","35646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515823","2016-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to ban the routine preventive use of antibiotics in farming.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35647","35647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515824","2016-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Hunting Act 2004 in each police force area in 2014.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35640","35640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515825","2016-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Hunting Act 2004 in each police force area in 2015.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35644","35644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515826","2016-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Protection of Badgers Act 1992 in 2015.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35636","35636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515827","2016-05-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on assessing the effect on air quality and levels of emissions from motor vehicles of data published by Emissions Analytics and the Department for Transport on the level of emissions from new diesel cars.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35684","35684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515828","2016-05-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Rural Payments Agency is expected to resolve post-payment adjustments for the 2015 Basic Payments Scheme before September 2016; and if all outstanding cases will receive interest on their payments.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35675","35675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515829","2016-05-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, by when will 2015 payments to farmers from the Rural Payments Agency be completed; and when can farmers receiving a 50 per cent bridging payment expect to be paid in full.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35676","35676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515830","2016-05-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on future funding of research by the Department for Environment Food and Rural Affairs of the introduction of anti-lobbying clauses in government grant arrangements.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35706","35706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515831","2016-05-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which categories of recipients of grants awarded by her Department will be covered by the new anti-lobbying clause in Government grant agreements.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35708","35708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515832","2016-05-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which organisations have received public grant funding from her Department in each of the last five years; how much grant funding each organisation received; and what the purpose of each such grant was.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35707","35707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515833","2016-05-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many organisations in receipt of grant funding awarded by her Department were found to have engaged in activity that (a) influenced or attempted to influence Parliament, Government or the European Commission and (b) attempted to influence legislative or regulatory action in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35705","35705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515834","2016-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to encourage US-based IT companies to make customer use data available to UK intelligence services to help tackle international terrorism.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35727","35727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515835","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on action taken by the Egyptian government against Reuters as a result of that company's reporting of the case of Giulio Regeni; and what representations he has made to that government on such reports.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35686","35686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515836","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Indian government on the release from prisons of the five Britons working for the AdvanFort Security Company.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35673","35673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515837","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many members of his Department's staff from which of his Department's sections were seconded to (a) the Joint Intelligence Organisation's Assessments Staff and (b) the National Security Secretariat in the Cabinet Office during 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35670","35670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515838","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of confiscation of land (a) in Biafra and (b) owned by Biafrans by the Nigerian government.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35692","35692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515839","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has undertaken of the incidence of repression of Christians by the Nigerian government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35688","35688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515840","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government supports the request made by the Italian government to the Egyptian government to access telephone records relating to the case of Giulio Regeni; and whether he has made representations on that request to the Egyptian government.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35685","35685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515841","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of Christian churches that have been destroyed in Nigeria since 1990; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35690","35690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515842","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the potential effects of the grazing bill being considered by the Nigerian National Assembly on land rights in Biafra.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35691","35691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515843","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential risk of civil war in Nigeria as a result of the policy of the government of Nigeria on Biafra.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35689","35689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515844","2016-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions the Government has had with (a) UK companies and (b) the Malawian government on oil exploration around Lake Malawi.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35634","35634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515845","2016-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what checks his Department undertakes to ensure that EU Missions  are compliant with all European labour laws and that such missions have proper grievance procedures in place for complaints by staff seconded by the UK and other EU member states.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35623","35623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515846","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political situation in Mozambique and  tensions between that country's opposition party's militia and state security forces.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35613","35613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515847","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of freedom of speech for (a) bloggers and (b) other people in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35614","35614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515848","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of implications for democracy and the rule of law in Macedonia of the recent presidential pardon for politicians in that country.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35615","35615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515849","2016-05-04","Home Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government authorised the National Crime Agency to supply evidence to the Thai government on the case of Zaw Lin and Wai Phyo without seeking written assurances that they would not be sentenced to death by that government.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35616","35616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515850","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last made representations to the Chinese government on the fate of the Panchen Lama; and what response he received to such representations.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35550","35550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515851","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Chinese government on the safety of British journalists working in China.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35588","35588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515852","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what beneficial shifts in the human rights approach of the Chinese government there have been as a result of steps taken by his Department.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35592","35592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515853","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking with his EU counterparts to enable (a) EU diplomats and (b) journalists to enter Tibet.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35591","35591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515854","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when (a) a minister and (b) officials in his Department last visited the area described by the Chinese government as the Tibetan Autonomous Region.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35590","35590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515855","2016-05-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on LGBT rights in Bangladesh of the murder of Xulhaz Mannan in Dhaka.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35521","35521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515856","2016-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the proportion of (a) native Tibetans, (b) Han Chinese and (c) others who were resident in Tibet in (i) 2015, (ii) 2005 and (iii) 1995.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35531","35531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515857","2016-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on whether decisions on the reincarnation of Tibetan Lamas should made made by the Tibetan people.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35532","35532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515858","2016-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change on the climate threat arising from Chinese activities affecting the third pole region.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35542","35542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515859","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people diagnosed with dementia have access to appropriate treatment and support.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35548","35548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515860","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33688, how many individuals were screened for tuberculosis among populations deemed to be at high risk of that infection in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35527","35527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515861","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 33687, what investment there has been related to the Collaborative TB Strategy for England 2015 to 2020 for (a) tuberculosis (TB) awareness raising, (b) TB case finding (screening) and (c) treatment for under-served populations such as the homeless; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35528","35528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515862","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects all regions in England to have a complete Liaison and Diversion service.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35523","35523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515863","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the decision on the business case for Liaison and Diversion services to be announced by HM Treasury.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35524","35524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515864","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people with acute strokes were treated with thrombolysis in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35576","35576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515865","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence on granting that Institute the power to be able to approve cancer drugs for use off-license.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35569","35569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515866","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mental health referrals have been made in (a) England and (b) London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35587","35587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515867","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS agencies have changed their name or merged in the last (a) 12 and (b) 24 months; and what the cost was to the public purse of such mergers and name changes.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35567","35567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515868","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to develop a national cross-departmental strategy for reducing and eliminating excess winter deaths.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35607","35607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515869","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 32700, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) extent to which clinical need can be determined in the absence of a comprehensive specialist initial assessment and (b) extent to which Local Transformation Plans assess need.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35620","35620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515870","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether Public Health England will be responsible for drafting and publishing the obesity strategy.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35641","35641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515871","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for the publication of the obesity strategy; and what role (a) Public Health England and (b) his Department is playing in the drafting of that strategy.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35639","35639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515872","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which private sector companies (a) provided financial resources, (b) submitted evidence  and (c) provided any in-kind support during the development of the new Eatwell Guide.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35642","35642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515873","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to promote habilitation training.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35649","35649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515874","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department will be responsible for drafting and publishing the obesity strategy.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35638","35638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515875","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will carry out a cost-benefit analysis on the use of pre-exposure prophylaxis as a preventative measure for HIV.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35645","35645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515876","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on campaigns promoting the cessation of smoking in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35653","35653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515877","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make additional funding available to expand access to habilitation training for young people with sight loss.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35648","35648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515878","2016-04-28","Cabinet Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of neonatal deaths in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) the UK in each of the last ten years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35654","35654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515879","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 April 2016 to Question 34838, under which clauses of the National Health Service Act 2006 he exercised the range of powers used in deciding to proceed to introduce a new contract.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35683","35683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515880","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department monitors the performance of Sussex Clinical Commissioning Group's patient transport services.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35674","35674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515930","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2016 to Question 29568, what steps he has taken to ensure all local transformation plans cover transitions between services including moving from adolescent to adult mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35737","35737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515933","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 33552, if the National Clinical Audit and Patient Outcomes Programme will audit the number of avoidable deaths from epilepsy in adults.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35728","35728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515935","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many paramedics have taken time off work due to stress in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35738","35738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515937","2016-05-04","Home Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers have taken time off work due to stress in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35740","35740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515939","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 33552, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policy of the Epilepsy Society's longitudinal study on epilepsy mortality.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35730","35730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515941","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department collects on trends in e-cigarettes used in the UK across the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35711","35711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515943","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effects of moderate alcohol consumption on cardiovascular and cognitive health.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35731","35731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515945","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 33552, if he will make an assessment of the extent of regional variation in premature death from epilepsy.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35729","35729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515947","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2016 to Question 30262, what plans Health Education England has to reform funding not related to the bursary scheme for postgraduate training in (a) child psychotherapy, (b) clinical psychology and (c) improving access to psychological therapies from 2017-18.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35739","35739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515949","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 April 2016 to Question 34485, on mental health services, when he expects NHS England to publish the website addresses referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35736","35736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515951","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what further discussions his Department plans to hold with industry and other interested parties on the decision of NHS England to end the specialised commissioning process for HIV medicines used for Pre-Exposure Prophylaxis; what plans he has for the provision of such medicines before the end of the current pilot of early implementer sites over the next two years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35694","35694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515953","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to create a Best Practice Tariff or similar sustained improvement incentive for sepsis.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35699","35699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515955","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is planning to take to improve professional awareness of sepsis.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35700","35700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515957","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what financial impact analysis his Department has conducted on the proposed new model of community pharmacy.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35745","35745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515958","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to launch a public awareness campaign for sepsis.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35742","35742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515960","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that affected women and their partners have access to bereavement counselling after early miscarriage.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35733","35733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515962","2016-04-28","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that treatment is provided to detainees held in immigration removal centres who are (a) self-harming and (b) experiencing post-traumatic stress disorder.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35734","35734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515964","2016-04-28","Home Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made in rolling out Project Griffin to security managers in the private sector and what budget has been provided to the National Counter Terrorism Security Office to promote Project Griffin.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35665","35665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515965","2016-04-28","Home Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 April 2016 to Question 34987 and the Answer of 25 April 2016 to Question 34792, how much of the £10 million LIBOR fines funding has been allocated to mental health in total; and whether that allocation was made in October 2014 or October 2015.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35628","35628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515966","2016-04-28","Home Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the treatment of single mothers and victims of trafficking who have been returned from the UK to Albania after their return to that country.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35629","35629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515967","2016-04-28","Home Office","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what involvement (a) Ministers and (b) officials of her Department had in the Security and Counter Terror Conference at Olympia on 19 and 20 April 2016.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35597","35597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515968","2016-04-28","House of Commons Commission","2016-04-26","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, what assessment the Commission has made of the effectiveness of the Education Service in engaging the attention of children during their visits to Parliament.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35602","35602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515969","2016-04-28","Department for International Development","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what work her Department is carrying out using its funding priorities to encourage gender equality around the world.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35652","35652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515970","2016-04-28","Department for International Development","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding priorities her Department has in Bangladesh.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35651","35651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515971","2016-04-28","Department for International Development","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has had discussions with the Royal Botanic Gardens, Kew on the potential role of that organisation in advising the UN and other institutions on desertification.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35543","35543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515972","2016-04-28","Department for International Development","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department is offering advice to African countries on desertification.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35544","35544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515973","2016-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that prisoners with mental health problems can access appropriate treatment.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35549","35549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515974","2016-05-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions he has had with the Sentencing Council on the offence of refusing carriage to an assistance dog.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35672","35672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515975","2016-04-28","Prime Minister","2016-04-26","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions he had with President Obama on his recent visit to London in April 2016 on tackling the funding of ISIS/Daesh by people from Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35584","35584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515976","2016-05-04","HM Treasury","2016-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his oral contribution of 23 March 2016, Official Report, column 1558, when his Department plans to carry out an impact assessment of the proposed closure of HM Revenue and Customs offices on the local economy of East Kilbride.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35744","35744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515978","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.103 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, what discussions his Department had with the Ministry of Justice on the decision to remove the right to general damages for minor soft tissue injuries and raising the personal injury small claims limit to £5,000.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35687","35687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515979","2016-05-04","Department of Health","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department took when devising the new model of community pharmacy to take into account both (a) rural and (b) urban deprivation.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35703","35703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515980","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much revenue was raised from fines levied on heavy goods vehicles for exceeding weight restrictions on weight restricted roads in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35704","35704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515981","2016-04-28","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government has taken to promote cycling to work.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35564","35564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515982","2016-04-28","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a bicycle highway code.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35600","35600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515983","2016-04-28","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to promote awareness among cyclists of the importance of wearing helmets and visible clothing.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35601","35601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515984","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish his Department's senior officials' business expenses and hospitality data for 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35612","35612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515985","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on signing the Luxembourg rail protocol.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35525","35525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515986","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent by (a) Highways England and (b) the Highways Agency per head of population in each region of England in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35517","35517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515987","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on which motorways at which locations automatic number plate recognition cameras are in use; and what offences such cameras are being used to detect.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35552","35552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515988","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to further restrict the use of drones to ensure (a) the safety of aircraft and (b) privacy of members of the public.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35553","35553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515989","2016-05-04","Department for Transport","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he was consulted before the imposition of a 40 mph speed limit on the A15 north Caenby Corner; what guidance is provided to highway authorities on imposing and varying speed limits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35554","35554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515990","2016-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of introducing an adoption allowance for self-employed adopters.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35572","35572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515991","2016-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department offers to grandparents that care for grandchildren.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35559","35559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515992","2016-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of extending statutory (a) maternity pay, (b) paternity pay and (c) sick pay to self-employed people.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35573","35573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515993","2016-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department is taking steps to protect the pensions of grandparents that care for grandchildren.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35556","35556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515994","2016-04-28","Department for Education","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of grandparents that care for grandchildren.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35558","35558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515995","2016-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to offer childcare services to grandparents that care for grandchildren.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35557","35557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515996","2016-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 192 of the Office of Budget Responsibility's report, Economic and fiscal outlook, published in March 2016, how the estimated savings of £0.8 billion by 2020-21 from the minimum income floor of universal credit were calculated.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35545","35545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515997","2016-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to universal credit, what his estimate is of Government spending on transitional protection where entitlement is lower in each year until 2018-19.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35546","35546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515998","2016-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his oral contribution of 21 March 2016, Official Report, column 1269, whether his Department plans to proceed with the removal of housing benefit for people aged between 18 and 21 years old.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35547","35547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515999","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's total legal costs were in case EA/2013/0148/9 heard by the First-Tier Tribunal General Regulatory Chamber Information Rights on 22 February 2016.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35718","35718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516000","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which one of his Department's assets Telereal Trillium are responsible for maintaining.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35717","35717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516001","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many ongoing legal disputes his Department is currently engaged in.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35716","35716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516002","2016-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the effect of the reduction of work allowances under universal credit announced in the Summer Budget 2015 on the number of children living in relative poverty in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19, (d) 2019-20 and (e) 2020-21.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35664","35664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516003","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the under-occupancy penalty on families with severely disabled children.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35677","35677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516004","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he intends to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Pontypridd dated 28 March 2016 on the Government's priorities for social security.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35715","35715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/516005","2016-05-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average distance is travelled by residents of Hove for face-to-face personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35712","35712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515188","2016-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the (a) Law Society and (b) other representatives of the legal profession on the issuing of seven day notices of legal proceedings at the same time as invoices for payment to consumers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35350","35350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515189","2016-04-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the cyber security implications of driverless cars.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35322","35322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515190","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answers of 25 February 2016 to Questions 27493 and 27494, and with reference to Article 29 of the UN Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods, what the evidential basis is for the Government's conclusion that the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership does not automatically apply to British Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35358","35358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515191","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answers of 25 February 2016 to Questions 27493 and 27494, and with reference to Article 29 of the UN Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods, what the evidential basis is for the Government's conclusion that the Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement does not automatically apply to British Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35359","35359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515192","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department has produced an implementation plan for the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35363","35363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515193","2016-04-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much EU (a) 7th Framework Programme and (b) Horizon 2020 funding has been provided to (i) universities, (ii) other research institutions and (iii) small businesses in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35370","35370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515194","2016-04-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government is taking to promote trade between the UK and other Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35417","35417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515195","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many vehicles were acquired under the 2009-10 vehicle scrappage scheme; and how many of those vehicles had not been disposed of on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35431","35431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515196","2016-04-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many places were awarded on nursing degrees at each institution in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35415","35415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515197","2016-04-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) applicants and (b) accepted offers of places there were for nursing degrees at each institution in 2014-15 from (i) A-levels and (ii) Access students.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35416","35416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515198","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects to agree a budget settlement for the apprenticeship levy for the devolved nations of the UK.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35475","35475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515199","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to maintain the apprenticeship levy rate of 0.5 per cent on employers' pay bills over £3 million until 2020.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35476","35476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515200","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if the Government will continue to pay for training to enable apprentices to achieve Level 2 or GCSEs in English and mathematics, as required, once the Apprenticeship Levy has been introduced.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35477","35477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515201","2016-04-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 21 April 2016 to Question 34465, if his Department will take steps to allow web-users to include honours when completing government online forms.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35204","35204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515202","2016-04-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on safeguarding the future of the UK helicopter industry.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35235","35235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515203","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33699, what the duties of the board members of the Institute for Apprenticeships will be prior to the launch of that Institute in April 2017.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35306","35306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515204","2016-04-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Skills Funding Agency statistics on Apprenticeship Achievements by framework code, level and gender, 2002-03 to 2013-14, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the reduction in the proportion of engineering apprenticeships which were undertaken by women between 2002 and 2014.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35317","35317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515205","2016-04-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the finding of the Young Women's Trust on page 13 of its report, Making apprenticeships work for young women, that apprenticeships are reinforcing, rather than challenging, occupational segregation by gender.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35318","35318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515206","2016-05-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the efficiency of the National Consumer Council pension scheme in discharging its duty to ensure payment to new pensioners on attainment of scheme payment eligibility.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35486","35486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515207","2016-05-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the transparency of contact details for the National Consumer Council pension scheme.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35487","35487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515208","2016-05-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will investigate the fitness for purpose of the members' payments division of the National Consumer Council pension scheme.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35488","35488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515209","2016-05-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what arrangements are in place to ensure that the pension schemes of abolished non-departmental public bodies which lay within his Department's remit efficiently discharge their liabilities to pensioners.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35489","35489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515210","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on consumers of businesses issuing seven-day legal procedure notices with invoices.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35485","35485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515211","2016-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on taking steps to tackle recent reductions in the number of employers posting apprenticeship vacancies.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35478","35478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515212","2016-04-28","Cabinet Office","2016-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many EEA nationals living in the UK have resided in the UK for (a) less than three months, (b) three to six months, (c) six to 12 months, (d) one to two years, (e) two to three years, (f) three to four years, (g) four to five years and (h) longer than five years.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35280","35280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515213","2016-04-28","Cabinet Office","2016-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young people from Kettering constituency have participated in the National Citizen Service in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35473","35473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515214","2016-04-28","Cabinet Office","2016-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many prosecutions have been brought under Section 70 of the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each year since the coming into force of that Act.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35424","35424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515215","2016-04-28","Cabinet Office","2016-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish a list of representatives he has invited to the Anti-Corruption Summit to be held in May 2016.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35425","35425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515216","2016-04-28","Cabinet Office","2016-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people from other EEA member states settled in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) Scotland, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland (i) before and (ii) since 1 January 2004.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35430","35430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515217","2016-04-28","Cabinet Office","2016-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many prosecutions were brought under Section 77 of the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each year since the coming into force of that Act.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35423","35423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515218","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many stakeholders responded to his Department's informal consultation on the transitional arrangements for the removal of the Climate Change Levy exemption for renewably sourced electricity.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35432","35432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515219","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a summary of responses to his Department's informal consultation on the transitional arrangements for the removal of the Climate Change Levy exemption for renewably sourced electricity.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35437","35437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515220","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of income tax paid annually by London taxi drivers, in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35450","35450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515221","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the annual amount of corporation tax paid by minicab businesses, in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35452","35452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515222","2016-04-27","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to mitigate the risk posed to the economy by the increased Chinese debt load.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35463","35463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515223","2016-04-27","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the economic security implications of the proposed merger between the London Stock Exchange and Deutsche Borse.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35464","35464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515224","2016-04-27","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many brokers and traders who work in finance have lost their Financial Industry Regulatory Authority licence as a result of financial misconduct since 2008.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35391","35391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515225","2016-04-27","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many financial firms were fined for financial misconduct in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) 2015; and what the amount of the fine was in each such case.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35392","35392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515226","2016-04-27","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many companies have been prosecuted for tax evasion during the last 10 years; and what revenue has been recovered as a result of those prosecutions.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35377","35377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515227","2016-04-27","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have been prosecuted for tax evasion during the last 10 years; and what revenue has been recovered as a result of those prosecutions.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35378","35378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515228","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the UK's (a) payments to the EU, (b) receipts through EU schemes and (c) receipts through the UK rebate in each year between 2020 and 2030.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35338","35338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515229","2016-04-27","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 21 April 2016 to Question 34465, if HM Revenue and Customs will take steps to enable web-users to include honours when completing government online forms.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35292","35292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515230","2016-04-27","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.256 of Budget 2016, what meetings (a) he and (b) his officials have had with the Department of Health regarding the UK's bid to host the 2021 Rugby League World Cup.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35286","35286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515231","2016-04-27","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the accuracy of the methodology used to measure productivity in the UK.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35257","35257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515232","2016-04-27","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraphs 3.16 to 3.26 of the report, Independent review of UK economic statistics, published on 11 March 2016, what plans he has to improve the accuracy of estimates of the contribution of the digital economy to UK productivity.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35259","35259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515233","2016-04-27","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.256 of Budget 2016, what meetings (a) he and (b) his officials have had with the Department for Culture, Media and Sport on supporting the UK's bid to host the 2021 Rugby League World Cup.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35285","35285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515234","2016-04-28","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many officials work in his Department's Referendum Unit; and what the estimated cost of that unit is.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35339","35339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515235","2016-04-27","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Northern Powerhouse strategy will include his pledge in paragraph 2.256 of Budget 2016 to support the UK's bid for the 2021 Rugby League World Cup; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35217","35217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515236","2016-04-27","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.256 of Budget 2016, what meetings (a) he and (b) his officials have had with the Rugby Football League on his support for the UK's bid to host the 2021 Rugby League World Cup.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35218","35218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515237","2016-04-27","HM Treasury","2016-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.256 of Budget 2016, what meetings (a) he and (b) his officials have had with the Department for Education on his support for the UK's bid to host the 2021 Rugby League World Cup.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35219","35219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515238","2016-04-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to paragraph 2.256 of Budget 2016, when he plans to take a decision on the details of the Government's support for the UK bid to host the 2021 Rugby League World Cup; and if he will do so in time for the Rugby Football League to meet the deadline of 30 June 2016.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35220","35220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515239","2016-04-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 April 2016 to Question 34465, if his Department will take steps to allow web-users to include honours when completing government online forms.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35205","35205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515240","2016-04-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support the provision of adult social care in the Stockport local authority area.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35253","35253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515241","2016-04-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 32951, what measures he plans to introduce to ensure that social housing stock sold under the Right to Buy scheme is replaced by like-for-like replacements that are built in the same local authority area.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35264","35264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515242","2016-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what further steps he plans to take to ensure that local government pension scheme members are consulted on proposed guidance on the ability of local government to account for non-financial factors in pension scheme investment decisions; and what steps he plans to take to ensure that that proposed guidance will be subject to parliamentary scrutiny.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35272","35272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515243","2016-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the responses to the non-financial factors section of the recent consultation on revoking and replacing the Local Government Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35271","35271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515244","2016-04-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he plans to take to provide information to enable future planning by supported housing providers during the next 12 months.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35328","35328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515245","2016-04-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of how much local authorities will be able to collect through business rates under the Government's devolution proposals in (a) East Yorkshire, (b) North Lincolnshire and (c) elsewhere.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 35369","35369"
