"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137154","2019-07-09","Department for Education","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of looked-after children who were taken into care as a result of their mother receiving a custodial sentence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273741","273741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137155","2019-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the 29 April 2019 Health Select Committee news item, Committee publishes doctors’ views on Fit Notes and ESA appeals, what estimate her Department has made of the number of claimants who challenged their work capability assessment decisions but were refused employment support allowance while their appeal was pending due to her Department sending ambiguous ESA65B letters to claimants’ GPs.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273727","273727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137156","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what is his timeframe is for the publication of the Prevention Green Paper.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273728","273728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137157","2019-07-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the total value of the NHS England Children’s Hospice Grant will be in (a) 2020-21 (b) 2021-22 (c) 2022-23 and (d) 2023-24.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273783","273783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137158","2019-07-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will ensure that the total value of the children’s hospice grant does not fall below £12million between the years 2020-21 and 2023-24 inclusive.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273784","273784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137159","2019-07-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for publishing the 2020-21 NHS England children’s hospice grant allocations.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273785","273785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137160","2019-07-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that children’s hospices receive notice of their individual 2020-21 NHS England children’s hospice grant allocation in time to inform their budget planning for that year.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273786","273786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137161","2019-07-10","Treasury","2019-07-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue his Department received though collection of the sugar tax in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273729","273729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137162","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  with reference to the Childhood Obesity Plan: a plan for action, chapter 2, published on 25 June 2018, what progress he has made on reducing children's consumption of sugary drinks and food.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273730","273730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137163","2019-07-10","Department for Education","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to require schools to offer pupils breakfast on the morning of their exams.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273743","273743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137164","2019-07-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to fund at least one alcohol care team or specialist in every hospital.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273736","273736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137165","2019-07-10","Department for Education","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many hours of schooling were lost due to schools reducing the length of the school day as a result of insufficient funding in the 2017-18 academic year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273737","273737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137166","2019-07-10","Department for Education","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the proportion of school buildings that contain asbestos; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273787","273787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137167","2019-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her Department's policy is on mandatory asbestos testing in public sector buildings.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273788","273788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137168","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many not-for-profit legal aid providers provided legal services in each region in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273812","273812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137169","2019-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential for (a) tree-planting and reforestation and (b) the prevention of deforestation to help the UK meet its goal of net zero emissions by 2050.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273789","273789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137170","2019-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings of The global tree restoration potential report, published in Science on 5 July 2019 that there are 1.7 billion hectares of treeless land on which 1.2 trillion native tree saplings would naturally grow, providing immense potential for tree-planting as a cheap and effective strategy to tackle climate change; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273790","273790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137171","2019-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to promote (a) reforestation and (b) prevent deforestation in each region and nation of the UK in the last five years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273791","273791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137172","2019-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to make the UK a world leader in electric car manufacturing.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273738","273738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137173","2019-07-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to publish the minutes of the Anti-Muslim Hatred Working Group meetings.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273792","273792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137174","2019-07-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many meetings the Anti-Muslim Hatred Working Group has held.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273793","273793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137175","2019-07-09","Department for Education","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the University and College Union report entitled, Counting the costs of casualisation in higher education, published June 2019, what assessment he has made of the (a) effect of job insecurity on mental and physical health and (b) level of financial stability of Cambridge teaching staff; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273794","273794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137176","2019-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled, Upstream: Microplastics in UK Rivers, published by Greenpeace UK on 18 June 2019, what assessment he has made of the level plastic pollution in UK rivers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273795","273795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137177","2019-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to (a) prevent plastic entering rivers and (b) remove plastic pollution from rivers.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273796","273796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137178","2019-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2019 to Question 269807 on HM Courts and Tribunals Service: Staff, if he will publish the information for March 2019.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273813","273813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137179","2019-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many court buildings were referred to the Health and Safety Executive because of (a) the presence of asbestos and (b) other concerns in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273814","273814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137180","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what records his Department holds on the number of cases started by law centres in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273815","273815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137181","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of one-year contracts on the (a) quality and (b) oversight of education in prisons.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273816","273816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137182","2019-07-10","Home Office","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress his Department has made on compensating people affected by the Windrush scandal.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273739","273739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137183","2019-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time taken was to complete a single employment tribunal claim by employment tribunal office in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273817","273817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137184","2019-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of outstanding employment tribunal cases was by employment tribunal office in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273818","273818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137185","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total number of days of detached duty worked was in each prison where performance was found to be of serious concern in the Annual Prison Performance Ratings 2017-18 in (a) the last six months of 2017 and (b) the last six months of 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273819","273819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137186","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of healthcare provision in custodial institutions that hold children.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273820","273820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137187","2019-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Commonwealth Heads of Government meeting in April 2018 in Belfast, what progress he has made in developing a business strategy for Northern Ireland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273750","273750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137188","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time was between first court appearance and trial in (a) magistrates courts and (b) Crown courts in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273758","273758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137189","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the court utilisation rate at Bradford Crown Court in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273759","273759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137190","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time was between arrest and charge in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273760","273760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137191","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were on police bail in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273761","273761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137192","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases involving defendants in criminal courts commenced with a postal requisition by the Crown Prosecution Service in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273762","273762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137193","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was money was spent by his Department on constructing a secure dock in Bradford Crown Court.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273763","273763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137194","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sentences were reduced on appeal because they were manifestly excessive in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273764","273764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137195","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the number of judges available to conduct criminal cases in crown courts.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273765","273765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137196","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the court utilisation rate was at (a) Camberwell Green and (b) Croydon Magistrates Court in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273766","273766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137197","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress he has made on plans to relocate of the work of Camberwell Green Magistrates' Court to other courts following the closure of that court; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273767","273767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137198","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has sold Camberwell Green Magistrates' Court building.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273768","273768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137199","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the criteria was for the selection of people to join the review on how the family courts protect children and parents in cases of domestic abuse and other serious offences announced on 21 May 2019; whether one of the criterion was equality of gender representation; for what reason that selection did not include representatives of fathers or men; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273769","273769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137200","2019-07-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the letter from his Department cited in the 3 July 2019 InsideHousing article entitled, Check cladding on buildings under 18m - government tells building control, whether his Department is directing building control to check the safety of cladding on all buildings including those already constructed.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273797","273797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137201","2019-07-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the letter from his Department cited in the 3 July 2019 InsideHousing article entitled Check cladding on buildings under 18m - government tells building control, if his Department will provide local authorities with additional resources to check the safety of cladding within their geographical area.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273798","273798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137202","2019-07-09","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many visits there have been to UK naval bases by foreign vessels carrying nuclear weapons in each of the last ten years; which bases those vessels visited; and what nations those vessels originated from.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273805","273805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137203","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data his Department holds on (a) police force strength and (b) recorded crime in Cambridgeshire for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273833","273833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137204","2019-07-09","Department for Education","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the amount of pupil premium funding provided to schools in (a) Cambridgeshire (b) the Peterborough constituency in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273834","273834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137205","2019-07-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what data his Department holds on the amount of central government funding provided to (a) Cambridgeshire County Council and (b) Peterborough City Council, in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273835","273835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137206","2019-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of free television licences issued to residents in (a) Peterborough City Council and (b) Peterborough constituency in each of the last three years; and what the total annual value was of those licences.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273836","273836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137207","2019-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the maintenance of animal welfare standards in relation to live animal exports when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273831","273831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137208","2019-07-09","Department for Transport","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if it is his policy that the rail (a) network and (b) supply chain will be net carbon neutral by 2050.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273803","273803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137209","2019-07-09","Department for Education","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that the specification of laptops supplied to students with vision impairment through the disabled students’ allowance is updated allow updating of necessary software over the duration of degree programme.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273733","273733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137210","2019-07-09","Department for Transport","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to ensure that his Department's plans announced in June 2019 to increase freight network capacity in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal will deliver value for money for the public purse.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273804","273804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137211","2019-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant the Answer of 4 July 2019 to Question 271441 on Armed Forces: Heart Diseases, for what reason RAF recruits do not receive an electrocardiogram test; and whether such a test is a requirement for a recruit to gain a pilot's licence.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273752","273752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137212","2019-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2019 to Question 271441 on Armed Forces: Heart Diseases, whether she has plans to change the criteria clinicians follow when seeking to detect significant structural and electrophysiological abnormalities in recruits.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273753","273753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137213","2019-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of discarded cigarettes on ocean plastic pollution.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273776","273776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137214","2019-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to reduce cigarette end littering.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273777","273777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137215","2019-07-09","Department for Transport","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's timescale is for permanently ceasing operation of Pacer trains on Northern Rail franchise routes.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273778","273778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137216","2019-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on an EU-wide ban on shark fin imports.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273779","273779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137217","2019-07-09","Department for Transport","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the economic growth in the Humber since the 2012 decision to halve tolls on the Humber Bridge.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273780","273780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137218","2019-07-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Housing of 6 June 2019, Official Report, column 331, if he will provide details of the work the Government is doing on stay put advice in fire safety policy.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273832","273832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137219","2019-07-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with mobile phone network operators on improving coverage across Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273781","273781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137220","2019-07-10","Department for Transport","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many days the A14 Orwell Bridge has been closed in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273775","273775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137221","2019-07-10","Department for Education","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of 16 and 17 year old children awaiting an in need assessment in 2017-18.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273799","273799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137222","2019-07-10","Department for Education","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assistance his Department is providing to (a) children in care and (b) care leavers who are non-UK EU citizens to regularise their status in the UK through the EU settlement scheme.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273800","273800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137223","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department plans to issue national guidance to local authorities on tackling child criminal exploitation through county lines.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273801","273801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137224","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department plans to create a statutory definition of child criminal exploitation.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273802","273802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137225","2019-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to inform the public of the (a) need to de-carbonise heat and (b) potential changes required to domestic appliances.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273751","273751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137226","2019-07-10","Treasury","2019-07-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to increase support for parents who care for disabled children at home.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273782","273782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137227","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2019 to Question 271379, how many people were extradited from the UK to the US for non-violent crimes in each year from 2003 to 2012.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273740","273740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137230","2019-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to facilitate cross-governmental co-operation on tackling climate change.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911861","911861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137503","2019-07-11","Women and Equalities","2019-07-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she has taken to promote LGBTQ+ rights in the religious community.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 274440","274440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136048","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of increasing local housing allowance to the 30th percentile point for current market rents in each size category of dwelling.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271443","271443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136405","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent steps her Department has taken to increase public understanding of invisible disabilities.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272164","272164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136629","2019-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with soft drinks manufacturers on phasing out single-use plastic bottles.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272774","272774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136636","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the level of central Government funding required to enable local authorities to assist in meeting the Government’s target of halving rough sleeping by 2022 and eliminating it by 2027.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272720","272720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136860","2019-07-09","Treasury","2019-07-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what programmes will be funded through the £10 million allocated for fisheries innovation South West announced in Budget 2018.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273381","273381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136861","2019-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans to allocate funding to ensure the future of Brixham Harbour.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273382","273382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136862","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many post office branches advertised on the Post Office business opportunities website are (a) hard to place, (b) stranded branches and (c) stuck offices.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273425","273425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136863","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been detained in hospital under the Mental Health Act 1983 at (a) NHS and (b) private facilities in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273364","273364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136864","2019-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic steps he has taken with the Nigerian Government to help prevent the alleged funding of supply of weapons to terrorist groups by the oil industry in that country.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273311","273311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136865","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his Answer 11 June 2019 to Question 258961 on Boilers, whether the variables listed in that answer apply to the heating system and not the boiler.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273312","273312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136866","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2019 to Question 266632 on Boilers, if he will publish the (a) country and (b) organisation that each of the 34 members of the CEN committee comes from.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273313","273313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136867","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his Answer or 19 June 2019 to Question 266634, Boilers, what information his Department holds on any requirements to disable or remove any parts of the boiler in order to perform or complete the test.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273314","273314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136868","2019-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's paper, Water conservation report,  action taken and planned by Government to encourage the conservation of water, published in December 2018, when he plans to publish the consultation paper on water efficiency.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273498","273498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136869","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that public health funding is increased as part of the Government’s spending review.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273408","273408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136870","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that communities and local authorities work together to provide adequate numbers of affordable homes in rural areas when drawing up Local Plans and Neighbourhood Plans.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273315","273315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136871","2019-07-09","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, in the absence of devolved government, if she will consult on the potential merits of introducing a children’s funeral fund in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273337","273337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136872","2019-07-09","Cabinet Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his policy is on adopting environmental, social, and governance criteria in relation to civil service pension funds.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273389","273389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136874","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure people have access to dental care in the area they live.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273499","273499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136875","2019-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of birds slaughtered without stunning under a shackle line system are required to be individually assessed for signs of consciousness by a food business operator before birds progress to the next stage of production.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273369","273369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136876","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the sale price was of each (a) magistrates' court building, (b) youth court and (c) Crown court sold in the last two years.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273363","273363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136877","2019-07-09","Department for Education","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to implement the recommendations of A better deal: boosting competition to bring down bills for families and firms, November 2015, Cm 9164, in relation to school uniforms.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273500","273500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136878","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the availability of school uniform grants in each local authority in England.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273501","273501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136879","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what is his policy on placing his Department’s guidance on school uniform on a statutory footing.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273502","273502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136880","2019-07-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what account he has taken of his Department's report entitled What is the relationship between public and private investment in science, research and innovation published in July 2015, in determining future funding for science.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273388","273388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136881","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's announcement of 3 July 2019 on specialist life vests to improve fishing safety, how much of the additional £700,000 in funding will be allocated to the Scottish Government to administer safety training.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273395","273395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136882","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's announcement of 3 July 2019 on specialist life vests to improve fishing safety, what proportion of the additional £700,000 in funding will be allocated to the Scottish Government to administer.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273396","273396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136883","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's announcement of 3 July 2019 on specialist life vests to improve fishing safety, how many personal floatation devices fitted with locator beacons will be made available to Scottish fishermen.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273397","273397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136884","2019-07-09","Cabinet Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what changes were introduced in postal and proxy voting procedures for the 2019 European Parliamentary Elections compared to previous (a) European or (b) General Elections.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273338","273338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136885","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the UK will continue to be a part of the European Reference Network for rare diseases after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273339","273339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136886","2019-07-09","Department for International Trade","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2019 to Question 268564, if he will publish the (a) number, (b) type and (c) item code for (i) all extant licences for military goods to each of Saudi Arabia's coalition partners and (ii) any such licences under review as a result of the Court of Appeal Judgment of 20 June 2019; and what the timetable is for the completion of those reviews.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273478","273478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136887","2019-07-09","Department for International Trade","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the total value of standard individual export licences for arms exports to (a) Saudi Arabia,  (b) the UAE and (c) other coalition partners that were still valid on 20 June 2019.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273479","273479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136888","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timescale is for the review of the financial eligibility thresholds for people seeking legal aid.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273455","273455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136889","2019-07-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress the Government has made in ensuring that non-compliant fire doors in housing are replaced.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273456","273456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136890","2019-07-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what financial support the Government is making available to the housing industry to ensure that non-compliant fire doors are replaced.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273457","273457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136891","2019-07-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance the Government has issued to the housing industry on the replacement of non-compliant fire doors.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273458","273458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136892","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to help reduce the number of women smoking during pregnancy.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273483","273483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136893","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to promote the benefits of adult learning in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273484","273484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136894","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants have been employed in secondary schools in Nottinghamshire in each of the last three years for which data are available.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273485","273485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136895","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending VAT relief to community interest companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273430","273430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136896","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish the (a) forecast number of new claims for universal credit between April 2018 and March 2019, (b) date on which that forecast was made and (c) actual number of new claims made during that period.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273365","273365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136897","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether requests were made for Ministers to meet with Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe ahead of (a) his visit to Tehran on 19 November 2018 and (b) the Minister of State for the Middle East and North Africa's visit to Tehran on 22-23 June 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273366","273366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136898","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to secure a British consular visit to assess the health and wellbeing of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273367","273367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136899","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance his Department can provide to Richard Ratcliffe to obtain a visa to visit his wife, Nazanin Zaghari Ratcliffe, in prison in Iran.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273368","273368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136900","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many referrals have been received by his Department under sub-section 244 of the National Health Service Act 2006 since the implementation of the Health and Social Care Act 2012 by (a) local authority and (b) clinical commissioning group where such a request has been passed to the Independent Reconfiguration Panel; and what the outcome was of any decision.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273476","273476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136901","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will bring forward legislative proposals on a regulatory category medicinal cannabis.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273329","273329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136902","2019-07-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of opportunities advertised on the Post Office business opportunities website are for (a) new branches and (b) branches where the current postmaster is seeking a replacement.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273426","273426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136903","2019-07-09","Treasury","2019-07-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will place in the Library a copy of the detailed methodology used to calculate Equitable Life payment scheme compensation payments.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273354","273354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136904","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many pedestrians were involved in road traffic accidents while using a mobile phone in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273297","273297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136905","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many contracts his Department has awarded to Serco since July 2013; and what the value is of those contracts.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273402","273402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136906","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many contracts his Department has awarded to Serco since July 2013; and what the value is of those contracts.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273403","273403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136907","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many contracts his Department has awarded to Serco since July 2013; and what the value is of those contracts.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273404","273404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136908","2019-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on the continued harassment and detention of human rights lawyers in China since the mass arrest of lawyers and their colleagues on 8 July 2015.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273374","273374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136909","2019-07-09","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many contracts her Department has awarded to Serco since July 2013; and what the value is of those contracts.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273405","273405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136910","2019-07-09","Department for Transport","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many contracts his Department has awarded to Serco since July 2013; and what the value is of those contracts.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273406","273406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136911","2019-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Chinese Government on the health of imprisoned human rights lawyer Wang Quanzhang.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273375","273375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136912","2019-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the (a) financial implications and (b) net effect on jobs of the closure of benefit processing centres in London.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273307","273307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136913","2019-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many requests for diplomatic access to the Tibet Autonomous Region were submitted by Government officials (a) in the UK and (b) working at the British embassy in Beijing in each of the last five years; and how many of those requests were granted.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273298","273298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136914","2019-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Government made any requests to open a mission in Lhasa.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273299","273299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136915","2019-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what restrictions have been placed on British tourists and officials who have been granted access to the Tibet Autonomous Region in recent years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273300","273300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136916","2019-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what restrictions the UK Government places on diplomats from China travelling in the UK; and who is responsible for those diplomats.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273301","273301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136917","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which universities (a) Philip Augar and (b) members of the associated panel visited during the Post-18 review of education and funding.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273353","273353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136918","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2019 to Question 250476, when he plans to start the recruitment process for a new chair of the Migration Advisory Committee when Professor Manning’s term ends in November 2019.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273370","273370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136919","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria was used to appoint the members of the Family Justice panel; and what gender balance requirements were applied.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273302","273302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136920","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answers of 20 June 2019 to Questions 265420, 265421 and 265422 on Extradition: USA, for what reason the figures are collected from local government level and not held centrally.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273322","273322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136921","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many extradition requests have been made by the UK for US citizens in each year since 2014; and how many of those requests were (a) successful and (b) remain outstanding.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273323","273323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136922","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many dental practices have closed in (a) Enfield and (b) London since 2010.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273304","273304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136923","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS dentists are accepting patients in Enfield.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273305","273305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136924","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the viability of the Verify scheme; and what role the private sector is planned to play in the future of that scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273377","273377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136925","2019-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to 25 Year Environment Plan published on 11 January 2018, what estimate he has made of the additional financial resources required to deliver the commitments made in that plan for the financial years (a) 2019-20 (b) 2020-21 and (c) 2021-22.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273465","273465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136926","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether there are specific planning requirements for building (a) schools and (b) hospitals in air pollution hotspots.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273466","273466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136927","2019-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding has been allocated to support ultra-low emission zones in England in the (a) current and (b) previous financial year.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273467","273467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136928","2019-07-08","Scotland Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273326","273326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136929","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue accrued to the public purse in Vehicle Excise Duty on cars registered in London in each of the last three financial years; and what estimate he has made of the amount of that revenue which will accrue to the public purse in the next two financial years.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273468","273468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136930","2019-07-08","Wales Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273327","273327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136931","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Clean Air Strategy 2019, what guidance he has issued to ports on developing effective and targeted air quality strategies; and what recommendations the rail industry has made on phasing out diesel-only trains by 2040.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273469","273469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136932","2019-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Clean Air Strategy 2019, how much of the £3.5 billion allocated to tackle poor air quality through cleaner road transport has been allocated to projects in London.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273470","273470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136933","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Clean Air Strategy 2019, what progress he has made in reviewing current uses of red diesel to ensure that its lower cost is not discouraging the transition to cleaner alternatives.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273471","273471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136934","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the July 2017 tobacco control plan for England, when the Government plans to announce a date for achieving its smokefree generation target of smoking prevalence at 5 per cent or below.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273383","273383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136935","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that tobacco companies have no involvement in (a) smoking cessation services and (b) public health campaigns.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273384","273384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136936","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support the 2.3 million children estimated by the Children's Commissioner to be growing up with a vulnerable family background.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273477","273477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136937","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of training for NHS staff on diagnosing and treating alcohol abuse.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273324","273324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136938","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2019 to Question 267162, whether he has made additional funding available to support new alliances with military charities to help offenders who are veterans of the armed forces.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273306","273306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136939","2019-07-09","Department for Transport","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will allocate funding to (a) improve road safety and (b) ensure sufficient capacity on the A19 in respect of traffic created by the Jade Business Park in Murton and the South of Seaham Garden Village.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273378","273378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136940","2019-07-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to (a) improve housing standards for older people living in the rental sector and (b) ensure the adequacy of that housing.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273348","273348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136941","2019-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has in place to help people in receipt of universal credit with the cost of childcare over the summer holidays.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273325","273325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136942","2019-07-09","Prime Minister","2019-07-04","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2019 to Question 270779 on Climate Change and with reference to with reference to her oral contribution of 26 June 2019, Official Report, column 650, what the evidential basis is for the statement that a regret motion in the House of Lords has the effect of blocking a Statutory Instrument.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273409","273409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136943","2019-07-09","Department for Education","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to update the April 2016 Regional Vision Statement for the West Midlands and publish a new statement.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273482","273482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136944","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he is taking steps to ensure that gay and bisexual men accessing the Gate Clinic at Kent and Canterbury Hospital have access to PrEP; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273480","273480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136945","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he is having discussions with the Crawley Sexual Health Clinic on accommodating some of the outstanding 40 per cent of PrEP impact trial places.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273376","273376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136946","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of maternal postnatal checks in identifying maternal mental health problems.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273308","273308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136947","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the effectiveness of GPs in identifying and treating perinatal mental health problems in mothers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273309","273309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136948","2019-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent steps she has taken to ensure that older people receive the financial support they are entitled to.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273349","273349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136949","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent progress the Government has made in ensuring that children receive regular dental examinations and treatment.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273341","273341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136950","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on dental health of water fluoride concentration.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273342","273342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136951","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to improve dental care for the elderly in care homes.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273343","273343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136952","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of foetal alcohol spectrum disorders.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273344","273344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136953","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to ensure that clinical commissioning groups commission services for (a) preventing and (b) diagnosing foetal alcohol spectrum disorders; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273345","273345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136954","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to reduce the time it takes to go through the adoption process.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273346","273346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136955","2019-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to protect children from the effect of toxic air on their health.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273347","273347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136956","2019-07-08","Cabinet Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Departments have introduced the cycle to work scheme.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273400","273400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136957","2019-07-08","Cabinet Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government has plans to implement the cycle to work scheme across all Departments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273401","273401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136958","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the next stage of its Challenge on Dementia builds on the progress made by (a) the Dementia Research Institute and (b) other such initiatives.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273372","273372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136959","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people are employed on a full-time equivalent basis in the (a) cancer, (b) cardiovascular disease, (c) stroke care, (d) diabetes, (e) respiratory disease, (f) adult mental health services and (g) alzheimer’s and dementia care teams.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273373","273373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136960","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made in securing the release of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe following his meeting with Iranian officials on 23 June 2019.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273355","273355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136961","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for human rights in parts of Myanmar of a reported block on internet access in that country.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273356","273356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136962","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the report by the Armed Conflict Location and Event Data project on 18 June 2019, what estimate he has made of the number of deaths resulting from the current conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273357","273357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136963","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of potential links between the Nordkreuz network in Germany and extremist groups in the UK.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273358","273358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136964","2019-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to support staff of William Hill following the announcement that 700 branches will close; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273427","273427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136965","2019-07-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to support William Hill and its staff following the announcement that 700 branches will close; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273428","273428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136966","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent steps his Department has taken to reduce homelessness.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273503","273503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136967","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Government report entitled Process evaluation of the Global Positioning System (GPS) Electronic Monitoring Pilot: Qualitative findings, published 16 February 2019 whether the research in that report covers both male and female offenders.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273385","273385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136968","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugees from Yemen the UK (a) accepted asylum applications from and (b) granted asylum to in (i) 2014, (ii) 2015, (iii) 2016, (iv) 2017, (v) 2018, and (vi) 2019 to 4 July 2019.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273359","273359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136969","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to (a) disseminate and (b) monitor the implementation of the police guidance entitled Managing vulnerability: women, fact pack.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273386","273386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136970","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to safeguard 16 and 17 year-olds from being groomed by adults in a position of power and influence.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273504","273504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136971","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he bring forward a new protection of civilians strategy to help safeguard children in conflict zones throughout the world.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273495","273495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136972","2019-07-09","Treasury","2019-07-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy on the soft drinks industry levy of research by Cancer Research UK linking obesity and cancer.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273450","273450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136973","2019-07-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to prevent young people from becoming addicted to gambling.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273451","273451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136974","2019-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times the Child Maintenance Group has registered the maintenance debt of a non-resident parent with credit rating agencies in the last year.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273429","273429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136975","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department plans to respond to the correspondence of 28 May 2019 from the hon. Member for Glasgow Central to the Under-Secretary of State for Mental Health, Inequalities and Suicide Prevention on food for special medical purposes.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273407","273407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136976","2019-07-09","Treasury","2019-07-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money from the public purse has been spent on the creation of the new 50p coin to commemorate the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273452","273452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136977","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many non-British employees are employed (a) full time and (b) part-time by the Royal Mint.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273453","273453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136978","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent progress the Government has made on the 2030 Energy Strategy.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273454","273454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136979","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full-time equivalent employees there were in UK Visas and Immigration and its predecessor bodies in each of the last 10 financial years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273410","273410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136980","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were employed by UK Visas and Immigration in assessing and processing claims for asylum in each of the last 10 financial years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273411","273411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136981","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding the Government is allocating towards meeting its targets for walking and cycling.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273330","273330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136982","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people at Full Time Equivalent have been employed to establish and administer the system for compensation for victims of the Windrush scandal in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273412","273412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136983","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for visitor visas have been received, by nationality of country of origin, in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273413","273413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136984","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which Government Department is responsible for enforcing The Trading Schemes Act 1996.","Biography information for James Heappey","James Heappey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273472","273472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136985","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase supplies of the drug Montelukast.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273473","273473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136986","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department is having with the Kings Chambers clinic in Cambridgeshire on that clinic accepting the remaining 40 per cent of allocated places on the PrEP impact trial.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273505","273505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136987","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications there have been for visitor visas for the purposes of visiting family, by country of origin of applicant, in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273414","273414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136988","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average ratio is of detainees to detention officers at (a) Colnbrook and (b) Harmondsworth immigration removal centres in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273415","273415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136989","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to increase the take-up of pension credit among people without internet access.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273486","273486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136990","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average amount of unclaimed pension credit is per eligible claimant in the constituency of Lincoln in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273487","273487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136991","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the ratio of detainees to detention officers in immigration removal centres that is considered to be safe.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273416","273416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136992","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of potentially eligible claimants of pension credit who have not claimed that benefit in the constituency of Lincoln in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273488","273488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136993","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to engage with local organisations in Lincoln to increase the take-up of pension credit in that city.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273489","273489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136994","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many hours per day are detainees in (a) Harmondsworth and (b) Colnbrook immigration removal centres routinely locked in their rooms.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273417","273417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136995","2019-07-09","Department for Education","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the affordability of school uniforms for people on low incomes.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273490","273490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136996","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the highest number of detainees was in (a) Harmondsworth and (c) Colnbrook immigration removal centres in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273418","273418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136997","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support his Department provides to help people with agoraphobia to live independently.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273491","273491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136998","2019-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to authorise the General Licence for land designated as (a) Special Areas of Conservation and (b) Special Protection Areas.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273303","273303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136999","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date the Government plans to publish its formal response to the public consultation on a new legal duty to support multi-agency action to tackle serious violence.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273463","273463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137000","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many mental healthcare professionals are employed in (a) Harmondsworth and (b) Colnbrook immigration removal centres.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273419","273419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137001","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to reduce the number of people held in UK immigration removal centres.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273420","273420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137002","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to change the provision of immigration removal centres in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273421","273421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137003","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have applied for compensation from the Windrush compensation scheme to date.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273422","273422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137004","2019-07-09","Department for Education","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding to support breakfast clubs in primary schools.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273492","273492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137005","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the effect of a wrong decision being made denying a person the right to re-enter the UK under the Windrush scandal on eligibility for benefits and tax credits which require residency in the UK for the last two years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273423","273423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137006","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for compensation by people affected by the Windrush scandal have been successful, and how many of those successful applicants have received compensation.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273424","273424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137007","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who decided not to pursue an appeal for personal independence payments due to the length of the waiting time for an appeal.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273493","273493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137008","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of whether the HM Courts and Tribunals service has the capacity to reduce the waiting time for an appeal for personal independence payments.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273494","273494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137009","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the threat posed to Israel by cross-border tunnels dug by Hamas.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Djanogly","Mr Jonathan Djanogly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273340","273340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137010","2019-07-09","Department for Transport","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions Great Western trains ran with reduced carriage numbers as a result of a shortage of sets in each month since the introduction of the new trains in October 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273317","273317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137011","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase BAME recruitment to the stem cell registry.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273333","273333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137012","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of children in (a) Ashfield, (b) Rushcliffe and (c) England have been classified as (i) overweight or (ii) obese in reception class in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273360","273360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137013","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of children in (a) Ashfield, (b) Rushcliffe and (c) England have been classified as (i) overweight or (ii) obese in school year six in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273361","273361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137014","2019-07-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the oral contribution of the hon. Member for Warwick and Leamington of 13 June 2019, Official Report, column 860, whether his Department plans to adopt the target to build 155,000 social rented homes a year with at least 100,000 being council homes.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273481","273481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137015","2019-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions her Department's assessors have formally questioned a prognosis given by health professionals in DS1500 forms in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273334","273334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137016","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of adults in (a) Ashfield, (b) Rushcliffe and (c) England have been classified as (i) overweight or (ii) obese in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273362","273362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137017","2019-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment claims made under special rules and supported by a clinician via a DS1500 were rejected by her Department in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273335","273335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137018","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the proportion of people caring for someone at the end of their life who experience financial hardship.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273336","273336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137019","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the health risks of rubber crumb on artificial sports pitches.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273474","273474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137020","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of disabled car parking spaces at each assessment centre for (a) personal independence payments and (b) employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273387","273387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137021","2019-07-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has received representations from health experts on the health risks of rubber crumbs from artificial sports pitches.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273475","273475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137022","2019-07-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report by the Children's Commissioner entitled vulnerable children: time for action, published in July 2019, what steps his Department is taking to support children’s social care services to meet their statutory duties.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273350","273350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137024","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent steps she has taken to improve support in the workplace for sufferers of rheumatoid arthritis and osteoarthritis.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273371","273371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137025","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many properties new asylum-accommodation provider Mears has procured in the North East; how many service-users can be accommodated in those properties; and the number of service users in the North East for whom new accommodation has not been procured.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273390","273390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137026","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department will take in the event that asylum-accommodation provider Mears is unable to procure sufficient housing stock to accommodate service users  in the North East.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273391","273391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137027","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers in the North East will be required to leave their properties during the transition to a new accommodation provider.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273392","273392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137028","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps his Department is taking to increase fire safety in (a) care homes and (b) other residential blocks.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273379","273379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137029","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support the Government provides to vulnerable asylum-seekers in the North East in the transition period between asylum accommodation contracts; and how the needs of those service-users are assessed.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273393","273393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137030","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether fire evacuation guidance issued by his Department includes information on the additional time required to evacuate vulnerable people.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273380","273380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137031","2019-07-09","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how his Department plans to record complaints by service users during the transition period between asylum accommodation contracts; and whether that information will be made public.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273394","273394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137032","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of funding PrEP through section 7a of  Public Health funding from April 2020.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273310","273310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137033","2019-07-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all elderly people live in decent and accessible homes.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273459","273459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137034","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to ensure that higher accessibility standards for elderly people are incorporated into the current review of the decent homes standard; and how that standard will be applied to estate refurbishment programmes in order to meet the needs of an ageing population.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273460","273460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137035","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he made of the value of each court that his Department intended to sell prior to each sale.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273431","273431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137036","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Health and Social Care on integrating health and care needs into planning frameworks and strategies.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273461","273461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137037","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of uprating local housing allowance rates from April 2020; and if she plans to bring forward proposals to extend the current exemption from the shared accommodation rate for people who have lived in a homeless hostel to include people aged 18 to 25 years-old.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273462","273462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137038","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of procuring services for prisons in the private sector.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273432","273432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137039","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of prison education is provided under the dynamic purchasing system in each prison.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273433","273433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137040","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding his Department has provided to law centres in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273434","273434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137041","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of law centres in each local authority area since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273435","273435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137042","2019-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the use of Tazir laws to facilitate punishment against members of the Baha’i community in Iran; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273318","273318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137043","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what statistics his Department holds on trends in the proportion of people who receive a custodial sentence as a child and then go on to receive a custodial sentence as an adult in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273436","273436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137044","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the accessibility of the planned small claims portal for people without internet access.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273437","273437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137045","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what protections will be in place in the planned small claims portal to ensure that the rights of minors and vulnerable people are safeguarded.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273438","273438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137046","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2019 to Question 269813, for what reason information is not collated in relation to children.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273439","273439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137047","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether (a) salary and (b) pension contributions for HM Courts and Tribunals Service staff are determined by length of service.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273440","273440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137048","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many victims of sexual abuse have had their applications for compensation from the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme rejected because they had an unspent criminal conviction in the first six months of 2019.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273441","273441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137049","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total number of days of detached duty worked was in each of the prisons in the 10 Prisons Project in (a) the last six months of 2017 and (b) the last six months of 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273442","273442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137050","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of prisoners in each of the prisons in the 10 Prisons Project was in (a) the last six months of 2017 and (b) the last six months of 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273443","273443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137051","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average amount above Certified Normal Accommodation was in each of the prisons where performance was found to be of serious concern in the Annual Prison Performance Ratings 2017-18 in (a) the last six months of 2017 and (b) the last six months of 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273444","273444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137052","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of prisoners was in each of the prisons where performance was found to be of serious concern in the Annual Prison Performance Ratings 2017-18 in (a) the last six months of 2017 and (b) the last six months of 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273445","273445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137053","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of prison officers in post was in each prison where performance was found to be of serious concern in the Annual Prison Performance Ratings 2017-18 in the last six months of (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273446","273446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137054","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total additional capital spend on physical security was in each of the prisons where performance was found to be of serious concern in the Annual Prison Performance Ratings 2017/18 in the last six months of (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273447","273447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137055","2019-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time to complete a single employment tribunal claim was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273448","273448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137056","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Government remains on track to achieve its target of 300,000 new homes a year by 2025.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273351","273351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137057","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, by what year will each person entitled to an employment tribunal fee refund have received one.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273449","273449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137058","2019-07-08","Department for International Trade","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will reassess the potential merits of adding imports of eggs and egg products to the tariffs list.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273319","273319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137059","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans his Department has to ensure that the egg industry has access to migrant workers after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273320","273320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137060","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons SHINE sexual health services at Salford are not open for gay and bisexual men on the PrEP impact trial.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273398","273398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137061","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to encourage EU nationals working in the agricultural and food production sectors to remain in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273321","273321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137062","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that gay and bisexual men accessing the SHINE clinic in Salford have access to PrEP.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273399","273399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137063","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Chief Executive of HMRC on providing extra support to people new to self-assessment in order that they understand the deadlines they must meet and the steps they must take.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273352","273352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137064","2019-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many trees will be planted in order to reach the Government’s target of 11 million trees in each year from July 2019 to the end of this Parliament.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273331","273331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137066","2019-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2019 to Question 268974, if his Department will impose a moratorium on development on peatlands pending the publication of his Department's England Peat Strategy.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Sir Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273328","273328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137067","2019-07-09","Department for Education","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of (a) primary and (b) secondary schools (i) are eligible for and (ii) receive the full amount of funding under the sparsity element of the national funding formula; and what the average amount was that each eligible school received in the latest period for which data is available.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273496","273496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137068","2019-07-09","Department for Education","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many mainstream (a) primary and (b) secondary schools received a lump sum payment, and for how many schools that lump sum represented (i) less than one per cent, (ii) 2 to five per cent; (iii) five to 10 per cent, (iv) 10 to 20 per cent, (v) 20 to 30 per cent, (vi) 30 to 40 per cent, and (vii) over 50 per cent of their total income.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273497","273497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137111","2019-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to facilitate cross-governmental co-operation on tackling climate change.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911847","911847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137112","2019-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to facilitate cross-governmental co-operation on tackling climate change.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911859","911859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136507","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 08 May 2019 to Question 249959 on Tobacco, if his Department will establish a publicly accessible central record of contacts made between departmental officials and tobacco stakeholders; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272893","272893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136508","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the UN General Assembly Resolution of 22 May 2019 on the Advisory Opinion of the International Court of Justice on the legal consequences of the separation of the Chagos Archipelago from Mauritius in 1965, if he will support the Chagos Refugees Group and Mauritian Government in arranging a visit to the Chagos Archipelago for UK-based Chagossians after the six month time period set out in that Resolution.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272901","272901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136509","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provisions exist under the one name for all policy for citizens with dual nationality to maintain legal recognition of previous or original names.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272919","272919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136510","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2019 to Question 266803 on Taxation: Electronic Government, when he plans to open a consultation on proceeding with Making Tax Digital for Corporation Tax.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272880","272880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136511","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a)  self-employed and (b) other carers that work with (i) elderly and (ii) vulnerable people are DBS checked.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272918","272918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136512","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June to Question 263698, whether Big Ideas is contractually required to ensure the impartiality of its public engagement work on the proposed use of Victoria Tower Gardens for the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272745","272745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136513","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's publication, Apprenticeship and levy statistics: December 2018, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the reduction in Level 2 and Level 3 apprenticeship starts of 32 per cent between 2015-16 and 2017-18.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272828","272828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136514","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to announce the outcome of his review of the Disclosure and Barring Service.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272744","272744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136515","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many post office branches are currently being served by a (a) outreach and (b) mobile service; and how many of those post office branches are awaiting a permanent location.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272881","272881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136516","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2019 to Question 268391, if he will make an estimate of the number of looked-after children placed (a) inside and (b) outside the borough that were reported (i) missing and (ii) away without authorisation in each local authority area in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272767","272767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136517","2019-07-08","Women and Equalities","2019-07-03","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her Department's policies of the recommendations in the report by the charity Guide Dogs entitled, Access denied: a report into the frequency and impact of access refusals on assistance dog owners in 2019, on the establishment of an equality ombudsman.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272844","272844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136518","2019-07-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the uptake of Huawei Cyber Security Evaluation Centre advice and guidance on the risk management of operators.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272941","272941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136519","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to make Changing Places toilets a mandatory requirement for public (a) buildings and (b) spaces.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272920","272920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136520","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to encourage venues with a Changing Places facility to register with the Changing Places Consortium.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272921","272921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136521","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government  what assessment he has made of the effect on disabled people and their ability to leave their homes of the availability of publicly accessible changing and toilet facilities.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272922","272922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136522","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure equitable access to less invasive treatments for structural heart diseases throughout the regions of England.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272771","272771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136523","2019-07-08","Cabinet Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 21 May 2019 to Question 255390, whether strategic oversight for the collection and use of data held by Government departments provided by the cross-government Data Advisory Board, chaired by the Chief Executive of the Civil Service, is a permanent​ arrangement.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272942","272942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136524","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on studies undertaken by the Committee on the Medical Effects of Air Pollutants (COMEAP) on the effects on human health of (a) PM0.1 and (b) PM1.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272727","272727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136525","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints have been submitted to the Financial Ombudsman Service in each of the last three years; what the average wait was for a final decision in each of those years; how many complaints are currently outstanding; and what the current average waiting time is for a final decision.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272805","272805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136526","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will hold discussions with his counterparts in the devolved regions on recent changes in rates of cancer involving children to ensure reductions in all parts of the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272769","272769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136527","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Department of Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings in The evaluation of Minimum Unit Pricing (MUP) for alcohol report, published by NHS Scotland in June 2019, that alcohol sales in Scotland have dropped during the last year, while they have risen in England and Wales.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272936","272936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136528","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Department of Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 3 September 2018 to Question 169474 on Alcoholic Drinks: minimum unit pricing, when Public Health England’s review into the impact of minimum unit pricing of alcohol will be published.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272937","272937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136529","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2019 to Question number 268957 on High Rise Flats: Insulation, what non-ACM cladding is being tested; when the results will be known; and how many buildings are estimated to be affected.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272722","272722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136530","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit payments were subject to a deduction, excluding sanctions, in the latest month for which data is available.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272806","272806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136531","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the proportion of universal credit claimants who have a deduction for any arrears in the first month of their claim for the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272807","272807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136532","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment she has made of the future of the UK-Saudi defence relationship.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272884","272884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136533","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of funding allocated to her Department.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272885","272885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136534","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment she has made of the security situation in Iran.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272886","272886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136535","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment she has made of trends in the number of aircraft in the RAF fleet.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272887","272887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136536","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment she has made of the UK’s ability to defend itself against cyber-attacks.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272888","272888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136537","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on Hamas's rule in Gaza.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272812","272812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136538","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on reports set out in the BBC documentary, One day in Gaza, that Hamas transported Gazan civilians to violent areas on the border with Israel last year.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272813","272813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136539","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the (a) list of stations nominated for the latest round of Access for all funding and (b) final weighted score of all stations in consecutive order after being assessed against the criteria (i) nationally, (ii) regionally and (iii) by franchise in the Library.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272829","272829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136540","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department plans to publish a response to the consultation on Further advertising restrictions for products high in fat, salt and sugar, published on 18 March 2019.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272950","272950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136541","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timeframe is for the implementation of the recommendations in chapter two of the Childhood Obesity Plan, published in June 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272951","272951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136542","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data her Department holds on the proportion of (a) construction workers and (b) the general population with silicosis.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272923","272923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136543","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of terminally-ill people with  silicosis.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272924","272924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136544","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what evidence his Department holds on trends in the level of co-morbidity in people with silicosis.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272925","272925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136545","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether occupational health nurses take the occupational history of their client into account when assessing people who are showing signs of lung disease.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272926","272926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136546","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress her Department is making on the (a) construction and (b) commissioning of offshore patrol vessels for deployment in the South West.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272894","272894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136547","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the implications of fighting between Hamas and Fatah for a two-state solution between Israel and the Palestinians.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272916","272916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136548","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how feedback from presenting officers in personal independence payment tribunals is used to inform future decision making on personal independence payment cases.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272897","272897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136549","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to tackle the loop-hole which allows people to register second homes as Air B&B facilities.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272728","272728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136550","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the quality of the feedback received from presenting officers on personal independence payment tribunals.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272898","272898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136551","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to introduce an affordable homes target for rural England into Homes England’s objectives.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272729","272729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136552","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps (a) his Department and (b) agencies of his Department have taken to support the National Pollinator Strategy on (i) roads (ii) railway lines.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272930","272930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136553","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS dentists are currently accepting patients in (a) Plymouth and (b) Devon and Cornwall.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272949","272949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136554","2019-07-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much Big Lottery funding was allocated to Mansfield constituency in each of the last two years for which data are available.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272931","272931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136555","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2019 to Question 269008 on Pupils: Sanitary Protection, what criteria his Department uses to assess the environmental friendliness of those products.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272791","272791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136556","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Mansfield constituency received cold weather payments in each of the last two winter periods.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272932","272932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136557","2019-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken in the Midlands to support pollinators.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272933","272933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136558","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of homeless people under the age of 25.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272934","272934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136559","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what account is taken of income from compensation payments under the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme in disability benefit calculations.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272845","272845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136560","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether a cap is placed on compensation for lost earnings paid as part of the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272846","272846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136561","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether funding will be allocated to support adult learners taking T Levels.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272917","272917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136562","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many contracts his Department has awarded to G4S since July 2013; and what the value was of each of those contracts.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272874","272874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136563","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps she is taking to ensure the modernising defence programme is coordinated with the NATO defence planning process.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272778","272778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136564","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence,  what estimate she has made of the (a) number and (b) value of contracts her Department has awarded to G4S since July 2013.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272875","272875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136565","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) value of contracts his Department has awarded to G4S since July 2013.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272876","272876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136566","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) value of contracts his Department has awarded to G4S since July 2013.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272877","272877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136567","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of British national overseas passport holders.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272882","272882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136568","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) value of contracts his Department has awarded to G4S since July 2013.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272878","272878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136569","2019-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to set up tree planting schemes (a) nationally and (b) in Gloucestershire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272732","272732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136570","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps she is taking to improve the interoperability of UK and US armed forces.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272779","272779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136571","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the value of apprenticeship levy funds expiring from employers' accounts was in June 2019; and what plans the Government has for those funds.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272836","272836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136572","2019-07-08","Department for International Trade","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to paragraph 141 of the Court of Appeal judgment in R (on the application of Campaign Against Arms Trade) v The Secretary of State for International Trade, for what reason his Department's policy was not to assess past violations of international humanitarian law by the Saudi-led coalition in Yemen.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272914","272914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136573","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment she has made of the effect of the suspension of arms sales to Saudi Arabia on UK contractors assisting the Saudi-led coalition in Saudi Arabia .","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272716","272716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136574","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2019 to Question 267154, what additional steps the Government has taken to ensure that all UK traders that only trade with the EU hold a UK Economic Operator Registration and Identification (EORI) number.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272717","272717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136575","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to allow the Northern Rail franchise to be publicly run.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272940","272940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136576","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps she is taking to reduce the affordability gap between the equipment plan and her Department's budget.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272780","272780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136577","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2019 to Question 270341 on Personal Independence Payment, what improvements to processing mandatory reconsiderations have been made since her Department adopted the quality-driven approach.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272815","272815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136578","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of ensuring that new gas boilers are hydrogen-ready.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272772","272772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136579","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish a response to the petition entitled, Give schools the money they need, that was presented to the House on 5 June 2019.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272792","272792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136580","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of hotels and hostels by local authority which are (a) below and (b) above 18 metres in height that have high pressure laminate cladding.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272794","272794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136581","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending the roll out of the HPV vaccine to boys over the age of 13.","Biography information for Suella Braverman","Suella Braverman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272892","272892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136582","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the nuclear industry on the development of new nuclear power stations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272733","272733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136583","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of student accommodation blocks (a) below and (b) above 18 metres in height in each local authority areas that have high pressure laminate cladding.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272795","272795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136584","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department plans to publish the pay award for prison officers following the recommendations made by the Public Sector Pay Review Board.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272768","272768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136585","2019-07-08","Cabinet Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has plans to implement the Law Commission’s recommendation to consolidate the UK’s electoral laws into a single, consistent legislative framework governing all elections.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272740","272740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136586","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of training for prison officers working with women with a mental health need.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272741","272741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136587","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of hospitals by local authority which are (a) below and (b) above 18 metres in height that have high pressure laminate cladding.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272796","272796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136588","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of care homes by local authority which are (a) below and (b) above 18 metres in height that have high pressure laminate cladding.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272797","272797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136589","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Office, what steps he is taking to expedite security clearance for Afghan interpreters formerly employed by UK Armed Forces in Afghanistan to be relocated to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272742","272742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136590","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure new builds are meeting fire safety requirements.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272798","272798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136591","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage secondary schools and their pupils to take part in student exchange programmes with schools in other countries.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272743","272743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136592","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of reports that Iran has quadrupled its production of low-enriched uranium.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272883","272883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136593","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2019 to Question 270440 on Schools: Fire Regulations, if he will estimate the number of schools that have combustible timber cladding.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272847","272847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136594","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is her Department's policy that all female benefits claimants are asked whether they are or have been victims of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272899","272899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136595","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the UK (a) retains and (b) attracts highly skilled contractors from the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mark Pawsey","Mark Pawsey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272825","272825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136596","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how the future skills-based immigration system will enable highly skilled contractors from overseas to fill temporary roles on a (a) self-employed and (b) employed basis after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mark Pawsey","Mark Pawsey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272826","272826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136597","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what visa routes will be introduced in the future skills-based immigration system to enable highly skilled contractors from overseas to continue to provide temporary and specialist services in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mark Pawsey","Mark Pawsey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272827","272827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136598","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many dental practices have closed in (a) the UK, (b) Hampshire and (c) Portsmouth since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272927","272927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136599","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average time taken is for NHS England to recommission dental practices following the closure of a practice.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272928","272928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136600","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent trends in dental practice closures in Portsmouth on patient access to dental services in that city.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272929","272929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136601","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to tackle homophobic, biphobic and transphobic hate crimes.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272837","272837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136602","2019-07-08","Department for International Trade","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to tackle the concerns of export and import businesses in North east England on the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272838","272838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136603","2019-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support farmers in Northumberland in preparation for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272839","272839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136604","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to introduce a scheme for frontier workers to allow them to apply for a Frontier Worker Permit.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272855","272855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136605","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the number of frontier workers resident in the Republic of Ireland but working in Northern Ireland who would be entitled to retain rights under Article 10 (1) (c) of the Agreement on the withdrawal of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland from the European Union and the European Atomic Energy Community.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272856","272856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136606","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether isolated incidents of sleepwalking between the ages of 13 to 18 years old constitutes grounds for a permanent bar to entry to the armed forces.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272816","272816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136607","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who attended the summit for the sub-postmasters pay review which was announced and convened on 13 June 2019; and when that group is next scheduled to meet.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272781","272781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136608","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the terms of reference are of the sub-postmasters pay review.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272782","272782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136609","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timescale is for the sub-postmasters pay review.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272783","272783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136610","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what funding has been made available by the Post Office Ltd to pay for the outcome of the sub-postmasters pay review; and whether that funding is to be additional money to pay sub-postmasters.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272784","272784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136611","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Post Office Ltd will be required to ballot all postmasters on the outcome of the sub-postmasters pay review.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272785","272785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136612","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Subpostmasters Pay Review will ensure that Postmasters will not receive less than the national minimum wage after the deduction of legitimate expenses for each hour they are required to work.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272786","272786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136613","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Subpostmaster Pay Review will include provisions for the Sub Postmaster to be paid for annual leave to conform with the Working Time Regulations.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272787","272787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136614","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Subpostmaster Pay review will include provisions for Subpostmasters to join the Post Office pension scheme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272788","272788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136615","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions officials in his Department have had with officials in the Office for Rail and Road on the development of that organisation’s (a) service standards and (b) strategic objectives in (a) 2017, (b) 2018 and (c) 2019.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272849","272849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136616","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has he made of the adequacy of the statutory remit of the Office for Rail and Road to work on behalf of the interests of rail passengers.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272850","272850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136617","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the (a) effectiveness and (b) value for money of organisations working to protect the interests of consumers throughout the rail industry.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272851","272851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136618","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps his Department has taken to reduce food waste in schools.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272773","272773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136619","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the cost to the public purse has been of prescription fraud in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272864","272864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136620","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money the NHS Business Services Authority has reclaimed from prescription fraud in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272865","272865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136621","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many prescriptions Penalty Charge Notices were withdrawn in the 2017-18 financial year; and much those withdrawals amounted to in fines.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272866","272866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136622","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money the NHS collected from prescription prepayment certificates in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272867","272867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136623","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the administrative cost to the NHS of collecting prescription charges.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272868","272868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136624","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on wellbeing of prescription penalty charge notices.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272869","272869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136625","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the availability of free prescriptions on the medication compliance of patients with a chronic illness.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272870","272870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136626","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has analysed the potential costs and benefits to the NHS of increasing the number of free prescriptions.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272871","272871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136627","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of ringfencing money raised from prescription charges for the development of future medicines.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272872","272872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136628","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the proportion of motor neurone disease sufferers who were able to fast-track access to benefits for the latest period for which figures are available; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272734","272734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136630","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will take steps to make it easier for sufferers of motor neurone disease to access the Special rules for terminal illness; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272735","272735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136631","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals to implement EU Directive 2014/45 to exempt classic cars over 30 years old from periodic roadworthiness testing.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272770","272770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136632","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on his Department’s ability to make decisions on funding for local authorities.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272718","272718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136633","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on his Department’s ability to bring forward and implement the NHS Workforce Plan.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272719","272719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136634","2019-07-08","Department for International Development","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans he has to ensure that human rights are prioritized within his Department's approach to achieving the (a) SDGs and (b) other development outcomes.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272857","272857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136635","2019-07-08","Department for International Development","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his Department’s support to human rights defenders on the ground; and what plans he has to increase that support.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272858","272858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136637","2019-07-08","Department for International Development","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps he will take to ensure that, in line with the UN Statement of Common Understanding, a human-rights based approach is integrated within his Department's development co-operation and programming.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272859","272859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136638","2019-07-08","Department for International Development","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans he has to ensure that his Department's strategic decision-making is explicitly guided by human rights principles and instruments.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272860","272860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136639","2019-07-08","Department for International Development","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps he will take to further integrate human rights considerations into his Department's country-level programming, particularly in human rights priority countries.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272861","272861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136640","2019-07-08","Department for International Development","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if he will take steps to make funding more accessible to civil society organisations in his Department's partner countries.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272862","272862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136641","2019-07-08","Department for International Trade","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which weapons and equipment were licenced for sale to Israel on 18 May 2018.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272863","272863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136642","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders in each Police Force Area were convicted but not sentenced to immediate custody who had (a) 26 to 50 previous convictions, (b) 51 to 75 previous convictions, (c) 76 to 100 previous convictions and (d) over 100 previous convictions in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272944","272944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136643","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders in each Police Force area who were convicted but not sentenced to immediate custody had (a) 26 to 50 previous convictions or cautions, (b) 51 to 75 previous convictions or cautions, (c) 76 to 100 previous convictions or cautions and (d) over 100 previous convictions or cautions, in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272945","272945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136644","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to require Whirlpool to pay compensation to people who personally paid for repairs or replacement of their tumbledryer due to their safety concerns prior to the recall of the product.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272730","272730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136645","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the policy on stopping child benefit for families whose children start apprenticeships on social mobility.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272853","272853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136646","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the policy on stopping child benefit for families whose children start apprenticeships on access to and take up of apprenticeships.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272854","272854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136647","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many pacer trains are serving stations in (a) Leeds, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272820","272820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136648","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential (a) time taken and (b) cost incurred to replace a Type 45 destroyer.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272910","272910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136649","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which rail operators are running pacer trains on their service.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272821","272821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136650","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how long it takes and at what cost to replace an F35 fighter jet.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272911","272911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136651","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how long it would take and at what cost to replace a Typhoon Eurofighter.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272912","272912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136652","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how long it would take and at what cost to replace an Astute class submarine.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272913","272913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136653","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the prevalence of (a) Type 1 and (b) Type 2 diabetes in each local authority area in each of the last three years; what steps his Department is taking to tackle the prevalence of diabetes; and what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his Department's policy on tackling diabetes.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272840","272840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136654","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many pacer trains will be taken out of service by 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272822","272822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136655","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what sanctions will be taken against franchise holders who fail to remove all pacer trains from their rolling stock by 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272823","272823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136656","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when (a) he and (b) his Ministers were made aware that all pacer trains would not be withdrawn from service by rail operators before 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272824","272824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136657","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government expects to publish the findings of the public consultation on restricting exit payments in the public sector.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272902","272902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136658","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to respond to the public consultation on restricting exit payments in the public sector.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272903","272903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136659","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to engage with (a) local authorities and (b) trade unions as part of the public consultation on restricting exit payments in the public sector.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272904","272904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136660","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings by the Overseas Development Institute in their 2018 G7 fossil fuel subsidy scorecard that the UK ranks 7th among G7 nations for transparency in its progress in ending Government support for fossil fuels; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272841","272841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136661","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of an exemption for low-paid workers as part of the Government's plan  to restrict exit payments in the public sector.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272905","272905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136662","2019-07-08","Cabinet Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the capacity of civil service pension funds to engage in shareholder advocacy with the companies in which they have holdings; and to what extent those funds have exercised that capacity to date.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272842","272842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136663","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he will undertake an equality impact assessment on the Government's plan to restrict exit payments in the public sector.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272906","272906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136664","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government has made an assessment of the effect of restricting exit payments in the public sector on the pensions of staff employed by local authorities.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272907","272907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136665","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Exchequer Secretary to the Treasury of 2 July 2019, Official Report Vol 662, Column 1054, which countries in Europe his Department considers to have higher levels of social inequality than the UK, and what criteria his Department used to make that assessment.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272889","272889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136666","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the oral contribution  of 1 July 2019, Official Report, Column 903, what additional funding has been made available to East Ayrshire Council to mitigate the costs associated with the roll-out of universal credit.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272890","272890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136667","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that long-service public sector workers on lower pay scales are not inequitably affected by the restriction on exit payments in the public sector.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272908","272908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136668","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to her oral contribution on 1 July 1 2019, Official Report Vol 662, whether her investigation on the costs associated with the rollout of universal credit will consider the economic effects of that rollout on East Ayrshire Council.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272891","272891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136669","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average sentence length in months was for people who received an immediate custodial sentence and had (a) zero, (b) between one and four, (c) between five and nine, (d) between 10 and 15, (e) between 16 and 25, (f) between 26 and 50, (g) between 51 and 75, (h) between 76 and 100 and (i) 101 or more previous convictions in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272946","272946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136670","2019-07-08","Cabinet Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress he has made on the assessment of the reasons that EU citizens living in the UK were unable to register and vote in the 2019 European Parliament elections.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272799","272799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136671","2019-07-08","Cabinet Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had with the Electoral Commission on EU citizens being unable to vote in the 2019 European Parliament elections.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272800","272800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136672","2019-07-08","Cabinet Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has made an assessment of the level of voter turnout of EU citizens living in the UK at the 2019 European Parliament elections.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272801","272801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136673","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2019 to Question 269609 on Spinal Muscular Atrophy, if he will place in the Library a copy of the managed access agreement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272723","272723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136674","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of the equity of the fee structure for applying to become a UK citizen for people who have been (a) born and (b) raised in the UK.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272802","272802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136675","2019-07-08","Prime Minister","2019-07-03","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer on 21 May 2019 to Question 255260, whether she plans to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Christchurch, dated 18 February 2019 before the Summer recess.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272724","272724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136676","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he has taken to ensure that a person eligible to apply for UK citizenship is not prevented from doing so as a result of the fee structure.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272803","272803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136677","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average sentence length was in months for people who received an immediate custodial sentence and who had (a) no, (b) between one and four, (c) between five and nine, (d) between 10 and 15, (e) between 16 and 25, (f) between 26 and 50, (g) between 51 and 75, (h) between 76 and 100 and (i) 101 or more previous convictions, and who were convicted of (i) violence against the person (ii) theft, (iii) drug offences, (iv) robbery, (v) common assault and battery, (vi) burglary in a dwelling, (vi) production, supply and possession with intent to supply a controlled drug - Class A, (vii) possession of article with blade or point and (viii) assaulting, resisting or obstructing a constable or designated officer in execution of duty over the last 10 years.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272947","272947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136678","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what funding her Department has allocated to providers of local specialist domestic abuse services in anticipation of a potential increase in demand for such services as a result of her Department's policy to identify and refer survivors of domestic abuse to those services.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272900","272900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136679","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of reduced VAT for domestic fuels and tax reliefs for fossil fuel companies on the ability of the UK to phase out fossil fuel infrastructure in alignment with the goals of the Paris Agreement and to achieve net zero emissions by 2050.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272843","272843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136680","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2019 to Question 269610 on Spinal Muscular Atrophy: Drugs, what the maximum length of time is for the period of further data collection.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272725","272725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136681","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted but did not receive an immediate custodial sentence who had (a) zero, (b) between one and four, (c) between five and nine, (d) between 10 and 15, (e) between 16 and 25, (f) between 26 and 50, (g) between 51 and 75, (h) between 76 and 100 and (i) 101 or more previous convictions for (i) violence against the person, (ii) theft, (iii) drug offences, (iv) robbery, (v) common assault and battery, (vi) burglary in a dwelling, (vi) production, supply and possession with intent to supply a controlled drug - Class A, (vii) possession of an article with a blade or point and (viii) assaulting, resisting or obstructing a constable or designated officer in execution of duty in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272948","272948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136682","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department has taken to co-ordinate cross-government policy on disabled children.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272879","272879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136683","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2019 to Question 369611 on Spinal Muscular Atrophy: Drugs, what estimate he has made of the number of patients affected by the NICE announcement of 15 May 2019.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272726","272726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136684","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June to Question 266642, for what reasons her Department holds information on the number of universal credit claimants with an existing advance who also receive a maximum budgetary advance and have offered to repay that advance over the maximum time period allowed but does not hold information on the proportion of those people who have repaid their budget advance within the pre-agreed time period.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272736","272736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136685","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28 June to Question 266643, how many people received a universal credit payment between June 2015 and May 2019.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272737","272737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136686","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many properties have been procured by the new asylum accommodation provider Mears in the North East; how many service-users can be accommodated in those properties; and for how many service-users in the North East has new accommodation not yet been procured.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272830","272830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136687","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contingency plans have been put in place in the event that the asylum accommodation provider in the North East is unable to procure sufficient housing stock to accommodate the service-users in that region.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272831","272831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136688","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers in the North East will be required to leave their property during the transition to a new accommodation provider; and what steps he is taking to minimise disruption for those people who rely on local services.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272832","272832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136689","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans have been put in place to support vulnerable asylum seekers in the North East through the transition period between asylum accommodation contracts; and how the needs of those service users will be assessed.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272833","272833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136690","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how his Department plans to record complaints during the transition period between asylum accommodation contracts; and whether that information will be published.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272834","272834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136691","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether risk management information and contingency plans on the transition to the new asylum accommodation provider in the North East have been shared with local authorities involved in dispersal in that region.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272835","272835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136692","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 20 June 2019 to Question 266646, what recourse is available to a member of a joint claim whose partner has falsely confirmed that their partner knows and agrees to a universal credit advance.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272738","272738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136693","2019-07-08","Women and Equalities","2019-07-03","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps her Department is taking to support the Home Office in its internal investigation into the causes of the Windrush scandal.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272952","272952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136694","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2019 to Question 266647 on Universal Credit, for what reason his Department does not hold data on the number of claimants of universal credit that were refused an advance during the that period.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272739","272739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136695","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons his Department ceased to use a multiplier of 1.9 for the radiative forcing or non-CO2 effects of air travel in 2011 for Departmental passenger demand and CO2 forecasts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272852","272852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136696","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure an adequate supply of affordable housing in rural areas to meet the demand from (a) young people and (b) families.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272775","272775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136697","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money was accrued to the public purse from the Soft Drinks Industry Levy in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272873","272873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136698","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of work days lost by police officers from sick leave as a result of an assault while on duty.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272817","272817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136699","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on the potential merits of the Government providing upfront financial support for childcare to parents claiming universal credit.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272776","272776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136700","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many properties have been procured by the new asylum accommodation provider Mears in the North East; how many service users can be accommodated in those properties; and how many service users there are in the North East for whom new accommodation has not yet been procured.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272938","272938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136701","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contingency plans his Department has made in the event that the asylum accommodation provider in the North East is unable to procure sufficient housing stock to accommodate service-users in the region.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272939","272939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136702","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of emissions at train stations.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272818","272818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136703","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many energy companies have ceased trading in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272819","272819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136704","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and which higher education institutions have adopted the IHRA definition of antisemitism.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272895","272895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136705","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps her Department is taking to increase UK maritime capabilities in the Arctic and the High North.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272789","272789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136706","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much the Government spent on legal costs on the court case on reforms to firefighters pensions.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272935","272935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136707","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the Government's plans to provide free sanitary products in secondary schools and colleges from September 2019.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272793","272793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136708","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the electric vehicle charging infrastructure investment fund will open for applications.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272896","272896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136709","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what comparative assessment the Government has undertaken on the restriction of exit payments on public sector staff in (a) local authorities, (b) the Civil Service (c) the NHS, (d) the armed forces and (e) police forces.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272909","272909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136710","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make it his policy to take into account the skills and qualifications of non-EEA nationals applying for entry clearance under Appendix FM; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272790","272790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136711","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Network Rail on their progress in implementing the recommendations of the John Varley Vegetation Management Review.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272814","272814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136712","2019-07-08","Attorney General","2019-07-03","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272746","272746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136713","2019-07-08","Cabinet Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272747","272747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136714","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272748","272748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136715","2019-07-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272749","272749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136716","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272750","272750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136717","2019-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272751","272751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136718","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2019 to Question 269775, whether the practice of loansharks applying on behalf of an individual for a universal credit advance payment which is then issued as a loan to the individual is being investigated by her Department.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272943","272943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136719","2019-07-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the total amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272752","272752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136720","2019-07-08","Department for International Development","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272753","272753"
