"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790174","2017-11-20","Scotland Office","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many people in his Department with responsibility for social media are employed on an (a) full and (b) part-time basis.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113291","113291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790175","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people in his Department with responsibility for social media are employed on a (a) full and (b) part-time basis.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113292","113292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790176","2017-11-22","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure rural areas, like East Yorkshire, have adequate road connections to the strategic road network which will encourage and not deter future economic growth in the region.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113272","113272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790177","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the merits of the request from the Peninsula Rail Task Force for funding of £600,000 for the Speed to the West study; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113296","113296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790178","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on safety for passengers travelling from (a) Scotland to England and (b) England to Scotland of the Scottish Government's plans to integrate the British Transport Police in Scotland into Police Scotland.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113306","113306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790179","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of deaths on UK roads.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113305","113305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790180","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111403, whether the Government plans to extend the proposed Rail Passengers Ombudsman beyond the rail sector to cover other areas of passenger transport remit including aviation, buses and ferries.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113213","113213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790181","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to review the (a) volume of traffic and (b) level of toll charges at toll bridges operating under the provision of pre-20th century acts of Parliament.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113222","113222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790182","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the extent to which traffic queuing for toll bridges operating under the provision of pre-20th century acts of Parliament contributes to traffic congestion in the areas around those toll bridges.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113223","113223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790183","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on toll bridges operating under the provision of pre-20th century acts of Parliament.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113224","113224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790185","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the performance and punctuality of services on the Tyne and Wear Metro.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113229","113229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790186","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2017 to Question 108535, what funds are available to support replacement of rolling stock on the Tyne and Wear Metro.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113228","113228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790187","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on additional transport infrastructure investment for the North East ahead of Autumn Budget 2017.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113227","113227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790188","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much the Government plans to spend out of the Congestion Relief programme on projects in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside and (c) the North East.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113193","113193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790189","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much from Highways England's Growth and Housing Fund has been spent on projects in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside and (c) the North East.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113194","113194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790190","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with the Northern Ireland authorities on continuing co-operation with the EU in the area of aviation and air passenger rights under each possible deal for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113187","113187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790191","2017-11-21","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations his Department has received from Shropshire Council on the timing of receipt of its business case for the North West Relief Road; what process his Department plans to apply to assess that business case; what the timetable is from its receipt for a decision on that business case; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113431","113431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790192","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Scottish Government's plans to integrate the British Transport Police in Scotland into Police Scotland on the delivery of British Transport Police Services in the North of England.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113379","113379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790193","2017-11-20","Wales Office","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with reference to the Government's sectoral analysis of 58 sectors of the economy, what assessment he has made of that analysis with regard to the effect on the Welsh economy of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113384","113384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790194","2017-11-20","Wales Office","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether his Department has carried out or contributed to any quantitative analysis that provides an evidential basis for the UK leaving the EU being of benefit to the Welsh economy.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113166","113166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790195","2017-11-20","Wales Office","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many jobs he estimates could be (a) lost and (b) gained in Wales in the event of there being no deal at the end of UK negotiations to exit the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113334","113334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790196","2017-11-20","Wales Office","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many people in his Department with responsibility for social media are employed on an (a) full and (b) part-time basis.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113294","113294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790197","2017-11-20","Women and Equalities","2017-11-15","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many people in the Government Equalities Office with responsibility for social media are employed on an (a) full and (b) part-time basis.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113282","113282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790198","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in his Department with responsibility for social media are employed on an (a) full and (b) part-time basis.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113295","113295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790199","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has estimated how many victims of rape, following a conviction, with a third child have been successful in claiming for child tax credits.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113304","113304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790200","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government plans to seek formal agreement to participate in the European Insurance and Occupational Pensions Authority after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113251","113251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790201","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost of Statutory Adoption Pay has been to the public purse in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113235","113235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790202","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people were in receipt of Statutory Paternity in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113236","113236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790203","2017-11-17","Home Office","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will introduce a seasonal agricultural workers scheme once the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113255","113255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790204","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to train staff about whether potentially vulnerable claimants should be placed in the all work requirements group.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113360","113360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790205","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many journals each journal manager working on universal credit in his Department is responsible for.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113396","113396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790206","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many hours of job-specific training (a) journal managers and (b) work coaches working on universal credit receive prior to commencing work as a qualified journal manager or work coach.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113397","113397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790207","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of data in the Royal London National Funeral Cost Index 2017 on the difference between average funeral costs and average Social Fund Funeral Expenses Payment (SFFEP) awards; what assessment he has made of trends in the difference between average funeral costs and average SFFEP awards; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113162","113162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790208","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his Department's policy to raise the funeral director's fees element of the funeral fund in line with inflation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113185","113185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790209","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what provision was made for advice to be given to members of the Tata Steel pension scheme on their pension options after the creation of the new pensions scheme; and what the cost to the public purse of that provision was.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113174","113174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790210","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department provides free advice to Tata Steel pension scheme members on their pension options.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113175","113175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790211","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had or plans to have with the Pension Protection Fund on the number of Tata Steel pension scheme members requesting valuations to transfer their pots out of the scheme.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113176","113176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790212","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had or plans to have with the Financial Conduct Authority on the specific targeting of cold calls to Tata Steel pension members by financial advisers.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113177","113177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790213","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the planned date for the transition to full service of universal credit is for the London Borough of Waltham Forest.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113178","113178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790214","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how and when claimants will be advised of changes to their benefits when universal credit full service is rolled out to different claimant groups.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113203","113203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790215","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost of statutory maternity pay and maternity allowance has been to the public purse in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113238","113238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790216","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women were in receipt of statutory maternity pay and maternity allowance in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113237","113237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790217","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims of the assessment rate of employment and support allowance have been processed (a) successfully and (b) unsuccessfully in each month since January 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113402","113402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790218","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) claims and (b) successful claims have been made for the child element of child tax credit for a third, or later child, born on or after 6 April 2017 on the grounds that the child was born as a result of a non-consensual conception; and for how many of those claims the supporting third-party professional was a midwife.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113401","113401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790219","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress he has made in implementing the Fuller Working Lives strategy since February; and whether statistics on the employment status of people over 50 years old will in future show the number of hours worked.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113418","113418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790220","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109749, on universal credit: disability, how his Department plans to determine the extent to which users of universal credit statistics consider reporting on disabled people a high priority when reviewing the responses of the consultation.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113411","113411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790221","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what engagement his Department has had with the part-time distance learning sector on delivering the recommendations made in the final report of the Made Smarter Review.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113388","113388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790222","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the incentives to retrain and re-skill as part of the industrial strategy.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113389","113389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790223","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education and the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport on the recommendations proposed in the final report from the Made Smarter Review.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113387","113387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790224","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109395, what steps the Nuclear Skills Strategy Group is taking to ensure that the nuclear industry has access to the skills it needs.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113436","113436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790225","2017-11-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109395, what steps the Nuclear Sills Strategy Group is taking to make it easier to attract qualified and experienced people from other sectors into the nuclear industry.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113438","113438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790226","2017-11-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109395, what steps the Nuclear Sills Strategy Group is taking to remove barriers to entry into the nuclear industry.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113439","113439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790227","2017-11-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how resources from the new Industrial Strategy Challenge Fund will be allocated across the country to challenge regional economic inequality.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113440","113440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790228","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has any plans to develop carbon capture and storage projects in the North East.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113230","113230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790229","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to enter a contract with the EURATOM Supply Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113233","113233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790230","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to seek formal membership, participation in, or co-operation with the European Institute of Innovation and Technology after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113245","113245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790231","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to seek formal cooperation with or participation in the European Research Council Executive Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113234","113234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790232","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to seek formal participation with the Executive Agency for Small and Medium-sized Enterprises after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113246","113246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790233","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to seek formal participation with Fusion for Energy after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113232","113232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790234","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment the Government has made of the opportunities presented by the provisions included in the Space Industry Bill [Lords] for (a) specialist manufacturing and (b) other businesses in the UK.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113186","113186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790235","2017-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on minimum levels of domestic content in renewable energy construction projects after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113182","113182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790236","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals for the regulation of geo-engineering.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113158","113158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790237","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how he plans to implement the recommendations proposed in the final report from the Made Smarter Review.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113386","113386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790238","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2017 to Question 111705, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the level of financial support for small and medium-sized enterprise homebuilders.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113372","113372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790239","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential contribution of part-time distance learning in supporting the delivery of the recommendations in the final report from the Made Smarter Review.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113385","113385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790240","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2017 to Question 111704, what representations he has received from business organisations on the extent of delay in payment to SMEs in the construction sector.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113349","113349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790241","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of children in need (a) applied to and (b) entered university in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113315","113315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790242","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people in his Department with responsibility for social media are employed on an (a) full and (b) part-time basis.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113273","113273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790243","2017-11-20","Department for International Trade","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2017 to Question 111584, on World Trade Organisation (WTO), what his planned timetable is for the (a) preparation and (b) agreement with the WTO of the amended schedules.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113264","113264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790244","2017-11-20","Department for International Trade","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2017 to Question 111399, on trade agreements: USA, whether the Trade and Investment Working Group involves discussions between US and Commonwealth nations.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113267","113267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790245","2017-11-20","Department for International Trade","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2017 to Question 111584, on World Trade Organisation, which schedules need to be updated in order to minimise disruption.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113269","113269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790246","2017-11-20","Department for International Trade","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent assessment he has made of the availability of funding to help the North East join trade missions and grasp export opportunities.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113336","113336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790247","2017-11-20","Department for International Trade","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many people in his Department with responsibility for social media are employed on an (a) full and (b) part-time basis.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113286","113286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790248","2017-11-20","Department for International Trade","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2017 to Question 110584, on Trade Agreements: Arbitration, what estimate he has made of the cost of the establishment of the trade remedies framework, January to August 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113323","113323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790249","2017-11-20","Department for International Trade","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2017 to Question 110584, on Trade Agreements: Arbitration, what estimate he has made of the cost of the development of the policy, legislative and operational plans for a new trade remedies framework.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113324","113324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790250","2017-11-20","Department for International Trade","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2017 to Question 110584, what representations he has received from business organisations on the establishment of a trade remedies framework.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113374","113374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790251","2017-11-20","Department for International Trade","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111584, which aspects of the UK's membership of the WTO the UK needs to update to replicate as far as possible current obligations after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113348","113348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790252","2017-11-20","Department for International Trade","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether free trade agreements agreed between the EU and (a) Turkey, (b) Switzerland, (c) South Korea, (d) South Africa, (e) Norway and (f) Iceland will allow the cumulation of EU and UK content during any transition period after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113163","113163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790254","2017-11-20","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the joint statement from the European Chemical Industry Council and the Chemical Industries Association published on 15 November 2017, what assessment he has made of the effect on the chemicals industry when the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113341","113341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790255","2017-11-20","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many people in his Department with responsibility for social media are employed on an (a) full and (b) part-time basis.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113280","113280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/790256","2017-11-21","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether Northern Ireland will remain in the EEA to secure a seamless and frictionless border with the Republic of Ireland after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113433","113433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/792134","2017-11-17","Home Office","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  if she will introduce a seasonal agricultural workers scheme once the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 114519","114519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/792140","2017-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government,  whether his Department has consulted those people in receipt of EU structural funds on a replacement for that scheme once the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 114523","114523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/817981","2017-11-20","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether his Department has consulted those people in receipt of EU structural funds on a replacement for that scheme once the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113148","113148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788980","2017-11-16","Attorney General","2017-11-14","To ask the Attorney General, how many successful prosecutions for using a mobile telephone while in control of a motor vehicle were recorded in London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112849","112849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788981","2017-11-16","Attorney General","2017-11-14","To ask the Attorney General, how many successful prosecutions for using a mobile telephone while in control of a motor vehicle were recorded in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112850","112850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788982","2017-11-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of changes to the operation or administration of the Supreme Court as a result of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112993","112993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788983","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the pay review bodies that determine public sector pay.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112930","112930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788986","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on productivity of businesses adopting digital technology; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112803","112803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788987","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the per head spending from the public purse was in 2016-17 on islands around (a) Scotland and (b) the rest of the UK.","Biography information for Mr Bob Seely","Mr Bob Seely","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112815","112815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788988","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 110350, on the proposed transfer of HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) posts from East Kilbride to Glasgow, on what dates meetings between HMRC and departmental trade unions took place.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112821","112821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788989","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an estimate of the scale of tax avoidance in the Crown dependencies.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112864","112864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788990","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the level of foreign direct investment in the UK was in the 12 months (a) prior to and (b) from July 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112858","112858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788991","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will place in the Library any information his Department holds on the performance indicators for individual valuation offices in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112859","112859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788992","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111910, whether (a) Government Ministers and (b) HM Revenue and Customs have had discussions with their counterparts in the (i) UK Overseas Territories and (ii) Crown Dependencies to ascertain an estimate of the scale of tax avoidance in those territories.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112870","112870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788993","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has any plans to review the six-month contribution holiday for Save As You Earn schemes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112910","112910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788994","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will award increased funding to the NHS in Shropshire in the forthcoming Budget and in particular to the Shropshire and Telford Hospitals NHS Trust.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112917","112917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788995","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111680, how many individual cases the Rhyl valuation office has processed in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112988","112988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788996","2017-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2017 to Question 110466, on private rented housing: homelessness, what the timetable is for the conclusion and publication of his consideration of the effectiveness of existing projects.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112996","112996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788997","2017-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2017 to Question 110466, on private rented housing: homelessness, which projects are included in his consideration of the effectiveness of existing projects.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112997","112997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788998","2017-11-16","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the employee turnover rate for social workers in (a) Redcar and Cleveland Borough Council, (b) the North East and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113035","113035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788999","2017-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities, parish and town councils have submitted proposals to his Department under the Sustainable Communities Act 2007 since its inception.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112959","112959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789000","2017-11-16","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of looked-after children being placed 20 miles or more outside the boundary of their local authority.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113036","113036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789001","2017-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of local authorities' budgets have been spent on children's services by (a) Redcar and Cleveland Borough Council, (b) local authorities in the North East and (c) local authorities in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113037","113037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789002","2017-11-16","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that local authorities provide adequate pastoral support for social workers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113038","113038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789003","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what powers local authorities in England have to regulate bike share schemes within their boundaries.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112924","112924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789004","2017-11-20","Cabinet Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many requests for financial support the Government has (a) received and (b) granted as a result of the 2017 Manchester terrorist attack.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112932","112932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789005","2017-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2017 to Question 110466, on private rented housing: homelessness, in what way he is considering the effectiveness of existing projects operating across the country.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112998","112998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789006","2017-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2017 to Question 110466, on private rented housing: homelessness, what projects were previously notified of the measures he is using in considering the effectiveness of existing projects operating across the country.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112999","112999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789007","2017-11-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much financial support has been provided to services offering support for families and victims of the Manchester terrorist attack of 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112939","112939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789009","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of average broadband speeds in (a) rural and (b) urban areas.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112823","112823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789010","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what statistics her Department holds on average broadband speeds on a constituency basis.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112903","112903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789011","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government plans to seek third country participation with the European Union Agency for Network and Information Security under Article 30 of the Regulations (EU) No. 526/2013 after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113005","113005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789012","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the UK plans to seek observer status at the Body of European Regulators for Electronic Communications after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112897","112897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789013","2017-11-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on establishing a National Football League franchise in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112994","112994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789014","2017-11-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many live quarry have been killed during a trial hunt on Ministry of Defence land in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113019","113019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789015","2017-11-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many licences for trail hunts have been issued for Ministry of Defence land in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113024","113024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789016","2017-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the safety of the Trident nuclear weapons system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112915","112915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789017","2017-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether expenditure for planned nuclear infrastructure projects at Faslane and Coulport will come out of the existing budget for Trident.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112914","112914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789018","2017-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will hold discussions with the Board of Combat Stress on its plans to end residential care for veterans at Audley Court, Newport, Shropshire.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112916","112916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789019","2017-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether additional funds will be allocated to the Trident replacement programme in the 2017-18 financial year which have not already been budgeted for.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112918","112918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789020","2017-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list the costs of the Government's planned nuclear infrastructure projects at Faslane and Coulport.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112912","112912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789021","2017-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what specific projects and programmes are scheduled to take place to expand nuclear infrastructure at Faslane and Coulport.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112913","112913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789022","2017-11-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many apprenticeships the Royal Navy provides; and in which sectors.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112877","112877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789023","2017-11-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many apprenticeships the British Army provides and in which sectors.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112886","112886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789024","2017-11-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many apprenticeships the Royal Air Force provides and in which sectors.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112887","112887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789025","2017-11-16","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to add political education to the national curriculum.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112904","112904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789026","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Data Exchange project began; and what progress has been made in achieving the aims of that project.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112860","112860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789027","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish impact and risk assessments undertaken on schools for the Data Exchange project.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112861","112861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789028","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to share best practice with and from the devolved Parliament and Assemblies on delivering improvements in educational attainment among young people from disadvantaged backgrounds.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112854","112854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789029","2017-11-16","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of children who are at risk of experiencing hunger during the school Christmas holidays in 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112829","112829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789030","2017-11-16","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will continue to fund the Autism Education Trust to help ensure that teachers in England can access training in autism as part of their continuous professional development.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112817","112817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789031","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students have studied at least two arts subjects at GCSE level in Coventry in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112806","112806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789032","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many GCSE entries for arts subjects there were from students in Coventry in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112807","112807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789033","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary schools in Coventry South constituency were full or oversubscribed in the school years commencing in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112808","112808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789034","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many secondary schools in Coventry South constituency were full or oversubscribed in the school years commencing in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112809","112809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789035","2017-11-16","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to respond to Greater Manchester Combined Authority's bid for funding from the Children's Social Care Innovation Programme.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112946","112946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789036","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what work her officials are doing with West Sussex County Council to improve the performance of maintained schools and academies.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112929","112929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789037","2017-11-16","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will promote active travel schemes as part of the PE and Sport Premium available to schools in England.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113013","113013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789038","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 112004, on academies: admissions, whether the Secretary of State declined any of the 14 requests in the academic year 2016-17 for direct admission of a looked-after child to an academy.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112985","112985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789039","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the amount of underspend on the apprenticeship levy; and what proportion of this amount is for the North West.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112983","112983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789040","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) financial and (b) other support will be made available to schools to promote (i) walking to school and (ii) other modes of active travel for the purposes of improving concentration and reducing congestion and air pollution around schools.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113012","113012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789041","2017-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make representations to Cornwall Council on increasing the quantity of beverage cartons it recycles.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112962","112962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789042","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to Article 49 of EU Regulation No 178/2002, whether the UK plans to seek participation with the European Food Standards Agency after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113028","113028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789043","2017-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to prohibit the sale and keeping of primates as pets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113003","113003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789044","2017-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to seek the UK's continued participation with the European Chemicals Agency, as set out under Article 106 of EU Regulation 1907/2006, after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113008","113008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789045","2017-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions officials of his Department have had with officials from the Scottish Government on UK common agricultural frameworks after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112800","112800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789046","2017-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the Scottish Government on designing a new agricultural subsidy system for Scotland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112802","112802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789047","2017-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what priority his Department accords to animal sentience when setting its policies on animal welfare standards.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112827","112827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789048","2017-11-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) red and (b) grey squirrels there are in the UK (i) now and were (ii) in 2007.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112856","112856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789049","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations her Department has (a) received on and (b) made to the United Nations on animal testing for cosmetic products.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112831","112831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789050","2017-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to seek observer status of the Community Plant Variety Office after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112843","112843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789051","2017-11-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the devolved administrations on animal breeding and vending.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112871","112871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789052","2017-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Government of the Cayman Islands on (a) automatic exchange of beneficial ownership information with HM Revenue and Customs and UK law enforcement agencies and (b) a public register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112862","112862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789053","2017-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the World Press Freedom Index 2017, which noted a decline in press freedom in 62.2 per cent of the 180 countries in the Index.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112906","112906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789054","2017-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made an estimate of the scale of tax avoidance in the overseas territories.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112863","112863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789055","2017-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on protecting Oman's security, sovereignty and territorial integrity.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112945","112945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789056","2017-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Chinese Government on ensuring protection for bloggers and writers exercising freedom of expression.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112948","112948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789057","2017-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to help secure the release of writers, academics, teachers and lawyers arrested following the coup attempt in Turkey.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112947","112947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789058","2017-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on that country's commitment to the 2015 Iranian Nuclear Deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112921","112921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789059","2017-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on international efforts to pursue dialogue with North Korea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112922","112922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789060","2017-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made any representations to the recent International Symposium on Nuclear Weapons at the Vatican.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112919","112919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789061","2017-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he plans to make to the UN High-Level Conference on Nuclear Disarmament in May 2018.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112920","112920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789062","2017-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in how many cases of UK citizens abroad including dual nationals his Department has received claims of torture and similar human rights abuses; and in how many of such cases his Department consulted its pro bono medical panel since 2010 for each (a) year and (b) country.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112980","112980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789063","2017-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has consulted its pro bono medical panel about harms and risks to the mental and physical health of Ms Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112981","112981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789064","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect of not aligning with the forthcoming EU clinical trials regulation on patient access to clinical trials.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112982","112982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789065","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2017 to Question 67522, on pharmacy: disadvantaged, if he will provide the most up to date version of the data requested in that Question.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112950","112950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789066","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure adequate support for the families of people with asthma.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112953","112953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789067","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received on payments being (a) requested and (b) made for the submission to a doctor, GP or consultant of a death certificate for signature; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112961","112961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789068","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ask (a) the local clinical commissioning groups and (b) University Hospitals of North Midlands NHS Trust to publish the reasons for (i) closing wards in March 2017 and (ii) re-opening wards from November 2017 at Bradwell community hospital in Newcastle-under-Lyme; and what the cost to the NHS was of such decisions.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112952","112952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789069","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of times the NHS Constitution has been breached in the last (a) week, (b) month and (c) year.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112989","112989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789070","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to coordinate with the devolved authorities the learning and development of best practice in helping people stop smoking.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112954","112954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789071","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the HSC Business Services Organisation on ensuring effective provision of financial support for people in Northern Ireland affected by contaminated blood; and whether he plans to establish a point of appeal for people in all parts of the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112955","112955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789072","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that access to dental services for the prevention of decay is not subject to significant regional or national variation across the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112956","112956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789073","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of whether the conditions it attaches to National Institute for Health Research and National Health Service research grants safeguard affordable access for NHS patients to drugs and treatments that result from that research.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112958","112958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789074","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of palliative care available in England; and what change in that level he estimates will occur by 2020.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112969","112969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789075","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the fee chargeable by NHS general practices for providing medical information to patients for the purposes of other public authorities was last reviewed by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113026","113026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789076","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the future of Urgent Care Centres (a) in Northamptonshire and (b) across England.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112992","112992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789077","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance has been given to NHS general practices on the circumstances under which volunteers are permitted to carry out non-confidential medical work; and whether this guidance is the same as that for permitted activities of volunteers in other parts of the NHS.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113025","113025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789078","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on palliative care in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112968","112968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789079","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes in funding of community pharmacies on access to healthcare for people in rural areas who use such pharmacies as their first point of contact for healthcare and treatment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112957","112957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789080","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 3 November 2017 to Questions 110464 and 110465, on tomography: leasing, if he will take steps to collate this information centrally; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112995","112995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789081","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to Article 13 of EU Council Regulation No 302/93, whether the UK plans to seek formal cooperation with the European Monitoring Centre for Drugs and Drug Addiction after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113030","113030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789082","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many human eggs were frozen in each of the last five years by centres registered by the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority by (a) the slow-cooling method and (b) the process of vitrification.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112909","112909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789083","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to increase the provision of specialist palliative care in (a) Southampton, (b) the South East and (c) England.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112971","112971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789084","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many terminally ill people were offered end-of-life care in their own homes in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112972","112972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789085","2017-11-16","Cabinet Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the survival rate is for people with brain tumours; and what the comparative rate is for people with all forms of cancer.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112973","112973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789086","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department provides to carers for people who are undergoing end-of-life care.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112974","112974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789087","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average time is for which a terminally ill person receives palliative care.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112975","112975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789088","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost is of treating a terminally ill person.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112976","112976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789089","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people identified as having a terminal illness have had referrals for treatment delayed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112977","112977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789090","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average age is of women who have submitted their oocytes for freezing in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112888","112888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789091","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women have submitted their oocytes for freezing (a) as a result of medical treatment affecting their fertility and (b) for other reasons, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112889","112889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789092","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that unnatural deaths in mental health settings are investigated by an independent body; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112943","112943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789093","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the number of GPs in areas such as new towns where the population is rapidly expanding.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112944","112944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789094","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the guidance issued by his Department to NHS trusts on the VAT payable for subsidiary companies set up by those trusts.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112891","112891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789095","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what additional support his Department plans to provide to Oxford University Hospital's NHS Foundation Trust during winter 2017.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112925","112925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789096","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the capability of the UK's 12 Notified Bodies to continue operating after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112926","112926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789097","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications were received for the new position of Joint Accountable Officer for the six clinical commissioning groups in Staffordshire, how many initial interviews were held with applicants; and how many applicants were shortlisted for second interviews.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112895","112895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789098","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons his Department (a) re-opened wards at Bradwell community hospital in Newcastle-under-Lyme, (b) recommissioned facilities at Brighton House in Newcastle-under-Lyme and (c) reopened Ward 4 at the Harplands hospital in Stoke-on-Trent; and if he will publish the projected financial costs of each such decision.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112949","112949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789099","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse has been of (a) redundancies and (b) the decommissioning of facilities following the closure in March 2017 of wards at Bradwell community hospital in Newcastle-under-Lyme.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112896","112896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789100","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications to National Institute or Health Research for pancreatic cancer have been (a) made and (b) accepted in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113014","113014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789101","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department or NHS England has undertaken an evaluation of the six demonstration sites providing IAPT services for people with severe mental illness; and whether he plans to implement the service nationally.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112934","112934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789102","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many pieces of correspondence his Department has received from (a) hon. Members, (b) members of the House of Lords, (c) external organisations and (d) members of the public relating to patient transport to and from NHS appointments.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113022","113022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789103","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the name of the commissioned provider for health services in each prison in England and Wales.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113023","113023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789104","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will hold discussions with the Secretary of State for Transport on the effect of decreases to (a) bus routes and (b) the frequency of bus services on the ability of older people to access NHS appointments.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113015","113015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789105","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent evaluation he has conducted of secondary care psychological therapy services in the NHS.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112933","112933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789106","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's guidelines are for follow-up post-discharge support for patients who are diagnosed at accident and emergency departments with a mental health condition and with problems associated with substance or alcohol misuse.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112824","112824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789107","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients diagnosed at accident and emergency departments with a mental health condition and with problems associated with substance or alcohol misuse are (a) treated and (b) turned away from those departments by NHS trust for each year from 2011 to 2016.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112825","112825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789108","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2017 to Question 111080, when his Department plans to begin to collect data on (a) mental health, (b) substance misuse and (c) learning disability nurses recruitment and retention to inform future workforce planning.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112826","112826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789109","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department still plans to publish a Carers' Strategy; and whether young carers will be included in that strategy.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112819","112819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789110","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with (a) the Accountable Officer for Stoke-on-Trent Clinical Commissioning Group, (b) Stoke-on-Trent City Council, (c) Staffordshire and Stoke-on-Trent Partnership Trust and (d) University Hospital of the North Midlands Trust on the Care Quality Commission review of local health and the social care system.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112811","112811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789111","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions (a) he and (b) NHS England have had with the University Hospital of North Midlands on the permanent appointment of a Trust chair.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112812","112812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789112","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the budget for Stoke-on-Trent Clinical Commissioning Group has been in each year since its creation.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112814","112814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789113","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage more people to train to become specialist (a) mental health and (b) learning disability nurses.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112851","112851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789114","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many subsidiary companies have been set up by NHS trusts; and what the purpose is of those companies.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112852","112852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789115","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the Government has to develop a national strategy for self care.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Sir Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112866","112866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789116","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulance call outs were for type 3 conditions in (a) England and (b) each clinical commissioning group in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Sir Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112865","112865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789117","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2017 to Question 110509, on health services: Greater Manchester, if he will place a copy of the minutes of the meeting between the affected parties on 13 July 2017 in the Library.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112841","112841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789118","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings he has had with external experts on hormone pregnancy tests in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112845","112845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789119","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for the Expert Panel Working Group Inquiry into hormone pregnancy tests to release its report.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112846","112846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789120","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for the publication of the Government's Green Paper on social care.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112847","112847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789121","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2017 to Question 111046, what discussions NHS England has had with the six clinical commissioning groups in Staffordshire on merging those groups into one county-wide body; and who led any such discussions.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112832","112832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789122","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 10 November 2017 to Questions 111038 and 111043, if he will instruct (a) his Department, (b) NHS England, (c) NHS Improvement or (d) the local clinical commissioning groups to publish the Capped Expenditure Programme report for Staffordshire and Stoke-on-Trent.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112833","112833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789123","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2017 to Question 111044, on University Hospitals of North Midlands NHS Trust, for what reasons (a) his Department and (b) NHS England do not receive financial reports on NHS trusts in financial special measures.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112834","112834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789124","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 8 November 2017 to Questions 111039 and 111045, on NHS: reorganisation, what the final funding gap was for social care in (a) Staffordshire and (b) Stoke-on-Trent for 2016-17; and what the projected funding gaps for each such organisation are for (i) 2017-18, (ii) 2018-19, (iii) 2019-20 and (iv) 2020-21 within the updated local sustainability and transformation plan process.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112835","112835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789125","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2017 to Question 111042, on Better Care Fund: Stoke-on-Trent, whether the Regional Assurance Panel has made a recommendation to his national team on Stoke-on-Trent's Better Care Fund Plan.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112836","112836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789126","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2017 to Question 111051, on Haywood Hospital, what discussions the new Accountable Officer for the six clinical commissioning groups in Stoke-on-Trent and Staffordshire has had with (a) NHS England and (b) NHS Improvement on the future of wards at the Haywood Hospital in Stoke-on-Trent.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112837","112837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789127","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2017 to Question 111051, on Haywood Hospital, what the remuneration is of the (a) new Chair of the Health and Transformation Board overseeing the Staffordshire and Stoke-on-Trent Sustainability and Transformation Plan (STP) and (b) the Director overseeing the STP; and what the combined remuneration is of the (i) Assistant Director, (ii) Finance Director and his support staff and (iii) Medical Director of that STP","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112838","112838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789128","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2017 to Question 111041, on Haywood Hospital, when his Department received the Independent reconfiguration Panel's report and recommendations into local authority referrals of community hospital bed closures in North Staffordshire and Stoke-on-Trent; and what advice he has received on the legal basis of the local clinical commissioning group's decision to close beds in the hospitals before that consultation is complete.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112839","112839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789129","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with (a) NHS England and (b) the Accountable Officer for the Stoke-on-Trent Clinical Commissioning Group on the waiving of fines for the University Hospital of North Midlands Trust's failure to meet targets in the payment by results contract.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112885","112885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789130","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has invested in talking therapies in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112970","112970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789131","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients seeking mental health treatment were sent out of area for treatment in each trust in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113001","113001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789132","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the evidential source is for the number given for the increases of NHS staff and in people being treated in his tweet in response to Ralf Little on 8 November 2017.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113002","113002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789133","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the UK plans to seek (a) observer status at or (b) formal participation in the European Border and Coast Guard Agency after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112902","112902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789134","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the UK plans to seek formal co-operation with or third country participatory membership of the European Maritime Safety Agency after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112899","112899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789135","2017-11-20","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2017 to Question 108858, on visas, what percentage of non-straightforward applications for 2017 Q1 were completed within service standards.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112872","112872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789136","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to seek formal operational cooperation with the European Asylum Support Office as set out in that office's External Action Strategy after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112842","112842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789137","2017-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to combat access to anti-Semitic propaganda among young people.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112855","112855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789138","2017-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funding has been provided to Stoke-on-Trent constituency through the Migration Fund; and how much of that provision has been spent in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112813","112813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789139","2017-11-20","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with Staffordshire's Police and Crime Commissioner on future governance arrangements for Staffordshire Fire and Rescue Service.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112810","112810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789140","2017-11-20","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which funding authority is responsible for the installation of (a) rising bollards and (b) other such permanent road furniture designed to prevent terrorist attacks; and what assessment she has made of the potential benefits of establishing a central fund for such installations.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113016","113016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789141","2017-11-20","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of security of open spaces in cities against terrorist attacks using vehicles.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113020","113020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789142","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on data protection rights for immigrants; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113006","113006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789143","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the recommendation of page 5 of the Women for Refugee Women's report, We are still here, published in November 2017, if she will implement a proactive screening process to ensure that survivors of sexual and gender-based violence, and others who are vulnerable are identified before detention.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112940","112940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789144","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with whom she plans to consult on new measures to tackle domestic violence and abuse; and when that consultation will commence.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112890","112890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789145","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to develop alternatives to immigration detention on the basis of support and engagement in the community.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112911","112911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789146","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations the Government is making to the US Administration on the detention and extradition of Charlie Caulfield; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112967","112967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789147","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with Ministers from other Departments on the value to the UK economy of mid-level skills or those skills at Standard Occupational Classification levels 2 and 3; and what plans her Department has to ensure that any future changes to immigration policy allow businesses to continue to access those mid-level skills necessary for growth and employment in the UK.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112965","112965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789148","2017-11-20","Department for International Development","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what change there has been in rates of malaria in countries receiving UK funding for anti-malarial products since January 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112857","112857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789149","2017-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2017 to Question 111090, what estimate he has made of the proportion of higher-rate customer service lines that were transferred to local rate numbers in 2014.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112840","112840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789150","2017-11-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests relating to restricted patients were made to the Mental Health Casework Section in each year since 2009-10; and of those requests in each such year how many (a) have been completed and (b) still need to be completed.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112880","112880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789151","2017-11-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the backlog of cases being processed by the Mental Health Casework Section was in each year since 2009-10; and how long on average from the case being logged to the decision being made it took to clear cases on that backlog in each of those years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112881","112881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789152","2017-11-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of calendar days was from the case being logged to the final decision being made for the Mental Health Casework Section to progress requests for restricted patients to (a) transfer to another hospital, (b) transfer to community care, (c) discharge and (d) recall to hospital in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112882","112882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789153","2017-11-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding has been allocated to the Mental Health Casework Section in each year since 2009-10; and how many full-time equivalent staff have been employed by that section in each of those years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112879","112879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789154","2017-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of litigants having to turn to third-party funders to meet the cost of issuing proceedings.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112801","112801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789155","2017-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2017, to Question 111090, if he will make it his policy to collate data on incoming telephone calls and charges to devolved organisations who work under contract to his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112951","112951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789156","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many bail applications were made by EU nationals held in immigration detention in the last 12 months; and how many of those applications were successful.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112923","112923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789157","2017-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans to build new private prisons.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113011","113011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789158","2017-11-20","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will appoint an independent person to chair the talks between the main political parties in Northern Ireland to agree the means for restoring a functioning assembly at Stormont; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112874","112874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789159","2017-11-20","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to his oral contribution of 13 November 2017, Official Report, column 72, for what reasons the full staffing allowances of MLAs have been omitted from the remit of the independent review announced on 13 November 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112883","112883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789160","2017-11-20","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to his oral contribution of 13 November 2017, Official Report, column 72, if he will confirm that the independent assessment being undertaken into the continued payment of MLA salaries in the absence of a functioning Assembly will be published; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112884","112884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789161","2017-11-20","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress has been made on defining the nature of the border between the UK and the Republic of Ireland after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112990","112990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789162","2017-11-16","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether Charlie Caulfield received a letter of comfort.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112966","112966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789163","2017-11-16","Prime Minister","2017-11-14","To ask the Prime Minister, what meetings she has had with (a) hon. Members and (b) external experts on (i) hormone pregnancy tests and (ii) the Expert Working Group on hormone pregnancy tests.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112844","112844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789164","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the UK plans to participate in the European Aviation Safety Agency after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112898","112898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789165","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his Written Ministerial Statement of 20 July 2017, HCWS85, on rail update, which Cardiff station is the intended recipient of funds for improvements referred to.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112875","112875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789166","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Office of Rail and Road's enforcement of train-operating company licence provisions in terms of their meeting their retail code of practice obligations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112876","112876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789167","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much the Rail Delivery Group spent on marketing and advertising in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2014-15.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112937","112937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789168","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Rail Delivery Group; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112938","112938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789169","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of trends in the safety of helicopter transport in the offshore oil and gas sector.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112798","112798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789170","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent information his Department holds on trends in the cost of insuring commercial helicopter flights in the North Sea oil and gas industry since January 2009 to date.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112799","112799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789171","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government classifies the Solent as (a) an estuary or (b) open water.","Biography information for Mr Bob Seely","Mr Bob Seely","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112816","112816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789172","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Article 75 of EU Regulation 2016/796, whether the UK plans to seek formal third country participation with the European Union Agency for Railways after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113027","113027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789173","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the feasibility of reinstating the train station in Consett; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113009","113009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789174","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse has been of (a) marketing and (b) advertising associated with the Rail Delivery Group's In Partnership for Britain's Prosperity campaign.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112935","112935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789175","2017-11-20","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether train-operating company participation in the Rail Ombudsman will be compulsory.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112936","112936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789176","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Scottish Government about regeneration of the A75 euro-route from Gretna to Stranraer.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112894","112894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789177","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure agreements are in place between each EU member state and the UK to enable the provisions of the European Common Aviation Area to continue to apply after the UK leaves the EU; when he plans to put those agreements in place; and whether his Department plans to take on additional staff or other resources to meet that timetable.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112942","112942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789178","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to upgrade the A75 euro-route from Gretna to Stranraer.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112893","112893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789179","2017-11-20","Wales Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will have discussions with the Department for Exiting the European Union on conducting an assessment of the potential outcomes of the UK's negotiations with the EU on the Welsh economy.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112984","112984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789180","2017-11-20","Wales Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 111256, on economic situation: Wales, what the outcome of the economic analysis has been to date.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112873","112873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789181","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2017 to Question 110379, on Tidal Lagoons Independent Review, if he will (a) set out the costs that make up that approximate figure and (b) place the evidential basis for those costs in the Library.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112869","112869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789182","2017-11-16","Women and Equalities","2017-11-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the extent of disability discrimination against those with (a) type 1 and (b) type 2 diabetes; and what steps are being taken to address disability discrimination for people with diabetes.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112908","112908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789183","2017-11-16","Women and Equalities","2017-11-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to Article 8 of EU Regulation No 1922/2006, whether the UK plans to seek formal cooperation with the European Institute for Gender Equality after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113029","113029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789184","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit claimants in Warrington North constituency have an advance payment agreement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113021","113021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789185","2017-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people in North West Durham Constituency will be affected by the Support for Mortgage Interest benefit becoming a loan.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113010","113010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789186","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people referred to foodbanks by Jobcentre Plus in the Halton and Cheshire West and Chester local authority areas in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113017","113017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789187","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2017 to Question 106439, on pensions, other than Master Trusts, if the Government will establish an approved list of regulated pension schemes with regulated underlying investments that are deemed safe; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112927","112927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789188","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he will respond to the consultation, Pension Protection Fund: draft regulations to take account of bridging pensions, published on 31 August 2017.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112928","112928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789189","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that training offered to those carrying out work capability assessments complies with statutory obligations under the Autism Act 2009.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112979","112979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789190","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the change in the rate of (a) employment and (b) unemployment since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112991","112991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789191","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support job coaches are able to offer jobseekers with health conditions and disabilities in the event that those jobcentres are unable to access the Work and Health programme.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113000","113000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789192","2017-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department has issued on the effect of pension clauses.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112905","112905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789193","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether people administering work capability assessments are required to undertake training on autism and autistic spectrum disorders; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112878","112878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789194","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what contingency plans his Department has put in place to protect his Department's staff who are subject to TUPE transfer, in the event that Interserve the contractor for cleaning, messengerial and other support functions, is unable to fulfil its contract; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112868","112868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789195","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department made of the financial sustainability of the company, Interserve, prior to awarding that company the contract for cleaning, messengerial and other support functions for his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112867","112867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789196","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department made of the suitability of Interserve as a fit and proper company before the award of the contract for cleaning, messengerial and other support functions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112853","112853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789197","2017-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will develop scientific training in autism for work coaches in Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112818","112818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789198","2017-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2017 to Question 110670, on work capability assessment, when he plans to publish the document setting out his Department's recent work, its response to the consultation and its next steps.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112820","112820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789199","2017-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of, and promote, the Access to Work programme.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112822","112822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789200","2017-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of existing legislation regulating the sale of fireworks.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112830","112830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789201","2017-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government has made an assessment of the effect of the UK's withdrawal from the EU on the cost of EU allowances.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112848","112848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789202","2017-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to introduce small modular reactors to the UK.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112907","112907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789203","2017-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the UK plans to seek observer status at the European Agency for Safety and Health at Work after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112900","112900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789204","2017-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the UK plans to seek formal co-operation with the European Foundation for the Improvement of Living and Working Conditions after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112901","112901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789205","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of moving to a Smart Grid on energy-intensive industries; and what discussions he has had with representatives of such industries.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113018","113018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789206","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to respond to the report of the Law Commission, Consumer Prepayments on Retailer Insolvency, HC 543, published on 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112978","112978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789207","2017-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph two of page 77 of the Clean Growth Strategy, when the consultation on making the private rented sector energy efficiency regulations more effective will open.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112892","112892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789208","2017-11-20","Department for International Trade","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with which countries the EU has trade deals; and how many of those countries he has visited since taking office.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112931","112931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789209","2017-11-20","Department for International Trade","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with countries that the EU has trade deals with about the operation of free trade agreements after March 2019.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112804","112804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789210","2017-11-20","Department for International Trade","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans he has to maintain elements of existing free trade agreements between the EU and other countries when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112805","112805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789211","2017-11-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions his Department has had with Michel Barnier on the future of non-UK EU citizens working in the Civil Service in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112828","112828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789212","2017-11-16","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps he is taking to ensure that food standards will be maintained after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113007","113007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789213","2017-11-16","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on exports from farms in North West Durham constituency.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113004","113004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789214","2017-11-16","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his policy is on protecting the existing rights of British citizens residing in Switzerland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112941","112941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789215","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the value to the UK economy of mid-level skills or those at Standard Occupational Classification levels 2 and 3; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112963","112963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789216","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what external engagement her Department is engaged in to improve its understanding of the importance to the UK economy of access to mid-skilled labour or labour rated at Standard Occupational Classification skill levels 2 and 3; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112964","112964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789217","2017-11-16","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the estimated cost to the public purse is of the additional lawyers who are being recruited to deal with the complexities of the work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112960","112960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789219","2017-11-20","Cabinet Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many more people were registered to vote as of 1 November 2017 than was the case at the time of the publication of the official 2015 electoral register in (a) Liverpool, Walton constituency, (b) Liverpool and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113051","113051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789220","2017-11-20","Cabinet Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to replicate the Ministry of Justice Data Lab model across other government departments.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113063","113063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789221","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to extend creative tax relief to new sectors.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113062","113062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789222","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what income the Exchequer has received from duty on (a) online gambling and (b) betting shop income in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113121","113121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789223","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the remit and activities are of the joint initiatives between HM Revenue and Customs and the Department for Work and Pensions referred to as Late, Missing and Incorrect.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113074","113074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789224","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to delay UK implementation of the EU Commission's proposals for a European track and trace scheme for the tobacco market.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113135","113135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789225","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the inter-operability of the EU Commission's proposals for a pan-European track and trace scheme for the tobacco market and the existing tobacco retail registration scheme in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113136","113136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789226","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on small businesses in Northern Ireland of the proposal from the EU Commission for a European track and trace scheme for the tobacco market.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113137","113137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789227","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the EU Commission's proposal for a pan-European track and trace scheme for the tobacco market in tackling the illicit tobacco trade in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113138","113138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789228","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 112174, on charities: VAT, what recent representations he has received from (a) business and (b) charity organisations on exempting trading subsidiaries of charities from the Government's Making Tax Digital scheme.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113140","113140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789229","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111358, on the Royal Bank of Scotland: small businesses, what representations he has received from business organisations on the date for publication of the further report of the Financial Conduct Authority on Royal Bank of Scotland's treatment of small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113141","113141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789230","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111380, on small businesses: technology, what recent representations he has received from business organisations on the use of research development tax credits and the effectiveness of those tax credits in supporting business growth and job creation.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113142","113142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789231","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111345, on bank services: small businesses, what representations he has received from business organisations on the (a) accessibility of full banking services for small and medium-sized enterprises when their bank branch closes and (b) suitability of the Post Office counter network for business banking.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113143","113143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789232","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111438, on Revenue and Customs, how many staff work in the joint initiative between HM Revenue and Customs and the Department for Work and Pensions referred to as Late, Missing and Incorrect.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113125","113125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789233","2017-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what financial assistance he plans to provide to local authorities to support their investigations into the safety of cladding on all properties.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113106","113106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789234","2017-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the results of October to December 2016 consultation on homes in multiple occupation and residential licensing reform.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113129","113129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789235","2017-11-16","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children were placed 20 miles or more outside the boundary of their local authority in (a) Redcar and Cleveland, (b) the North East and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113039","113039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789236","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with (a) Stoke-on-Trent City Council and (b) the Care Quality Commission on the review of the local health and social care system report published by the Core Quality Commission on 10 November 2017.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113031","113031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789237","2017-11-16","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the cost to local authorities in England of using independent fostering agencies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113040","113040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789238","2017-11-16","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of hours taken as long-term sickness leave by social workers in (a) Redcar and Cleveland Borough Council, (b) the North East and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113034","113034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789239","2017-11-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has carried out an assessment of the effectiveness of Help to Rent projects in helping homeless people access housing in the private rental market.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113088","113088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789240","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of fixed-odds betting terminals on gambling addiction rates in North West Durham.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113049","113049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789241","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to enhance provision of internet services in the rural areas of North West Durham.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113044","113044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789242","2017-11-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to extend the City of Football scheme following the two-year pilot in Nottingham.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113093","113093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789243","2017-11-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of City of Football status on Nottingham.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113094","113094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789244","2017-11-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how her Department is working with the Department for Education to increase organised sport in schools.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113090","113090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789245","2017-11-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to encourage female and BAME involvement in organised sport.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113091","113091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789246","2017-11-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of people played football regularly in (a) the UK and (b) Nottinghamshire in each of the last three years; and what proportion of those people were (i) female and (ii) BAME.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113092","113092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789248","2017-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2017 to Question 111545, on European fighter aircraft: exports, what representations he has received from (a) business organisations and (b) trade unions on support for the sale of Typhoon aircraft.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113144","113144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789249","2017-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111413, on military aircraft: procurement, what representations he has received from business organisations on the content of Defence Industrial policy.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113145","113145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789250","2017-11-16","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the levels of sexual harassment in schools in North West Durham.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113109","113109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789251","2017-11-16","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of teacher and other school professionals' experience of referring children and young people to the Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services; and what analysis has been conducted by her Department of the time taken from referral to treatment for such services.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113110","113110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789252","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what safeguards her Department operates to prevent the abuse of student loan funding by private Higher Education providers.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113082","113082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789253","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has been paid to students of private Higher Education providers who were subsequently determined to be ineligible in each of the last five full financial years.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113081","113081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789254","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the additional ring-fenced RDEL her Department will require to fund the increased RAB charge resulting from the increase to post-2012 loan repayment thresholds in each of the next three financial years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113057","113057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789255","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional funding allocation her Department will receive for each of the next three financial years to fund the increased RAB charge resulting from the increase to post-2012 loan repayment thresholds.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113058","113058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789256","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what monitoring and scrutiny of student recruitment agents for private Higher Education and Further Education providers her Department undertakes.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113080","113080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789257","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what safeguards her Department proposes that the Office for Students should implement to prevent the abuse of student loan funding by private higher education providers in respect of new private providers who will be eligible to offer courses under the provisions of the Higher Education and Research Act 2017.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113083","113083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789258","2017-11-20","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions Ministers or officials of her Department have had with the Chief Executive of the Student Loans Company on protections for higher education students enrolled with private providers.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113084","113084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789259","2017-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the average water and sewerage charge was for schools across local authorities in the South East in 2016-17.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113097","113097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789260","2017-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the average water and sewerage charge was for schools in Garston and Halewood constituency in 2016-17.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113098","113098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789261","2017-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the average water and sewerage charge was for schools across local authorities in the North West in 2016-17.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113096","113096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789262","2017-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to review the application to schools of the Guidance to Water and Sewerage Undertakers in relation to Concessionary Schemes for Community Groups for Surface Water and Highways Drainage Charges.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113099","113099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789263","2017-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the extent of renewed tunnel building into Israel by Hamas in Gaza.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113130","113130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789264","2017-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the extent of Hezbollah's weapon arsenal.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113131","113131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789265","2017-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the progress made on Iran's ballistic missile programme.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113132","113132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789266","2017-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the diplomatic implications of recent violence in Israel and the West Bank.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113133","113133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789267","2017-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the extent of institutionalised radicalisation in the Palestinian territories.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113134","113134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789268","2017-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is offering to Jagtar Singh Johal.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113073","113073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789269","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 110811, on patient transport, whether any meetings held in the last three years between the Secretary of State for Health and the Secretary of State for Transport discussed the effect of decreases to (a) bus routes and (b) the frequency of bus services on the ability of older people to access NHS appointments.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112986","112986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789270","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 110811, what discussions (a) Ministers or (b) officials in his Department have held with (i) Ministers or (ii) officials in the Department for Transport on the effect of decreases to (A) bus routes and (B) the frequency of bus services on the ability of older people to access NHS appointments.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112987","112987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789271","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his comments on the Andrew Marr BBC television programme on 29 October 2017, how many of the 4,000 more staff working in mental health trusts than there were seven years ago (a) are new members of staff and (b) previously worked for a primary care trust and transferred to a mental health trust after the NHS reorganisation of 2013.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113085","113085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789272","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his comments on the Andrew Marr BBC television programme on 29 October 2017, what specific mental health conditions are being treated among the 1,400 more people being treated each day.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113086","113086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789273","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the variation in (a) incidence and (b) mortality rates in pancreatic cancer between clinical commissioning group areas.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113123","113123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789274","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Five Year Forward View for Mental Health, what progress has been made on the development and publication of a comprehensive set of mental health care pathways; and what steps he is taking to ensure that such pathways include clear access and waiting time standards, quality standards, workforce requirements, and guidance for commissioners.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113064","113064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789275","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 111157, on dental services, what assessment he has made of the satisfaction rates of low-income citizens for dental healthcare services in 2017.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113126","113126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789276","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his assessment is of the adequacy of the level of research spend on pancreatic cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113065","113065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789277","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide an updated timetable for the publication and delivery of mental health pathways as set out in page 36 of the Five Year Forward View for Mental Health.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113127","113127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789278","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the reasons for variation in mortality rates for pancreatic cancer in each clinical commissioning group area.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113113","113113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789279","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of replacing the 10-year statutory time limit for the storage of frozen eggs and semen with a system of five-yearly reviews; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113114","113114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789280","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he holds on how many community pharmacies run by Celesio UK in Garston and Halewood constituency will be closed as part of the company's recent announcement to close 190 of its community pharmacies across the UK.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113101","113101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789281","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the UK plans to seek to participate in the European Centre for Disease Prevention and Control after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113115","113115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789282","2017-11-20","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons publication of mental health pathways for Crisis Care, Perinatal mental health, Children and young people's mental health, and Acute mental health care has been delayed; and when he expects those pathways will be published.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113128","113128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789283","2017-11-16","Department of Health","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many community pharmacies in Garston and Halewood constituency are owned by Celesio UK.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113100","113100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789284","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many warranted officers there were in Staffordshire Police on 1 January in (a) 2011, (b) 2012, (c) 2013, (d) 2014, (e) 2015, (f) 2016 and (g) 2017.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113111","113111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789285","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she will take to ensure Merseyside Police have adequate funding to tackle recent increases in gun crime, following the meeting with the Minister of State for Security on 18 July 2017.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113105","113105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789286","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the procedure is for a person to make an appeal against allegations made under the Prevention of Terrorism Act 2005.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113050","113050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789287","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugees have been resettled under the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Resettlement Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113048","113048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789288","2017-11-16","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the UK plans to seek formal participation in the European Policing College after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113041","113041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789289","2017-11-20","Home Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answers of 7 September 2017 to Questions 6955 and 8408, what public appointments process was used to appoint the Independent Anti-Slavery Commissioner for a second term; and how his performance in that role was reviewed.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113075","113075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789290","2017-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports the Government has received of possible human rights abuses by the Government of Togo against its citizens; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113061","113061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789291","2017-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports the Government has received on potential violations of the commitment to democracy, protection of human rights and other Commonwealth principles by the Government of Togo.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113060","113060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789292","2017-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment the Government has made of the political situation in Togo; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113059","113059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789293","2017-11-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what is the Government's estimate of (a) baseline certified normal accommodation and (b) operational capacity in England and Wales following the completion of the new for old prison regeneration and building plan.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113124","113124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789294","2017-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many animal cruelty offences and convictions there have been in Romford in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113043","113043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789295","2017-11-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 122018, on Community Rehabilitation Companies; staff, whether any community rehabilitation company contract contains an obligation to employ a specified minimum number of staff.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113122","113122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789296","2017-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 106318 on witnesses: video recordings, what the timetable is for the roll-out of section 28 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999 to the remaining 68 Crown Courts.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113046","113046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789297","2017-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2017 to Question 110760 on courts: Sunderland, for what reasons he failed to engage with the invitation to visit the court building in Sunderland.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113033","113033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789298","2017-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders were given community sentences in North Wales in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113032","113032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789299","2017-11-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the letter of 31 October 2017 from the Head of the Mental Health Casework Section (MHCS) on delays in mental health casework decisions;, how many (a) backlog cases and (b) critical work cases for restricted patients have been cleared by the MHCS in each month since April 2016.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113087","113087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789300","2017-11-21","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he will publish the guidance and regulations relating to the franchise for the Bus Services Act 2017.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113089","113089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789301","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2017 to Question 112096, on Railways: North of England, what assessment has been undertaken on the cases where serving locations on the planned Northern Powerhouse Rail between cities may enhance the business case, and therefore be beneficial.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113045","113045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789302","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate the cost of including a check on the age of tyres as part of the annual MOT test of public service vehicles.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113095","113095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789303","2017-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the UK plans to seek formal participation with the European Global Navigation Satellite Systems Agency after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113112","113112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789304","2017-11-20","Women and Equalities","2017-11-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what plans she has to ensure that gender pay gap reporting is effectively enforced when it comes into effect in April 2018.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113069","113069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789305","2017-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many former claimants of disability living allowance in Garston and Halewood constituency who have been unsuccessful in their claim for personal independence payments have been waiting more than (a) six weeks, (b) three months and (c) six months for their appeal to be heard.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113103","113103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789306","2017-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 2 November 2017, HCWS218, on social security, how many previously unsuccessful personal independence payment (PIP) claimants from Garston and Halewood constituency are now eligible for PIP under the updated PIP guidelines.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113102","113102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789307","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department provides to disabled people who claim universal credit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113068","113068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789308","2017-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111677, on social security benefits: North West Durham, what the (a) sample size and (b) margin of error in the data provided was.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113107","113107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789309","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who identify as disabled are currently in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113070","113070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789310","2017-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received from (a) the Trussell Trust and (b) other UK food bank providers over the last 12 months.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113104","113104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789311","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of universal credit advance payment recipients receive their advance payment within (a) the first day, (b) the first two days and (c) the first week of application.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113056","113056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789312","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect the introduction of work coaches has had on the number of disabled people in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113067","113067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789313","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of personal independence payment claimants are refused that entitlement upon making a claim.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113066","113066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789314","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of personal independence payment claimants are successful on appeal at tribunal.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113054","113054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789315","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the Government's definition is of what constitutes a change in circumstance in the transition to universal credit.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113055","113055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789316","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people aged 18 to 21 currently receive help with rent in (a) Liverpool, Walton constituency, (b) the North West and (c) England.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113053","113053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789317","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families currently receiving benefits have three children or more in (a) Liverpool, Walton constituency, (b) the North West and (c) England.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113052","113052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789318","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to collect information on the experiences of disabled people claiming universal credit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113071","113071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789319","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of disabled people who will be entitled to transitional protection through managed migration from legacy benefits to universal credit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113072","113072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789320","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to amend universal credit rules to allow deduction of unreimbursed work expenses as is the case in the tax credits system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113079","113079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789321","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 9 November 2017 to Question 111087 on telephone services, how many of his Department's telephone lines are (a) 01, 02 or 03, (b) chargeable 08, (c) 0800 or 0808, (d) 084, (e) 087 and (f) any other numbers.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113076","113076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789322","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to introduce a universal credit service to support vulnerable claimants analogous to HM Revenue and Customs' Needs Enhanced Support.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113077","113077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789323","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to amend universal credit rules to allow deduction of pension contributions in applying the minimum income floor; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113078","113078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789324","2017-11-16","Department for Education","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the UK plans to seek formal participation in or membership of the European Training Foundation after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113042","113042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789325","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111391, on business: ICT, what recent representations he has received from business organisations on ensuring that the Government's digital transformation programmes are affordable for (a) small and medium-sized enterprises, (b) micro businesses and (c) charities.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113116","113116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789326","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111294, on manufacturing industries: North West, what meetings he has had with the North West Business Leadership Team and other organisations which represent businesses in the North West in the last three years.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113117","113117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789327","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 112160, on the Royal Bank of Scotland, whether that Answer refers to (a) the Financial Conduct Authority's investigation which has already concluded or (b) the second Financial Conduct Authority investigation which has yet to report its findings.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113118","113118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789328","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111293, on Vauxhall Motors: employment, what recent representations he has received from (a) business organisations and (b) trade unions on safeguarding jobs at the Vauxhall plant in Ellesmere Port.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113120","113120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789329","2017-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111346, on small businesses: advisory services, what recent representations he has received from business organisations on the adequacy of the availability of mentoring services to small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113119","113119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789330","2017-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the amount of the financial reserves held under the Microgeneration Certification Scheme; and what plans he has for the use of those reserves.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113139","113139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789331","2017-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the privatisation of Royal Mail on the provision of postal services in North West Durham.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113108","113108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789332","2017-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations were made by the Government to the EU during the drafting of the EU Conflict Minerals Regulation (EU) 2017/821; and if he will make it his policy to incorporate that regulation into UK law after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113047","113047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789333","2017-11-16","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2017 to Question 111141, on EU law, what assessment he has made of which elements of the EU's supranational framework will not be retained.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113146","113146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788379","2017-11-15","Attorney General","2017-11-13","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussions he has had with the Crown Prosecution Service on cases involving sexual harassment.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112789","112789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788380","2017-11-16","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to answer Question 109638, tabled on 25 October 2017.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112759","112759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788381","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that (a) young people, (b) students, (c) people with disabilities and (d) people from minority ethnic groups are not disenfranchised as a result of voter ID pilots.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112479","112479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788382","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to prohibit the handling of postal ballots by campaigners for political parties.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112480","112480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788383","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when his Department plans to complete its review of the Government's website.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112481","112481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788384","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people registered to vote anonymously in the last general election.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112482","112482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788385","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of Government Departments use the services of the Government Digital Service.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112483","112483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788386","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance he has issued to the Elections Claims Unit on the publication of communications or queries relating to expenses for previous polls during subsequent polls.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112484","112484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788387","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the period to return deposits to one calendar week after the date of a poll.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112485","112485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788388","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the level of understanding of democracy and the UK political system in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112526","112526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788389","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent representations his Department has received on the votes at 16 campaign.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112527","112527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788390","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he has taken to locate Government Departments (a) outside London and (b) in Scotland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112549","112549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788391","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress the Government is making on trialling new methods of voter identification.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112683","112683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788392","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which local authorities expressed interest in conducting a voter ID pilot in polling stations for the May 2018 local elections but subsequently decided not to proceed with that pilot.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112666","112666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788393","2017-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2017 to Question 1216, on low pay: Barnsley Central, what steps he is taking to increase the average gross hourly earning in Barnsley.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112717","112717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788394","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111542, how many discussions his Department has had with the UK Government Ministers or Welsh Government Ministers in the last 12 months on valuation office closures; on what dates those discussions took place; who participated in those discussions; and whether there were any actionable outcomes from those discussions.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112656","112656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788395","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 27 April 2017 to Question 71682, on motor vehicles: insurance, if he has decided the direction of future policy on insurance premiums.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112693","112693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788396","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the timetable is for the Prudential Regulation Authority to issue guidance for insurance firms headquartered in the EEA on the criteria for authorisations for third party branches and subsidiaries in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112665","112665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788397","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Prudential Regulation Authority on its expected guidance to insurance firms headquartered in the EEA but which have branches in the UK on the process for future authorisations after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112664","112664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788398","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the ability of the financial service industry to continue to service cross-border clients after 2019 in the event that a transition period has not been agreed with the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112619","112619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788399","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111905, on Valuation Office Agency, against which benchmarks performance has been measured at those valuation offices marked for closure.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112570","112570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788400","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many enforcement actions for the sale of illegal tobacco products have taken place in North Wales in which locations in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112554","112554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788401","2017-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations he has received on the HSBC pension clawback policy.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112544","112544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788402","2017-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations he has received on the defined benefit occupational pension scheme at HSBC.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112545","112545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788403","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the potential effect on small and medium-sized enterprises of any reduction in eligibility for VAT registration.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112548","112548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788404","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people with non-domiciled status in the UK have left the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112496","112496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788405","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Government of Guernsey on the automatic exchange of beneficial ownership information with HM Revenue and Customs and UK law enforcement agencies and the setting up of a public register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112777","112777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788406","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Government of the Isle of Man on the automatic exchange of beneficial ownership information with HM Revenue and Customs and UK law enforcement agencies and the setting up of a public register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112778","112778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788407","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Government of the Jersey on the automatic exchange of beneficial ownership information with HM Revenue and Customs and UK law enforcement agencies and the setting up of a public register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112779","112779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788408","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Government of Anguilla on the automatic exchange of beneficial ownership information with HM Revenue and Customs and UK Law enforcement agencies and the setting up of a public register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112790","112790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788409","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Government of Gibraltar on the automatic exchange of beneficial ownership information with HM Revenue and Customs and UK Law enforcement agencies and the setting up of a public register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112791","112791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788410","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Government of Monserrat on the automatic exchange of beneficial ownership information with HM Revenue and Customs and UK Law enforcement agencies and setting up a public register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112792","112792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788411","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Government of Bermuda on the automatic exchange of beneficial ownership information with HM Revenue and Customs and UK Law enforcement agencies and setting up a public register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112793","112793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788412","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 112013, on HM Revenue and Customs staff, how many employees were employed in the (a) High Net Worth Unit and (b) Affluent Unit on 31 March 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112794","112794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788413","2017-11-16","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what target has been set for the Resource and Accounting Budgetary Charge on student loans.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112729","112729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788414","2017-11-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 9 November 2017 to Question 111426, on job creation: enterprise zones, what representations he has received from representatives of business organisations about the effectiveness of enterprise zones.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112732","112732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788415","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to prevent councils using offshore companies to avoid paying stamp duty when purchasing commercial property.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112476","112476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788416","2017-11-15","Department for Education","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students aged 24 or over have enrolled on courses at Level 3  or above in (a) healthcare, (b) social care and (c) business and accounting in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112507","112507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788417","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the consultation on social care announced in the Queen's Speech 2017 will begin; and for how long that consultation will last.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112528","112528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788418","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will ensure that the consultation on social care, announced in the Queen's Speech 2017, includes local authorities and people with dementia.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112555","112555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788419","2017-11-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2017 to Question 109056, on fracking: planning permission, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to make planning decisions the responsibility of the National Planning Regime.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112702","112702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788420","2017-11-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with HM Treasury on funding for existing EU structural and investment projects; and if all such projects meet the criteria of providing strong value for money and are in line with domestic strategic priorities.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112567","112567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788421","2017-11-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, in what ways the Government and HM Land Registry (a) monitor and (b) prevent land banking in local communities.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112667","112667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788422","2017-11-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to prevent land banking in local communities.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112668","112668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788423","2017-11-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that part-time students receive reductions in council tax proportionate to their studies.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112648","112648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788424","2017-11-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Local Government Association and individual local authorities on their progress on waste minimisation.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112673","112673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788425","2017-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the long term success and sustainability of the UK video games industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112653","112653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788426","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will place in the Library a copy of the KPMG report referenced in the Impact Report for her Department's Consultation on proposals for Changes to Gaming Machines and Social Responsibility Matters.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112719","112719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788427","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2016 to Question 107989, on gaming machines, what estimate she has made of the fiscal impact of each of the options set out in the Consultation on proposals for Changes to Gaming Machines and Social Responsibility Measures; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112720","112720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788428","2017-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with representatives from national museums sponsored by her Department on the issue of copyright on photographic reproductions of paintings, prints and drawings in the collections of those museums; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112649","112649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788429","2017-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of the total net income received by national museums sponsored by her Department as a result of charging for photographic reproductions of out of copyright artworks in the last financial year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112650","112650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788430","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the wider economic effect, other than on gambling industry revenue and player utility, of reducing B2 machine stakes; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112694","112694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788431","2017-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2017 to Question 108578, on cultural heritage, whether the figures cited include monies for the safeguarding of crafts other than those that contribute to the maintenance or restoration of an existing tangible heritage asset; and whether the Heritage Lottery Fund has set aside a specific sum for securing the continuation of those same crafts not including recording and oral history.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112579","112579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788432","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of changes to local authority budgets on the level of professional expertise available in the museums sector.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112605","112605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788433","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on maintaining freedom of movement between the UK and EU countries for time-limited activities within the creative industries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112606","112606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788434","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, to what proportion of UK Premises superfast broadband is available.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112607","112607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788435","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, in what proportion of UK premises 4G is available.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112608","112608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788436","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, in what proportion of the UK geographic area voice coverage is available.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112610","112610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788437","2017-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, at which locations staff of her Department working on issues related to (a) Hull City of Culture 2017 and (b) other City of Culture bids are based.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112581","112581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788438","2017-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will reduce the maximum stake on fixed-odds betting terminals to £2.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112525","112525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788439","2017-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with Scottish Government Ministers on the delivery of broadband roll-out between Scotland and England.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112515","112515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788440","2017-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the development and upgrading of USAF Fairford; and who will bear the costs of that development and upgrading.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112539","112539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788441","2017-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many senior officers from the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Army and (c) RAF have been assigned to duties within or seconded to HM Treasury in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112465","112465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788442","2017-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the functions and roles are that are performed by senior military officers assigned or seconded to HM Treasury.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112503","112503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788443","2017-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many meetings there were between senior officers from (a) Navy, (b) Army and (c) Air Command and officials of HM Treasury in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112467","112467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788444","2017-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many meetings there were between senior officers from (a) Navy, (b) Army and (c) Air Command and officials of HM Treasury in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112468","112468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788445","2017-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many finance staff within (a) Navy, (b) Army and (c) Air Command (i) have (ii) are working towards and (iii) do not have a professional accountancy qualification.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112469","112469"
