"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422307","2015-10-22","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of resources allocated within the Metropolitan Police to investigate cases of historical child sexual abuse; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12459","12459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422308","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with police authorities on the use of CCTV cameras with facial recognition and biometric tracking capabilities.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12296","12296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422309","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether there are processes in place to ensure that people not suspected of criminal offences can request deletion of data recovered by CCTV cameras with facial recognition and biometric tracking capabilities.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12291","12291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422310","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what access foreign security services have in the UK to CCTV cameras with facial recognition and biometric tracking capabilities.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12290","12290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422311","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to ensure that assessments of applications for leave to remain in the UK provide sufficient personal consideration to meet the individual needs of applicants.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12275","12275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422312","2015-10-22","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2015 to Question 11726, how many Prevent co-ordinators are employed in England and Wales.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12358","12358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422313","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from civil liberties campaign groups on the operation of and use of data from CCTV cameras with facial recognition and biometric tracking capabilities.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12294","12294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422314","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what legal advice she has sought on the use by police of data from CCTV cameras with facial recognition and biometric tracking capabilities; and if she will publish that advice.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12295","12295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422315","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support the Government is providing to disabled refugees from Syria who are currently in Europe.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12320","12320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422316","2015-10-27","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made on implementing the Prime Minister's proposal that mothers' names should be added to marriage certificates.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12409","12409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422317","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of current legislation regulating the use of CCTV cameras with facial recognition and biometric tracking capabilities.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12293","12293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422318","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what fields of data are held about people recorded by CCTV cameras with facial recognition and biometric tracking capabilities.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12292","12292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422319","2015-10-22","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse was of legal fees in the case of Bondada, R (on the application of) v Secretary of State for the Home Department [2015] EWHC 2661 (Admin) (15 October 2015).","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12371","12371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422320","2015-10-21","Department for International Development","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 16 September 2015 to Question 9671, for what reasons the Government cannot mandate companies to join the 2013 Accord on Fire and Safety in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12284","12284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422321","2015-10-21","Department for International Development","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 16 September 2015 to Question 9671, what estimate the Government has made of the proportion of UK companies which have joined the 2013 Accord on Fire and Safety in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12285","12285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422322","2015-10-21","Department for International Development","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to reduce aid spending in countries with their own space programme.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12448","12448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422323","2015-10-21","Department for International Development","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to prepare for the implementation of the proposed General Data Protection Regulation; which non-departmental public body (NDPB) and agencies overseen by her Department will be affected by that Regulation; and what estimate she has made of the potential liability of her Department and its agencies and NDPBs in connection with that proposed Regulation.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12426","12426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422324","2015-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to prepare for the implementation of the proposed General Data Protection Regulation; which non-departmental public bodies (NDPBs) and agencies overseen by his Department will be affected by that Regulation; and what estimate he has made of the potential liability of his Department, its agencies and NDPBs in connection with that proposed Regulation.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12427","12427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422325","2015-10-21","Department of Health","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people diagnosed with a mental health condition received a custodial sentence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12444","12444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422326","2015-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many magistrates have resigned from their positions in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12373","12373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422327","2015-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, further to the Answer of 9 October 2015 to Question 11183, if he will estimate the market value of the freehold buildings used by Grantham Magistrates' Court.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12467","12467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422328","2015-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what meetings he has had with trades union officials on the Trade Union Bill.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12372","12372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422329","2015-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the oral evidence given by Ann Beasley, DG Finance and Corporate Services, Ministry of Justice, to the Justice Committee on 13 October 2015, HC 416, Question 30, how many agency staff his Department employed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12353","12353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422330","2015-10-22","Department of Health","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times ambulances have been required to attend prisons as a result of emergency call-outs relating to (a) illegal drugs, (b) prescribed drugs and (c) psychoactive substances in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12352","12352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422331","2015-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the oral evidence given by Michael Spurr to the Justice Committee on 13 October 2015, HC 416, how many officials of his Department have travelled to Saudi Arabia in relation to their work with Just Solutions International; and what the cost to the public purse was of that travel.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12354","12354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422332","2015-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the proportion of people living in Copeland Borough who will be able to travel to (a) a magistrates' court and (b) a family court by public transport in under 60 minutes if the proposed closure of West Cumbria Court goes ahead.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12351","12351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422333","2015-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many under-18 year olds in prison have been starred up in each prison in each month during each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12319","12319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422334","2015-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the monetary value has been of criminal courts charges (a) imposed and (b) collected since the introduction of those charges.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12363","12363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422335","2015-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many days the Crown Court sat in each court chamber at Warrington in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12336","12336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422336","2015-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people (a) attempted to take and (b) took their own lives at Foston Hall Prison, Derbyshire, was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12322","12322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422337","2015-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the expected staffing rate at Foston Hall Prison, Derbyshire, is; and how often his Department assesses compliance with that rate.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12323","12323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422338","2015-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance or direction his Department has given on the amount of time that inmates at Foston Hall Prison, Derbyshire, should spend outside their cells; and what monitoring of such time his Department carries out.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12324","12324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422339","2015-10-22","Leader of the House","2015-10-19","To ask the Leader of the House, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the Leader of the House being elected by the whole House.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12452","12452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422340","2015-10-21","Northern Ireland Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps her Department has taken to prepare for the implementation of the proposed General Data Protection Regulation; which non-departmental public bodies (NDPBs) overseen by her Department will be affected by that Regulation; and what estimate she has made of the potential liability of her Department and its NDPBs in connection with that proposed Regulation.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12428","12428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422341","2015-10-21","Northern Ireland Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will make extra funding available for digital technology so that full monitoring of dissident Republicans can be maintained.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12489","12489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422342","2015-10-22","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Wilson Doctrine has been consistently applied to the communications of the hon. Member for Lincoln since his election; and whether that hon. Member has been subject to surveillance.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12436","12436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422343","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Wilson Doctrine has been consistently applied to the communications of the hon. Member for Washington and Sunderland West; and whether that hon. Member has been subject to surveillance.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12274","12274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422344","2015-10-21","Scotland Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps his Department has taken to prepare for the implementation of the proposed General Data Protection Regulation; and what estimate he has made of the potential liability of his Department in connection with that proposed Regulation.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12429","12429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422345","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to prepare for the implementation of the proposed General Data Protection Regulation; which non-departmental public bodies (NDPBs) and agencies overseen by his Department will be affected by that Regulation; and what estimate he has made of the potential liability of his Department, its agencies and NDPBs in connection with that proposed Regulation.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12430","12430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422346","2015-10-22","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2015 to Question 4425, when he expects Network Rail to publish an update to its industry electrification strategy.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12356","12356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422347","2015-10-22","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times his Department received complaints that an Oyster machine is not working properly on a London bus in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12382","12382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422348","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to monitor the use of drones in UK airspace.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12485","12485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422349","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that peak noise measurements are used by HS2 Ltd when developing proposals on the night use of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12280","12280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422350","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of noise on residents living across open land, with no sound barriers, from the proposed High Speed 2 route through Eddisbury.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12282","12282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422351","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the effect of noise from High Speed 2 on rural communities is minimised.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12283","12283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422352","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of legislation to prevent pavement parking in London.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12297","12297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422353","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received from local authorities, charities and disability groups on pavement parking.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12298","12298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422354","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to tackle vehicle parking on pavements.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12299","12299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422355","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the cost of the public inquiry into the New Generation Transport trolleybus scheme; and what he expects the final cost of that inquiry to be.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12300","12300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422356","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the public inquiry into the New Generation Transport trolleybus scheme to report.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12301","12301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422357","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of moving the Lakeside Energy from Waste Plant from its current site; and what his policy is on whether that cost would be met by Heathrow Airport or the Government.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12311","12311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422358","2015-10-22","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to review the adequacy of public transport options in the West Midlands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12393","12393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422359","2015-10-22","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to review the safety of roads and highways in the West Midlands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12394","12394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422360","2015-10-22","Department for Transport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to make an assessment of the case for an Eastern Branch of Crossrail 2 serving Hackney Central, Hackney Wick, Stratford, East Ham and Barking.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12388","12388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422361","2015-10-21","Wales Office","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps his Department has taken to prepare for the implementation of the proposed General Data Protection Regulation; and what estimate he has made of the potential liability of his Department in connection with that proposed Regulation.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12432","12432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422362","2015-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the implications for the workload of Jobcentre Plus of providing appropriate advice and support to parents with children aged two, three and four who (a) have never been employed, (b) do not have five A* to C grades at GCSE, (c) have a history of addiction, (d) have mental health problems and (e) were formerly looked-after children.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12345","12345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422363","2015-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to prepare for the implementation of the proposed General Data Protection Regulation; which non-departmental public bodies (NDPBs) and agencies overseen by his Department will be affected by that Regulation; and what estimate he has made of the potential liability of his Department, its agencies and NDPBs in connection with that proposed Regulation.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12433","12433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422364","2015-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants in (a) Liverpool, Walton constituency and (b) Liverpool have appealed against sanctions; what the average length of sanctions in those areas was in the last 12 months; and how many such appeals were successful.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12456","12456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422365","2015-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who are in receipt of employment and support allowance in (a) the work-related activity group and (b) the support group were initially assessed by a work capability assessment as being fit for work.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12340","12340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422366","2015-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants have been sanctioned in (a) Liverpool, Walton constituency and (b) Liverpool since the implementation of that policy.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12398","12398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422367","2015-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people with cancer who will be affected by proposals under the Welfare Reform and Work Bill to reduce the amount paid to new claimants in the employment and support allowance work related activity group.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12386","12386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422368","2015-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2015 to Question 11226, for what reasons decisions were not made on 118,039 of the applications his Department received in the period between October 2014 and September 2015 for Short Term Benefit Advance.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12404","12404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422369","2015-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish an impact assessment of the Universal Credit (Work Allowance) Amendment Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12392","12392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422370","2015-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants who are in the support group were previously in the work-related activity group.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12337","12337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422371","2015-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants there have been in (a) Liverpool, Walton constituency and (b) Liverpool city region since that policy's implementation.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12397","12397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422372","2015-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what (a) guidelines and (b) recommended timescales exist for processing last-minute Access to Work extra support requests.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12410","12410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422373","2015-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints his Department has received about the assessment assistance offered by CAPITA.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12407","12407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422374","2015-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2015 to Question 11269, whether a personal independence payment assessment provider would be breaking the terms of its contract with his Department if it were to provide audio equipment for use in assessments which complied with the required specifications.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12318","12318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422375","2015-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who had previously been in receipt of disability living allowance have been found ineligible for personal independence payments following assessment assistance by CAPITA.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12408","12408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422376","2015-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who were subject to the benefit cap between May 2015 and August 2015 had been in receipt of working tax credit at any point during the 12 months prior to May 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12276","12276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422835","2015-10-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that fans buying tickets for sporting and cultural events are not disadvantaged by organised gangs of online touts in the secondary ticket market.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901735","901735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423062","2015-10-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to tackle nuisance calls.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901734","901734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423063","2015-10-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his policy is on (a) data protection, (b) sponsorship of the Information Commissioner's Office and (c) sponsorship of the National Archives.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901738","901738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423064","2015-10-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his policy is on the digital single market.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901740","901740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423065","2015-10-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to encourage the Premier League adequately to contribute to the financing of grassroots football.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901739","901739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423066","2015-10-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to commemorate the centenary of the Battle of the Somme.","Biography information for James Berry","James Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901737","901737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421899","2015-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the total amount lost by small firms in the construction sector because of bankruptcies among firms holding cash retentions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12233","12233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421900","2015-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of cash retentions on the viability of small businesses in the construction sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12255","12255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421901","2015-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make it his policy to ensure that cash retentions in the construction industry are placed in trust to safeguard them against possible bankruptcy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12256","12256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421902","2015-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take to increase the number of gifted overseas students studying in the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12273","12273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421903","2015-10-21","Cabinet Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2015 to Question 10532, when he plans for the further 57 local authorities referred to in that Answer to find out about funding for the transition to individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12222","12222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421904","2015-10-21","Cabinet Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2015 to Question 10532, how many local authorities have applied for funding from his Department for the transition to individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12223","12223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421905","2015-10-21","Cabinet Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2015 to Question 10532, on electoral register: finance, with which local authorities his Department is agreeing funding.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12224","12224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421906","2015-10-20","Cabinet Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Department has responsibility for policy on supporting the children of people with alcoholism.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12192","12192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421907","2015-10-21","Cabinet Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to increase voter registration among students.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12200","12200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421908","2015-10-21","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of steps taken by local authorities to tackle loneliness; and what support the Government has provided to local authorities for such work.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12272","12272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421909","2015-10-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the economic benefit of investment in the arts over the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12250","12250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421910","2015-10-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of soldiers have been awarded the Public Services apprenticeship without having attained Level 2 in English and mathematics or having sat a test at Level 2 in English and mathematics as part of their apprenticeship course.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12216","12216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421911","2015-10-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have qualified for a war pension as a result of contracting Hepatitis C or HIV from an infected blood transfusion while serving in the armed forces.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12264","12264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421912","2015-10-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the memorandum from the Director of the US Office of the Secretary of Defense on Observations on the Marine Corps F-35B Demonstration on USS Wasp, published by Project on Government Oversight on 14 September 2015, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy on procurement of the F-35 of that memorandum's finding on that aircraft's reliability and combat readiness.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12180","12180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421913","2015-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many teachers currently work in young offender institutions; and how many of those teachers lack teaching qualifications.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12177","12177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421914","2015-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many teachers working in young offender institutions are qualified to work with young people with (a) special educational needs, (b) autism and (c) mental health issues.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12178","12178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421915","2015-10-21","Department for Education","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are entitled to receive free school meals but do not receive them.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12185","12185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421916","2015-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many young people in young offenders institutions receive 30 hours education each week.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12197","12197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421917","2015-10-21","Department for Education","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2015 to Question 11448, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of providing free school meals for Reception, Year 1 and Year 2 pupils in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12263","12263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421918","2015-10-20","Department for Education","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) primary and (b) secondary school students in (i) Suffolk and (ii) England and Wales have been funded by the pupil premium in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12257","12257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421919","2015-10-21","Department for Education","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential benefits of re-introducing compulsory work experience for under 16 year olds.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12267","12267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421920","2015-10-20","Department for Education","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding has been provided per pupil in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in the county of Suffolk (A) in cash terms and (B) at 2015 prices in each financial year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12207","12207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421921","2015-10-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the estimated cost to the public purse is of the examination into the planning consent application for the Navitus Bay Wind Park under the Planning Act 2008.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12248","12248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421922","2015-10-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Groceries Code Adjudicator in assisting farmers who have been unfairly treated by large retailers.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12254","12254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421923","2015-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Israeli government on the use of force by Israeli security personnel in response to protests.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12182","12182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421924","2015-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Palestinian Authority on action to prevent terrorist attacks in Israel.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12183","12183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421925","2015-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made on human rights in China.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12176","12176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421926","2015-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to assist Middle East countries in learning lessons from Tunisia in overcoming political instability.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12170","12170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421927","2015-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the implications for his Department's advice on travel to Egypt are of the accidental killing of foreign tourists in that country on 13 September 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12171","12171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421928","2015-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for the Israeli/Palestine peace process of Mahmoud Abbas's speech at the United Nations on 30 September 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12172","12172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421929","2015-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made in negotiations with the EU on addressing the level of duties imposed on cane sugar imported into Europe; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12268","12268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421930","2015-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will set out the record of attendance and participation in sessions of the Parliamentary Assembly of the Council of Europe and its committees by those hon. Members of the UK delegation who were appointed to the Parliamentary Assembly on 10 November 2010.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12244","12244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421931","2015-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the work of the members of the UK delegation to the Parliamentary Assembly of the Council of Europe who were appointed on 10 November 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12245","12245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421932","2015-10-21","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2015 to Question 8139, what (a) correspondence and (b) meetings Ministers and officials in his Department have had with Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust on patients being admitted to private facilities outside Lancashire in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12232","12232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421933","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to support carers.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12208","12208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421934","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of nurses in Yorkshire in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16; and what funding was allocated for nursing in Yorkshire in each of those years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12209","12209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421935","2015-10-21","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 September 2015 to Question 9845, what steps have been taken with Breast Cancer Now since the roundtable event.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12247","12247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421936","2015-10-21","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of steps taken by NHS bodies to tackle loneliness.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12271","12271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421937","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the morale of junior doctors of proposed changes to their employment contracts.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12243","12243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421938","2015-10-21","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to address the reported shortfall of 107 million in the Department's 2015 budget and the consequent imbalance in funding for mental health services.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12261","12261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421939","2015-10-21","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve tests for Lyme disease to ensure early diagnosis.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12262","12262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421940","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people on the NHS Organ Donor Register in each of the last five years; and what the number of such people was in each region of the UK.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12179","12179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421941","2015-10-21","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of chronic loneliness among older people on demand for GP appointments in (a) England and (b) Basildon and Billericay constituency.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12202","12202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421942","2015-10-21","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on the provision of medical supplies to NHS facilities in (a) Northamptonshire, (b) the East Midlands and (c) England of the introduction of the new IT system at NHS Supply Chain's Regional Distribution Centre in Rugby.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12199","12199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421943","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve working conditions for employees in the social care sector.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12194","12194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421944","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will include in the next Health Education England mandate a commitment that all foundation year doctors must undertake a rotation in psychiatry.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12195","12195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421945","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will include in the next NHS England mandate a commitment that all foundation year doctors must undertake a rotation in psychiatry.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12196","12196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421946","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish his Department's estimate of the average length of time a person waits between referral for and commencement of alcohol treatment services.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12188","12188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421947","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total number of referrals for alcohol treatment services was in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12189","12189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421948","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total forecast spending on alcohol treatment services is for the future years for which information is available.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12190","12190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421949","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total spending on alcohol treatment services was in England in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12191","12191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421950","2015-10-20","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people arrived at UK airports without travel documents in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12181","12181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421951","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 September 2015 to Question 9820, what information her Department holds on the bail conditions (a) sought and (b) applied in relation to the lorry drivers referred to in that Answer; and what information her Department holds on the whereabouts of those drivers.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12175","12175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421952","2015-10-20","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the number of offences of violence against a person in Bury St Edmunds constituency in the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12270","12270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421953","2015-10-20","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of calls received by Action Fraud result in a police investigation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12259","12259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421954","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the Memorandum of Understanding entered into by her Department with the Saudi Arabian government.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12218","12218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421955","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to work with her French counterpart to allow increased access by humanitarian organisations to the refugee camp at Calais.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12227","12227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421956","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will set out the matters that have been discussed under the Memorandum of Understanding her Department entered into with the Saudi Arabia Ministry of the Interior in March 2014.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12219","12219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421957","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the prevalence of sexual abuse of women in the Calais refugee camp; and what steps her Department is taking to ensure that women's safety in that camp is protected.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12228","12228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421958","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons humanitarian organisations do not operate inside the refugee camps at Calais.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12229","12229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421959","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are engaged in the Organised Immigration Crime Task Force; and in which countries those people are deployed.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12246","12246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421960","2015-10-21","Department for International Development","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2015 to Question 11278, who is responsible for restrictions on commercial and humanitarian shipping to Yemen.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12225","12225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421961","2015-10-21","Department for International Development","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2015 to Question 11278, who is currently responsible for impeding humanitarian access to people in need in Yemen.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12226","12226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421962","2015-10-20","Department for International Development","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support refugee camps near the Syrian border in order to tackle the root causes of migration to Europe.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12173","12173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421963","2015-10-20","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding has been made available to each local authority in London and Essex to resettle refugees in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12174","12174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421964","2015-10-21","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to manage the prevalence of Type 2 diabetes in the prison population; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12249","12249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421965","2015-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the value is of the freehold of Chichester Combined Court Centre.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12236","12236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421966","2015-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the Memorandum of Understanding entered into by his Department with the Saudi Arabian government.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12220","12220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421967","2015-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the offer made to the Saudi Arabian government for its prisons training contract.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12221","12221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421968","2015-10-20","Department for Transport","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) prosecutions and (b) convictions there have been under Article (i) 137, (ii) 139, (iii) 140, (iv) 141 and (v) 142 of the Air Navigation Order 2009 in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12211","12211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421969","2015-10-20","Department for Transport","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) maximum, (b) minimum and (c) average sentence was for people convicted under Article (i) 137, (ii) 139, (iii) 140, (iv) 141 and (v) 142 of the Air Navigation Order 2009 in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12210","12210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421970","2015-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what matters have been discussed under the Memorandum of Understanding on judicial co-operation entered into with Saudi Arabia in September 2014.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12217","12217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421971","2015-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the value is of the freehold of Chichester Crown Court.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12258","12258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421972","2015-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the current proposals are for the use of the Chichester Combined Court Centre freehold property in the event of that court's closure under current proposals.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12260","12260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421973","2015-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether fast track trials in Chichester County Court (a) have been or (b) are planned to be moved to Eastbourne County Court.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12238","12238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421974","2015-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of making Chichester Combined Court Centre compliant with the provisions of the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12239","12239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421975","2015-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much Chichester (a) County Court, (b) Crown Court and (c) Combined Court Centre collected in court fees in the 2014-15 financial year.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12237","12237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421976","2015-10-21","Department of Health","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the prevalence of Type 2 diabetes within the prison population; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12251","12251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421977","2015-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the nutritional adequacy of meals served to the prison population; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12252","12252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421978","2015-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to page 28 of his Department's consultation paper, Proposal on the provision of court and tribunal services in the South East Region, published in July 2015, on what statistical basis the figure of 78 per cent of court usage capacity was calculated; and if he will publish the data underlying that calculation.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12240","12240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421979","2015-10-21","Leader of the House","2015-10-16","To ask the Leader of the House, whether he has had discussions with the Chairs of the Business, Innovation and Skills, International Development, Foreign Affairs and Defence select committees on their re-establishment of the Committees on Arms Export Controls.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12205","12205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421980","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Wilson Doctrine has been consistently applied to the communications of the hon. Member for Rotherham; and whether that hon. Member has been subject to surveillance.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12184","12184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421981","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Wilson Doctrine has been consistently applied to the communications of the hon. Member for Walsall South; and whether that hon. Member has been subject to surveillance.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12204","12204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421982","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Wilson Doctrine has been consistently applied to the parliamentary communications of the hon. Member for Birmingham, Hall Green; and whether that hon. Member has been subject to surveillance.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12234","12234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421983","2015-10-21","Home Office","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Wilson Doctrine has been consistently applied to the parliamentary communications of the hon. Member for South Shields; and whether that hon. Member has been subject to surveillance.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12235","12235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421984","2015-10-20","Department for Transport","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) enforcement cases and (b) out-of-court settlements there were for non-payment of vehicle tax between (i) October 2013 and June 2014 and (ii) October 2014 and June 2015.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12214","12214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421985","2015-10-20","Department for Transport","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2015 to Question 11430, what steps his Department took before 15 September 2015 in relation to bus operators who submitted claims for Bus Service Operators Grant funding to support closed bus services.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12213","12213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421986","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2015 to Question 11431, which key senior stakeholders have been represented at the Bowe Review - Senior Liaison Board on each of the dates referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12231","12231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421987","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2015 to Question 11472, what (a) his Department's expenditure per head and (b) total expenditure from the public purse on cycling in each English region was in each year from 2011-12 to 2014-15; and what expenditure per head on cycling (i) by his Department and (ii) from the public purse is projected to be in each English region in 2015-16.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12230","12230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421988","2015-10-20","Department for Transport","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to deal with the problem of aircraft being targeted by laser pens.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12241","12241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421989","2015-10-20","Department for Transport","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been received from fines generated from vehicle clamping or instant removal for non-payment of vehicle excise duty in Northern Ireland between (a) 1 August 2013 and 31 July 2014 and (b) 1 August 2014 and 31 July 2015; and what proportion of this income has been retained in or returned to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12242","12242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421990","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Sheffield to Rotherham tram-train trial will start.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12269","12269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421991","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department made of Sir Howard Davies's potential business links to Heathrow Airport; and what other due diligence it conducted before appointing him as chair of the Airports Commission.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12198","12198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421992","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the case for and feasibility of an additional station on Crossrail at London City Airport.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12201","12201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421993","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what compensation the Government has made available to road and rail freight and passenger operators affected by the ongoing disruption at Calais.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12186","12186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421994","2015-10-21","Department for Transport","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on which dates (a) the full Cycling Shareholder Forum, (b) the safety sub-group of the Cycling Stakeholder Forum and (c) the High Level Cycling Group have held meetings in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12187","12187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421995","2015-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason his Department's guidance on accessible communication formats published on 14 August 2014 does not include email as an accessible format; and what consultation his Department had with disability groups before producing that guidance.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12203","12203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421996","2015-10-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many requests he has received for an inquiry into benefit sanctions.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12193","12193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421997","2015-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with hearing deficits or deafness in Preston constituency had (a) British Sign Language interpreters or (b) Communication Support Workers provided to assist them under the Access to Work programme between 1 October 2014 and 30 September 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12266","12266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421998","2015-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse was for (a) British Sign Language interpreters and (b) communication support workers provided for people in Preston parliamentary constituency with hearing deficits or deafness under the Access to Work programme in each month between January 2014 and June 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12265","12265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421999","2015-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposal to reduce the employment and support allowance work-related activity group rate on patients recovering from cancer.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12253","12253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422000","2015-10-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2015 to Question 11270, for what reason it was decided to make the provision of audio recording facilities available for employment and support allowance assessments but not for personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12212","12212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422001","2015-10-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people aged between 18 and 21 in the constituency of Bury St Edmunds were in receipt of housing benefit in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12206","12206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422002","2015-10-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to reply to the letter from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton dated 27 August 2015 with regard to Amy Jones.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12215","12215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421632","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of referral times for Child and Adolescent Mental Health Service appointments in Plymouth and Devon; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12041","12041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421633","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time for an autism diagnosis in Devon was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12042","12042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421634","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the Care Quality Commission's recent progress in meeting its inspection programme's targets.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12024","12024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421635","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has held with the Care Quality Commission's Head of Inspection on the number of vacant posts in the Commission's inspection teams.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12025","12025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421636","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the number of patients being offered a choice of outpatient facility by their GPs.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12026","12026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421637","2015-10-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she received the report by the group Together Against Sizewell C (TASC) Nuclear Power: New Evidence: a call for a full-scale statutory review of the Overarching National Policy Statement for Energy (EN-1); and what response she has made to the correspondents sending that report.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12023","12023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421638","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure whistleblowers and hon. Members can communicate with each other without their communications being intercepted.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12043","12043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421639","2015-10-19","Department for Education","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding was allocated to further education in (a) Yorkshire and (b) Leeds in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12110","12110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421640","2015-10-19","Leader of the House","2015-10-15","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will bring forward proposals to allow the online tabling and signing of Early Day Motions.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12044","12044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421641","2015-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his most recent estimate is of the number of children living in poverty; and if he will publish such data for each region and parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12109","12109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421642","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library a copy of (a) the grant application received from Action on Smoking and Health in May 2011 and (b) the revised grant application received from that organisation in June 2011.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12102","12102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421643","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons officials in his Department had discussions with Action on Smoking and Health on its grant application in June 2011; if he will place in the Library a copy of the minutes and notes from those discussions; and what action was taken as a result of those discussions.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12106","12106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421644","2015-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information he received about risks connected with the proposed right to buy scheme during the planning of that scheme.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12047","12047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421645","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Wilson Doctrine has been consistently applied to the communications of the hon. Member for Nottingham North; and whether that hon. Member has been subject to surveillance.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12036","12036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421646","2015-10-19","HM Treasury","2015-10-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue was raised from VAT on road fuel in (a) 2011, (b) 2012, (c) 2013, (d) 2014 and (e) 2015.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12104","12104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421647","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons the premium renewal service for passports is not available for children's passports.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12076","12076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421648","2015-10-19","Prime Minister","2015-10-15","To ask the Prime Minister, when he next plans to visit Herefordshire.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12068","12068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421649","2015-10-19","Department for Transport","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research he has commissioned on the condition of rural roads.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12071","12071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421650","2015-10-19","Department for Transport","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to ensure that local authorities fix potholes during winter 2015-16.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12072","12072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421651","2015-10-19","Department for Transport","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress is being made to create a safer road layout on the A417 at Birdlip Hill roundabout; and what plans he has to convert that road to a dual carriageway.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12069","12069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421652","2015-10-19","Department for Transport","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to reduce the duration of speed restrictions for repair and maintenance on the M4, M5 and M50 motorways.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12070","12070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421653","2015-10-19","Department for Transport","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which three counties he projects will receive the most funding from his Department for road repairs in the next three years.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12077","12077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421654","2015-10-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Government funding for science on the provision of infrastructure for cancer research.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12155","12155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421655","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the recommendations set out in the NHS England report Achieving world-class cancer outcomes: a strategy for England 2015-2020 are implemented without delay.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12156","12156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421656","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of accommodation and support available to vulnerable migrants in Calais; and what steps she is taking to ensure such migrants are appropriately cared for.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12083","12083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421657","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to attract high-skilled migrants and international students to the UK.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12080","12080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421658","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to protect the security and privacy of citizens' online activity.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12081","12081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421659","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of Police and Crime Commissioners.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12082","12082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421660","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding has been allocated to supporting people in migrant camps in Calais since August 2015","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12084","12084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421661","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding her Department has provided to (a) install fencing around the perimeter of the railhead at Coquelles, France, (b) install CCTV at the railhead at Coquelles and (c) strengthen security within the Channel Tunnel since 20 August 2015.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12090","12090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421662","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to encourage diversity in the police service.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12085","12085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421663","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her joint declaration with the French Minister of the Interior of 20 September 2014, how much funding her Department has contributed to the Joint Intervention Fund announced in that declaration.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12091","12091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421664","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many additional UK police and Border Force personnel have been deployed to join 24/7 freight search teams in Calais since 20 August 2015.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12086","12086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421665","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the system for removing (a) vulnerable people and (b) victims of trafficking to places of safety from the migrant camps in Calais; and how much funding her Department has provided to improve that system.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12092","12092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421666","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many translators and analysts in the UK specialising in (a) Pashtun, (b) Oromo, (c) Tingrinya, (d) Amharic and (e) Tamil have contributed to supporting policing efforts in Calais.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12087","12087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421667","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the joint ministerial declaration on UK/French co-operation in tackling ongoing illegal migration in northern France and across Europe, issued on 20 August 2015, what support the Government has provided to the government of France for dedicated facilities for people claiming asylum, in order to draw them away from the frontier in Calais, as announced in that declaration.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12093","12093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421668","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the September 2015 report from the Gold Command leaders appointed following the Joint Ministerial Declaration on UK/French Cooperation issued on 20 August 2015.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12088","12088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421669","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if (a) she and (b) other Ministers in her Department plan to attend the joint conference between the EU and African partners in Valletta, Malta, on 11 November 2015, on migration.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12094","12094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421670","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the joint ministerial declaration on UK/French co-operation in tackling ongoing illegal migration in northern France and across Europe, issued on 20 August 2015, how many of the security audit recommendations made by a British and French specialised team on 10 August 2015 have been fully implemented.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12095","12095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421671","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 13 of the joint ministerial declaration on UK/French cooperation in tackling ongoing illegal migration in Northern France and across Europe, issued on 20 August 2015, when she plans to publish the study of other Channel and appropriate North Sea ports that could be used by criminal gangs exploiting migrants, referred to in that declaration.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12089","12089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421672","2015-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential (a) economic and (b) health effects of the provisions of the Housing and Planning Bill on people who receive housing benefit and who are subject to the benefit cap in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12161","12161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421673","2015-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the potential effects of the provisions of the Housing and Planning Bill on the total amount of spending on housing benefit in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12162","12162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421674","2015-10-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that local authorities uphold the Military Covenant.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12078","12078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421675","2015-10-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that there are sufficient appropriately trained reserve forces to support regular service men and women to meet Force 2020 commitments.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12099","12099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421676","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training places were commissioned in England for new entrants to become (a) nurses and (b) midwives in each year between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12054","12054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421677","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training places he plans to commission in England for new entrants to become (a) nurses and (b) midwives in each year between 2016 and 2020.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12056","12056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421678","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many places were available for new entrants to study medicine in England in each year between 2010 and 2015; and how many places for new entrants to study medicine are planned to be available in each year between 2016 and 2020.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12057","12057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421679","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications were received per individual training place in England for (a) nurses and (b) midwives in each year between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12055","12055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421680","2015-10-20","Department for Education","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to change its policy on free school meal provision for infant school pupils.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12066","12066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421681","2015-10-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the report Comparing Motor-Vehicle Crash Risk of EU and US Vehicles, published in May 2015; and what the implications of that report are for the TTIP negotiations.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12065","12065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421682","2015-10-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of animal welfare laws on the protection of horses; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12058","12058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421683","2015-10-20","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2015 to Question 10467, when she plans for the results of the application of the Family Test on orders seeking to control drugs that are dangerous or otherwise harmful when misused to be published.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12131","12131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421684","2015-10-20","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the results of the Family Test applied to the policies proposed in the Immigration Bill.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12169","12169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421685","2015-10-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer to Question 10161 of 22 September 2015, on Sunday trading, when he plans to publish the results of the Family Test.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12101","12101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421686","2015-10-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the results of the Family Test applied to the policies proposed in the Cities and Local Government Devolution Bill [Lords].","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12168","12168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421687","2015-10-20","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her announcement on 9 February 2015 on an independent review of policies and procedures affecting the welfare of those held in immigration removal centres, and pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Immigration of 10 September 2015, Official Report, column 601, when she expects that review will be published.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12100","12100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421688","2015-10-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's latest estimate is of (a) the whole life programme cost of the Successor programme, (b) capital costs associated with (i) submarine acquisition, (ii) Trident missile renewal and (iii) basing facilities, (c) the running and support costs of the Successor fleet and associated capability to protect and sustain it, (d) all future costs associated with the Atomic Weapons Establishment maintaining a capability to maintain an on-going nuclear warhead design capability and (e) decommissioning costs.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12151","12151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421689","2015-10-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department last carried out an assessment of the whole life cost of the Successor programme.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12152","12152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421690","2015-10-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what risk assessments his Department has made of the Successor submarine and Trident missile renewal programmes; and whether a further such risk assessment is planned to inform a final main gate decision.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12153","12153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421691","2015-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for his policies of the measures contained within the European Council on Tolerance and Reconciliation's European Model Law for the promotion of tolerance and the suppression of intolerance.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12105","12105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421692","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what research licences are under consideration by her Department relating to medicinal benefits of cannabinoids.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12073","12073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421693","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the efficacy of her Department's procedures and adequacy of the end-to-end timescale in relation to applications for no time limit and biometric immigration documentation by someone who already has indefinite leave to remain in the UK.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12113","12113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421694","2015-10-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has of the environmental effect of underground coal gasification.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12112","12112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421695","2015-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Defence Nuclear Safety Regulator has amended his advice on when high security vehicles for transporting special nuclear materials should be withdrawn from service; and for what reasons those vehicles continue to be used after their retirement date.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12115","12115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421696","2015-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason high security vehicles were being used to transport components of nuclear weapons through Glasgow on 29 July 2015 after being withdrawn from service.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12114","12114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421697","2015-10-19","Northern Ireland Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the level of inequalities experienced by LGBTI people in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12111","12111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421698","2015-10-19","HM Treasury","2015-10-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many mandatory reconsiderations for tax credits which were undertaken by Concentrix took (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four, (e) five, (f) six, (g) seven, (h) eight, (i) nine, (j) 10 and (k) more than 10 weeks in each year since that company has been contracted by the Department.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12045","12045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421699","2015-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the authorities in Iraq on the Yazidi community in that country.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12167","12167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421700","2015-10-20","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on planned reductions to the policing budget in Cumbria.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12049","12049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421701","2015-10-20","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure reductions in funding to Cumbria Constabulary do not result in a reduction in police numbers.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12051","12051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421702","2015-10-20","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers there were in Cumbria in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12134","12134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421703","2015-10-20","HM Treasury","2015-10-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to set out in the forthcoming Comprehensive Spending Review that police budgets in Cumbria should not be reduced.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12050","12050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421704","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to reduce the waiting times for autism diagnosis; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12063","12063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421705","2015-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent progress towards achieving a political solution to the conflict in Syria.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12064","12064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421706","2015-10-22","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Wilson Doctrine has been consistently applied to the communications of the hon. Member for South Down; and whether that Member has been subject to surveillance.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12067","12067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421707","2015-10-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of poor player behaviour and discipline by Premier League football players on the field on the reputation of UK sport; and if he will hold talks with the Professional Footballers' Association and FA to discuss improving that behaviour and discipline.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12048","12048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421708","2015-10-20","Department for Transport","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the difference between step-free access to trains and step-free access to platforms means in the context of plans for different Crossrail stations.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12020","12020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421709","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the availability of NHS dentist places in (a) High Peak constituency, (b) Derbyshire Clinical Commissioning Group and (c) Tameside and Glossop Clinical Commissioning Group in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12014","12014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421710","2015-10-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what financial and other assistance his Department is giving to suppliers of SSI in Redcar.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12016","12016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421711","2015-10-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the number of jobs at risk in the supply chain and wider economy of Redcar as a result of the closure of the SSI steelworks.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12017","12017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421712","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Wilson Doctrine has been consistently applied to the communications of the hon. Member for Bridgend; and whether she has been subject to surveillance.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12103","12103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421713","2015-10-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals for stricter laws dealing with people who abuse animals.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12027","12027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421714","2015-10-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many prosecutions there have been for abandoning or neglecting dogs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12028","12028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421715","2015-10-19","Department for Transport","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people died on the roads in each region in incidents where a driver was using a mobile telephone in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12029","12029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421716","2015-10-19","Department for Transport","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to provide assistance to companies in training personnel to gain HGV qualifications.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12030","12030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421717","2015-10-19","Department for Transport","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the number of HGV drivers in the UK relative to demand.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12031","12031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421718","2015-10-19","Department for Transport","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to increase the number of HGV drivers.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12032","12032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421719","2015-10-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Government has provided in Start Up Loans in Mid Worcestershire constituency since their creation.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12075","12075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421720","2015-10-19","HM Treasury","2015-10-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether a kinship carer with more than two children in their care, either their own children or under a kinship arrangement, and who receives tax credits, will be affected by the decision not to permit an additional claim for the credits for a third child.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12097","12097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421721","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will roll out a national breathlessness campaign to follow the pilots in the North and East of England.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12166","12166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421722","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that carers are able to give each patient an appropriate amount of time on visits.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12117","12117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421723","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department intends to establish or encourage national training schemes for care providers to ensure consistency in care provision across the sector.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12118","12118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421724","2015-10-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the prevalence of giant hogweed.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12098","12098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421725","2015-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the human rights situation in Iran.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12120","12120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421726","2015-10-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to improve air quality in order to assist people with lung diseases.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12119","12119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421727","2015-10-19","HM Treasury","2015-10-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the Summer Budget 2015 has an equal impact on men and women.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12123","12123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421728","2015-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to prevent price-fixing in service charges by providers of retirement homes.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12163","12163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421729","2015-10-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans her Department has on funding for onshore wind energy development.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12121","12121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421730","2015-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will review the regulation of service charges to ensure that housing associations are not exploiting residents.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12164","12164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421731","2015-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to introduce a requirement that private landlords have a certificate confirming their accommodation has reached a minimum condition before it can be let.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12165","12165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421732","2015-10-19","Department for Transport","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve air quality in order to assist people with lung diseases.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12122","12122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421733","2015-10-19","HM Treasury","2015-10-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance his Department gives to ensure that the implications of missing national insurance contributions are made clear to those concerned at the time they are missed.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12116","12116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421734","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department and NHS England are taking to ensure that autism diagnosis waiting times for (a) children and (b) adults meet NICE guidance.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12039","12039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421735","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that primary care records accurately record the number of (a) children and (b) adults with a diagnosis of autism.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12040","12040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421736","2015-10-20","Department for Education","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has asked Ofsted to inspect and report on how well schools are providing citizenship as part of the revised inspection framework with its focus on British Values, the Prevent duty and SMSC.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12132","12132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421737","2015-10-19","Northern Ireland Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she has taken to establish on a statutory basis an Implementation and Reconciliation Group as proposed in the Stormont House Agreement.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12159","12159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421738","2015-10-20","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Wilson Doctrine has been consistently applied to the communications of the hon. Member for Haltemprice and Howden; and whether he has been subject to surveillance.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12135","12135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421739","2015-10-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will issue a response to EDM 402, Use of Cages to Rear Birds for Shooting.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12108","12108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421740","2015-10-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will issue a response to EDM 373, Applying Results of Experiments on Animals to Humans.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12107","12107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421741","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of amputations caused by diabetes (a) nationally and (b) in Gloucestershire in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12053","12053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421742","2015-10-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will amend building regulations to ensure that building extensions are fully accessible for people with disabilities.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12052","12052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421743","2015-10-20","Cabinet Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had with charities on respondents being required to tick boxes if they do wish to receive further communications; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12074","12074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421744","2015-10-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department took into account the global growth potential of solar energy in making its decision to end Government support for the UK solar sector.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12144","12144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421745","2015-10-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of Feed in Tariff component of the Levy Control Framework cost is accounted for by the cost of ongoing support for the installations made before 2012.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12145","12145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421746","2015-10-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of introducing net metering; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12146","12146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421747","2015-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times Medway Secure Training Centre has contacted an external teaching agency to request a teacher since it was awarded the contract.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12035","12035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421748","2015-10-20","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will direct the College of Policing to disclose the amounts paid by the Saudi Arabian government for training it has provided to Saudi police officers.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12148","12148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421749","2015-10-20","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will direct the College of Policing to disclose the content of each of the training courses it has provided to Saudi police officers.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12147","12147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421750","2015-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for which offences prisoners serving imprisonment for public protection sentences were convicted on the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12127","12127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421751","2015-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Written Statement by the Minister for the Courts and Legal Aid of 15 October 2015, HCWS 237, on HM Courts & Tribunal Service, if it is his policy for staff of that service to remain civil servants.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12126","12126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421752","2015-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Written Statement by the Minister for Courts and Legal Aid, of 15 October 2015, HCWS 239, on HM Courts and Tribunals Service, if he will initialise an internal review into the decision to discontinue the procurement competition referred to in the statement, with a view to subsequent publication of that review.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12149","12149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421753","2015-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Statement by the Minister for Courts and Legal Aid, of 15 October 2015, HCWS 239, on HM Courts and Tribunals Service, what the total cost to the Exchequer was of the discontinued procurement process referred to in the statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12150","12150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421754","2015-10-20","Department for Transport","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of ticket barriers at stations in London being left open.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12079","12079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421755","2015-10-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the reasons are for his proposal to exclude taught masters students who are over the age of 30 from the new postgraduate loans scheme proposed for England.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12018","12018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421756","2015-10-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the reasons are for the proposed exclusion from the new postgraduate loans scheme proposed for England of taught masters students who are studying via distance learning at a minimum of 50 per cent intensity.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12019","12019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421757","2015-10-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the reasons are for the proposal to include in the new postgraduate loans scheme proposed for England part-time taught masters students studying at a minimum of 50 per cent intensity not via distance learning.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12022","12022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421758","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he made of the effect of NHS England taking over responsibility for commissioning health services within the immigration detention estate in England on the adequacy of health provision within that estate.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12015","12015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421759","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure NHS melanoma patients are able to access nivolumab before its appraisal by NICE.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12038","12038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421760","2015-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Prime Minister's oral statement of 7 September 2015, Official Report, column 30, on counter-terrorism, whether the Foreign and Commonwealth Office's legal adviser was consulted on the legal basis for the military action against Reyaad Khan in Syria.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12130","12130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421761","2015-10-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer to Question 3393 of 30 June 2015, when the UKTI Defence and Security Organisation priority markets list for 2015-16 will be published.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12128","12128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421762","2015-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2015 to Question 4073, on what date the planned visit of President Sisi of Egypt to the UK will take place; and whether he plans to discuss the supply of military, security and police equipment with President Sisi during his visit.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12129","12129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421763","2015-10-19","Prime Minister","2015-10-15","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer to Question 9571 of 14 September 2015, whether the Attorney General was clear there was a legal basis for this action in domestic law.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12154","12154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421764","2015-10-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much (a) fair price and (b) non-fair price milk was purchased for Nobel House, 17 Smith Square, London in August 2015; and what plans she has to ensure that only fair price milk is used at Nobel House, 17 Smith Square, London.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12133","12133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421765","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many defibrillators there are in public places in Preston constituency; and what the location of those defibrillators is.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12059","12059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421766","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust paid in relation to the six patients admitted to The Priory, Darlington in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12061","12061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421767","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust paid in relation to the 33 patients admitted to Cygnet, Harrogate in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12062","12062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421768","2015-10-20","Department of Health","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust paid in relation to the 104 patients admitted to The Priory, Cheadle Hulme in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12060","12060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421769","2015-10-20","Home Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the revenue Lancashire Constabulary obtained from vehicle storage fees in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12021","12021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421770","2015-10-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether primary legislation is required to implement the proposals on the adult skills budget in the Sheffield City Region Devolution Agreement, announced on 2 October 2015.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12160","12160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421771","2015-10-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the total cost to the public purse was of the disability students' allowance in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12141","12141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421772","2015-10-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people have received the disability students' allowance in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12143","12143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421773","2015-10-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing safe-standing facilities at higher tier sports stadia.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12142","12142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421774","2015-10-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-UK overseas personnel the Royal Navy plans to recruit or loan from other countries' armed forces for each year up to 2020.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12137","12137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421775","2015-10-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-UK overseas personnel the RAF plans to recruit or loan from other countries' armed forces for each year up to 2020.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12139","12139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421776","2015-10-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-UK overseas armed forces personnel have been recruited or loaned from other countries' armed forces to serve in the UK armed forces over the last five years; and what were the countries of origin of those personnel.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12140","12140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421777","2015-10-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-UK armed forces personnel the army plans to recruit or loan for each year up until 2020.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12136","12136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421778","2015-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to provide better incentives for recruitment and retention in the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12124","12124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421779","2015-10-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-UK overseas armed forces personnel have been recruited or loaned by other countries to serve in the UK armed forces in the last five years; and how many such personnel hold which ranks in the UK armed forces.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12138","12138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421780","2015-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has any plans to reduce the length of deployments for Royal Navy personnel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12125","12125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421781","2015-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to ensure that the Armed Forces Covenant fully addresses the healthcare needs of all active and retired servicemen and women with (a) post-traumatic stress disorder and (b) other conditions.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12037","12037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421782","2015-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will introduce a service medal to people serving in Operation Helvetic.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12033","12033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421783","2015-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to distribute a proportion of the frozen assets of the Muammar Gaddafi administration in the UK to the families of people killed (a) by Libyan-supplied semtex and weapons and (b) on flight LW1103.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12034","12034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421784","2015-10-19","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-10-15","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, whether the Electoral Commission has made any assessment of the suitability of different dates for the forthcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12046","12046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421785","2015-10-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the implications for his Department's policies are of the finding in the British Journal of Sociology that despite rising numbers of young people from non-traditional backgrounds coming through the higher education system, there is declining social mobility.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12157","12157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421786","2015-10-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government (a) has taken and (b) plans to take in response to the finding of the Sutton Trust in its research brief entitled Private Pay Progression, published on 6 August 2015, that despite performing as well, if not better, at university, graduates from less privileged backgrounds are less likely to enter the professions.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12096","12096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421787","2015-10-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the implications for his Department's policies are of the finding of the Social Mobility and Child Poverty Commission that children from advantaged social class backgrounds are four times more likely to be in a high hourly income group in adulthood than children from disadvantaged social class backgrounds.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12158","12158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422736","2015-10-21","Cabinet Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress his Department is making on tackling rogue fundraising activities by charities.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901711","901711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422737","2015-10-21","Cabinet Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress he has made on increasing the level of electoral registration.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901708","901708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422738","2015-10-21","Cabinet Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment has the Minister made of the progress of the National Citizenship Service.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901707","901707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422739","2015-10-21","Cabinet Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his policy is on preventing charities from putting undue pressure on vulnerable donors.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901705","901705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422740","2015-10-21","Cabinet Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the progress of the National Citizenship Service.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901704","901704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422741","2015-10-21","Cabinet Office","2015-10-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment has the Minister made of the progress of the National Citizenship Service.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901710","901710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421288","2015-10-16","Attorney General","2015-10-14","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate he has made of the savings to the public purse from early guilty pleas in the Crown Court in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11882","11882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421289","2015-10-16","Attorney General","2015-10-14","To ask the Attorney General, what the Crown Prosecution Service's success rate was in cases which have gone to trial in (a) Magistrates' Courts and (b) Crown Courts in each year between 2010-11 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11883","11883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421290","2015-10-16","Attorney General","2015-10-14","To ask the Attorney General, what the (a) prosecution cost per defendant, (b) overall spend per completed case and (c) overall spend per full-time equivalent staff member in (i) the Crown Court and (ii) magistrates' courts was in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11888","11888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421291","2015-10-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of trials were (a) ineffective, (b) cracked and (c) vacated for reasons related to the prosecution in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11884","11884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421292","2015-10-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the vacated trial rate in (a) magistrates' courts and (b) the Crown Court was in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion of those vacated trials were for reasons related to the prosecution.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11889","11889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421293","2015-10-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the court system of delays caused by (a) ineffective criminal trials and (b) cracked trials was in each year between 2010-11 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11890","11890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421294","2015-10-16","Attorney General","2015-10-14","To ask the Attorney General, how many wasted cost orders were made (a) in favour and (b) against the Crown Prosecution Service in each year since 2010-11; and for what reasons such wasted cost orders were made against the Crown Prosecution Service.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11885","11885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421295","2015-10-16","Attorney General","2015-10-14","To ask the Attorney General, how many early guilty pleas there were in the Crown Court in each year from 2010-11; and what proportion of total pleas they represented in each such year.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11887","11887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421296","2015-10-16","Attorney General","2015-10-14","To ask the Attorney General, how many (a) prosecutors, (b) associate prosecutors, (c) caseworkers and (d) administrators were employed by the Crown Prosecution Service in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion of each such category were engaged in frontline services.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11886","11886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421297","2015-10-16","Attorney General","2015-10-14","To ask the Attorney General, how many exit packages the Crown Prosecution Service has agreed with a value of more than 100,000 since 2010-11; and what the total cost of such packages was to the public purse.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11895","11895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421298","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment the Government has made of the potential economic and employment effects of the proposed Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership on the (a) food and farming, (b) energy, (c) financial services, (d) technology, (e) textiles and (f) shipbuilding sectors.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11960","11960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421299","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment the Government has made of the potential economic and employment effects of the proposed Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership in each of the constituent parts of the UK.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11961","11961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421300","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will assess the potential economic and employment effects of the proposed Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership in each of the constituent parts of the UK.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11962","11962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421301","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of how many students (a) from Manchester, Withington constituency and (b) studying at Manchester University and Manchester Metropolitan University will be affected by the removal of maintenance loans.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11865","11865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421302","2015-10-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to increase the proportion of people whose earnings are above the living wage.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11824","11824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421303","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to ensure maximum financial benefit to the public purse from the sale of Royal Mail.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11811","11811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421304","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what (a) advice and (b) guidance his Department gives on the risks of (i) investment in and (ii) business with Israeli settlements in Occupied Palestinian territory.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11818","11818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421305","2015-10-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many of his Department's target of three million apprenticeship starts by 2020 he expects to be at Level 3 and above.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11924","11924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421306","2015-10-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of how many Hove residents who have taken out student loans since 2012 will be affected by proposals to freeze the repayment threshold of the loans at 21,000.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11923","11923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421307","2015-10-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2015 to Question 10357, how many arms export licences of what value and type have been issued for exports to (a) Saudi Arabia and (b) Yemen in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11944","11944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421308","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will assess the potential effect of the proposed Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership on (a) education, (b) health and (c) procurement in Scotland.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12010","12010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421309","2015-10-16","Cabinet Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many voluntary exit payments for Civil Service employees with a value of more than 95,000 have been rejected since May 2015.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11868","11868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421310","2015-10-16","Cabinet Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many requests for voluntary exit payments for Civil Service employees with a value of more than 95,000 he has received since May 2015.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11866","11866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421311","2015-10-16","Cabinet Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many requests for voluntary exit payments for Civil Service employees with a value of more than 95,000 have been outstanding since May 2015.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11869","11869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421312","2015-10-16","Cabinet Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average value was of voluntary exit payments for Civil Service employees with a value of more than 95,000 made since May 2015.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11867","11867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421313","2015-10-16","Cabinet Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average length of time is from receipt of a request for a voluntary exit payment for a Civil Service employee with a value of more than 95,000 to a decision on that request.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11870","11870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421314","2015-10-16","Cabinet Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many voluntary exit payments for Civil Service employees with a value of more than 95,000, have been rejected for employees who would have left the service by the end of September 2015.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11871","11871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421315","2015-10-16","Cabinet Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many voluntary exit payments for Civil Service employees with a value of more than 95,000 have been approved since May 2015.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11872","11872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421316","2015-10-16","Cabinet Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what criteria he agrees voluntary exit payments for Civil Service employees with a value of more than 95,000.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11873","11873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421317","2015-10-16","HM Treasury","2015-10-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2015 to Question 7017, on Block grant: Northern Ireland, what information his Department holds on which department in Northern Ireland will receive the additional funding.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11972","11972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421318","2015-10-16","HM Treasury","2015-10-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the practice of insurance companies basing premiums on postcode areas on differentials in premiums paid by consumers.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11908","11908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421319","2015-10-19","HM Treasury","2015-10-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households claiming working and child tax credits consist of (a) all UK nationals, (b) at least one UK national and at least one non-UK national and (c) all non-UK nationals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11929","11929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421320","2015-10-19","HM Treasury","2015-10-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Warrington North constituency who will receive a reduced amount of tax credit in the next financial year; and what estimate he has made of the average amount by which such tax credit payments will fall.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11983","11983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421321","2015-10-19","Cabinet Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate how many people in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency are employed in jobs paying less than the living wage.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11984","11984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421322","2015-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to improve the transparency of the corporate governance on housing associations.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11980","11980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421323","2015-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of new homes built in local authorities in the West Midlands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11946","11946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421324","2015-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the internal drainage board for West Lancashire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11942","11942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421325","2015-10-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many 16 and 17 year olds presented as homeless to Manchester City Council in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11913","11913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421326","2015-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will ensure that decisions on shale gas well locations are taken by local authorities.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11807","11807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421327","2015-10-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what (a) advice and (b) guidance his Department gives on the risks of (i) investment in and (ii) business with Israeli settlements in Occupied Palestinian territory.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11825","11825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421328","2015-10-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of reductions in central government revenue support to local government since 2010 on the management of the historic environment through the planning process.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11903","11903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421329","2015-10-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to improve supported accommodation for homeless young people in (a) Manchester, Withington constituency, (b) Manchester and (c) nationally.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11864","11864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421330","2015-10-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to revise the agreement reached with the National Housing Federation on right to buy to clarify that it does not cover almshouse residents.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11876","11876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421331","2015-10-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the (a) current and (b) capital expenditure was for Kew Palace in financial years 2001-02 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11917","11917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421332","2015-10-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if Ministers in his Department plan to attend Lancashire Day celebrations on 27 November 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11794","11794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421333","2015-10-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what legacy he expects from the UK's hosting of the Rugby World Cup.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11925","11925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421334","2015-10-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to support the work of the British Library during the next funding period; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11990","11990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421335","2015-10-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department took to comply with the requirement for transparency set out in paragraph 5c of Annex B of the Fishing Vessel Avoidance UK Code of Practice extracted from SMP 95 dated 5 June 2002 in the incident with MV Karen on 15 April 2015.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11964","11964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421336","2015-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any Minister in his Department plans to attend celebrations of the tercentenary of the Battle of Preston in November 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11797","11797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421337","2015-10-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that it reaches the target of 30,000 reservists by 2018.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11812","11812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421338","2015-10-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his NATO counterparts on ensuring that all NATO member states achieve the target of two per cent of GDP spending on defence.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11813","11813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421339","2015-10-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to introduce greater speed and efficiency in the handling of complaints made to the armed forces by injured veterans.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11919","11919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421340","2015-10-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons Submarine Exercise Areas Ardglass and Peel were not activated on 15 April 2015.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11912","11912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421341","2015-10-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Fishing Vessel Avoidance UK Code of Practice extracted from SMP 95 dated 5 June 2002 applies to Vanguard and Astute class submarines on operational patrols.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11963","11963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421342","2015-10-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the submarine involved in the incident with MV Karen on 15 April 2015 was participating in Exercise Joint Warrior at the time of the incident.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11911","11911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421343","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her policy on universal infant free school meals is part of the Government's obesity strategy.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11974","11974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421344","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to promote patriotism in schools.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11900","11900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421345","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of studio schools on pupil attainment.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11874","11874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421346","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress she is making on implementing Article 31 of the UN Convention of the Rights of the Child.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11820","11820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421347","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to ensure that special education needs are included as part of the core framework for Initial Teacher Training.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11832","11832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421348","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received about the length of time parents and young people wait for an Education Health and Care Plan; and if she will slow down the transfer to the new system to ensure that local authorities are better prepared to move to the new system.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11833","11833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421349","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to implement Article 31 of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child so that it supports childrens' mental health.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11821","11821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421350","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students attained grades (a) A, (b) B and (c) C in each Ebacc subject in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11816","11816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421351","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of effectiveness for parents of data published by schools on the number of children achieving five A to C grades in assessing performance.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11817","11817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421352","2015-10-19","Department for Education","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of how many children are entitled to but not registered to receive free school meals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11930","11930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421353","2015-10-19","Department for Education","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children receiving universal infant free school meals are not registered as free school meal the purposes of pupils for the purposes of pupil premium funding.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11931","11931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421354","2015-10-19","Department for Education","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect on (a) individual school budgets and (b) local education authority budgets of variations in the water and sewerage charges borne by schools in different parts of the country.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11941","11941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421355","2015-10-19","Department for Education","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent advice she has given to schools on tackling Islamophobia.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11927","11927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421356","2015-10-19","Department for Education","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will amend the school funding formula so that it recognises major cost variations in schools' water and sewerage charges.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11943","11943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421357","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect on claimants of the reduction in section 95 support for asylum seeker families and children.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11928","11928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421358","2015-10-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will announce the timetable for the publication of a new Energy White Paper.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11989","11989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421359","2015-10-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department has received legal advice on the effect of changes in the market price of wholesale electricity since agreeing a strike price with EDF for electricity from the proposed Hinkley Point C power station on whether the Government's support constitutes state subsidy.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11969","11969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421360","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the cross-compliance inspection regime in reducing soil erosion.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11893","11893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421361","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to limit the use of antibiotics on farms to sick animals.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11901","11901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421362","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2015 to Question 10625, which organisations the Government has met to discuss amendments to the Hunting Act 2004.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11907","11907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421363","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to evaluate the effectiveness of the Soil Protection Review form in reducing soil erosion.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11892","11892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421364","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance her Department provides for farmers on reducing soil erosion on their land.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11891","11891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421365","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department is making on research on the production of diverse forage mixtures to optimise animal production.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11790","11790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421366","2015-10-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the PCR test for tuberculosis; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11949","11949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421367","2015-10-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the incidence of bovine TB on farms situated in trial badger cull areas.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12013","12013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421368","2015-10-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the reasons for the difference between the water and sewerage charge per pupil in Lancashire and Kent; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11940","11940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421369","2015-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to express concern about persecution of religious groups in China with President Xi Jinping during his visit to the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11926","11926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421370","2015-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of crowded airspace on British military assets operating in Iraq; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11945","11945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421371","2015-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to monitor the use of weapons (a) manufactured in the UK or (b) sold by UK companies to the government of Saudi Arabia to ensure that such sales are compliant with international obligations.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11947","11947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421372","2015-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the government of Burma on the possible postponement of elections in that country.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11981","11981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421373","2015-10-19","Department for International Development","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to support economic growth in the Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11982","11982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421374","2015-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of weapons (a) manufactured in the UK or (b) sold by companies based in the UK being used by the government of Saudi Arabia in the military conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11948","11948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421375","2015-10-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent progress has been made on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11978","11978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421376","2015-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for peace talks in Colombia of the on-going violence perpetrated by paramilitaries in that country.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11986","11986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421377","2015-10-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Israeli government on the planned demolition of the village of Umm al-Hiran.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11999","11999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421378","2015-10-16","Department for International Development","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Occupied Palestinian Territory.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12000","12000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421379","2015-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the Russian intervention in Syria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12012","12012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421380","2015-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to ensure that interest earned on Libyan assets frozen in the UK is used to compensate the victims of IRA/Libyan-sponsored violence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11988","11988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421381","2015-10-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take a greater role in facilitating a two state solution in Israel.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11819","11819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421382","2015-10-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his European counterparts on providing possible alternative oil and gas supply to the Baltic states.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11809","11809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421383","2015-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of the situation of the Bah'i community in Iran.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11995","11995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421384","2015-10-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the government of Bahrain to hold talks with the opposition in Bahrain on human rights in that country; and what representations he has received on the arrest and trials of Ali Salman and Ebrahim Sharif.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11899","11899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421385","2015-10-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many of the recommendations of the 2011 report on Palestinian children in military custody, funded by his Department, have been carried out.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11958","11958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421386","2015-10-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with Israeli and Palestinian authorities on measures to reduce hostilities.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11894","11894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421387","2015-10-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support he is giving to EU proposals to provide sea access to Gaza.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11959","11959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421388","2015-10-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to prevent a similar incident to the airstrikes in Afghanistan which killed Medecins Sans Frontieres doctors occurring in future.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11970","11970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421389","2015-10-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many of the recommendations of the report on children in military custody published by his Department in June 2012 have been implemented.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11910","11910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421390","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of smokers who have switched to e-cigarettes; and what estimate he has made of the effect of that switch on the NHS budget.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11909","11909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421391","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library (a) agendas and (b) minutes of meetings of the NHS England Industry Council; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11897","11897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421392","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the effect on employment in Southend University Hospital NHS Foundation Trust of proposals that Tier 2 visa immigrants from outside the European Economic Area must be earning 35,000 or more to qualify for UK indefinite leave to remain; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11902","11902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421393","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps the Government has taken to improve care and support for people with breast cancer.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11918","11918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421394","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposed new junior doctor contract on the ability of female doctors to take time out of training for parental leave.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11896","11896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421395","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any grant monitoring forms in relation to funds awarded by his Department to Action on Smoking and Health were submitted late.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11968","11968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421396","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans next to publish a report on international comparisons of medicines usage; at what frequency he will publish such reports; what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the most recently published report; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11898","11898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421397","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that people who are homeless have access to talking therapies.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11880","11880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421398","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to improve the physical and mental health of homeless people.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11879","11879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421399","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of minimum and maximum payments terms for suppliers to the NHS.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11815","11815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421400","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health of 20 July 2015, Official Report, column 1221, when he plans for the public consultation on support available for people affected by contaminated blood products to begin.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11834","11834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421401","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to cost potential recommendations for reform of the schemes to assist people affected by contaminated blood products.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11835","11835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421402","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of junior doctors about their hours and rates of pay.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11826","11826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421403","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria the Government and NHS employers will use to distinguish between residential and non-residential on call duties in the proposed new contract for junior doctors.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11827","11827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421404","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the Government and NHS employers plan to supplement junior doctors' salaries for (a) residential and (b) non-residential on call duties in the proposed new contract for junior doctors.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11828","11828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421405","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the Government and NHS employers have involved Health Education England in the planning and negotiation of the new junior doctors contract.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11829","11829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421406","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what formal role Health Education England has played in his Department's engagement and meetings with the BMA and other health care unions in developing the new proposed junior doctors and consultant contracts.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11830","11830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421407","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which meetings on the proposed new junior doctor and consultant contracts organised by his Department or NHS employers were attended by representatives from Health Education England.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11831","11831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421408","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the implications for his Department's policy are of the recent study funded by the Institute of Cancer Research and published in Nature Medicine of bowel cancer being regarded as four district diseases.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11822","11822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421409","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to assist and advise all British ex-servicemen resident in the Republic of Ireland on financial support for medicines and medical aftercare.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11810","11810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421410","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received on the (a) award and (b) disbursement of grants made under section 64 of the Health Services and Public Health Act 1968.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11791","11791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421411","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what arrangements are in place to ensure that grants made by his Department under section 64 of the Health Services and Public Health Act 1968 are awarded transparently.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11792","11792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421412","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether under the new junior doctor contract proposals, doctors will be prevented from receiving remuneration or other financial support for teaching advanced life support and other medical training courses.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11939","11939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421413","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish a new national strategy for carers.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11991","11991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421414","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people working in social care (a) on zero-hours contracts and (b) paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11992","11992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421415","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 6.34 of his Department's Health Education England mandate: April 2015 to March 2016, published on 12 March 2015, what progress Health Education England has made on ensuring that a minimum of 3,250 trainees per year are recruited to GP training programmes in England by 2016.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11993","11993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421416","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of (a) adult social care providers and (b) GP practices have been inspected by the Care Quality Commission since September 2013.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11994","11994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421417","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to improve the morale of junior doctors in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11935","11935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421418","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much in real terms the NHS spent on administration in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11954","11954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421419","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much (a) his Department and (b) NHS England has spent on photocopier and printer paper since January 2013.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11955","11955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421420","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether under the new junior doctor contract proposals, doctors will be prevented from giving their time to (a) the British Medical Association, (b) the General Medical Council, (c) other healthcare, education and training organisations and (d) trade unions.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11938","11938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421421","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has taken disciplinary action in respect of section 64 grants made to Action on Smoking and Health and their subsequent use.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11916","11916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421422","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons information held by her Department regarding the ethnicity, age and gender of people involved in police Taser incidents has not been included in annually published statistics; and if she will ensure such information is included in future publications of annual police Taser incident statistics.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11921","11921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421423","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what length of time her Department retains information about a person after they have been referred to the Channel programme.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11932","11932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421424","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what priority is being given to abandoned and orphaned children in the selection of Syrian refugees likely to be offered a new home in the UK.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11936","11936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421425","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects the first Syrian refugees rescued from camps in the Middle East to arrive in the UK.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11937","11937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421426","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish the findings of the follow-up audit of reports made under Rule 35 of the Detention Centre Rules 2001.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Mrs Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11915","11915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421427","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to protect women visiting pregnancy advisory centres and residents living near such centres from harassment.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11934","11934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421428","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Moussa Koussa met UK police forces or security agencies between his entry into the UK at Farnborough airfield on 30 March 2011 and departure to Qatar three days later; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11996","11996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421429","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to secure the extradition of Moussa Koussa in connection with IRA/Libyan-sponsored terrorism in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11997","11997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421430","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what occasions Ministers or officials of her Department discussed the Immigration Bill with (a) the Chief Constable of the Police Service of Northern Ireland and (b) the Justice Minister in the Northern Ireland Executive; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11998","11998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421431","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to reduce the time taken to process asylum applications.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11987","11987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421432","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will merge the Hampshire, Surrey and Sussex police forces.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11979","11979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421433","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she plans to take to ensure that delays in Disclosure and Barring Service checks by (a) the Metropolitan Police and (b) other constabularies are minimised.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11975","11975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421434","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Disclosure and Barring Service has to protect vulnerable groups from exposure to unchecked employees and unregistered employers.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11976","11976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421435","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Disclosure and Barring Service checks were carried out in (a) the UK, (b) Lancashire and (c) Ribble Valley constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11977","11977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421436","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 12 October 2015 from the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Refugees, Official Report, column 13, on Refugee crisis, if she will place in the Library a copy of the letter of 1 October to chief executives of local authorities.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11985","11985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421437","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full-time equivalent staff her Department allocated to responding to hon. Members' enquiries on their constituents' immigration issues on 1 September (a) 2012, (b) 2013, (c) 2014 and (d) 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11793","11793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421438","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to withdraw the courses and services provided by the College of Policing to the government of Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11805","11805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421439","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the costs and difficulties faced by Chinese visitors and tourists wishing to enter the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11823","11823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421440","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will carry out a review of asylum dispersal areas in the UK with a view to expanding the number of such areas.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11804","11804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421441","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of Prevent strategy funding for each of the last five years has been allocated to tackling far right extremism.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11801","11801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421442","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what indicators are used by the Government and local authorities to assess the effectiveness of initiatives funded by the Prevent strategy.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11802","11802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421443","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the membership of the Community Engagement Forum is.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11808","11808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421444","2015-10-16","Cabinet Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate how many people working in front-line public sector jobs in 2014 were not able to speak fluent English.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11906","11906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421445","2015-10-19","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will commission an investigation into the reasons for the proportion of Taser incidents which involve black people; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11920","11920"
