"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035313","2019-01-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will ensure that future funding settlements for fire and rescue services take account of geographical differences in council tax revenue.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205265","205265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035314","2019-01-09","Home Office","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will set a timescale for reinstating capital funding for fire and rescue services.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205266","205266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035315","2019-01-08","Department for Transport","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list the third party organisations that undertook due diligence on Seaborne Freight in advance of his Department’s awarding of a contract to that company for ferry services.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205178","205178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035316","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Your Army Needs You British Army recruitment campaign was signed off by Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205412","205412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035317","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of the contraband in prisons that enters prisons via drone.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205339","205339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035318","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much money from the public purse has been spent on the Your Army Needs You British Army recruitment campaign.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205413","205413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035319","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel were recruited by the armed forces in each month since January 2018.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205414","205414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035320","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that NHS services are accessible for people with hearing loss.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205415","205415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035321","2019-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number of women in prison who are victims of human trafficking.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205340","205340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035322","2019-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government has plans to publish a response to the ILO Brown Report on ending violence and harassment in the world of work.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205356","205356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035323","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many eggs have been used to enable (a) pro-nuclear transfer and (b) maternal spindle transfer in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205252","205252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035324","2019-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many victims of sexual abuse have had their applications for compensation from the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme rejected because they had an unspent criminal conviction in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205341","205341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035325","2019-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total value of uncollected court fines is in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205342","205342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035326","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total value is of uncollected victims surcharges in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205343","205343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035327","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many acts of concerted indiscipline have there been in prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205344","205344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035328","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of children in secure institutions were on average confined to their cells for more than 22 hours a day in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205345","205345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035329","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much (a) his Department and (b) his Department's arm's length bodies spent on consultants in 2017-18.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205346","205346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035330","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many parents had no representation at a family court case relating to a child in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205347","205347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035331","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the long term viability of the criminal duty solicitors scheme.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205348","205348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035332","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many mandatory drug tests have taken place in prison in each month in the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205349","205349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035333","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many witnesses have received support from the court-based witness service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205350","205350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035334","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients were admitted in 2018 by each acute hospital; and how many inpatients experienced thefts by acute hospital in that same year.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205251","205251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035335","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost has been of each consultation conducted by his Department since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205351","205351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035336","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2018 to Question 196269, on Prisons: Contracts, if he will publish the review that found that establishing an internal bid team was unnecessarily complex.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205352","205352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035337","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2018 to Question 196269, on Prisons: Contracts, what protections are being put in place to ensure that the public-sector benchmark against which potential operators’ bids will be assessed is (a) sufficiently robust and (b) covers all delivery requirements that will be expected from private-sector providers.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205353","205353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035338","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total value is of compensation claimed for loss or damage to prisoners' property held by the prison service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205354","205354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035339","2019-01-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure sufficient stocks of insulin for people with type 1 diabetes, in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205376","205376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035340","2019-01-09","Department for Transport","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the (a) inspection regime, (b) repair turnaround period and (c) availability of fast chargers provided by M6 motorway service stations.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205329","205329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035341","2019-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the additional staff required by her Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205309","205309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035342","2019-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy,  what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205310","205310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035343","2019-01-08","Department for International Development","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the additional staff required by her Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205311","205311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035344","2019-01-08","Department for International Trade","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205312","205312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035345","2019-01-08","Department for Transport","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205313","205313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035346","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205314","205314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035347","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205315","205315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035348","2019-01-08","Scotland Office","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205316","205316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035349","2019-01-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205317","205317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035350","2019-01-08","Home Office","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205318","205318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035351","2019-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205319","205319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035352","2019-01-08","Wales Office","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205320","205320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035353","2019-01-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205321","205321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035354","2019-01-08","Treasury","2019-01-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205322","205322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035355","2019-01-08","Cabinet Office","2019-01-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205323","205323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035356","2019-01-08","Northern Ireland Office","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate she has made of the additional staff required by her Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205324","205324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035357","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205325","205325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035358","2019-01-09","Department for International Trade","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2018 to Question 203424, how the Government represents each region of the UK on trade show stands.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205267","205267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035359","2019-01-08","Attorney General","2019-01-04","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205326","205326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035360","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205327","205327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1035361","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205328","205328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017308","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-12-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on international co-operation on policing and justice of the UK leaving the EU .","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197432","197432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1030179","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-21","What assessment the Government has made of the effectiveness of universal credit in helping people into work.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908382","908382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028701","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the sustainability of local authority children’s services budgets.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203970","203970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029158","2018-12-20","Women and Equalities","2018-12-20","What progress the Government has made on repealing the duty under the amendment to section 9 of the Equality Act 2010 in relation to caste discrimination.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908344","908344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029160","2018-12-20","Department for International Trade","2018-12-20","What progress is being made on increasing UK exports.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908325","908325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029161","2018-12-20","Department for International Trade","2018-12-20","What recent steps his Department has taken to improve its response times to freedom of information requests.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908326","908326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029162","2018-12-20","Department for International Trade","2018-12-20","What recent discussions he has had with the Government of Israel on bilateral trade and investment.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908327","908327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029163","2018-12-20","Department for International Trade","2018-12-20","What steps he is taking to promote aerospace exports.","Biography information for Rachel Maclean","Rachel Maclean","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908328","908328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029164","2018-12-20","Department for International Trade","2018-12-20","What opportunities he identified for further trade co-operation with Israel during his recent visit to that country.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908329","908329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029165","2018-12-20","Department for International Trade","2018-12-20","What progress the Government has made on its Export Strategy.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908331","908331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029309","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  how many (a) people have been charged, (b) cases have been taken to court and (c) convictions have been made since the Serious Crime Act 2015 created a new offence of controlling or coercive behaviour in an intimate or family relationship.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204514","204514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029310","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to ensure visa-free travel between the UK and the EU for (a) tourism and (b) temporary business activities in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204554","204554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029311","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether trade unions and the Trade Union Congress have been consulted on the managed migration of universal credit.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204628","204628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029312","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the rate of penalties charged in cases of over payment of Carers Allowance were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204629","204629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029313","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of care leavers went into full-time (a) education and (b) work in each of the last five years for which information is available; and what plans the Government has to improve those figures.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204515","204515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029314","2019-01-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the letter of 18 November from the Minister of State for Agriculture, Fisheries and Food to the hon. Member for High Peak on small abattoirs, if he will provide (a) a list the 79 LEADER groups in England and (b) the closing date of applications for each LEADER group in each area.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204630","204630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029315","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the 2016 strategy entitled Keep on caring: supporting young people from care to independence, when the Government plans to review the implementation of the Staying Put duty.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204516","204516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029316","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the November 2018 Fostering Network report entitled Staying Put: An Unfulfilled Promise, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a national minimum Staying Put allowance.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204517","204517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029317","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding is planned to be allocated to each placement of Staying Put.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204518","204518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029318","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the report entitled, Staying Put: An Unfulfilled Promise, published in November 2018 by the Fostering Nework, what steps his Department is taking to prevent foster carers losing their approval as a foster carer through Staying Put arrangements.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204519","204519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029319","2019-01-08","Women and Equalities","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of the recommendations in the Equality and Human Rights Commission’s strategic plan 2016-19 on tackling the barriers facing women in politics and public life.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204520","204520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029320","2019-01-08","Women and Equalities","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of whether the recommendations of the Equality and Human Rights Commission’s strategic plan 2016-19 support key parts of the Equalities Act 2010 such as the implementation of section 106 on the Information about diversity in range of candidates.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204521","204521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029321","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of level of funding from the public purse required by Birmingham City Council to deliver children’s services in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2019-20, and (c) 2020-21.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204522","204522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029322","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the likely demand for children’s services in Birmingham in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2019-20, and (c) 2020/21.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204523","204523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029323","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2018 to Question 179213 on Asylum: Children, how many of the of the unaccompanied children who were granted asylum in the UK in 2017 made applications for refugee family reunion outside of the immigration rules; and how many of those applications were granted by (a) the Home Office and (b) an immigration judge.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204505","204505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029324","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has carried out an equality impact assessment on the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204506","204506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029325","2019-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate the Office for Product Safety and Standards has made of the number of modifications that Whirlpool has made to the dryers referenced in its November 2015 safety announcement to date.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204439","204439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029326","2019-01-08","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2018 to Question 193470 on Ministers: Resignations, which Department monitors the number of independent reviews commissioned by the civil service into the behaviour and actions of civil servants.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204502","204502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029327","2019-01-08","Northern Ireland Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to her Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204497","204497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029328","2019-01-08","Scotland Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204498","204498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029329","2019-01-08","Wales Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204499","204499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029330","2019-01-08","Women and Equalities","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to her Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204500","204500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029331","2019-01-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to protect social housing tenants from carbon monoxide poisoning; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204501","204501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029332","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases the Independent Case Examiner has closed (a) after investigation and (b) without investigation; and for what reason those cases were closed in each month since September 2017.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204482","204482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029333","2019-01-08","Department for International Development","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the recently reported reductions in funding from the US to co-existence projects in Israel-Palestine on peace efforts in that region.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204610","204610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029334","2019-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to include debts owed to her Department in its new breathing space scheme.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204424","204424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029335","2019-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff were employed in her Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204533","204533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029336","2019-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204534","204534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029337","2019-01-08","Department for International Development","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff were employed in her Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204535","204535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029338","2019-01-08","Department for International Trade","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204536","204536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029339","2019-01-08","Department for Transport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204537","204537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029340","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204538","204538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029341","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204539","204539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029342","2019-01-08","Scotland Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204540","204540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029343","2019-01-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204541","204541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029344","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204542","204542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029345","2019-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204543","204543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029346","2019-01-08","Wales Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204544","204544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029347","2019-01-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204545","204545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029348","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204546","204546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029349","2019-01-08","Treasury","2018-12-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204547","204547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029350","2019-01-08","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204548","204548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029351","2019-01-08","Northern Ireland Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many staff were employed in her Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204549","204549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029352","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204550","204550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029353","2019-01-08","Attorney General","2018-12-20","To ask the Attorney General, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204551","204551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029354","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff were employed in his Department on (a) 20 December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204552","204552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029355","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many school children on Education, Health and Care Plans in Derbyshire do not have extra funding allocated to their schools for their plan.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204475","204475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029356","2019-01-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times a tribunal (a) has been required to meet to consider amendments, (b) found in favour of the application for amendment and (c) decided there would be no change to an Education, Health and Care Plan in each local authority area in each year since the plans were introduced.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204476","204476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029357","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many school children (a) are there and (b) have an Education, Health and Care Plan in each local authority area.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204477","204477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029358","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much was spent in the main categories of NHS commissioner spending as recorded centrally by NHS England for (a) acute, (b) mental Health, (c) community care, (d) continuing care and (e) primary care by clinical commissioning group in (i) 2015-16, (ii) 2016-17 and (iii) 2017-18.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204632","204632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029359","2019-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to publish its proposals on recompensing small scale renewables exporting to the grid.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204408","204408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029360","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how his Department is ensuring that funds allocated under the Teachers' Pay Grant for 2018-19 are being used to fund teachers' pay and not for any other purpose.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204598","204598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029361","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many educational psychological assessments have been carried out in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204513","204513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029362","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of trends in life expectancy.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204558","204558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029363","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the NHS's preparations for winter.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204559","204559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029364","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the level of staff shortages across the NHS.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204560","204560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029365","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of referral to treatment waiting times.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204561","204561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029366","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on contingency planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204562","204562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029367","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Draft Political Declaration setting out the framework for the future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, published on 22 November, whether the reciprocal arrangements on the future rules around some defined elements of social security coordination will include UK access to the A1 system exempting UK orchestras touring in European Union countries from paying social security contributions in those countries.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204363","204363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029368","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to improve the retention level of GPs within the NHS.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204563","204563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029369","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to tackle preventable blindness.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204564","204564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029370","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his timescale is for Public Health England's assessment of the effectiveness of minimum unit pricing in Scotland.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204570","204570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029371","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the capacity of the mental health workforce.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204565","204565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029372","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for the social care of (a) older people and (b) working-age disabled adults.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204566","204566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029373","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the pledges set out in the NHS Constitution on waiting times are met.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204567","204567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029374","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent meetings he has had with Babylon Healthcare.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204568","204568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029375","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to reports that some academies have chosen not to pay the 2018-19 teacher pay award despite receiving the Teacher's Pay Grant for that year, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that academies in receipt of the pay grant deliver the pay award to their teachers.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204599","204599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029376","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to tackle NHS workforce shortages.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204569","204569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029377","2019-01-08","Prime Minister","2018-12-20","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to her oral contribution of 19 December 2018, Official Report, column 786, what the evidential basis is for the statement that will of people in the EU referendum 2016 was to end free movement; and if she will place a copy of that research in the Library.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204601","204601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029378","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that teachers in sixth form colleges that (a) are and (b) are not academies receive the same Teachers' pay grant.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204600","204600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029379","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Commonwealth countries residents (a) need a visa and (b) do not need a visa to visit the UK for tourism purposes.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204602","204602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029380","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he plans to publish an alcohol workforce strategy to accompany the alcohol strategy.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204571","204571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029381","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) effectiveness and (b) cost-effectiveness of alcohol care teams in hospitals.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204572","204572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029382","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure midwives are aware of the Chief Medical Officers’ advice that it is safest not to drink alcohol during pregnancy.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204573","204573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029383","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure midwives communicate the Chief Medical Officers’ advice that it is safest not to drink alcohol during pregnancy.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204574","204574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029384","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding his Department has  allocated to training for midwives on the Chief Medical Officers’ advice that it is safest not to drink alcohol during pregnancy.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204575","204575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029385","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding his Department has allocated to training for health care professionals on the Chief Medical Officers’ advice that it is safest not to drink alcohol during pregnancy.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204576","204576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029386","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to inform the public of the Chief Medical Officers’ advice that it is safest not to drink alcohol during pregnancy.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204577","204577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029387","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have had in 2018 with representatives of (i) the alcohol industry and (ii) public health advocates to discuss minimum unit pricing for alcohol.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204578","204578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029388","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to put NHS-funded counsellors in every school to ensure easy access to mental health services for children.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204507","204507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029389","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of an independent inquiry on the treatment of ex-service personnel with mental health issues.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204508","204508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029390","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what financial advice serving military personnel receive.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204509","204509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029391","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of a voluntary system in which serving military personnel have a proportion of their pay directly transferred to a Lifetime ISA.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204510","204510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029392","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Independent Breast Screening Review report, published on gov.uk on 13 December 2018, what discussions his Department has had with (a) Public Health England and (b) NHS England on communicating the findings that report to women who were informed they may have been affected by a screening invitation error.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204445","204445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029393","2019-01-07","Department for International Development","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effect on poverty reduction in sub-Saharan countries of the increasing levels of debt owed by those countries.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204380","204380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029394","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has held with representatives of the Iraqi Government on (a) rebuilding and (b) rehabilitation programmes in territory previously occupied by Daesh.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204381","204381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029395","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has held discussions with representatives of (a) drug support charities and (b) other organisations on the level of drug-related deaths in relation to the abstinence and recovery agenda set out the Drug Strategy.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204555","204555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029396","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle alcohol-related health inequalities in England.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204579","204579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029397","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to increase funding for treatment of alcohol misuse.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204580","204580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029398","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to increase access to treatment for alcohol misuse.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204581","204581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029399","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria he will use to decide whether to include a minimum unit pricing for alcohol in the new joint alcohol strategy.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204582","204582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029400","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people over the age of 18 have used the Staying Put arrangements to stay with foster parents in Gloucestershire since 2014; and how many time was such a person not granted continuity of care.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204375","204375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029401","2019-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many infrastructure contracts overseen by his Department have been let with the stipulation that a Project Bank Account must be applied in the last year.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204611","204611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029402","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of UK troops deployed in operations to tackle the international drugs trade.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204382","204382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029403","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many infrastructure contracts overseen by his Department have been let with the stipulation that a Project Bank Account must be applied in the last year.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204612","204612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029404","2019-01-08","Department for International Development","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure nutritional support is considered by all teams and divisions within her Department.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204437","204437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029405","2019-01-08","Department for International Development","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she has taken to ensure the sharing of expertise on nutrition with Governments in her Department’s priority countries.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204438","204438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029406","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many infrastructure contracts overseen by his Department have been let with the stipulation that a Project Bank Account must be applied in the last year.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204613","204613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029407","2019-01-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many infrastructure contracts overseen by his Department have been let with the stipulation that a Project Bank Account must be applied in the last year.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204614","204614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029408","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many infrastructure contracts overseen by his Department have been let with the stipulation that a Project Bank Account must be applied in the last year.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204615","204615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029409","2019-01-08","Department for Transport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many infrastructure contracts overseen by his Department have been let with the stipulation that a Project Bank Account must be applied in the last year.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204616","204616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029410","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the (a) effectiveness of Sativex as a treatment for and (b) adequacy of access to Savitex on the NHS by patients with aggressively advancing relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204491","204491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029411","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Rwandan counterpart on that Government's request for the extradition of individuals residing in the UK that are accused of involvement in the Rwandan Genocide.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204383","204383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029412","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the CO2 regulations in Scotland in relation to private landlords.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204525","204525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029413","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what (a) guidance and (b) public awareness campaigns his Department has issued on the risk of carbon monoxide poisoning; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204526","204526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029414","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking reduce the risk of carbon monoxide poisoning in communities not on the gas distribution grid; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204527","204527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029415","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) number and (b) cost of refrigerators bought for the preservation of medicines as part of contingency planning in the event the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204430","204430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029416","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to ensure the maintenance of a skilled workforce in the rail industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204384","204384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029417","2019-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2018 to Question 202141 on UK Research and Innovation: Per Capita Costs, what assessment he has made of the disparities in per head funding for R&D throughout the (a) regions and (b) constituent parts of the UK.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204503","204503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029418","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant the Answer of 26 November 2018 to Question 194124 on Blood: Contamination, what plans he has to increase the level of financial support provide to people affected by infected blood and blood products; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204532","204532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029419","2019-01-08","Department for International Development","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what commitments the UK is legally bound by as a result of signing up to the UN Global compact on migration.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204586","204586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029420","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that the audit industry supports the assessment and disclosure of climate-related financial risk.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204444","204444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029421","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the UN Global compact on migration, what plans the UK has to take in additional migrants in 2019.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204587","204587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029422","2019-01-08","Department for International Trade","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2019 to Question 200631 on EU External Trade: Trade Agreements, how many and what proportion of third countries have confirmed that they will treat the UK as an EU Member State for the purposes of international agreements during the implementation period.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204504","204504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029423","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of drivers that have received fines for not renewing their road tax since the removal of the physical tax disc.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204426","204426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029424","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's policy is on sending out reminders to drivers to renew their road tax; and for what reason some drivers do not receive reminders.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204427","204427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029425","2019-01-08","Department for Transport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of tonnage on the UK Ship Register was from the (a) coastal freight, (b) container, (c) bulk carrier, (d) cruise and (e) offshore supply sectors in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204483","204483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029426","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representation he has made to his counterpart in the US Administration on its decision to withdraw American troops from Syria.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204605","204605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029427","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Turkish counterpart on the potential for a new military offensive by that country in Northern Syria.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204606","204606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029428","2019-01-08","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants in his Department are currently working on planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how many have been moved from other projects to work on those plans.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204446","204446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029429","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many civil servants in his Department are currently working on planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how many have been moved from other projects to work on those plans.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204447","204447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029430","2019-01-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many civil servants in his Department are currently working on planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how many have been moved from other projects to work on those plans.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204448","204448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029431","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civil servants in his Department are currently working on planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how many have been moved from other projects to work on those plans.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204449","204449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029432","2019-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many civil servants in his Department are currently working on planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how many have been moved from other projects to work on those plans.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204450","204450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029433","2019-01-08","Treasury","2018-12-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many civil servants in his Department are currently working on planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how many have been moved from other projects to work on those plans.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204451","204451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029434","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many civil servants in his Department are currently working on planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how many have been moved from other projects to work on those plans.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204452","204452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029435","2019-01-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many civil servants in his Department are currently working on planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how many have been moved from other projects to work on those plans.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204453","204453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029436","2019-01-08","Department for International Trade","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many civil servants in his Department are currently working on planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how many have been moved from other projects to work on those plans.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204454","204454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029437","2019-01-08","Department for Transport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many civil servants in his Department are currently working on planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how many have been moved from other projects to work on those plans.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204455","204455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029438","2019-01-08","Department for Transport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many projects his Department has put on hold due to the requirements of planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204456","204456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029439","2019-01-08","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many projects his Department has put on hold due to the requirements of planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204457","204457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029440","2019-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will hold a meeting with political representatives of the Kurdish population in Syria to discuss that community's concerns on (a) the withdrawal of US troops and (b) a potential new Turkish military offensive in Northern Syria.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204607","204607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029441","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many projects his Department has put on hold due to the requirements of planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204458","204458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029442","2019-01-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many projects his Department has put on hold due to the requirements of planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204459","204459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029443","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many projects his Department has put on hold due to the requirements of planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204460","204460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029444","2019-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many projects his Department has put on hold due to the requirements of planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204461","204461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029445","2019-01-08","Treasury","2018-12-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many projects his Department has put on hold due to the requirements of planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204462","204462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029446","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many projects his Department has put on hold due to the requirements of planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204463","204463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029447","2019-01-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many projects his Department has put on hold due to the requirements of planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204464","204464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029448","2019-01-08","Department for International Trade","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many projects his Department has put on hold due to the requirements of planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204465","204465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029449","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of changes in the level of activity of ISIS in Syria.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204608","204608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029450","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 11 December 2018 to Question 198864 on Ministry of Defence: Staff, for what reason that information which was available for the Answer of 12 May 2014 to Question 188387 on Nuclear Reactors is not available now.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204524","204524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029451","2019-01-07","Northern Ireland Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many civil servants in her Department are currently working on planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how many have been moved from other projects to work on those plans.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204466","204466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029452","2019-01-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many civil servants in his Department are currently working on planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how many have been moved from other projects to work on those plans.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204467","204467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029453","2019-01-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many projects his Department has put on hold due to the requirements of planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204468","204468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029454","2019-01-07","Northern Ireland Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many projects his Department has put on hold due to the requirements of planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204469","204469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029455","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the (a) suitability of gas operators current rights of entry and (b) effectiveness of the communication of those rights to vulnerable customers.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204557","204557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029456","2019-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Turkish counterpart to ensure that any military action in Northern Syria should not seek to evict the Kurdish population that lives there.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204609","204609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029457","2019-01-08","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what meetings Ministers in his Department have had with representatives of Interserve in 2018.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204484","204484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029458","2019-01-08","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2018 to Question 201666, how many meetings the Cabinet Office Markets and Suppliers team have had with representatives of Interserve plc in 2018.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204485","204485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029459","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the political situation in the Central African Republic; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204376","204376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029460","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people (a) recruited into and (b) resigned from each infantry regiment in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017 and (d) 2018; and the extent to which each regiment is at full complement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204377","204377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029461","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on what advice his predecessor made the decision to announce a serious incident in the NHS Breast Screening Programme when full information about the incident was not yet available.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204588","204588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029462","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether organisations such as charities and the Advisory Committee for Breast Cancer Screening will have an opportunity to respond officially to the independent review of the breast screening incident.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204589","204589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029463","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and which rail stations have (a) undertaken work in the last five years and (b) planned work within the next two years to improve access arrangements.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204378","204378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029464","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children are currently being represented by children and family court advisory and support service guardians in courts in England.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204583","204583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029465","2019-01-08","Department for Transport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the closure of Gatwick Airport on 19 and 20 December 2018 after illegal drone use threatened flight safety for the future resilience at that airport.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204480","204480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029466","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of Clinical Commissioning Groups which have been placed into financial directions by NHS England in each year since 2011-12; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204365","204365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029467","2019-01-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with counterparts in (a) the EU and (b) Governments of EU Member States on the potential consequences of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on carnet-free travel between the UK and the EU for musicians travelling for work purposes.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204425","204425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029468","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how often the judiciary in family courts including the lay bench have mandatory specialist training on domestic abuse.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204584","204584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029469","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that survivors of trafficking and modern slavery are not held in immigration detention.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204473","204473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029470","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the increase of the number of women from China held in immigration detention from 28 at the end of Q3 2017 to 52 at the end of Q3 2018.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204474","204474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029471","2019-01-07","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to (a) diversify public sector supply chains and (b) ensure greater account is given to social value in those supply chains.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204511","204511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029472","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2018 to Question 195064, what the maximum length of time was between the date when a First Tier Tribunal personal independence payment appeal was lodged and heard for cases involving claimants in Blaenau Gwent during 2017-18.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204470","204470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029473","2019-01-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on loneliness of the measures announced in Budget 2018.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204512","204512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029474","2019-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2018 to Question 195064, what the maximum length of time was between the date of a successful First Tier Tribunal personal independence payment decision and arrears being paid for claimants in Blaenau Gwent during 2017-18.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204471","204471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029475","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of refrigerators purchased for the preservation of medicines as part of contingency planning in the event the UK leaves the EU without a deal up to 20 December 2018.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204472","204472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029476","2019-01-08","Treasury","2018-12-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, where his Department archives information on wholly owned government companies; and whether such information is available for public review.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204590","204590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029477","2019-01-08","Treasury","2018-12-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will place a copy of Financial relationships with International Military Services Ltd (IMS) 1981-1984 [T 458/55], currently withheld from the National Archives, in the Library.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204591","204591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029478","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will instruct the directors of International Military Services Ltd to declassify their records using the same protocols that apply to his Department's own records.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204592","204592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029479","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish any (a) records and (b) documents relating to International Military Services Ltd that are currently kept in the care of (i) his Department and (ii) its associated agencies.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204593","204593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029480","2019-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department plans to publish a communique on the UK-Sudan Strategic Dialogue meeting which took place in London on 7 November 2018.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204492","204492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029481","2019-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress Sudan has made towards the ratification of the United Nations Convention Against Torture since the initiation of the UK-Sudan Strategic Dialogue in March 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204493","204493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029482","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place a file list of (a) records and (b) documents his Department holds on International Military Services Ltd in the Library.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204594","204594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029483","2019-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the powers allocated to the National Intelligence and Security Services in Sudan under that country's 2010 National Security Act.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204494","204494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029484","2019-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the powers allocated to the National Intelligence and Security Services in Sudan under the National Security Act 2010.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204495","204495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029485","2019-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Sudanese counterpart on reforms to that county's 2010 National Security Act.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204496","204496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029486","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department holds (a) records and (b) documents relating to International Military Services Ltd operations in Zimbabwe in 1983.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204595","204595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029487","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department has published all (a) records and (b) documents relating to the activities of International Military Services Ltd; and whether such documents have been made available to the public.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204596","204596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029488","2019-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 20 December 2018 on Personal Independence Payment, Official Report HCWS1224, what estimate her Department has made of (a) the number of claimants in Inverclyde that have received personal independence payments arrears and (b) the total amount paid to those claimants in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204556","204556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029489","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether resident EU citizens and their family members applying for UK immigration status under the EU Settlement Scheme will be required to show that they meet all the requirements of current free movement rules.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204621","204621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029490","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, at what rate he estimates the UK needs to build houses in order to cope with the additional demand created by current levels of immigration.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204387","204387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029491","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of refugees who have entered the UK in each of the last five years were male.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204388","204388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029492","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what comparative estimate he has made of the levels of crime committed by British citizens and non-British citizens in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204389","204389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029493","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to increase support for families who have suffered baby loss.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204429","204429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029494","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of illegal immigrants residing in the UK.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204390","204390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029495","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of EU workers arriving in the UK would not have qualified for a highly-skilled work permit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204391","204391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029496","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the effect of low-skilled migration on the economy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204392","204392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029497","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many new migrants have registered with general practitioners since 2015.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204393","204393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029498","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of illegal immigrants that have committed crimes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204394","204394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029499","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many first generation immigrants have been convicted of committing crimes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204395","204395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029500","2019-01-08","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people convicted of murder have committed the same crime again following their release from prison.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204396","204396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029501","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of refugees resettled in the UK identify as (a) Christian, (b) Jewish, (c) Hindu, (d) Islamic, (e) Sikh and (f) Buddhist.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204397","204397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029502","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to protect people from antisocial behaviour.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204398","204398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029503","2019-01-08","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many instances of antisocial behaviour have been recorded in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204399","204399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029504","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS patients are suffering from psychosis related to their use of cannabis.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204400","204400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029505","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many abortions were performed after 20 weeks in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204401","204401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029506","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the point at which an unborn child can experience pain.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204402","204402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029507","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the point at which an unborn child is able to recognise light.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204403","204403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029508","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the point at which an unborn child's heart begins to beat.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204404","204404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029509","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what comparison he has made of the divorce rates of married heterosexual and married same-sex couples.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204405","204405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029510","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the current average waiting time for fraud cases to be allocated for investigation by police forces in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204418","204418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029511","2019-01-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Written Statement of 29 November 2018 on Grenfell Update, Official Report HCWS1126, what types of dangerous cladding local authorities are able to remove from high-rise buildings under new measures on enforcement and remedial action.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204419","204419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029512","2019-01-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his department has made of the reasons for the decline in the number of water voles in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204420","204420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029513","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 21 of the Cross-Government Fraud Landscape Annual Report 2018, to what incident or incidents the £111.2 million for detected error refers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204409","204409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029514","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received from the British Counties Campaign; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204421","204421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029515","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 21 of the Cross-Government Fraud Landscape Annual Report 2018, to what incident or incidents the £88.2 million for detected fraud in his Department refers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204410","204410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029516","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date the immigration health surcharge will be increased from £200 to £400; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204481","204481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029517","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish all the information his Department holds on whether International Military Services Ltd was included in the National Audit Office’s value for money work on defence sales in the 1980s and early 1990s and in any associated work that may have been unpublished.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204597","204597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029518","2019-01-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time is for appeals to the Tribunal against (a) personal independence payments and (b) employment and support allowance assessments to be heard in (i) Leeds and (ii) England in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204422","204422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029519","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to give the Parachute Regiment permissions to accompany (a) the Afghan National Defence and Security Forces and (b) the Kabul Security Force; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204440","204440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029520","2019-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her policy is on having defibrillators available in all her Department's premises.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204423","204423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029521","2019-01-08","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the subject of imprints for digital electoral material was discussed in meetings the Minister for the Consitution had with Facebook and Google on electoral reform in September 2018.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204411","204411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029522","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the status is of Tier 1 (investor) visa applications.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204622","204622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029523","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Written Statement of 6 September 2018, HCWS1159, how the review of Tier 1 (investor) visas will be conducted; which bodies will be consulted as part of that review; and what the timescale is for that review to report.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204623","204623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029524","2019-01-08","Prime Minister","2018-12-20","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2018 to Questions 202895 and 202896, for what reasons she did not specify in that answer whether any of her staff have (a) met or (b) held discussions with former Prime Minister, David Cameron in the last two months.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204618","204618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029525","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Office, how many Unexplained Wealth Orders have been invoked in each month since they were introduced.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204624","204624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029526","2019-01-08","Prime Minister","2018-12-20","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2018 to Questions 202895 and 202896, whether she has held discussions with former Prime Minister, David Cameron via (a) written communication and (b) telephone.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204619","204619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029527","2019-01-07","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Office of the Registrar of Consultant Lobbyists plans to publish all documents relating to its concluded investigation into the Institute of Economic Affairs.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204412","204412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029528","2019-01-07","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether any of the Voter ID Pilot authorities present at the meeting with the Minister for the Constitution in August 2018 raised objection to the pilots.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204413","204413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029529","2019-01-07","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether staff at the Office of the Registrar of Consultant Lobbyists are instructed to cross-reference information from published ministerial meetings data with that provided by companies on the register in their returns.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204414","204414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029530","2019-01-08","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the change in the number of invoices his Department paid within 30 days in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204415","204415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029531","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how often Cafcass professionals undergo mandatory specialist training on domestic abuse.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204585","204585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029532","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's report The United Kingdom’s Future Nuclear Deterrent: 2018 Update to Parliament, which companies that are part of the supply chain to the Nuclear Enterprise are located in the EU 27; and in what countries those companies are located.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204441","204441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029533","2019-01-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the report entitled DCMS gender pay gap 2017/18, published on gov.uk on 19 December 2018, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the rise in the median measure for the difference in hourly rate between male and female civil servants between 2016-2017 and 2017-2018.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204416","204416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029534","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's report entitled The United Kingdom’s Future Nuclear Deterrent: 2018 Update to Parliament, when he plans to make a decision on replacing the warhead used by the UK's nuclear-armed submarines.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204442","204442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029535","2019-01-08","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2018 to Question 185519, whether the move to the new shared service platform resulted in any payment delays in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204417","204417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029536","2019-01-08","Department for International Development","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to (a) make employment in the aid sector a regulated activity and (b) bring disclosure and barring requirements in line with other professions that work with children and vulnerable adults.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204603","204603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029537","2019-01-08","Department for International Development","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of regulating employment in the aid sector.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204604","204604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029538","2019-01-07","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many and what proportion of his departmental officials (a) are foreign nationals, (b) are EU citizens and (c) hold dual nationality.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204486","204486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029539","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his policies of the Royal College of Psychiatrists report Suffering in Silence: age inequality in older people’s mental health care which concluded that older adults are the least likely group to seek treatment for mental health care despite being the group who achieve the highest recovery rates in services provided under the Improving Access to Psychological Therapies programme.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204487","204487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029540","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 13 December 2018 to Question 200657, how specifically the EU Withdrawal Agreement and the Political Declaration lay the foundation for a strong NHS.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204488","204488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029541","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the December 2017 Green Paper entitled Transforming the Mental Health of Children and Young People, what progress has been made on implementing the four-week waiting time target.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204489","204489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029542","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  with reference to the December 2017 Green Paper entitled Transforming the Mental Health of Children and Young People, whether the four-week waiting time target refers to a waiting time from referral to (a) assessment or (b) treatment.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204490","204490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029543","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much allowance he has made for taxes and national insurance in his Department's calculations of the cost of a Type 31e frigate with a set price of £250m.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204634","204634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029544","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in how many countries the UK military is conducting counterterrorism operations; and in how many of those countries the UK is (a) conducting air and drone strikes, (b) deploying combat troops, (c) constructing or retaining military bases  and (d) building the capacity of partners to conduct counterterrorism and other actions.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204354","204354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029545","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Court of Appeal judgment on firefighters' pensions of 20 December 2018, what his Department's total legal costs were in that case; what estimate his Department has made of the potential costs of implementing that judgment; and how those potential costs are planned to be defrayed between central and local government.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204379","204379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029546","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2018 to Question 202300 on Global Navigation Satellite Systems: Costs, when the engineering, design, and development phase is expected to report.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204443","204443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029547","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Office, what information his Department holds on the nationality of people affect by the imposition of Unexplained Wealth Orders.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204625","204625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029548","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the changes to the civil standard of proof proposed in the recent consultation from the Solicitors Disciplinary Tribunal on users of legal services.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204631","204631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029549","2019-01-07","Treasury","2018-12-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the Financial Conduct Authority's ability to enforce their own affordability checks on high-cost credit.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204617","204617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029550","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs to be lost as a result of automation in the UK in the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204364","204364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029551","2019-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to publish the results of his Department's consultation on the creation of a new offence of failure to prevent economic crime.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204626","204626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029552","2019-01-08","Department for International Development","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the conflict in Yemen on that country's economy; and what steps her Department is taking to support economic recovery in that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204385","204385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029553","2019-01-08","Department for International Development","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to strengthen local service delivery in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204386","204386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029554","2019-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the effect of noise from military aircraft operations from RAF Benson on Abingdon residents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204620","204620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029555","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase the funding available to local authorities to provide effective children's services to support children and their families.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204478","204478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029556","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make a comparative assessment of the changes in the level of his Department's spending on children's services (a) in total and (b) per child in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204479","204479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029557","2019-01-07","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2018 to Question 202801, for what reason no reference was made in that Answer to the number of Government Departments which use (a) a system for identifying external emails to recipients and (b) a protocol for timely staff reporting of suspicious emails.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204633","204633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029558","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the (a) support and (b) treatment for people detained under the Mental Health Act 1983.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204428","204428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029559","2019-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to previous cases brought by the Office of Fair Trading (OFT) against retailers under Chapter 1, Section 2, Subsection 2 of the Competition Act 1998, what discussions he has had with the OFT on the treatment of joint working between supermarkets to enable food security in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204627","204627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029560","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will define a (a) high-skilled, (b) medium-skilled and (c) low-skilled migrant in the context of The UK's future skills-based immigration system White Paper.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204528","204528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029561","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what occupations would be considered (a) high-skilled, (b) medium-skilled and (c) low-skilled in the context of The UK's future skills-based immigration system White Paper.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204529","204529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029562","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) investigate claims about patient safety in the Eye Department of University Hospital Southampton NHS Foundation Trust (UHS); (b) protect patients treated in that Department from harm; (c) assure whistle-blowers that they will not suffer reprisals for speaking out; (d) inquire into above average sight loss amongst patients operated on by a particular surgeon in the Department; (e) investigate the alleged use of NHS lists by the same individual for use by a private practice; (f) establish why external experts were not invited to inspect the clinical records of patients who had lost their sight; (g) protect patients from further risk by conducting an independent inquiry; (h) draw lessons for the future from this situation and the treatment by UHS of a senior consultant who attempted to blow the whistle three years ago; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204355","204355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029563","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which countries his Department has identified as a high risk of abuse of the immigration system.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204530","204530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029564","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which countries his Department has identified as a low risk of abuse of the immigration system.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204531","204531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029565","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much capital funding his Department has allocated to each NHS trust in London in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204366","204366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029566","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the amount of capital funding which will be allocated to each NHS trust in London in each year between 2019 and 2022.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204367","204367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029567","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much capital funding has been approved by his Department for Barking, Havering and Redbridge Universities NHS Trust in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204368","204368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029568","2019-01-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to increase investment to meet social care needs in north-east London.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204369","204369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029569","2019-01-08","Department for Transport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the time frame is for the Elizabeth Line to be fully operational.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204370","204370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029570","2019-01-08","Department for Transport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the total cost of Crossrail.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204371","204371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029571","2019-01-08","Department for International Trade","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many specialist trade negotiators have been appointed by his Department in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204372","204372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029572","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will increase support to Redbridge Council to combat homelessness and rough sleeping in Ilford.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204373","204373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029573","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what material changes have been made to the 2015 National Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre planning brief since its publication.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204356","204356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029574","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which criteria (a) local authorities, (b) the Royal Parks and (c) his Department uses to assess applications to construct substantial buildings in (i) Royal Parks and (ii) world heritage sites.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204357","204357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029575","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the business case for the (a) construction and (b) continuing costs of the National Holocaust Memorial and Leaning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204358","204358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029576","2019-01-08","Department for Education","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to improve Ofsted's inspection regime for small private schools to combat extremism and radicalisation.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204374","204374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029577","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether entry to the National Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre is planned to be free of charge.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204359","204359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029578","2019-01-08","Home Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the accounting officer for his Department has sought a written ministerial direction for expenditure on contingency planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204431","204431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029579","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will meet Lords and Commons Members to discuss their concerns about building in Victoria Tower Gardens.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204360","204360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029580","2019-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the accounting officer for his Department has sought a written ministerial direction for expenditure on contingency planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204432","204432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029581","2019-01-08","Cabinet Office","2018-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the accounting officer for his Department has sought a written ministerial direction for expenditure on contingency planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204433","204433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029582","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which Government Departments officials in his Department have had meetings with to discuss the National Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre; and the dates on which those meetings took place.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204361","204361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029583","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the accounting officer for his Department has sought a written ministerial direction for expenditure on contingency planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204434","204434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029584","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if the Minister will make representations to the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation on the potential merits of the Foundation engaging with (a) a variety of members of the Jewish community and (b) representatives of the Buxton memorial against slavery to increase support for that Memorial.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204362","204362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029585","2019-01-07","Treasury","2018-12-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the accounting officer for his Department has sought a written ministerial direction for any expenditure on contingency planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204435","204435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029586","2019-01-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timetable is for the publication of the independent review of disabled facilities grants.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204553","204553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029587","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the accounting officer for his Department has requested a written ministerial direction for expenditure on contingency planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204436","204436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029588","2019-01-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the Overseas Territory of Anguilla of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204406","204406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029589","2019-01-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the merits of the proposal from the Government of Anguilla for a customs union and common travel area with St Martin.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204407","204407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1029590","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in how many countries the UK is conducting military counterterrorism operations, and in how many of those countries the UK is (a) conducting air and drone strikes, (b) deploying combat troops, (c) constructing or retaining military bases and (d) building the capacity of partners to conduct counterterrorism and other operations.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204635","204635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038939","2019-01-15","Treasury","2018-12-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the press release of Her Majesty's Treasury Press Release entitled Crackdown on financial crime made reference to the Written Statement of 6 December 2018 on Statement of Changes in Immigration Rules, HCWS1159.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207272","207272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028407","2018-12-19","Cabinet Office","2018-12-19","What plans he has to change the time limit on the entitlement of UK citizens living overseas to register to vote in UK parliamentary elections.","Biography information for Greg Hands","Greg Hands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908302","908302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028408","2018-12-19","Cabinet Office","2018-12-19","What steps the Government is taking to protect the UK electoral system from overseas interference.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908303","908303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028409","2018-12-19","Cabinet Office","2018-12-19","What recent discussions he has had with Interserve on the viability of its public sector contracts.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908305","908305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028476","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to ensure that all state-funded schools provide pupils with the opportunity to develop specific and age-appropriate knowledge and understanding of religions as part of promoting mutual respect and tolerance of people with different faiths and beliefs.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","Mr William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203925","203925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028477","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Bahraini counterpart on the quashing of the death sentences of Mohamed Ramadhan and Husain Moosa by Bahrain’s Court of Cassation and their upcoming retrial before that country's Court of Appeal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203820","203820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028478","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his US counterpart on the UK Government's opposition to the use of torture.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203821","203821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028479","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the number of vehicles using (a) the M4, (b) the M25, (c) the A4 and (d) the local road network to access Heathrow airport in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203822","203822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028481","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2018 to Question 183860 on High Rise Flats: Fire Prevention, and reports of high concentrations of toxins in the soil around Grenfell Tower, what assessment the Government has made about the safety of school sites where there have been fires.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203823","203823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028482","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the report entitled, Cost of energy: independent review, published by his Department in August 2017, if he will make it his policy to place all electricity policy costs into a single levy; and exempt energy intensive industry from those costs.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203872","203872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028483","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate the Government has made of the cost of energy in the steel sectors in the (a) UK, (b) Germany and (c) France.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203873","203873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028484","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many adults who have been detained for immigration purposes since they were under 18 years of age are still detained.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203948","203948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028485","2019-01-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of court cases which will have to be referred to the Crown Prosecution Service to establish if they were affected by compromised data from private forensic drug testing firm Randox Testing Services Laboratory.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203909","203909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028486","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the effects of Israel’s settlement expansion on the welfare Palestinian refugees in the West Bank.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203855","203855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028488","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to raise concerns with the Israeli Government on the imminent demolition of Khan al-Ahmar.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203856","203856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028489","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Energy and Clean Growth of 20 November 2018, Official Report, column 701, when he plans to publish proposals on rewarding small-scale renewables that export to the grid.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203947","203947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028490","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department takes in cases where British citizens of dual nationality are held in arbitrary detention in their country of other nationality.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203949","203949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028491","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department’s policy is on (a) consular access and (b) private visits by embassy staff for British nationals detained abroad at risk of torture or ill-treatment.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203950","203950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028492","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2018 to Question 196822 on High Speed 2 Railway Line, what steps he has taken to act on the representations made by constituents of Hampstead and Kilburn on settlement damage to buildings along the High Speed Two tunnel route.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203951","203951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028493","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Clause 4.5 and Clause 7 of HS2 Information Paper C3 precludes (a) Settlement Deeds or (b) a Defect Survey for individual buildings on (i) Alexandra Place, (ii) Dinerman Court, (iii) The Alexandra and Ainsworth Estate and (iv) The Rowley Estate in the constituency of Hampstead and Kilburn.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203952","203952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028494","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment has he made of the implications for the national curriculum of the findings of the British Council’s 2018 Language Trends Survey.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","Mr William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203926","203926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028496","2019-01-07","Treasury","2018-12-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether a return of duty free would see the return of allowances and see an end to personal duty paid goods coming in from the EU.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203929","203929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028497","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether EU nationals who are police officers in the UK will be entitled to hold a warrant card in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203930","203930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028498","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has had discussions with the National Police Co-ordination Centre on the circumstances in which military assistance will be required to support policing operations in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203931","203931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028499","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what processes are in place to ensure that an individual who is serving in the armed forces is aware that the Child Maintenance Service is investigating a case relating to them; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203825","203825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028501","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, under what circumstances his Department reveals to a third party that an individual is receiving a war disablement pension.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203826","203826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028502","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department provides assistance to (a) serving and (b) retired personnel when they are in dispute with the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203827","203827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028503","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases from the (a) 1993 and (b) 2003 Child Support Agency schemes remain open.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203828","203828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028505","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the March 2017 report of the NAO entitled Child maintenance: closing cases and managing arrears on the 1993 and 2003 schemes, HC 1054, for what reason fewer than expected parents who were asked by her Department to join the new scheme have been joining that scheme when their 1993 and 2003 scheme cases are closed.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203829","203829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028506","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the March 2017 report of the NAO entitled Child maintenance: closing cases and managing arrears on the 1993 and 2003 schemes, HC 1054, what assessment is made of the implications for the level of Child Maintenance Service payments of the (a) war pension and (b) other legacy benefits that a person claims.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203830","203830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028507","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what record is made of (a) whom and (b) which Department has supplied information during the assessment of (i) Child Support Agency and (ii) Child Maintenance Service payments.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203831","203831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028509","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how long records of conversations relating to the (a) Child Support Agency and (b) Child Maintenance Service by phone or email with employers are kept.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203832","203832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028510","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appeals to the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman relating to the (a) Child Support Agency and (b) Child Maintenance Service have been upheld in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203833","203833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028511","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will ensure that social care receives a real terms increase in funding in the forthcoming comprehensive spending review.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203981","203981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028513","2019-01-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on confidentiality agreements signed by the owners of vessels used by CEFAS in studying the effect of electric fishing in UK waters.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203853","203853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028514","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to cover the £65 application fee for the resettlement process for EU Nationals employed by his Department after March 2019.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203966","203966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028515","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment has been made of the potential risk of the £65 application fee for the resettlement process to the retention of EU Nationals employed by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203967","203967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028517","2019-01-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the implications were for the cost of the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre project of the Government’s decision to locate that centre in Victoria Tower Gardens instead of on Millbank.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203794","203794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028518","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of students who have been granted a university place after obtaining three D grades or lower at A-level in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203932","203932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028519","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the proportion of students granted a place at (a) Russell Group, (b) University Alliance, (c) Million Plus and (d) Guild HE universities having obtained three D grades or lower at A-level in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203933","203933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028520","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the BBC Panorama programme of 17 November 2018, what assessment he has made of the validity of the reports on that programme of the financial situation of HS2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203760","203760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028521","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of health visitors (a) in England, (b) regionally and (c) in each local authority area in each year since September 2009.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203898","203898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028522","2019-01-07","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will make it his policy to seek to secure a ring-fenced agreement with the EU on citizens rights even if no agreement on other matters related to the UK leaving the EU can be concluded and ratified by 29 March 2018.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203913","203913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028524","2019-01-07","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which pieces of retained EU law it has identified as unable to operate effectively after Brexit but it which it does not intend to remedy or mitigate under the European Union (Withdrawal) Act 2018.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203914","203914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028525","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effects of the policies outlined in the Waste and Resources Strategy, published on 18 December 2018, on public health.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203774","203774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028526","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2018 to Question 193367, what evidence Public Health England has considered on the effects of dioxins released during incineration of municipal waste on human health.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203775","203775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028527","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made in tackling money laundering between the UK and Pakistan.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203971","203971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028528","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people that work in the NHS that have been paid an annual salary of (a) less than and (b) more than £30,000 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203789","203789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028529","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of people employed by schools that have been paid an annual salary of (a) less than and (b) more than £30,000 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203790","203790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028530","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made the number of members of the armed forces that have been paid an annual salary of (a) less than and (b) more than £30,000 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203791","203791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028532","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence on how many occasions Russian aircraft not using an on-board transponder have been detected in (a) approaches to and (b) inside UK airspace in each of the last five years; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203811","203811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028533","2019-01-07","Cabinet Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of civil service staff that have been paid an annual salary of (a) less than and (b) more than £30,000 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203792","203792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028534","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have died while waiting for their personal independence payment assessment to be completed; and what conditions those people died from.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203812","203812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028535","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who applied for personal independence payment died within six months of making their application.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203813","203813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028536","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions she has had with the Scottish Government on enabling registered medical practitioners to make clinical judgments about whether illnesses are terminal.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203814","203814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028537","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she will ask the Scottish Government for advanced sight of the guidance being developed to enable registered medical practitioners to make a clinical judgement on whether an illness is regarded as terminal.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203815","203815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028539","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the financial effect of enabling registered healthcare professionals to make clinical judgments about whether illnesses are terminal without using the six-month time limit.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203816","203816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028540","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate she has made of the completion date for the roll-out of universal credit.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203793","203793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028541","2019-01-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of policies in the Government's Immigration White Paper on the level of staffing in the food and drink manufacturing sector.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203797","203797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028542","2019-01-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much his Department bid for from the Treasury for EU-exit resources in 2019-20; pursuant to the written statement of 18 December 2018 of the Chief Secretary to the Treasury, Official Report HCWS1205, how he plans to spend the £35 million his Department has been allocated in 2019-20 for EU-exit; and pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2018 to Question 181171 on Emergencies: Planning, (a) what the cost to the public purse was of funding G7 Resilience Advisers in 2018-19 and (b) from which budget of his Department that cost has been met.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203795","203795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028543","2019-01-07","Treasury","2018-12-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer,  with reference to the Written Statement of 18 December 2018 on Public Spending, HCWS1205, what the value was of each Department's bid for funding.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203796","203796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028544","2019-01-07","Treasury","2018-12-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to implement an affordable repayment plan for people affected by the disguised remuneration loan charge.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203982","203982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028546","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Government's Immigration White Paper on the level of staffing for (a) clinical roles in the NHS, (b) non-clinical roles in the NHS and (c) the social care sector.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203798","203798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028547","2019-01-07","Treasury","2018-12-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203877","203877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028548","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203878","203878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028550","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203879","203879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028551","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many occasions his Department has invited home-country officials to interview asylum seekers; and what the nationality of those officials was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203899","203899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028552","2019-01-07","Attorney General","2018-12-19","To ask the Attorney General, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203880","203880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028554","2019-01-07","Cabinet Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203881","203881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028555","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203882","203882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028556","2019-01-07","Department for International Development","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Report on the work of the Independent Expert Panel on prevention of and response to harassment, including sexual harassment, bullying and abuse of power at UNAIDS Secretariat, what recent assessment she has made of the allegations against UNAIDS; and if she will make a statement on the future of the UK's contributions to that agency.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203900","203900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028557","2019-01-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203883","203883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028558","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate her Department has made of the number of mixed-age couples who have been negatively affected by changes to universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203901","203901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028559","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203884","203884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028561","2019-01-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203885","203885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028562","2019-01-07","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203886","203886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028564","2019-01-07","Department for International Development","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to her Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203887","203887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028565","2019-01-07","Department for International Trade","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203888","203888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028566","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203889","203889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028567","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to her Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203890","203890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028569","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203891","203891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028570","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203892","203892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028571","2019-01-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203893","203893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028573","2019-01-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to his Department for financial year 2018-19 for planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203894","203894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028574","2019-01-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what powers his Department has devolved to the Mayor of London to tackle homelessness and rough sleeping; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203818","203818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028575","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to publish the Maximising Competition on Defence Procurement Strategy, as set out in the Government response to the Twentieth to the Thirtieth reports from Committee of Public Accounts.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203849","203849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028576","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the written statement of 18 December 2018 of on public spending, Official Report HCWS1205, to which programmes his Department will allocate the £12million for planning for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203850","203850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028578","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the social care green paper.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203761","203761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028579","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have died while waiting for their eligibility for personal independence payment to be determined, and what the main disabling condition was of those people.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203817","203817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028580","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Oral Statement of 18 December 2018, Official Report, column 657, on Modernising Defence Programme, if he will publish the details of the increase in the mass of the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203804","203804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028581","2019-01-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if his Department will bring forward legislative proposals to require the installation of CO2 alarms in private rental properties with any fuel-burning appliance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203895","203895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028583","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Written Statement of 18 December 2018, Public Spending, HCWS 1205, if he will publish the budget headlines under which he plans to allocate the £190 million funding in relation to preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203915","203915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028584","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to announce his Department's response to the review of single source procurement legislation.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203851","203851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028585","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he or his officials have had with US counterparts on the use of renewable energy in defence.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203852","203852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028586","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of electronic conspicuity devices on safety in general aviation.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203762","203762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028587","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to promote the use of electronic conspicuity devices in general aviation.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203763","203763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028589","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's publication, Mobilising, Modernising and Transforming Defence: A Report on the Modernising Defence Programme, whether (a) headline findings of the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Review have been preserved and (b) Force 2025 remains on track.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203805","203805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028590","2019-01-07","Treasury","2018-12-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to exempt electronic conspicuity devices used in general aviation from VAT.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203764","203764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028591","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much (a) his Department and (b) NHS England has spent on refrigerators in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203980","203980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028592","2019-01-07","Department for International Development","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to collect disaggregated population data on minority groups in the Middle East region to establish whether UK aid reaches those groups.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203809","203809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028593","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's publication of 18 December 2018, Mobilising, Modernising and Transforming Defence: A report on the Modernising Defence Programme, for what reasons that publication contains no reference to his Department's Equipment Plan estimated budget deficit.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203806","203806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028594","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's publication, Mobilising, Modernising and Transforming Defence: A Report on the Modernising Defence Programme, whether the Modernising Defence Programme is extant; and whether its principle purpose is to inform the planned cross-departmental Comprehensive Spending Review.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203807","203807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028596","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which units from the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Army, (c) Royal Air Force and (d) Royal Marines will be deployed to Operation Yellowhammer.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203808","203808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028597","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department instructed the Home Office not to offer asylum to Asia Bibi due to potential unrest in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203810","203810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028598","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what is the minimum amount that will be granted from the Holiday Activities and Food 2019 fund.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203902","203902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028599","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which of the nine civil Magnox nuclear power stations were modified to enable the production of military grade plutonium.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203865","203865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028600","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which Magnox reactors based in the UK have produced military grade plutonium.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203866","203866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028601","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made any payments to The Bulldog Trust in each financial year since 2015-16.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203869","203869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028603","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has made any payments to The Bulldog Trust in each financial year since 2015-16.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203870","203870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028604","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has made any payments to The Bulldog Trust in each financial year since 2015-16.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203871","203871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028605","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when her Department plans to respond to the National Audit Office report entitled Child maintenance: closing cases and managing arrears on the 1993 and 2003 schemes published 28 March 2017; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203834","203834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028607","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many liability orders were granted to the Child Support Agency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203835","203835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028608","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many liability orders granted in magistrates' courts to the Child Support Agency were for an amount over £5,000.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203836","203836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028609","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the procedure in the Child Support Agency is to report alleged benefit fraud to her Department.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203837","203837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028611","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases of alleged benefit fraud were reported to her Department in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203838","203838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028612","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff are employed by the Child Support Agency.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203839","203839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028613","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether there is a bonus scheme in the Child Support Agency.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203840","203840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028615","2019-01-07","Wales Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with reference to the White Paper, The UK’s future skills-based immigration system, published on 19 December 2018, what discussions his Department has had with the Home Secretary on the effect of the proposed minimum salary requirement of £30,000 for skilled migrants on the Welsh economy.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203921","203921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028616","2019-01-07","Wales Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of funding it requires to plan for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and if he will place any documentation on such estimates in the Library.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203922","203922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028617","2019-01-07","Treasury","2018-12-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been allocated to the devolved administrations to help them prepare for the possibility that the UK does not agree a Withdrawal Agreement with the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203923","203923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028618","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place in the Library the Government's full plans to facilitate traffic flows (a) into, (b) through and (c) around Welsh ports after 29 March 2019 in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203924","203924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028620","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman has found against the Child Support Agency for maladministration; and how much compensation was paid in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203841","203841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028621","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when NHS England plans to review and update the National Genomic Test Directory to reflect the NICE guidance published December 2018 on tumour profiling tests to guide adjuvant chemotherapy decisions in early breast cancer.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203874","203874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028622","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NICE guidance, Tumour profiling tests to guide adjuvant chemotherapy decisions in early breast cancer, published in December 2018, what NHS England’s position is on that guidance.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203875","203875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028623","2019-01-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements the Child Support Agency has entered into in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203842","203842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028625","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to The UK’s future skills-based immigration system White Paper, published on 19 December 2018, how low-risk countries be determined.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203972","203972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028626","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has commissioned or undertaken external workforce modelling for nursing.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203771","203771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028627","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to The UK’s future skills-based immigration system White Paper, published on 19 December 2018, whether there will be a numerical cap on temporary short-term workers.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203973","203973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028628","2019-01-07","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2018-12-19","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if she will place in the Library a copy of the guidance that the Electoral Commission uses when determining the proportionality of setting the level of a variable monetary penalty.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203928","203928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028629","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to publish the results of the consultation on draft guidance for elective home education; and how many submissions were received for that consultation.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203979","203979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028630","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the validity of reports of continued enforced disappearances of minorities, dissidents and others in Pakistan.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203799","203799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028631","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the Government of Pakistan in tackling cases of enforced disappearances in that country.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203800","203800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028633","2019-01-07","Department for International Development","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the UK Government takes to ensure that UK aid is not used to support military, security and intelligence authorities in Pakistan allegedly involved in the enforced disappearance of people in that country.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203801","203801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028634","2019-01-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to ensure that UK military goods exported to Pakistan are not used (a) in military operations in Balochistan, Federally Administered Tribal Areas or Khyber Pakhtunkhwa and (b) by internal security forces or the intelligence services to monitor the activities of (i) political activists, (ii) human rights defenders and (iii) peaceful civilians in that country.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203802","203802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028635","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2018 to Question 201214 on Rare Diseases: Drugs, on how many occasions NICE has made a conditional recommendation for a rare disease treatment that do not qualify for conditional recommendation through the cancer drugs fund; and what criteria NICE uses to determine whether such treatments are eligible for conditional recommendations.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203975","203975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028637","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what  steps his Department is taking to reduce waiting times between referral and the start of treatment for adults with eating disorders.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203953","203953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028638","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time between GP referral and the start of NHS treatment is for adults with eating disorders.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203954","203954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028639","2019-01-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Questions 189756 and 189757 on Prison Sentences: Males, how many (a) men and (b) women were sentenced to prison in the first six months of 2018 by Home Office offence code.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203938","203938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028640","2019-01-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information the Animal and Plant Health Agency holds on the estimated number of game birds on game farm premises as supplied by owners of those game farms to that agency.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203896","203896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028642","2019-01-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which organisation or Department holds data on the mortality rates for game bird farms.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203897","203897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028643","2019-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has entered into in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203843","203843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028644","2019-01-07","Treasury","2018-12-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has entered into in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203844","203844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028645","2019-01-07","Home Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has entered into in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203845","203845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028646","2019-01-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has entered into in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203846","203846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028648","2019-01-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has entered into in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203847","203847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028649","2019-01-07","Northern Ireland Office","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department has entered into in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203848","203848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028650","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the (a) role and (b) responsibilities are of the Chief Executive of Tameside and Glossop NHS Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203819","203819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028651","2019-01-07","Department for International Development","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what consultation his Department has undertaken with local communities prior to activities being (a) finalised and (b) implemented under her Department's Pakistan Economic Corridors Programme.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203803","203803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028653","2019-01-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of minimum unit pricing for alcohol in Scotland on (a) the level of consumption of alcohol and (b) public health.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203934","203934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028654","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to increase motorcycle safety.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203935","203935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028655","2019-01-07","Department for Transport","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Road Safety Statement: Progress Report document published 13 June 2018, what progress has been made since the publication of that document to strengthen the compulsory basic training regime for motorcyclists.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203936","203936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028657","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the accuracy of the statement by the Mayor of London that there is a climate emergency.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203937","203937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028658","2019-01-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment the Department has made of the potential effect on the number of households choosing to install solar panels of the cessation of payment for excess electricity exported to the grid by solar households.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203776","203776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028660","2019-01-07","Attorney General","2018-12-19","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 10 of September 2018 to Question 199279, which motoring offences remain the responsibility of the CPS.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203777","203777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028661","2019-01-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions for the offence of consumption of alcohol in a designated public place under the Criminal Justice and Police Act 2001 were made by each police force in each year from 30 September 2008.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203778","203778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028662","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the answer of 5 December 2018 to Question 199283 on Disabled Students Allowances, what information his Department holds on the demographic characteristics of the students that chose to take up the disabled students’ equipment allowance in each year since 2014-15.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203779","203779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028664","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2018 to Question 199283 on Disabled Students Allowances, how many full-time undergraduate students were domiciled in England  in each year since 2014-15.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203780","203780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028665","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2018 to Question 199283 on Disabled Students Allowances, if he will publish the information for part-time students.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203781","203781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1028666","2019-01-07","Department for Education","2018-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2018 to Question 199283 on Disabled Students Allowances, what the provisional figure is for 2016-2017.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203782","203782"
