"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4267","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the importance of clothes to fit in influencing the subjective wellbeing of children.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154613","154613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4268","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the comparative wellbeing of the (a) black ethnic community and (b) Bangladeshi community.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154614","154614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4269","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the differences between anxiety levels of (a) non-white and (b) white ethnic groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154615","154615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4270","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effects of unemployment on levels of wellbeing.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154616","154616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4271","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what comparative assessment he has made of differences in unemployment levels between (a) white, (b) mixed race, (c) Indian, (d) Pakistani, (e) Bangladeshi, (f) Chinese and (g) black ethnic groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154617","154617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4272","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative assessment he has made of differences between gender in the appearance of self-reported wellbeing.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154618","154618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4273","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 25 April 2013, Official Report, column 1097W, on senior civil servants: pensions, when he plans to disclose the details of the remuneration rates for all persons in receipt of Civil Service pensions who are senior civil servants and those paid by non-departmental public bodies at rates in excess of the minimum applicable to the senior Civil Service.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154619","154619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4274","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects that the hon. Member for Warley will receive a reply to his letter of 8 February 2013 to the UK Border Agency regarding the case of Baljinder Singh Bhatia.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154634","154634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4275","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects that the hon. Member for Warley will receive a reply to his letter of 19 March 2013 to the UK Border Agency regarding the case of Mr Anthony Anderson.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154635","154635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4276","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects that the hon. Member for Warley will receive a reply to his letter of 14 February 2013 to the UK Border Agency regarding the case of Mr Hardip Singh.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154636","154636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4277","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals killed in the UK were repatriated in each of the last five years; and at what cost to the public purse in each such year.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154621","154621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4278","2013-05-10","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how she influences how funds are spent and projects scrutinised by (a) Europeaid and (b) the European Development Fund.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154622","154622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4279","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the road infrastructure costs involved in raising the motorway speed limit to 80 miles per hour.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154625","154625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4280","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has considered the possibility of widening and deepening rivers to help alleviate flooding in regularly affected areas.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154626","154626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4281","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how much was spent by the Crown Prosecution Service on external advocacy in (a) 2012-13 and (b) each of the preceding 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154667","154667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4282","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Serious Fraud Office's evidence storage systems.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154668","154668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4283","2013-05-10","Women and Equalities","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent assessment she has made of the effects on (a) all women and (b) women bringing pregnancy-related cases of the introduction of fees for employment tribunals.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154669","154669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4284","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the User Requirements Document being written by the current Falkland Islands support helicopter supplier service users and service personnel to inform the role of Defence in search and rescue has been completed.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154670","154670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4285","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Ministers attended meetings of the Interdepartmental Ministerial Group on Human Trafficking between January 2011 and April 2013.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154671","154671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4286","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to publish the progress report on the first round of Portas pilot projects.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154191","154191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4287","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to publish the findings of the Building Standards Review.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154192","154192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4288","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of affordable homes built in 2012.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154193","154193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4289","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the implementation of the National Planning Policy Framework and its effects on the average number of weeks local planning authorities take to decide (a) major and (b) minor planning applications.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154194","154194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4290","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the success of the first round of Portas pilots.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154195","154195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4291","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to monitor effects of the abolition of the Agricultural Wages Board on wages in the agricultural sector.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154196","154196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4292","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses there were at University Hospital Durham in (a) May 2010 and (b) the latest month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154197","154197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4293","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions there have been for corporate manslaughter since 2007.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154198","154198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4294","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses there were in the NHS in (a) May 2010 and (b) the latest month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154199","154199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4295","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of new and enhanced contracts awarded to agricultural workers in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154200","154200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4296","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154521","154521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4297","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many elderly people were hospitalised as the result of an unprovoked attack or mugging in the last year.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154185","154185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4298","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the letter sent to hon. Members of 19 April 2013, on making it easier for families to improve their home, what plans he has to monitor the effects of the new rules on extensions.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154187","154187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4299","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential cost to local authorities of providing planning services to homeowners wishing to extend their property by up to eight metres.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154188","154188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4300","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the letter sent to hon. Members of 19 April 2013, on making it easier for families to improve their home, what guidance his Department plans to publish to support the implementation of the new rules on extensions.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154189","154189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4301","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the letter sent to hon. Members of 19 April 2013, on making it easier for families to improve their home, what discussions he had with external organisations about the new rules on extensions prior to their introduction to the Growth and Infrastructure Bill.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154190","154190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4302","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of hospital trusts that receive donated organs which allocate donor organs to other trusts.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154212","154212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4303","2013-05-10","Prime Minister","2013-05-08","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will establish a single honours list each year rewarding the giving of money to charitable works and foundations and to honour equally those who similarly generously give their time to charitable activity.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154213","154213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4304","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish a series of graphs showing percentage capacity usage for the West Coast Mainline on working days on the vertical axis and time of day on the horizontal axis for the (a) London to Milton Keynes, (b) London to Birmingham, (c) London to Manchester and (d) London to Lichfield Trent Valley stretches of the line in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154216","154216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4305","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward plans to restrict the marketing, sales and promotion of electronic cigarettes so that they (a) are only sold to adults at licensed outlets, (b) are only targeted at smokers as a way of reducing smoking or quitting and (c) do not appeal to non-smokers, particularly children.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154217","154217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4306","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward proposals to extend existing smoking legislation in the UK to include vapour from electronic cigarettes.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154218","154218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4307","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154522","154522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4308","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether, within the consultation on reform of criminal legal aid, any consideration has been given to how a service based on geographical areas might impact on specialist firms who may have to act outside their area.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154286","154286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4309","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the potential for harm to those animals exported live.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154287","154287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4310","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many sexual assaults occur, where the perpetrator is (a) unknown and (b) known to the victim in each year; and what estimate she has made of the number of unreported sexual offences in cases where the perpetrator is known to the victim.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154180","154180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4311","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has taken steps under section 56 of the Marine and Coastal Access Act 2009 to publish the Direction issued under section 55 of that Act, and to draw this to the attention of those persons likely to be interested or affected by it.","Biography information for Mr Tom Harris","Mr Tom Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154221","154221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4312","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he issued a Direction to the Marine Management Organisation (MMO) under section 55 of the Marine and Coastal Access Act 2009, empowering the MMO to carry out marine planning functions; and when the MMO consented to that under section 55.","Biography information for Mr Tom Harris","Mr Tom Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154222","154222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4313","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many shops received empty property rate relief in each (a) local authority area and (b) parliamentary constituency in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154224","154224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4314","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will give consideration to reforming the system of compulsory purchase orders to allow local authorities and business improvement districts to buy a medium-term lease on empty shops.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154225","154225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4315","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received from (a) trade organisations and (b) individuals on local authority car parking strategies.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154226","154226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4316","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will introduce measures to require landlords receiving empty property rate relief to make public details of that relief and the properties affected.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154227","154227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4317","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the next adult psychiatric morbidity survey will be completed.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154228","154228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4318","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, what the current level of expenditure by the Law Officers' Departments is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154546","154546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4319","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps he has taken in respect of flood insurance.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154201","154201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4320","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department issues guidance to local authorities on engaging with food bank providers and donors to ensure adequate and balanced coverage in their area.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154206","154206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4321","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of supply of (a) loperamade and (b) trazodone; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154207","154207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4322","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on organ allocation.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154208","154208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4323","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effects on measured child poverty rates of the additional childcare support announced in the 2013 Budget.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154209","154209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4324","2013-05-10","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department gave to (a) EuropeAid and (b) the European Development Fund; how such spending is scrutinised and relates to each other; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154210","154210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4325","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the current level of expenditure by his Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154547","154547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4326","2013-05-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the current level of expenditure by her Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by her Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154548","154548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4327","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current level of expenditure by his Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154549","154549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4328","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the current level of expenditure by his Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154550","154550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4329","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the current level of expenditure by his Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154551","154551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4330","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the current level of expenditure by his Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154552","154552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4331","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the current level of expenditure by his Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154553","154553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4332","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the current level of expenditure by his Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154554","154554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4333","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the current level of expenditure by her Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by her Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154555","154555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4334","2013-05-10","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the current level of expenditure by her Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by her Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154556","154556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4335","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the current level of expenditure by his Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154557","154557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4336","2013-05-10","Northern Ireland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the current level of expenditure by her Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by her Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154558","154558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4337","2013-05-10","Scotland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the current level of expenditure by his Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154559","154559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4338","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the current level of expenditure by his Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154560","154560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4339","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the current level of expenditure by his Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154561","154561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4340","2013-05-10","Wales Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the current level of expenditure by his Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154562","154562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4341","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the current level of expenditure by his Department is on contracts with G4S; and how much was spent by his Department on contracts with G4S in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154563","154563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4342","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, what steps the Law Officers' Departments are taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance he has given to the Law Officers' Departments' executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154524","154524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4343","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance he has given to his Department's executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154525","154525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4344","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance he has given to his Department's executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154526","154526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4345","2013-05-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance she has given to her Department's executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154527","154527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4346","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how much funding (a) the Law Officers' Departments and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154507","154507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4347","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154508","154508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4348","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154509","154509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4349","2013-05-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding (a) her Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which she is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154510","154510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4350","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154511","154511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4351","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154512","154512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4352","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154513","154513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4353","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154514","154514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4354","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154515","154515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4355","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154516","154516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4356","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding (a) her Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which she is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154517","154517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4357","2013-05-10","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding (a) her Department and (b) each non-departmental public body for which she is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154518","154518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4358","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154519","154519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4359","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154520","154520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4360","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints there have been to her Department that passports and official documents have been lost while in the care of a Government department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154261","154261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4361","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what (a) organisations and (b) public authorities have provided information in response to her Department's request for business cases for access to communications data; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154262","154262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4362","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what local authorities have provided information about their ongoing requirement for communications data in response to her Department's request for business cases for access to communications data; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154263","154263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4363","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library copies of the information received from all local authorities in response to her Department's request for business cases for access to communications data; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154264","154264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4364","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library copies of the information received from the (a) Charity Commission, (b) Environment Agency, (c) Food Standards Agency, (d) Gambling Commission, (e) Health and Safety Executive, (f) Office for Communications, (g) Pensions Regulator and (h) Royal Mail in response to her Department's request for business cases for access to communications data; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154265","154265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4365","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate HM Revenue and Customs has made of the number of requests for access to communications data it would make under the Communications Data Bill if that bill received Royal Assent; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154266","154266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4366","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many requests were made by HM Revenue and Customs for access to communications data in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154267","154267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4367","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost was to the public purse of all requests for access to communications data made by HM Revenue and Customs in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154268","154268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4368","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the distribution by income decile of additional gains to families arising from the additional childcare support announced as part of Budget 2013.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154279","154279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4369","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether local police authorities are required to collect data for the user satisfaction survey.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154291","154291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4370","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many procurement contracts issued in relation to the running of the NHS have used the social value clauses within the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 to date; and what the estimated value of these contracts has been.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154115","154115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4371","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many contracts awarded to build schools through the Priority School Building Programme have used clauses in the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 to date; and what the estimated value of these contracts has been.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154116","154116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4372","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many procurement contracts have been issued by local authorities using clauses within the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 to date; and what the estimated total value of such contracts has been.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154117","154117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4373","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of recent trends in female employment in (a) Clwyd South constituency, (b) Wales and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154118","154118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4374","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) women and (b) men in Clwyd South constituency were unemployed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154119","154119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4375","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average salary in Clwyd South constituency was for (a) women and (b) men in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154120","154120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4376","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential increase in the cost of car insurance if the motorway speed limit were raised to eighty miles-per-hour.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154121","154121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4377","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential increase in damage to road surfaces and fixtures if the motorway speed limit were raised to eighty miles-per-hour.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154122","154122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4378","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential increase in the number of people killed or seriously injured in road traffic accidents if the motorway speed limit were raised to eighty miles-per-hour.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154124","154124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4379","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 23 April 2013, Official Report, column 733W, on Ashleigh Ewing, for what reasons the investigation by NHS England into the death of Ashleigh Ewing is taking longer than was originally expected; and when he expects the report to be published.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154142","154142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4380","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will amend the Surveying Prisoner Crime Reduction report to include a section on the needs of victims and the prisoners' attitudes towards their victims.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154181","154181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4381","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure coordination between police and crime commissioners and prisons for work with victims of crime.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154182","154182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4382","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisoners serve the full length of their original sentence.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154183","154183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4383","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the role of police and crime commissioners is with regards to public complaints about police handling of their cases.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154184","154184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4384","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance he has given to his Department's executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154528","154528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4385","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding his Department obtains from (a) the private sector and (b) other sectors for the purposes of flood defence.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154271","154271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4386","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what procedures are in place to enable foundation trusts to (a) offer and (b) access donated organs from other foundation trusts.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154274","154274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4387","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of variations in organ allocation policies across NHS trusts in England and Wales.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154275","154275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4388","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of people on waiting lists who receive organ transplants in (i) North West England, (ii) Stretford and Urmston constituency and (iii) England.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154276","154276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4389","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients on an organ transplant waiting list in each region of England waited more than (a) six months, (b) 12 months and (c) 18 months for each type of organ transplanted in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154277","154277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4390","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of households eligible for the higher rate of childcare support under universal credit as announced in Budget 2013.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154278","154278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4391","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an estimate of the potential increase in costs to drivers of increased fuel usage arising from an increase in the motorway speed limit to 80 miles per hour.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154364","154364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4392","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, for which offences the Serious Fraud Office is named in legislation as the lead prosecutor; and how many (a) investigations and (b) prosecutions it has undertaken for each of these offence categories in the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154365","154365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4393","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions the Serious Fraud Office carried out in 2012-13, by category of offence; and what the conviction rate was in that period.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154366","154366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4394","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what sentences have been imposed on people found guilty of committing an offence of (a) misconduct in public office and (b) conspiracy to commit misconduct in public office since 2005.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154294","154294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4395","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many people have been prosecuted for the offence of conspiracy to commit misconduct in a public office since 2005.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154295","154295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4396","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many residents of each parliamentary constituency in England and Wales were born in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154296","154296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4397","2013-05-10","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on UK funding towards the European Defence and Security Policy which is then marked against the UK's Overseas Development Assistance target; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154297","154297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4398","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reports of assault with intent to rob are recorded daily in each region of the UK.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154290","154290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4399","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average change in benefit will be for residents of Coatbridge, Chryston and Bellshill constituency affected by the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154303","154303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4400","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what methodology was used by his Department to calculate the amount of 155 million allocated to local authorities in Scotland for discretionary housing payments.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154304","154304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4401","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether calculation of the amounts allocated to local authorities for discretionary housing payments took into account the level of smaller accommodation in the housing stock in each area.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154305","154305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4402","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance he has given to his Department's executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154530","154530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4403","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance he has given to his Department's executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154531","154531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4404","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance he has given to his Department's executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154532","154532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4405","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance he has given to his Department's executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154533","154533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4406","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance he has given to his Department's executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154534","154534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4407","2013-05-10","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance she has given to her Department's non-departmental public body on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154535","154535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4408","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance he has given to his Department's executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154536","154536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4409","2013-05-10","Northern Ireland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps her Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance she has given to her Department's non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154537","154537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4410","2013-05-10","Scotland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154539","154539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4411","2013-05-10","Wales Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154542","154542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4412","2013-05-10","Women and Equalities","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps her Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154544","154544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4413","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance he has given to his Department's executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154540","154540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4414","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance he has given to his Department's executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154541","154541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4415","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in its procurement procedures; and what guidance he has given to his Department's executive agencies and non-departmental public bodies on implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154543","154543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4416","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that payments to farmers under the single farm payment scheme are made on time.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154101","154101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4417","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to better regulate public houses and breweries.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154102","154102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4418","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many private sector jobs have been created in Worcestershire since 2010.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154103","154103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4419","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the recent negotiations between Serbia and Kosovo.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154104","154104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4420","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many bids he has received for the Remploy marine textiles division to date.","Biography information for Mr Gordon Brown","Mr Gordon Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154109","154109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4421","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many contracts issued as part of the high-level output specification project, have used clauses contained within the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 to date.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154111","154111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4422","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many defence procurement contracts have used social value clauses from the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 since implementation of that Act; and what the estimated value of these contracts has been.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154112","154112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4423","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many procurement contracts awarded to police forces in England and Wales have incorporated the social value clauses from the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 since implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154113","154113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4424","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many contracts for the running of prisons have used the social value clauses in the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 since that Act came into force.","Biography information for Hazel Blears","Hazel Blears","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154114","154114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4425","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to support the implementation of the forthcoming clinical guideline on acute kidney injury to be published by the National Institute for Health and Clinical Excellence in 2013.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154171","154171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4426","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding for training an apprentice was received in (a) Liverpool, Walton constituency, (b) Liverpool and (c) England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154086","154086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4427","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will issue guidance on the assessment of GCSE practical work and fieldwork in subjects including science and geography; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154088","154088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4428","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the likely effect of employment allowance on (a) businesses and (b) charities in Peterborough constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154089","154089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4429","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of current transport infrastructure in former coalfield villages in Sherwood constituency.","Biography information for Mark  Spencer","Mr Mark Spencer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154092","154092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4430","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the value of conversion of former coal transportation lines to passenger transportation lines.","Biography information for Mark  Spencer","Mr Mark Spencer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154093","154093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4431","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average investment in rail infrastructure has been in each parliamentary constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Mark  Spencer","Mr Mark Spencer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154094","154094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4432","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for the Home Department about extending the provision of independent sexual violence advisers.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154125","154125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4433","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many suspects the Crown Prosecution Service has successfully applied to have returned to the UK under an European Arrest Warrant in each of the last five years; and with what offence each suspect was charged.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154126","154126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4434","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many rape prosecutions have been preceded by a pre-trial interview between the prosecutor and the complainant in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154127","154127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4435","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, when the Crown Prosecution Service decided to procure 4,700 tablet computers from Logica.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154128","154128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4436","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on the granting of political asylum to Afghan political interpreters; and what assessment she has made of differences in this policy and that previously applied to Iraqi interpreters who had worked with UK armed forces.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154136","154136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4437","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what methodology was used by his Department to calculate the figure of 14 per cent reduction in housing benefit for one spare bedroom and the maximum 25 per cent reduction for under-occupancy.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154306","154306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4438","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the potential for evictions was taken into account in the formulation of the housing benefit under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154307","154307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4439","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his  Department has had with other government departments on allocating additional funding for the use of local authorities as a result of the introduction of the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154308","154308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4440","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he or officials of his Department held with groups representing the interests of disabled people when formulating policy on the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154309","154309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4441","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to allocate additional funding if the planned discretionary housing payments funding is insufficient to prevent evictions as a result of the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154310","154310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4442","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effects of eviction on the (a) education and (b) emotional stability of children.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154311","154311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4443","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 25 April 2013, Official Report, column 1049W, on British nationals abroad: death, what statistics his Department holds on the nature or cause of death in the 3,391 known cases; and in what respects this statistic differs from that given in the Answer of 25 April 2013, Official Report, columns 1049-50W, on British nationals abroad: death.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154312","154312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4444","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications of adding agricultural production to the considerations used by the Environment Agency when planning flood protection work.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154373","154373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4445","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will ensure that there is a balance between capital and revenue spend on flood defence measures so that any asset created has maintenance funding to ensure that it remains viable for the lifetime of the asset.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154374","154374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4446","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people subject to human trafficking in (a) Lichfield constituency and (b) the smallest area including Lichfield constituency for which data are available.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154361","154361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4447","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on providing gratis visas to charities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154077","154077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4448","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the expected rate of fugitive methane emissions from the development of UK onshore shale gas resources; and whether he intends to commission additional research on this subject.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154385","154385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4449","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the total UK onshore shale gas resource; and when he plans to publish the recent report on shale gas resources produced by the British Geological Survey.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154386","154386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4450","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals detained under immigration powers, were detained following closure of their educational establishment as a result of action by her Department, in each quarter since January 2009.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154070","154070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4451","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals detained under immigration powers, in each quarter since January 2009 entered the UK through Tier 4 of the Points Based System.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154071","154071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4452","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the mortality rates in hospital as a result of acute kidney injury were in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154072","154072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4453","2013-05-10","Women and Equalities","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much funding the Government Equalities Office has allocated to the London Borough of Enfield local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154073","154073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4454","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much investment in rail infrastructure there has been in (a) Sherwood constituency and (b) Nottinghamshire since 2000.","Biography information for Mark  Spencer","Mr Mark Spencer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154095","154095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4455","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the status is of those civil nuclear police officers who are unable to carry firearms as a result of illness or injury.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154099","154099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4458","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to receive a reply to her letter to the then Chief Executive, UK Border Agency of 21 March 2013 on behalf of a constituent, CTS ref B8512/13.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154057","154057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4459","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of prisoners are (a) invited to participate in and (b) participate in restorative justice.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153958","153958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4679","2013-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 15 April 2013, Official Report, column 73W, on floods: insurance, if he will make it his policy to require providers of flood insurance to take account of flood prevention measures put in place by local authorities when calculating premiums and the terms on which continuing cover will be offered.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154719","154719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4680","2013-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 15 April 2013, Official Report, column 73W, on floods: insurance, what steps he is taking to ensure that insurance premiums and terms of cover take account of all relevant flood mitigation measures not just recently-installed, property-level measures.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154720","154720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4681","2013-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will undertake (a) an audit of the flood prevention measures implemented by local authorities in each of the last five years and (b) an analysis of the relationship between such expenditure and the cover offered and premiums charged to householders occupying premises at historic risk of flooding.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154721","154721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4682","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to announce arrangements for the treatment of passported benefits under universal credit.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154707","154707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4683","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what amount has been paid to service providers involved in the delivery of IT for universal credit since 2011; and what amount he expects to be paid to such providers over the duration of their contracts.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154708","154708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4684","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have claimed universal credit in the pathfinder to date; and what estimate he has made of the total number of new claims for universal credit that will be processed by all the pathfinders.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154709","154709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4685","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 26 November 2012, Official Report, column 121W, on cancer, how many strategic clinical networks for cancer have been established to date; and which areas are covered by these networks.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154710","154710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4686","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2013, Official Report, column 354W, on cancer: surveys, what deicsion has been reached by the NHS Commissioning Board on whether to conduct the National Cancer Patient Experience Survey in 2013-14.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154711","154711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4687","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which private finance initiative projects under his Department have been refinanced in each year since May 2010; what the value is of each such project; what the refinancing gain has been in each such case; and how much of any such gain the relevant Government body received through a (a) lump sum and (b) reduction in the unitary charge.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154714","154714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4688","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which private finance initiative projects under his Department have been refinanced in each year since May 2010; what the value is of each such project; what the refinancing gain has been in each such case; and how much of any such gain the relevant Government body received through a (a) lump sum and (b) reduction in the unitary charge.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154715","154715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4689","2013-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which private finance initiative projects under his Department have been refinanced in each year since May 2010; what the value is of each such project; what the refinancing gain has been in each such case; and how much of any such gain the relevant Government body received through a (a) lump sum and (b) reduction in the unitary charge.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154716","154716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4690","2013-05-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which private finance initiative projects under her Department have been refinanced in each year since May 2010; what the value is of each such project; what the refinancing gain has been in each such case; and how much of any such gain the relevant Government body received through a (a) lump sum and (b) reduction in the unitary charge.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154717","154717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4822","2013-05-13","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take to address the concerns raised by the National Audit Office about the Equitable Life payment scheme.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154741","154741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4885","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish details of the remuneration rates for all those in receipt of Civil Service pensions who are (a) senior civil servants and (b) paid by non-departmental public bodies at rates in excess of the minimum applicable to the Senior Civil Service.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154828","154828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4886","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether a meeting was held between Ministers of her Department and police and crime commissioners in the week commencing 22 April 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154829","154829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4887","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asset confiscation orders have been made under the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002 in each year since 2008; what the value was of assets subject to such orders; and what amount of assets were confiscated in each such year.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154830","154830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4888","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training (a) judges, (b) magistrates and (c) prosecutors have to undergo in order to preside over or prosecute a case involving child sexual exploitation; and at what intervals such training requires re-accreditation.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154833","154833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4889","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of refugees who have left Burma as a result of the recent violence against the Muslim community in that country.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154837","154837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4890","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she last spoke to the US Secretary of Homeland Security.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154839","154839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4891","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of Iraqis killed as a result of terrorism and war-related violence since the invasion of that country in 2003.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154840","154840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4898","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to receive a reply to his letter to the Chief Executive of the UK Border Agency of 28 March 2013 on behalf of a constituent, ref H1162268.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154820","154820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4899","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much as a proportion of GDP was spent on the armed forces in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154825","154825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4900","2013-05-13","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff have been made redundant by HM Revenue and Customs in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154826","154826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4901","2013-05-14","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has any plans to bring forward legislative proposals to enable temporary Blue Badges.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154847","154847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4902","2013-05-14","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the number of people who have been wrongly advised by a financial adviser and have subsequently gone out of business in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154848","154848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4903","2013-05-14","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what (a) recourse and (b) compensation is available to people who have gone out of business as a result of being wrongly advised by a financial adviser.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154849","154849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4904","2013-05-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how he proposes to comply with the standstill obligation in EU state aid law if he enters into an investment contract or sets a strike price before the European Commission has decided whether to approve such measures.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154850","154850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4908","2013-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much has been spent by energy companies on the rural safeguard sub-obligation delivering their carbon saving communities obligation to rural low income houses to date; and how many (a) oil-fired and (b) LPG-fired boilers have been replaced under the Affordable Warmth Scheme of the Energy Companies Obligation to date.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153907","153907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4909","2013-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) assessments have been undertaken, (b) households have signed up to an installation and (c) households have received an installation under the Green Deal to date.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153908","153908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4910","2013-05-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answer of 15 April 2013, Official Report, column 261W, on climate change, what statistical models were used in any analyses done to calculate significances.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153909","153909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4911","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total cost to his Department has been of legal proceedings in respect of Sergeant Danny Nightingale up to the end of March 2013; what the estimated costs are of the current proceedings against Sergeant Nightingale; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154567","154567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4912","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what scientific evidence his Department relies in prescribing mefloquine hydrochloride as first-line malaria chemoprophylaxis for troops deploying to or exercising in sub-Saharan Africa.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154568","154568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4913","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the United States reserving mefloquine for third or fourth-line chemoprophylaxis only; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154569","154569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4914","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Cancer Drugs Fund in ensuring that decisions to approve quickly urgent access to anti-cancer drugs; what plans he has for the (a) continuation, (b) development and (c) funding level of the Cancer Drugs Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154570","154570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4915","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he will take to hold clinical commissioning groups to account for improving on one and five year survival rates from all cancers.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154637","154637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4916","2013-05-13","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, under which Vote costs and damages ordered by the European Court of Human Rights are paid.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154641","154641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4917","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to require airlines to provide onboard oxygen for patients reliant upon NHS-provided home oxygen equipment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154011","154011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4918","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received on the use of home oxygen equipment on (a) domestic and (b) international airlines; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154012","154012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4919","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to increase the number of countries offering reciprocal agreements for the provision of home oxygen equipment for UK citizens travelling abroad; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154013","154013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4920","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to enable individuals using an NHS-provided portable oxygen machine to use their machine (a) outside of the UK for short periods of time and (b) while they are in transit to and from the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154014","154014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4921","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to enable people reliant upon NHS-supplied home oxygen equipment to travel abroad; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154015","154015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/4922","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people of each age group were (a) arrested and (b) given anti-social behaviour orders on charges of vandalism and damage to property in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154016","154016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5016","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, if he will place in the Library copies of the contracts with Work Programme providers in Perth and North Perthshire constituency.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153985","153985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5017","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, if he will place in the Library copies of the contracts with Work Programme providers in Angus constituency.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153991","153991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5018","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, if he will publish full costings in respect of the operation of the Work Programme in Perth and North Perthshire constituency.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153986","153986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5019","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, if he will publish full costings in respect of the operation of the Work Programme in Angus constituency.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153992","153992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5020","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, on what date he intends to release financial data below the national level; what considerations will determine the timing of that release; and whether the data will be published by (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) local authority area.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153987","153987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5021","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, on what date he intends to release financial data below the national level; what considerations will determine the timing of that release; and whether the data will be published by (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) local authority area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153993","153993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5022","2013-05-13","Wales Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had regarding research and development funding for universities in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153994","153994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5023","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of Medical Research Council funding is donated to research in Welsh universities.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153995","153995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5024","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of research funding from research councils went to Welsh universities in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153996","153996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5025","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which organisations and individuals are part of the Task and Finish Group for developing a childminder agency framework; how those organisations and individuals were chosen; and whether any organisations and individuals were invited to join that group but declined.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154002","154002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5026","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of his More Great Childcare proposals on (a) childcare cost, (b) childcare quality, (c) the number of childcare places and (d) childcare providers.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154003","154003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5027","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he intends to publish the analysis of comparative costs and ratios of childcare in industrialised countries supplied to his Department by Professor Helen Penn and Professor Eva Lloyd.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154004","154004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5028","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on female employment of his plans for childcare reforms in More Great Childcare.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154005","154005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5029","2013-05-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 17 April 2013, Official Report, columns 416-7W, on non-domestic rates: wi-fi, what outcomes there were from the meeting hosted by the Broadband Stakeholder Group between the Valuation Office Agency and industry.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154006","154006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5045","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 11 May 2011 to the right hon. Member for East Ham, Official Report, column 1246W, on universal credit, whether his expected timescale for the completion of the IT development for universal credit of spring 2013 for live pathfinders and authmn 2013 is on track; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154827","154827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5051","2013-05-13","Scotland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, when the Scottish Business Board last met; and if he will place the papers from the meeting in the Library.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154049","154049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5052","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 15 April 2013, Official Report, column 59, on HMS Tireless, what the duration of the leak was in hours and minutes; what the volume of the lost coolant was; whether the reactor closed down or tripped as soon as the leak occurred; whether such a leak automatically closes down or trips the reactor in this class of submarine; whether the leak has been investigated to ascertain if the reactor was in operation for any length of time before the leak was discovered; when a radiological analysis of the leaked coolant was carried out or estimated; what the radiological inventory of the leaked coolant was; what clean-up action was required inside the submarine as a result of the leak; whether any radioactively contaminated solids or liquids were off-loaded at Devonport; and whether any of the leaked radioactively contaminated coolant was discharged to sea.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154050","154050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5053","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the hon. Member for Walsall North will receive a reply to his letter of 26 March 2013 concerning a constituent, ref: POS(5)10644/0143.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154056","154056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5054","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which areas have (a) complete coverage of the NHS 111 service, (b) coverage of the NHS 111 service on evenings and weekends only and (c) no coverage of the NHS 111 service.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154030","154030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5055","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to uprate income threshold for carer's allowance in light of the forthcoming increase in the minimum wage.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154043","154043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5056","2013-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will introduce an income or capital limit for eligibility for council tax exemption for full-time students.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154062","154062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5057","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answers of 5 March 2013, Official Report, columns 973-4W, on written questions: Government responses, and 10 September 2012, Official Report, column 120W, on public sector: civil proceedings, when he expects to provide a full update.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154064","154064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5058","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, on what date he intends to release financial data below the national level; what consideration will determine the timing of that release; and whether the data will be published by (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) local authority area.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153981","153981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5090","2013-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the risk of contamination of water sources in the vicinity of the Appspond Lane Recycling Centre following a recent fire on that site.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153912","153912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5091","2013-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of air quality near the Appspond Lane Recycling Centre after the recent fire on that site.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153913","153913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5092","2013-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the market for recycled wood.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153914","153914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5093","2013-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what procedures are in place to allow the Environment Agency to inspect sites with recycling permits.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153915","153915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5094","2013-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that individuals with prior convictions for environmental offences are not granted recycling permits.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153916","153916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5095","2013-05-13","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of extending the use of the HM Forces Railcard to all veterans of the UK Armed Forces.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153918","153918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5096","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time is for a response to a Freedom of Information request made to (a) South Yorkshire police force and (b) West Yorkshire police force; and what steps she is taking to help these forces improve the efficiency of their replies to Freedom of Information requests.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153919","153919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5097","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he had had with the Director of Public Prosecutions about the possible effect his resignation will have on the pending inquiries into individuals and organisations involved in the investigations into the Hillsborough disaster.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153920","153920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5098","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many employers in (a) Liverpool, Walton constituency, (b) Liverpool and (c) England have received funding for training an apprentice in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153921","153921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5099","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 23 April 2013, Official Report, columns 889-90W, on diseases, if his Department will (a) commission and (b) evaluate research on the number of people with (i) multiple sclerosis, (ii) Huntingdon's disease and (iii) 22q deletion syndrome.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153922","153922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5100","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many individuals are in receipt of payments from the Armed Forces Compensation Scheme.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153923","153923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5101","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many individuals are in receipt of payments from the War Pensions Scheme.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153925","153925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5103","2013-05-13","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress he has made on the upgrade of the Caledonian Sleeper Service.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153929","153929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5104","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what criteria his Department used to identify appropriate participants in training the Syrian opposition.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153930","153930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5105","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the training which his Department is providing to the Syrian opposition forces includes the use of equipment which is prohibited for transfer to Syria under current EU sanctions arrangements.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153931","153931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5106","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the training provided by his Department to Syrian opposition forces includes appropriate military conduct during armed conflict.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153932","153932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5107","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the rate of underemployment in each UK parliamentary constituency in Scotland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153939","153939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5108","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the total loss to the economy as a result of underemployment in Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153940","153940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5109","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to receive a reply to his letter to the Chief Executive, UK Border Agency of 21 March 2013 on behalf of a constituent, CTS ref B8512/13.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153948","153948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5110","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 23 April 2013, Official Report, columns 889-90W, on diseases, what consideration his Department gives to the number of people with (a) multiple sclerosis, (b) Huntingdon's disease and (c) 22q deletion syndrome when allocating research funding for these conditions.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153955","153955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5111","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he plans to take against any individual serving in the armed forces found to have been engaged in internet trolling.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153956","153956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5112","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of jobs advertised on the Universal Jobmatch website were for self-employment in each constituency in the UK since that website was introduced.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153957","153957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5113","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of people who accept victims' services are (a) offered and (b) participate in restorative justice programmes.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153959","153959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5114","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of violent misconduct occur in prisons on average on each day.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153960","153960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5115","2013-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what types of rewards are afforded to prisoners; and whether prisons have a minimum criterion for the requisite level of prisoner behaviour before distribution of such rewards.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153962","153962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5116","2013-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on enabling fire authorities to contract out their full range of services to a private provider.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153963","153963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5117","2013-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on giving external bodies those emergency powers currently held by firefighters employed by fire authorities.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153964","153964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5118","2013-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on enabling fire authorities to contract out firefighting duties to a private provider.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153965","153965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5119","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the representations made about pension entitlements for transpeople in paragraphs 9 to 13 of the paper submitted by Helen Belcher to the Marriage (Same Sex Couples) Bill Public Bill Committee; whether the Government plans to bring forward amendments to the Bill on pension entitlements at report stage; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153966","153966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5120","2013-05-13","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the likely timescale for the re-tendering of the Thameslink Rolling Stock Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153969","153969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5121","2013-05-13","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the reasons are for the time taken to agree the signing of the Thameslink contract; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153970","153970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5122","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 16 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, if he will place in the Library copies of the contracts with Work Programme providers in Dundee East constituency.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153979","153979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5123","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 16 April 2013, Official Report, column 713W, on Work Programme, if he will publish full costings in respect of the operation of the Work Programme in Dundee East constituency.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153980","153980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5385","2013-05-20","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which people and organisations the (a) Chairman and (b) Secretary of the Commission on a Bill of Rights have met to discuss the Commissions work since the Commission was established excluding (i) seminars, (ii) meetings with parliamentary committees and (iii) meetings during visits to Strasbourg, Belfast, Cardiff and Edinburgh.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153903","153903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5406","2013-05-20","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of whether the UK National Reform Programme is a submission the basis of which falls within the scope of section 5 of the European Communities (Amendment) Act 1993.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154851","154851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5407","2013-05-20","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in hearing the UK's case regarding Regulation (EU) No 236/2012; when he expects judgement on that case to be given by the CJEU; and if he will place in the Library the written legal submissions made by the Government to the CJEU in that case.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154852","154852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5408","2013-05-20","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in hearing the UK's case regarding the European Central Bank's proposed location policy for central counterparties dealing in euro-denominated financial products; when he expects judgement on that case to be given by the CJEU; and if he will place in the Library the written legal submissions made by the Government to the CJEU in that case.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154853","154853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5416","2013-05-20","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the damages ordered by the European Court of Human Rights to be paid to Mr Ilyas Elmi Hode and Ms Hawa Aden Adbi in its judgement of 6 November 2012 were paid.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153899","153899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5417","2013-05-20","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the costs and damages ordered by the European Court of Human Rights to be paid to Mr Brett James, Mr Nicholas Wells and Mr Jeffrey Lee in its judgement of 18 September 2012 were paid.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153900","153900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5418","2013-05-20","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the costs and damages ordered by the European Court of Human Rights to be paid to Mr William Beggs in its judgement of 6 November 2012 were paid.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153901","153901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5475","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the principal access numbers are for those calling the benefits helpline number; which such lines (a) are free to the caller and (b) may incur a charge to the caller; and if he will take steps to ensure that all calls made to these helplines are recorded.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154298","154298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5543","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the government of Fiji about that country's human rights record.","Biography information for Patrick Mercer","Patrick Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154106","154106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5544","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the government of Fiji about the status of Fiji within the Commonwealth.","Biography information for Patrick Mercer","Patrick Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154107","154107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5741","2013-05-20","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how his Department scrutinises the Fundraising Standards Board; when a review was last conducted; and what the outcome was of this review.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153902","153902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5768","2013-05-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the BDUK rural broadband framework contract covers marketing and communications for broadband services; and whether local authorities will have any future role in delivering marketing and communication services.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154686","154686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5769","2013-05-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the independent assurance review of BDUK rural broadband contracts conducted by Grant Thorton identified differences in (a) charges, (b) subsidy and (c) other matters in the offers made by BT to the local authorities concerned.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154687","154687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5770","2013-05-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to achieve EU broadband targets.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154688","154688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5771","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the costs of retrofitting cyber security to existing government systems.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154689","154689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5772","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with interested parties on IP address transparency.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154690","154690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5870","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many fire stations there were in (a) Birmingham and (b) the West Midlands in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154600","154600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5871","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have received the maximum custody sentence for possession of a knife in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154601","154601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5872","2013-05-10","Women and Equalities","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much funding was provided to rape crisis centres in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154602","154602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5873","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the reoffending rate was for (a) male and (b) female inmates in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154603","154603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5970","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of trades unions regarding aircraft cabin air contamination.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154423","154423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5971","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Cabinet Secretary for Health in Scotland regarding the incidence of aplastic anaemia with idiopathic causes.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154424","154424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5972","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he will next meet representatives of the PCS Union to discuss pay and conditions for civil servants.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154425","154425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5973","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Cabinet Secretary for Health in the Scottish Government regarding cross-border organ allocation.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154426","154426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5974","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent representations he has received regarding incentives for the purchase of renewable energy from independent generators after the Renewables Obligation ends.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154427","154427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5975","2013-05-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to support the arts sector to make an increased contribution to the economy.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154428","154428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5976","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Cabinet Secretary for Infrastructure, Investment and Cities in the Scottish Government regarding public procurement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154429","154429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5977","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 15 April 2013, Official Report, column 228W, on children: maintenance, how many of the 510,500 Child Support Agency cases in March 2012 where liabilities were being met in full remained fully compliant over the following (a) six months and (b) 12 months.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154818","154818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5978","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance has been provided to local authorities regarding the safe disposal of compact fluorescent lightbulbs.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154281","154281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5979","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many new recruits to the infantry were aged (a) 16, (b) 17 and (c) 18 or above at enlistment in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154051","154051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5980","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of (a) infantry soldiers and (b) non-infantry soldiers were aged 21 years or below in each year since 2001-02.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154052","154052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5981","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average length of service is for a soldier who enlists in the Army (a) aged 18 years or above and (b) below the age of 18 years.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154053","154053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5982","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that armed forces' recruitment activities are in accordance with Article 38 of the Convention on the Rights of the Child and give priority to potential adult recruits over those who are not yet 18 years of age.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154054","154054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5983","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many soldiers who enlisted (a) aged under 18 years and (b) aged 18 years or above left the Army before completion of their Phase Two training in each financial year since 1999-2000.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154055","154055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5984","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of public awareness of appropriate disposal of compact fluorescent lightbulbs.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154280","154280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6046","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for emergency service personnel waiting to receive trauma counselling.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154288","154288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6047","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has commissioned into the rate of suicide amongst emergency services personnel.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154289","154289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6077","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households containing a child and one adult earning (a) more and (b) less than the threshold for income tax in (i) the UK, (ii) each nation and each region of the UK and (iii) each parliamentary constituency in the UK will receive tax credits in each of the next four financial years.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154174","154174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6105","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 April 2013, Official Report, column 1015W, on income tax, what assessment he has made of the number of households containing children and with two adults each earning above the threshold for income tax who (a) will be in receipt of tax credits and (b) will not be in receipt of tax credits in (i) this and (ii) the next financial year.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154108","154108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6106","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households containing at least one child and only one adult earning (a) more and (b) less than the threshold for income there will be in (i) the UK, (ii) each nation and each region of the UK and (iii) each parliamentary constituency in the UK in each of the next four financial years.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154172","154172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6107","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on children born before 1 July 2006 being permitted to acquire UK citizenship on the basis of their father's UK nationality, where the father is not married to the child's mother, and the mother is not a UK national, but residing in the UK.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154173","154173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6108","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many households with children in (a) the United Kingdom, (b) England, (c) Wales, (d) Northern Ireland and (e) Scotland contain (i) two adults, who are both the parents of the children, (ii) three or more adults, two of whom are the parents of the children and (iii) only one adult, who is the parent of the children.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154065","154065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6168","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many agency workers are employed at each Defence Support Group site; what the security vetting level is of each such worker; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154564","154564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6169","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost has been of the recall and changes made to equipment sent to Afghanistan under the auspices of Purple Gate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154565","154565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6170","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Defence Support Group sites have the capacity to service and maintain nuclear biological chemical clean air supply in military vehicles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154566","154566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6272","2013-05-13","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 18 (b) of Appendix FM-SE (Family members - specified evidence to the UK Border Agency's Immigration Rules) whether the on-target earnings an applicant's spouse is expected to earn by way of commission in a job that will start within three months of arrival will be taken into account to meet the financial requirement.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154042","154042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6293","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been asked by his officials to complete the online signature strengths questionnaire; and what the range of results has been.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154821","154821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6294","2013-05-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many cross-departmental ministerial meetings have been held to discuss cultural education since February 2012; on what dates such meetings were held; and who attended each such meeting.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154061","154061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6337","2013-05-15","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on implementing a statutory register of herbal medicine practitioners; and when he expects such a register to be in place.","Biography information for Michael Ellis","Michael Ellis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154728","154728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6544","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with representatives of the zoo industry on the investment of that industry's profits into high-profile capital projects.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154068","154068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6545","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps he is taking to support (a) the tourism sector and (b) zoos and aquariums.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154069","154069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6554","2013-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have had with the US Administration on the proposal to establish a government-owned, contractor-operated (GOCO) organisation to replace Defence Equipment and Support.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154646","154646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6931","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much was paid in (a) travel, (b) accommodation and (c) other expenses to each local authority chief executive in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154129","154129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6932","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what (a) salary, (b) pension contribution and (c) expenses were paid to each local authority chief executive in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154130","154130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6933","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people will be affected by the planned increase in the number of qualifying years needed to gain a full state pension due to take place in April 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154131","154131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6934","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much each local authority spent on newspapers delivered to households in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154132","154132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6935","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) total and (b) each parliamentary constituency are not claiming pension credit.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154133","154133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6981","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on links between opposition politicians in Colombia, the FARC and activists being targeted by paramilitaries.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154007","154007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6993","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make a record of the main disabling condition for claimants of the personal independence payment; and if he will include cystic fibrosis as a category of main disabling condition in any such record.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154414","154414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6994","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people aged between 16 and 64 years old whose main disabling condition is cystic fibrosis have been in receipt of the (a) mobility and (b) care component for disability living allowance at the (i) lower, (ii) standard and (iii) higher rate in each year since 1992.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154415","154415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6995","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the comments by the Colombian Defence Minister that the demonstration in Colombia which took place on 12 April 2013 was financed by the FARC; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153951","153951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7171","2013-05-10","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many contracts awarded to private contractors in the last three years required her Department to release funding beyond the original tender.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154430","154430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7178","2013-05-13","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the cultural barriers indigenous peoples and other minority groups face in accessing health services; and what steps her Department is taking to address such barriers.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154643","154643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7181","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of produce and refreshments served at the upcoming G8 Summit in Northern Ireland will be FairTrade certified.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153935","153935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7182","2013-05-13","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she intends to attend the Third Global Forum on Human Resources for Health.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153953","153953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7183","2013-05-13","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, for what reason her Department committed additional resources to the CHARS Livelihood programme in Bangladesh prior to completion and publication of the evaluation of that project.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153974","153974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7184","2013-05-13","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's spending on private contractors was paid in bonuses to (a) the company concerned and (b) individual consultants.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153975","153975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7226","2013-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answer of 25 April 2013, Official Report, columns 1039-40W, on higher education: statistics; how many full-time first degree enrolments for the first year of academic study at university there have been since 2000; and how many of those students went on to (a) qualify and (b) obtain employment within six months of leaving university.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153971","153971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7227","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual cost to the NHS of religious and spiritual care has been over the last 10 years; which religion and spiritual faiths are included in that cost; and how much was spent in respect of each religion and spiritual faith.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153972","153972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7265","2013-05-15","Wales Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent assessment he has made of the potential contribution of Wales to the UK's national energy infrastructure.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153886","153886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7281","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will introduce measures to reduce the UK's dependence on imported gas.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154219","154219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7282","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to increase the proportion of apprenticeship places for those over 24.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154220","154220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7283","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the (a) Arctic Star and (b) Bomber Command clasp will be issued to (i) living veterans, (ii) surviving spouses and (iii) other next of kin.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154090","154090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7284","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure the timely issue of the (a) Arctic Star and (b) Bomber Command clasp to (i) living veterans, (ii) surviving spouses and (iii) other next of kin.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154091","154091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7327","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the progress made by (a) Atos and (b) Capita in relation to the commitment to engage with organisations representing disabled people in developing training materials in relation to the document entitled DWP Response to the Disability Benefits Consortium report on PIP Assessment Providers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154019","154019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7328","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the engagement by Atos with organisations representing disabled people in producing its training materials for the assessment of the personal independence payment.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154020","154020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7329","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria his Department has used in reviewing Atos' training materials for the assessment for the personal independence payment.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154021","154021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7354","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what educational courses are offered to prisoners; and what the running cost is for each such course.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154397","154397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7356","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of any additional amount of benefits to be claimed as a result of any increase in the number of Romanian and Bulgarian nationals expected to migrate to the UK over the next three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154416","154416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7357","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 15 April 2013, Official Report, column 114W, on Prisons: Visits, what the cost to the public purse was of facilitating such visits.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154422","154422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7358","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues to NHS hospitals regarding the amounts charged to patients for using television.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154409","154409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7359","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the additional cost to the NHS as a result of use by Romanian and Bulgarian nationals over the next three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154413","154413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7369","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners are in the same prison as other members of their family.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154395","154395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7370","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much the Homes and Communities Agency has spent on provision of services and facilities for Travellers in each of the last three years; and how much the Homes and Communities Agency intends to spend on such provision in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154396","154396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7478","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult specialist opthalmology services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154352","154352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7480","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult highly specialist rheumatology services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (i) being treated by such services and (ii) expected to be treated by such services in the financial year 2013-14 in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154323","154323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7481","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult specialist vascular services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (i) being treated by such services and (ii) expected to be treated by such services in the financial year 2013-14 in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154324","154324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7482","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish the number of patients who received intra-uterine insemination treatment through (a) North Staffordshire PCT, (b) Stoke-on-Trent PCT and (c) South Staffordshire PCT in the financial year ended 31 March (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154336","154336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7483","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish the number of patients who received intracytoplasmic sperm injection treatment through (a) North Staffordshire PCT, (b) Stoke-on-Trent PCT and (c) South Staffordshire PCT in the financial year ended 31 March (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154337","154337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7484","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish the number of patients who received in vitro fertilisation treatment through (a) North Staffordshire PCT, (b) Stoke-on-Trent PCT and (c) South Staffordshire PCT in the financial year ended 31 March (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154338","154338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7485","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget he plans to set for the commissioning of adult ataxia telangiectasia services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (i) being treated and (ii) expected to be treated by such services in financial year 2013-14 in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154339","154339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7486","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of Barth syndrome services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ended 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (i) receiving treatment and (ii) for which treatment has been budgeted  in that year for each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154340","154340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7487","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of Behcet's syndrome services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ended 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted  in that year for each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154341","154341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7488","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of Bardet-Biedl syndrome services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (i) receiving treatment and (ii) for which treatment has been budgeted  in that year for each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154342","154342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7489","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish the number of patients whose applications for intracytoplasmic sperm injection treatment were refused by (a) North Staffordshire PCT, (b) Stoke-on-Trent PCT and (c) South Staffordshire PCT in the financial year ended 31 March (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154333","154333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7490","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish the number of patients whose applications for inter uterine insemination treatment were refused by (a) North Staffordshire PCT, (b) Stoke-on-Trent PCT and (c) Staffordshire PCT in the financial year ended 31 March (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154334","154334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7491","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish the number of patients whose applications for in vitro fertilisation treatment were refused by (a) North Staffordshire PCT, (b) Stoke-on-Trent PCT and (c) Staffordshire PCT in the financial year ended 31 March (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154335","154335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7492","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of autologous intestinal reconstruction services for adults in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154343","154343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7493","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of Alstrom syndrome services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154344","154344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7494","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of alkaptonuria services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154345","154345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7495","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult thoracic services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154346","154346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7496","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult specialist services for patients infected with HIV in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154347","154347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7497","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult specialist renal services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154348","154348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7498","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult specialist orthopaedic services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154349","154349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7499","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of Beckwith-Wiedemann syndrome with macroglossia services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154350","154350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7500","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult congenital heart disease services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (i) being treated by such services and (ii) expected to be treated by such services in the financial year 2013-14 in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154320","154320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7501","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult highly specialist respiratory services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (i) being treated by such services and (ii) expected to be treated by such services in the financial year 2013-14 in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154321","154321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7502","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult highly specialist pain management services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (i) being created by such services and (ii) expected to be treated by such services in the financial year 2013-14 in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154322","154322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7503","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult specialist neurosciences services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154353","154353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7504","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult specialist intestinal failure services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154354","154354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7505","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult specialist endocrinology services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154355","154355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7506","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult specialist eating disorder services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154356","154356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7507","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult specialist cardiac services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154357","154357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7508","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of ataxia telengiectasia services for children in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154358","154358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7509","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of autoimmune paediatric gut syndromes services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154359","154359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7510","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) the administration budget for the Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS Area Team for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of staff in that team.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154325","154325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7511","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to (a) publish the current eligibility criteria for bariatric surgery in Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area; and (b) state whether there are any differences in such criteria in any of the sub-areas governed by different clinical commissioning groups in that NHS area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154326","154326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7512","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) the delegated budgets for the clinical commissioning groups in (i) North Staffordshire, (ii) Stoke-on-Trent, (iii) South Staffordshire and (iv) Shropshire in the year ending 31 March (A) 2013 and (B) 2014 and (b) what those budgets are per head of population in each such area in each financial year.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154327","154327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7513","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) what budget he has for the commissioning of specialised services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent, and (vi) South Staffordshire in the year ending 31 March 2014, (b) what the budget was in each such area for the year ending 31 March 2013 and (c) what the budget was per head of population in each such area in each financial year.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154328","154328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7514","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish the number of patients whose applications for treatment by in vitro fertilisation and related fertility services had previously been refused received treatment funded by North Staffordshire PCT in the year ending 31 March 2013.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154329","154329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7515","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish the number of (a) patients and (b) GPs whose applications for in vitro fertilisation treatment had previously been refused were contacted by (i) North Staffordshire PCT or (ii) North Staffordshire Clinical Commissioning Group following the adoption of the new Infertility and Assisted Reproduction Commissioning Policy and Eligibility Criteria.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154330","154330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7516","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish the amount that was (a) budgeted and (b) spent on in vitro fertilisation and associated fertility services by (i) North Staffordshire PCT, (ii) Stoke-on-Trent PCT and (iii) South Staffordshire PCT in the financial year ending 31 March (A) 2010, (B) 2011, (C) 2012 and (D) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154331","154331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7517","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish the number of appeals made under the exceptionality procedures by patients whose applications for in vitro fertilisation treatment were refused by (a) North Staffordshire PCT, (b) Stoke-on-Trent PCT and (c) South Staffordshire PCT in the financial year ending 31 March (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013; and to publish the number of such appeals to each such body in each such year which were successful.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154332","154332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7518","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Area Director of NHS England in Shropshire and Staffordshire to publish (a) his anticipated budget for the commissioning of adult specialist pulmonary hypertension services in (i) Shropshire and Staffordshire NHS area, (ii) Shropshire, (iii) Staffordshire, (iv) North Staffordshire, (v) Stoke-on-Trent and (vi) South Staffordshire for the year ending 31 March 2014 and (b) the number of patients (A) receiving treatment and (B) for which treatment has been budgeted in that year in each such area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154351","154351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7551","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department spent on (a) meat inspections and (b) vets in UK abattoirs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154037","154037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7552","2013-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what expenditure his Department incurred on the cancelled tendering process to replace the National Equine Database.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154038","154038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7553","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prosecutions under food labelling or trade descriptions legislation have been initiated as a result of the horsemeat scandal; and against which food producers and retailers such prosecutions have been initiated.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154039","154039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7554","2013-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to audits carried out in Canada and Mexico by the European Commission's Food and Veterinary Office between 2010 and 2013, which found evidence of shortcomings in North American systems for preventing horsemeat contaminated with banned substances entering the food chain, whether he plans to take steps to reduce import of horsemeat from North America.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154040","154040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7558","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 18 April 2013, Official Report, column 495W, on anaemia, how many aplastic anaemia cases of idiopathic cause there were in each hospital trust area by age group including individuals aged 20 and under in each year since 2002.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153967","153967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7617","2013-05-13","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which advisers to his Department (a) work for banks, (b) are seconded from banks and (c) were previously working for banks.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154008","154008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7618","2013-05-13","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when officials of his Department were first informed of the 40 per cent under estimate by HS2 of the cost of planned works at Euston Station.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154009","154009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7619","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what total amount was held in contingency funds by publicly-funded secondary and primary schools in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154010","154010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7620","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) nurses were employed in the NHS and (b) student nurses there were in each year since 1996-97.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154035","154035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7621","2013-05-13","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) doctors were employed in the NHS and (b) medical students there were in each year since 1996-97.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154036","154036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7693","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times Kettering General Hospital has issued public statements in which it urged people not to come to accident and emergency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154624","154624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7694","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what jobs initiatives his Department is supporting in Corby constituency.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154175","154175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7695","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have waited more than four hours in accident and emergency at Kettering General Hospital in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154176","154176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7696","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting times are at each individual accident and emergency unit in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154177","154177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7697","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting times are at each individual accident and emergency unit in East Anglia.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154178","154178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7698","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have used accident and emergency at Kettering General Hospital in each of the last five years; and what estimate he has made of demand for the service in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154179","154179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7760","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the housing cost contribution under universal credit on (a) levels of homelessness and (b) the number of people aged from 21 to 25 years making a separate claim for universal credit to cover housing costs.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154372","154372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7763","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his German counterpart about the deportation of Professor Davinderpal Singh Bhullar from that country in 1995.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153933","153933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7764","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Indian  counterpart on (a) Professor Davinderpal Singh Bhullar and (b) the abolition of the death penalty in that country.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153934","153934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7765","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Cambodia.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153936","153936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7766","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Cambodian counterpart on (a) land grabs, (b) human rights, (c) independence of the judiciary and (d) freedom of expression in that country.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153937","153937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7767","2013-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Prime Minister's Trade Envoy to Vietnam, Laos and Cambodia regarding human rights in each of those countries.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153952","153952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7813","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154487","154487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7816","2013-05-10","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154488","154488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7817","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154489","154489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7818","2013-05-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154490","154490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7819","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154491","154491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7820","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154492","154492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7821","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154493","154493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7822","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154494","154494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7823","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154495","154495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7824","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154496","154496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7825","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154497","154497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7826","2013-05-10","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154498","154498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7827","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154499","154499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7828","2013-05-10","Northern Ireland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154500","154500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7829","2013-05-10","Scotland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154501","154501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7830","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154502","154502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7831","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154503","154503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7832","2013-05-10","Wales Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154504","154504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7833","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on subscriptions to academic journals published by (a) Reed-Elsevier, (b) Wiley-Blackwell, (c) Springer and (d) any other academic publisher in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154505","154505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7945","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to announce which families in receipt of universal credit will be eligible for free school meals.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154026","154026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7950","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of households in each local authority area in London whose weekly income will be reduced by (a) less than 20, (b) between 20 and 39.99, (c) between 40 and 59.99, (d) between 60 and 79.99, (e) between 80 and 99.99 and (f) over 100 through the introduction of the benefit cap.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154027","154027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7951","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Thameside will be receiving universal credit by 30 May 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154028","154028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7952","2013-05-13","Cabinet Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people employed on zero-hours contracts in each government office region.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154029","154029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7953","2013-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 18 April 2013, Official Report, column 555W, on Construction (Head Protection) Regulations 1989, what evidence he has received that the wearing of head protection has become largely culturally embedded in the construction sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154031","154031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8116","2013-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his policy is on proposals for a ban on the use of HFC refrigerants in new centralised supermarket refrigeration systems from 2020.","Biography information for Mr Tim Yeo","Mr Tim Yeo","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 153973","153973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8154","2013-05-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many Green Deal providers have (a) applied to the Green Deal Finance Company, (b) been successful in their applications and (c) awarded the finance obtained through those applications to customers to date.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154702","154702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8155","2013-05-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when the first Green Deal finance package was paid out by the Green Deal Finance Company to a Green Deal provider.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154703","154703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8156","2013-05-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what amount has been allocated through the Energy Company Obligation brokerage system to date.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154704","154704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8157","2013-05-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what amount has been spent on the Energy Company Obligation to date.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154705","154705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8158","2013-05-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what total amount has been transferred from the Green Deal Finance Company to Green Deal providers to date.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154706","154706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8356","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 2 April 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr B O'Malley.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154476","154476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8357","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to the Minister for Immigration dated 3 April 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr George Martin McCarthy.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154477","154477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8358","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 27 March 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Mohammad Yahya Butt.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154478","154478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8359","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to the Minister for Immigration dated 15 March 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Muhammad Tausif.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154479","154479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8360","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 18 March 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr S. Ahmed.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154480","154480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8361","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to the Minister for Immigration dated 18 March 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms A. Rose.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154481","154481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8362","2013-05-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 14 March 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Marko Lambert.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154482","154482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8363","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 4 March 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr K. Jobanputra.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154483","154483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8364","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 25 March 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mrs Francisca Blandisva Matiza.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154484","154484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8365","2013-05-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 20 March 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr O. Wahid.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154485","154485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8366","2013-05-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 22 March 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Richard Belshaw.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154486","154486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8367","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 28 March 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Mohammed Butt and Mrs Raheela Kavsar.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154474","154474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8368","2013-05-10","Home Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 2 April 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr T N Tchinda.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154475","154475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8414","2013-05-13","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons students attending sixth form colleges are not eligible for free school meals but those students who attend schools with a sixth form are.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154033","154033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8415","2013-05-13","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will  exempt sixth form colleges from VAT on goods and services.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154034","154034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8436","2013-05-10","Department of Health","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies, other than for buildings primarily used for the provision of medical services, in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154242","154242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8437","2013-05-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154243","154243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8438","2013-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies, other than buildings such as job centres intended to be used primarily for meetings with members of the public, in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154244","154244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8439","2013-05-10","Department for Transport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154245","154245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8440","2013-05-10","Department for International Development","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by her Department and its non-departmental public body in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154246","154246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8441","2013-05-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by her Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies, except for buildings constructed for the 2012 London Olympics in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154247","154247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8442","2013-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies, in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154248","154248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8443","2013-05-10","Department for Education","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies other than buildings used primarily for the provision of education, in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154249","154249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8451","2013-05-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154231","154231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8452","2013-05-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154232","154232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8453","2013-05-10","Women and Equalities","2013-05-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by the Government Equalities Office in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154233","154233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8454","2013-05-10","Attorney General","2013-05-08","To ask the Attorney General, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by the Law Officers' Departments, their agencies and non-departmental public bodies in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154234","154234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8455","2013-05-10","Wales Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by his Department in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154235","154235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8456","2013-05-10","Scotland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by his Department in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154236","154236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8457","2013-05-10","Northern Ireland Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by her Department and its non-departmental public bodies in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154237","154237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8458","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies, except for prisons and buildings used primarily for judicial purposes, in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154238","154238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8459","2013-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies, other than buildings operated exclusively by the armed services, in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154239","154239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8460","2013-05-10","HM Treasury","2013-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154240","154240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8461","2013-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has for the future of (a) Worksop and (b) Mansfield Magistrates' Court.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154186","154186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8462","2013-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the total running costs were for each building used, owned or rented in central London by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 154241","154241"
