"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670304","2017-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she has taken to implement the most recent IMB Annual Report on HM Prison Birmingham.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59015","59015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670305","2017-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2016 to Question 54906, whether payments to a community rehabilitation company are reduced when an offender is returned to court having (a) committed a further offence or (b) failed to comply with a community order.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59010","59010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670306","2017-01-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what number of days of sick leave have been recorded by prison officers in each year since 2010; and what number of those were as a consequence of violence within prisons.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59096","59096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670307","2017-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress her Department has made on implementing the recommendations of the review on the care and management of transgender offenders, published in November 2016 on the safeguarding of transgender prisoners on the prison estate.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59161","59161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670308","2017-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate she has made of the wastage rates of public sector prison support staff in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59169","59169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670309","2017-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many civil servants in each unit of her Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59150","59150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670310","2017-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders were released from Crown courts on post-conviction bail for the offences of (a) murder, (b) rape, (c) manslaughter, (d) attempted murder and (e) child sex abuse in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59222","59222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670311","2017-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of making the presentation of birth certificates compulsory for UK-born residents leaving prison to help ensure that they have adequate ID for accessing benefits and other services.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59224","59224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670312","2017-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders of which offence type released from Crown courts on post-conviction bail subsequently failed to surrender for sentencing in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59221","59221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670313","2017-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2016 to Question 57404, on Ministry of Justice: translation services, which authority sets the quality threshold; and what score is required to reach that threshold.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59198","59198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670314","2017-01-11","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether discussions between Ministers or officials of his Department and the Northern Ireland Executive on budgetary challenges facing that Executive during 2015 included the escalated spending exposure under the Northern Ireland non-domestic Renewable Heat Incentive Scheme.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59190","59190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670315","2017-01-11","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the discussions between Ministers and officials of his Department and HM Treasury on budgetary challenges facing the Northern Ireland Executive during 2015 included the escalated spending exposure under the Northern Ireland non-domestic Renewable Heat Incentive Scheme.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59191","59191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670316","2017-01-11","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many civil servants in each unit of his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59151","59151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670317","2017-01-12","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many former non-state actors who were formerly paramilitaries have been charged following a referral by the Northern Ireland Historical Enquiries Team to the Police Service of Northern Ireland or Public Prosecution Service.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59030","59030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670318","2017-01-12","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many (a) current and (b) former members of the Armed Forces currently under investigation by the Police Service of Northern Ireland's Legacy Investigations Branch were previously informed by the Northern Ireland Historical Enquiries Team that there would be no further action against them.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59031","59031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670319","2017-01-11","Cabinet Office","2017-01-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants in each unit of 10 Downing Street are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59152","59152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670320","2017-01-12","Department of Health","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2016 to Question 56695 and with reference to the press release issued by the Prime Minister on 8 January 2017, what the reasons are for the discrepancy between the estimated £11.7 billion figure that release said was being spent on mental health and the estimates for such spending derived from the Mental Health Dashboard.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59218","59218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670321","2017-01-12","Department for Education","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to announce measures for further education as part of her reforms to young people's mental health.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59211","59211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670322","2017-01-11","Scotland Office","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many civil servants in each unit of his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59153","59153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670323","2017-01-11","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many civil servants in each unit of his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59154","59154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670324","2017-01-11","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many members of staff who ceased to be employed by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies in the last three years have subsequently been re-employed by his Department on a temporary basis or as a third-party contractor or consultant.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59176","59176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670325","2017-01-11","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many children under the age of three have a blue parking badge in (a) England, (b) Scotland and (c) Wales.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59049","59049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670326","2017-01-11","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to publish the findings of research commissioned by his Department into the effects of 20 mph speed zones.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59048","59048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670327","2017-01-12","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to publish a draft Modern Transport Bill.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59028","59028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670328","2017-01-12","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects a permanent Chief Executive at HS2 Ltd to be appointed.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59021","59021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670329","2017-01-12","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the MP hotline for HS2 Ltd will be set up and operational.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59022","59022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670330","2017-01-12","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when a permanent High Speed 2 Construction Commissioner will be appointed.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59023","59023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670331","2017-01-12","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many applications have been received for High Speed 2 road safety fund monies; and from whom.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59024","59024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670332","2017-01-12","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, over what period of time the High Speed 2 Community and Environment Fund and Business and Local Economy Fund will be available; and when applications for funding will open.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59025","59025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670333","2017-01-11","Wales Office","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many civil servants in each unit of his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59156","59156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670334","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many civil servants in each unit of his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59157","59157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670335","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been in receipt of carers credit in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59199","59199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670336","2017-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many personal independence payment (PIP) claimants who lost their entitlement to a Motability vehicle successfully appealed and were awarded a new Motability vehicle, (b) what proportion of PIP claimants whose award was reduced, or who were awarded a lower rate of PIP than they previously received for disability living allowance, so that they were no longer eligible for a Motability vehicle, successfully challenged that decision on appeal and (c) what the cost of supplying new replacement Motability vehicles has been (i) on average per person and (ii) in total over each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59105","59105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670337","2017-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether a person starting their own business is required to stay on the Work Programme in order to continue to receive related benefits.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59103","59103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670338","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many members of staff who ceased to be employed by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies in the last three years have subsequently been re-employed by his Department on a temporary basis or as a third-party contractor or consultant.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59178","59178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670339","2017-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2016 to Question 57065, on what date was responsibility for child poverty policy and analysis transferred to his Department from the Child Poverty Unit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59237","59237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670340","2017-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the implications of its policies of the Supreme Court ruling in November 2016 on the under occupancy penalty; and what estimate he has made of how many people in (a) Southwark and (b) England were incorrectly charged.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59245","59245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670341","2017-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many personal independence payments appeal cases have been successful since the introduction of that benefit.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59202","59202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670342","2017-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to his oral contribution of 9 January 2017, on health outcomes: work, what the evidential basis is for his statement that his Department will spend an extra £330 million on employment support for employment support allowance claimants compared with current arrangements under the Work Programme and Work Choice.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59210","59210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670343","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people claiming carer's allowance by age in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59195","59195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670345","2017-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which Ministers of his Department have visited a food bank since their appointment; and what the date of each such visit was.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59059","59059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670346","2017-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will take steps to enable organisations to provide computer skills training to claimants within Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59033","59033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670347","2017-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the hon. Member for Walsall North will receive a reply to his letter to the Benefit Director on 6 December 2016 on employment and support allowance; and what the reasons are for the delay in responding to that letter.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59039","59039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670348","2017-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether in his meetings with the Benefits Director he has discussed the process of replies being sent to hon. Members.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59041","59041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670350","2017-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of individuals in receipt of carers allowance in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59092","59092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670351","2017-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many individuals were subject to benefit sanctions and for what reason in each of the last 12 months in Cardiff South and Penarth constituency.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59080","59080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670352","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of trends in unemployment since June 2016.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59069","59069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670353","2017-01-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the viability of proposals for tidal lagoons in the Bristol Channel, including off Cardiff.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59079","59079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670354","2017-01-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish Ministers' transparency details for July to September 2016.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59083","59083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670355","2017-01-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to help carbon-intensive industries to reduce emissions.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59094","59094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670356","2017-01-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps the Government has taken against employers for not paying the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59056","59056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670357","2017-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on UK jobs of the UK leaving the Single Market in the five years (a) before and (b) after that action is taken.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59011","59011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670359","2017-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps Companies House takes to ensure that all legally required Limited Liability Partnership filing information is provided.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59180","59180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670360","2017-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many members of staff who ceased to be employed by his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies in the last three years have subsequently been re-employed by his Department on a temporary basis or as a third-party contractor or consultant.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59170","59170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670361","2017-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which UK government agency is responsible for ensuring that Limited Liability Partnership registrations comply with section 18 of the Limited Liability Partnerships (Application of Companies Act 2006) Regulations 2009.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59132","59132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670362","2017-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what sanctions have been applied against Limited Liability Partnership designated members that are offshore corporate members and did not supply the details specified in section 18 of the Limited Liability Partnerships (Application of Companies Act 2006) Regulations 2009 since the coming into force of those regulations.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59133","59133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670363","2017-01-11","Department for International Trade","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to increase British beer exports.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59136","59136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670365","2017-01-11","Department for International Trade","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many civil servants in each unit of his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59149","59149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670366","2017-01-12","Department for International Trade","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to his written ministerial statement of 5 December 2016, Official Report, HCWS316, on the UK's commitments at the World Trade Organisation, what process he plans to adopt to secure parliamentary approval of the necessary draft schedules he is preparing.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59071","59071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670367","2017-01-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will make it his policy in immigration negotiations with the EU that (a) there is no discrimination between applicants on the basis of their country of origin and (b) no preferential access is granted for citizens of EU member states.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59100","59100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670368","2017-01-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many civil servants in each unit of his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59144","59144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670369","2017-01-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many officials have resigned from his Department since it was established.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59134","59134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670370","2017-01-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of maintaining the provisions of the Lawyer Services Directive after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59238","59238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670818","2017-01-12","Home Office","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on future levels of staffing of border checkpoints at UK airports.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908121","908121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/671692","2017-01-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will require private car parking firms to join an accredited trade association.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908132","908132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/671971","2017-01-12","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on possible legislative steps to bring an end to the Southern Rail industrial action.","Biography information for Huw Merriman","Huw Merriman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908139","908139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/671972","2017-01-12","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department is making on formulating the second Roads Investment Strategy.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908135","908135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/671973","2017-01-12","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve co-ordination on track renewal and train operations on the railways.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908136","908136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/671974","2017-01-12","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve the condition of local roads.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908133","908133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/671975","2017-01-12","Department for Transport","2017-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he is making on his plans for increased private sector involvement in rail infrastructure projects.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908137","908137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668846","2017-01-10","Cabinet Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many convictions there have been for offences under electoral law in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58795","58795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668847","2017-01-10","Cabinet Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many electoral law offences have been committed by (a) voters and (b) political candidates or their agents in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58796","58796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668848","2017-01-10","Cabinet Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many of the 50 recommendations made in Securing the Ballot the Government plans to see implemented by (a) the Government or (b) other parties, including the Electoral Commission and returning officers, in time for (i) local authority elections in 2017, (ii) local authority elections in 2018, (iii) the next general election due in 2020 and (iv) elections of police and crime commissioners in 2020.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58805","58805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668849","2017-01-10","Cabinet Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many of the recommendations made in Securing the Ballot that the Government identifies in its response to that report as requiring or likely to require primary legislation the Government plans to implement in the (a) current Parliamentary session and (b) remainder of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58804","58804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668850","2017-01-10","Scotland Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many official visits Government Ministers have made to Scotland in the last six months.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58868","58868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668851","2017-01-11","Cabinet Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what date the annual civil service report into socio-economic data for fast-stream recruits will be published.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58908","58908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668852","2017-01-10","Cabinet Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Data Steering Group last met.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58918","58918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668853","2017-01-10","Cabinet Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to reply to the letter of 17 October 2016 from the hon. Member for Bridgend on the Gulf Strategy Unit.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58953","58953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668854","2017-01-11","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the changes to the community amateur sports club scheme on the number of clubs registered in that scheme since 2015.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58961","58961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668855","2017-01-10","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Department of Health's departmental expenditure limit affects the level of the NHS in Wales' block grant allocation.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58997","58997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668856","2017-01-11","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether (a) targets and (b) financial rewards formed part of HM Revenue and Customs' contract with Concentrix for its processing of claims for tax credits.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58936","58936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668857","2017-01-11","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which organisation will run the compliance process for tax credits for (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58935","58935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668858","2017-01-10","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2016 to Question 56889, what the timescale is for the text of the World Health Organisation Protocol to Eliminate Illicit Trade in Tobacco Products to be laid before Parliament as a Command Paper.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58873","58873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668859","2017-01-11","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to require return mail addresses to be provided on HM Revenue and Customs tax correspondence.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58824","58824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668860","2017-01-10","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to prevent false self-employment.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58768","58768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668861","2017-01-10","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to business of amending coin collections systems as a result of the new pound coin entering circulation in March 2017.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58784","58784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668862","2017-01-11","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which charities successfully bid for money from the Tampon Tax Fund; and how much money each such charity received.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58827","58827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668863","2017-01-10","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to increase the stamp duty threshold.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58797","58797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668864","2017-01-10","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of lost (a) income tax and (b) national insurance contributions revenue to the Exchequer as a result of false self-employment.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58767","58767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668865","2017-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of business rate increases on the UK solar industry.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58790","58790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668866","2017-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to prevent proposed business rate changes from causing potential detriment to the solar industry.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58791","58791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668867","2017-01-10","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to improve access to basic bank accounts.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58729","58729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668868","2017-01-10","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the Government plans to improve and promote access to credit unions.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58730","58730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668869","2017-01-10","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) companies are being pursued by his Department for failing to collect aggregate levy tax as a consequence of certificates of exemption that have been retrospectively revoked after having been previously issued in respect of the extraction and mining of shale rock.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58754","58754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668870","2017-01-10","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the gross value is of uncollected aggregate levy tax outstanding as a consequence of retrospectively revoking certificates of exemption previously issued in respect of the extraction and mining of shale rock.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58755","58755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668871","2017-01-10","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) value of unused mobile spectrum and (b) benefits to the economy of bringing that unused spectrum into use through introducing a 30 per cent cap on mobile spectrum holdings.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58745","58745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668872","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the value to the economy of the teaching of English as a second language.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58660","58660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668873","2017-01-10","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is the Government's policy not to make any staff subject to compulsory redundancy as a result of the relocation of the HM Revenue and Customs office in West Lothian to the new regional centre by 2020.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58688","58688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668874","2017-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discretionary powers he proposes to allow local authorities to (a) provide older residents with lifetime local authority tenancies and (b) tailor fixed-term tenancies to suit local housing needs.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58708","58708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668875","2017-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, (a) how many people live in local authority housing in (i) Newcastle upon Tyne, (ii) the North East and (iii) England and (b) what proportion of such people are in receipt of housing benefit.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58709","58709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668876","2017-01-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with local authorities on the effect on (a) mobile coverage of uneven mobile spectrum holdings and (b) the potential benefits of introducing a 30 per cent cap on those holdings.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58744","58744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668877","2017-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what safeguards he plans to put in place to prevent older people from having to relocate at the end of a fixed-term local authority tenancy.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58722","58722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668878","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many local authorities are rated good for children's services.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58780","58780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668879","2017-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funding streams are available to communities that require remediation of contaminated land.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58769","58769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668880","2017-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what mechanisms are in place to enable the Government to assess whether funding will be agreed for specific European Social Fund and European Regional Development Fund projects signed since the Autumn Statement 2016; how such projects will be assessed against the two criteria of value for money and alignment with domestic priorities; and whether such assessments will be undertaken before or after agreements have been signed.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58757","58757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668881","2017-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to incentivise housebuilders to develop brownfield sites.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58770","58770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668882","2017-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, who will be invited to contribute to the fair funding review on local government finances; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58819","58819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668883","2017-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects the fair funding review on local government finance to be completed.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58820","58820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668884","2017-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what local government services will be included in the fair funding review on local government finance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58825","58825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668885","2017-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, who is leading the fair funding review on local government finance.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58826","58826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668886","2017-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the cost of letting agent fees on the ability of homeless people go access private tenancies.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58921","58921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668887","2017-01-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the ruling of Leeds City Council v Broadley on 6 December 2016, what plans he has to amend Guidance to local councils on good practice in the collection of council tax arrears, published in June 2013; and what steps he is taking to enable district and unitary councils in England and Wales to obtain council tax payments from tenants who have vacated periodic tenancies without notice.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58938","58938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668888","2017-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what powers local authorities have to enforce planning conditions placed on housing developments.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59004","59004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668889","2017-01-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to notify hon. Members in the event that 21st Century Fox gives to her formal notification of its takeover bid for Sky.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58915","58915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668890","2017-01-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made by (a) the National Trust and (b) National Parks England in providing proposals to her Department that outline better engagement with communications providers to tackle mobile not spots, as requested at her Department's not spot summit in February 2016.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58783","58783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668891","2017-01-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to amend Ofcom's duties to include the regulation of social media platforms; and if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the non-imposition of a general duty to monitor in Article 15 of E-Commerce Directive 2000/31/EC as it relates to the means by which social media platforms might be expected to monitor abusive content.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58720","58720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668892","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on the mental, physical and general health of users of social media platforms of online abusive content.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58706","58706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668893","2017-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the objectives set for the armed forces operating in (a) Iraq and (b) Syria include the identification of UK nationals involved in conflicts in those countries.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58694","58694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668894","2017-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether training and assistance provided by the Government to non-governmental forces in Libya is subject to an agreement with the Libyan Government of National Accord.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58696","58696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668895","2017-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the armed forces provide training and assistance to forces operating in Libya which are (a) allied with the Libyan Government of National Accord and (b) other Libyan-based forces.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58697","58697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668896","2017-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what rules of engagement have been given to UK forces in Syria on the status in terms of the law of armed conflict of UK nationals whom they encounter who are supporting forces allied to (a) the government of Syria, (b) Daesh and (c) the Free Syrian Army.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58698","58698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668897","2017-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what rules of engagement have been given to UK armed forces operating in Iraq on the status in terms of the law of armed conflict of UK nationals whom they encounter who are supporting forces allied to (a) the government of Iraq and (b) Daesh.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58699","58699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668898","2017-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether specific rules of engagement have been given to UK special forces in Iraq on the status in terms of the law of armed conflict of UK nationals whom they encounter who are supporting forces allied to (a) the government of Iraq and (b) Daesh.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58700","58700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668899","2017-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether specific rules of engagement have been given to UK special forces in Syria on the status in terms of the law of armed conflict of UK nationals whom they encounter who are supporting forces allied to (a) the government of Iraq, (b) Daesh and (c) the Free Syrian Army.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58701","58701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668900","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will publish the findings on which its assessment of alleged violations of international humanitarian law by airstrikes from the Saudi-led coalition in Yemen is based.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58670","58670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668901","2017-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support his Department is providing to anti-Assad forces in and around Idlib.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58739","58739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668902","2017-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, at what rank and in which section of the armed forces is the officer who holds overall responsibility for management of RAF Tain Air Weapons Range.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58792","58792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668903","2017-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, at what rank and in which section of the armed forces is the officer responsible for day-to-day management of RAF Tain Air Weapons Range.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58793","58793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668904","2017-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to ensure that future charges for use of Ministry of Defence land for civilian events are set at a rate that ensures the long-term financial viability and sustainability of physical activities such as orienteering and are consistent with the Government's cross-departmental Sporting Future strategy.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58974","58974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668905","2017-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of lean manning on HM ships on their ability to fight in high-intensity and sustained action.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58989","58989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668906","2017-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the sustainability of the Royal Navy fleet in terms of (a) spare parts and (b) missiles.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58990","58990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668907","2017-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the financial situation of the Royal Navy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58988","58988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668908","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many of his Department's staff he plans to allocate to support EU negotiations on EU research funding programmes after Article 50 has been triggered.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58992","58992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668909","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons ill-health retirement pensions for teachers do not allow recipients to supplement their income by seeking work as private tutors.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58996","58996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668910","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will conduct a formal review of the effectiveness of having qualified early years teachers in early years settings on children's attainment at early years foundation stage.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58779","58779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668911","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of recruitment and retention in early years education; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58661","58661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668912","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will conduct a formal review of progression and professional development in early years education.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58662","58662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668913","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve early language development.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58663","58663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668914","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of qualified early years teachers on pre-school children meeting the expected standards of early development at age five.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58687","58687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668915","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much financial support was given to higher education institutions by government directly or through the Higher Education Funding Council for England (HEFCE) for widening participation; how much such support was allocated through higher education institutions access agreements for widening participation; and how much of that support was given by government directly or through HEFCE in each financial year from 2010-11 (a) in total and (b) to each such institution in England.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58703","58703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668916","2017-01-11","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Government expects to publish the early years workforce strategy.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58710","58710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668917","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2016 to Question 56161, if she will list the free schools for which £800,000 has been written off; and how much of that money has been written off for each of those schools.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58916","58916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668918","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2016 to Question 56161, how much her Department spent to date on recovering money from free schools.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58917","58917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668919","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish the Education Bill.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58923","58923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668920","2017-01-11","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what academy trusts failed to comply with the terms of a financial notice to improve in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58937","58937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668921","2017-01-11","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much of the Fund for European Aid to the Most Deprived allocated to her Department in 2015 to support school breakfast clubs has (a) been spent and (b) not been spent.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58945","58945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668922","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answers of 14 December 2016 to Question 56128 and of 23 December 2016 to Question 58051, whether she will issue guidance for schools and teachers on how the provisions in section 60 of the School Standards and Framework Act 1998 that allow the employment of all teachers in voluntary aided schools to be reserved teachers can be interpreted reasonably and proportionately to comply with the EU Employment Equality Directive Article 4(2).","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58878","58878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668923","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2016 to Question 58805, on how many occasions (a) Ministers and (b) officials of her Department have met (i) Ofsted and (ii) the Department of Health on the Ofsted thematic review of obesity, healthy eating and physical activity since 18 August 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58888","58888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668924","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2016 to Question 58004, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of her Department have had with Public Health England on updating the School Food Standards since 18 August 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58889","58889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668925","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children eligible for the 30 hours free childcare or education offer are in receipt of the offer in London.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58864","58864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668926","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will provide a London weighting to children eligible for the 30 hours free childcare or education offer.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58863","58863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668927","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with UK higher education institutions on the nine per cent drop in applications for medicine courses in UK universities for the 2017-18 academic year.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58860","58860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668928","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 57874, whether any agency or authority under the Department for Education holds data on the improper reporting of pupil exclusions.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58806","58806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668929","2017-01-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with her EU counterparts about preventing whale meat and other whale-based products from passing through EU ports.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58898","58898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668930","2017-01-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with her Chinese counterpart on preventing the breeding of tigers for commercial purposes.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58899","58899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668931","2017-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Environment Agency about (a) its responsibility to enforce the waste hierarchy and (b) cases in which that hierarchy has not been observed.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58723","58723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668932","2017-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what powers local authorities have to enforce flood planning conditions on new houses being built.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59005","59005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668933","2017-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what role her Department has on planning consultations for housing in areas at risk of flooding.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59006","59006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668934","2017-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to prevent flooding in Lancashire.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59007","59007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668935","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to protect the Arctic environment and its eco-system.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58978","58978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668936","2017-01-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department's press release, UK leading global fight against illegal wildlife trade, published on 17 November 2016, how and in what areas the additional funding to tackle the illegal wildlife trade will be spent.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58979","58979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668937","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many of his Department's staff he plans to work on conducting negotiations with the EU after Article 50 has been triggered.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58993","58993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668938","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the objectives of the Government's diplomatic and political policy on Turkey are for 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58983","58983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668939","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the objectives of the Government's diplomatic and political policy on Pakistan are for 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58982","58982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668940","2017-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps HM Ambassador to Iran has taken to support (a) Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe and (b) Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe's family.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58960","58960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668941","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the objectives of the Government's diplomatic and political policy on Russia are for 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58984","58984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668942","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the objectives of the Government's diplomatic and political policy on Palestine are for 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58985","58985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668943","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that UK citizens travelling to India, Thailand and other elephant-range states are made aware of the illegal practice of capturing and breaking young elephants for use in the tourism industry.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58743","58743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668944","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of women's rights in Bangalore after reports of alleged sexual assaults on women in that country on New Year's Eve 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58756","58756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668945","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has asked the Pakistani High Commissioner to lift the seal on the Ahmadi mosque in Chakwal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58775","58775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668946","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the earliest date is on which the Government expects (a) to appoint a replacement for Sir Ivan Rogers and (b) for his successor to be in post.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58776","58776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668947","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to prevent British citizens from receiving organs overseas from the forced organ harvesting trade.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58668","58668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668948","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the number of Yemeni civilians who have been killed in airstrikes since the bombing of a funeral hall in Sanaa on 10 October 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58672","58672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668949","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to work with the Palestinian Authority to promote gender equality in the Palestinian territories.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58704","58704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668950","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what formal and informal discussions his Department had with the US administration before the UN Security Council Resolution 2334 (2016) vote was taken.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58875","58875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668951","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department provided in the drafting process for UN Security Council Resolution 2334 (2016).","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58876","58876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668952","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Ministers of his Department were made aware of the final text of UN Security Council Resolution 2334 (2016) before the vote on that resolution took place.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58877","58877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668953","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contribution his Department made to the drafting and promoting of UN Security Council Resolution 2334.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58927","58927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668954","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department held with 10 Downing Street before the UN Security Council Resolution 2334 vote took place in December 2016.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58870","58870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668955","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in which month the Carers Strategy for England will be published.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58843","58843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668956","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what records his Department holds of the number of children born with cerebral palsy each year in (a) each Community Care Group area, (b) each local authority area, (c) each region and (d) nationally.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58867","58867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668957","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 57868, when he plans to publish the outcomes of testing the new innovative approach to serious illness conversations at the New Care Model sites at Airedale and Southend.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58810","58810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668958","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the GP-to-patient ratio is in (a) North Lancashire Community Care Group (CCG), (b) Blackpool, Fylde and Wyre CCG and (c) England.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58856","58856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668959","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has made an assessment of the recommendations in Action Cerebral Palsy's audit of cerebral palsy provision, Variations in Care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58866","58866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668960","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of the symptoms of ovarian cancer.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58857","58857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668961","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that palliative care is accessible to all people who need it.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58799","58799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668962","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of whether the proper protocols were followed in the CLOTHES trial at Nottingham Clinical Trials Unit.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58811","58811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668963","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to investigate why no independent audit body observed the CLOTHES trial at Nottingham Clinical Trials Unit in any assessment of that trial.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58812","58812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668964","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how many people had to wait in corridors and other locations prior to being admitted to and (b) what the average waiting time was to be seen at accident and emergency units at (i) Royal Preston Hospital, (ii) Royal Blackburn Hospital, (iii) Royal Lancaster Infirmary and (iv) Blackpool Victoria Hospital on each day from 23 December 2016 to 2 January 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58828","58828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668965","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 57868, when Health Education England plans to publish its core competency framework for the standardisation of end of life care training.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58815","58815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668966","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the robustness of the peer review system for clinical trials especially in relation to reviewing the CLOTHES trial at Nottingham Clinical Trials Unit.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58813","58813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668967","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulance crews were provided by (a) St John's Ambulance, (b) Jigsaw Medical Services and (c) other providers to North West Ambulance Services on each day from 23 December 2016 to 2 January 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58829","58829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668968","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 57868, what outcomes are being measured at the New Care Model sites at Airedale and Southend with regard to the new innovative approach to serious illness conversations.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58816","58816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668969","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will investigate the potential conflict of interest at the Health Technology Assessment Programme for those people responsible for awarding funding for the CLOTHES clinical trials who were also heading the Nottingham Clinical Trials Unit to which funding was ultimately granted.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58814","58814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668970","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps NHS England is taking to measure the effect of NHS test beds on patient outcomes, efficiency and value for money; and what data is available on the effect of each innovation to date.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58830","58830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668971","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 57868, when Health Education England plans to publish the new competency framework for all midwifery staff on basic bereavement training that is being developed with NHS England and the Royal College of Midwives.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58817","58817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668972","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on the NHS test beds programme announced by the Chief Executive of NHS England in January 2016.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58831","58831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668973","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to support the adoption of successful NHS test bed innovations more widely in the NHS; and whether additional funding will be made available for that purpose.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58832","58832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668974","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost of NHS test beds to date.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58833","58833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668975","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mental health trusts the Care Quality Commission has identified as being short-staffed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58834","58834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668976","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what sustainability and transformation plans have been identified as failing to make adequate plans for mental health provision; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all areas have adequate mental health plans in place.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58835","58835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668977","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Improving Access to Psychological Therapies services are based within a primary care setting.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58836","58836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668978","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what treatment options are available for patients with HER2-positive metastatic breast cancer who stop responding to Herceptin (trastuzumab).","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58939","58939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668979","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to improve provision of services available in the Welsh language on the gov.uk website.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58940","58940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668980","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that sufficient care home places are available for people with dementia.","Biography information for Mary Robinson","Mary Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58924","58924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668981","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department and Public Health England have to bring together all clinical guidance on HIV support to ensure that advice is readily available to local authorities, clinical commissioning groups and NHS England.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58920","58920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668982","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to amend the Health and Social Care Act 2012 to provide clearer guidance on the provision of HIV support services by local authorities, clinical commissioning groups and NHS England.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58919","58919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668983","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to improve provision of overnight accommodation for parents of babies receiving neonatal care.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58897","58897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668984","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time has been for a follow-up appointment at eye clinics in (a) Morecambe Bay NHS Trust and (b) Blackpool Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58882","58882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668985","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made towards achieving the targets set out in the Outcomes Strategy for Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease and Asthma, published in July 2011, which his Department estimated could save 7,800 lives annually.","Biography information for Dr James Davies","Dr James Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58880","58880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668986","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of identified carers in England have been assessed by their local authority under the terms of the Care Act 2014.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58842","58842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668987","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2016 to Question 58016, when his Department plans to publish the proposed timescale for the reviews of the nutrient profiling model.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58887","58887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668988","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times (a) Ministers and (b) civil servants of his Department have met Health Education England to discuss cancer workforce issues since January 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58895","58895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668989","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training places for health visitors have been (a) commissioned and (b) filled in each calendar year since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58896","58896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668990","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the number of patients diagnosed with idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis by a multidisciplinary team in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58914","58914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668991","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with GP representatives, primary care providers or mental health organisations about the quality of mental health support provided in primary care.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58682","58682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668992","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs in England have specialised in mental health; and how many mental health workers are attached to GP practices in England.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58683","58683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668993","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to develop a long-term sustainable funding system for social care.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58689","58689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668994","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many incidents of hospitalisation due to ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome have been reported to the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority (HFEA); and what steps the HFEA is taking to ensure that all suspected serious adverse reactions are reported to the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58664","58664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668995","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of human eggs that would be required annually for (a) pro-nuclear transfer and (b) maternal spindle transfer should the NHS provide mitochondrial transfer.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58665","58665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668996","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential of (a) research into the use of mitochondrial transfer techniques and (b) subsequent treatments which may be offered on the NHS.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58666","58666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668997","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adverse incidents due to ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome have been reported by the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority to the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency in each year since 1991.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58673","58673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668998","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to mitigate the risks of ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58674","58674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/668999","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in how many licensable IVF treatment cycles at least 20 eggs were collected in the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58675","58675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669000","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adverse incidents in fertility clinics were reported as grade (a) C, (b) B and (c) A incidents in the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58676","58676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669001","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will take steps to set up a National Antibiotic Register for recording all hospital and community patients who have an antibiotic resistant infection.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58778","58778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669002","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the Academic Health Science Centres have spent since their creation on (a) external contractors, (b) promotional materials and (c) furniture in each financial quarter for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58762","58762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669003","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what governance arrangements his Department plans to put in place for overseeing the implementation of each sustainability and transformation plan.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58759","58759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669004","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what costs have been (a) incurred to date and (b) committed for the development and management of the sustainability and transformation plan process for Cheshire and Merseyside.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58760","58760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669005","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what arrangements his Department has put in place for NHS provision in England for patients residing in Wales.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58761","58761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669006","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will take steps to record on death certificates  antibiotic resistant infection as the patient's cause of death.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58772","58772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669007","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether all blood assay results showing infection or resistance to antibiotics go onto a national register.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58773","58773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669008","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England plans to publish the decision of the prioritisation round for specialised services for 2017-18.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58766","58766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669009","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information will be made available to patients on how NHS England came to the decision routinely not to fund second stem cell transplants for those patients who have relapsed.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58765","58765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669010","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance and sanctions are in place in the event a clinical trial is found to have been mishandled.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58782","58782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669011","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times the CommandPoint system for the London Ambulance Service has experienced an outage or failure in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58750","58750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669012","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the contract with Northrup Grumman for the CommandPoint system used by the London Ambulance Service is due for renewal.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58751","58751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669013","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that NHS trusts provide prompt and accurate payments to small businesses.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58747","58747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669014","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on child mental health services in England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58724","58724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669015","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will investigate the potential conflict of interest within the Health Technology Assessment Programme whereby some people responsible for awarding funding for the CLOTHES clinical trials were simultaneously heading the Nottingham Clinical Trials Unit to which such funding was granted.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58727","58727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669016","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the peer review system for (a) the CLOTHES trial at Nottingham Clinical Trials Unit and (b) other clinical trials.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58728","58728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669017","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many beds were available at accident and emergency departments in the North West region in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58731","58731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669018","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the number of paramedics on ambulance services in the North West.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58998","58998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669019","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans that patients will lose access to Kadcyla (trastuzumab emtansine) if NICE does not recommend that drug in its final appraisal determination; what estimate his Department has made of the number of patients who are eligible for the drug Tyverb (lapatinib); and what estimate his Department has made of the number of patients who are receiving the drug Tyverb (lapatinib) on the NHS.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58987","58987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669020","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on patient outcomes of NHS England's decision not to routinely fund second stem cell transplants for patients whose disease relapses.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58976","58976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669021","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to improve the transparency of NHS England's clinical prioritisation process for specialised services.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58977","58977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669022","2017-01-11","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the financial situation of Brighton and Sussex University Hospitals NHS Trust; and what remedial steps he is taking to improve that Trust's financial situation.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58991","58991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669023","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what alternative options are available to a clinician who considers a second stem cell transplant to be the best course of treatment for their patient, as a consequence of NHS England's decision routinely not to fund such transplants for patients whose disease relapses.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58971","58971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669024","2017-01-10","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to contract fostering agencies directly to take unaccompanied asylum-seeking children arriving under section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016 and the Dublin regulations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58994","58994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669025","2017-01-11","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on the concerns of the Polish community since the EU referendum; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58962","58962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669026","2017-01-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners released from prison in (a) Wansbeck constituency and (b) the North East have reoffended in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59001","59001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669027","2017-01-11","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2016 to Question 56963, on motorcycles, what guidance her Department provides to the police on the use of those powers.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58721","58721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669028","2017-01-10","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many child refugees have been accepted for transfer to the UK under the (a) Dublin III Regulations and (b) Dubs amendment.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58748","58748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669029","2017-01-10","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many European citizens applying for permanent residency in the UK have had their applications rejected between 6 May 2015 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58742","58742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669030","2017-01-10","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Ealing Central and Acton of 21 October 2016 to Question 48536, on overseas students, if her Department will undertake a cost-benefit analysis of the economic contribution that net student migration makes to the UK economy.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58738","58738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669031","2017-01-10","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many current European citizens applying for permanent residency in the UK have had their applications rejected since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58741","58741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669032","2017-01-10","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons Eritrean minors have been excluded from her Department's guidance for enacting the Dubs amendment in France.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58749","58749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669033","2017-01-10","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugees have been supported through the Community Sponsorship scheme since that scheme was launched.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58764","58764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669034","2017-01-11","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refunds have been issued to customers who paid for a same-day decision service from UK Visas and Immigration in respect of applications for leave to remain.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58716","58716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669035","2017-01-11","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in how many cases of application for same-day decisions on leave to remain a biometric residence permit has not been issued within seven working days.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58717","58717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669036","2017-01-11","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2016 to Question 56963, what powers the police have to seize (a) off-road bikes and mopeds and (b) other vehicles on the grounds that the driver is not wearing a helmet.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58718","58718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669037","2017-01-11","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2016 to Question 56963, whether the guidance her Department provides to police forces on the use of the powers outlined makes reference to whether the driver of the vehicle is wearing a helmet; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58719","58719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669038","2017-01-11","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether projected savings arising from the closure of Dungavel immigration removal centre and its replacement with a new short-term holding facility are dependent on receipt of a capital return from the sale of Dungavel House.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58903","58903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669039","2017-01-11","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many detainees were held overnight in police cells as part of journeys to or from Dungavel immigration removal centre due to Dungavel's remoteness from an airport; on how many nights police cells were used; and what the cost was to the Home Office of those nights in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58904","58904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669040","2017-01-10","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 30 of the report by the Association of Directors of Children's Services Ltd on Unaccompanied Asylum Seeking and Refugee Children, published in November 2016, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of her Department's funding provided to local authorities for the provision of children's services.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58922","58922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669041","2017-01-11","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, by what date the fees for 2017-18 for (a) non-student visas, (b) work permit visas and (c) in-country visa extension applications will be announced.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58947","58947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669042","2017-01-10","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department had with G4S prior to the decision to equip G4S welfare officers with body cameras when visiting tenants in G4S properties.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58925","58925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669043","2017-01-10","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what factors were taken into consideration in the decision to extend the asylum housing contracts of G4S and Serco for the 2017 to 2019 period.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58926","58926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669044","2017-01-10","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the level of awareness of the requirement for EU students to have comprehensive sickness insurance during their five years' lawful continuous residence in the UK in order to qualify for permanent residence.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58952","58952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669045","2017-01-11","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any of the child refugees who were brought to the UK from Calais in 2016 have been subsequently assessed as being over the age of 18.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58821","58821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669046","2017-01-11","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers who arrived in the UK claiming to be under the age of 18 and who were subsequently assessed as being over the age of 18 have since been deported in the last three years.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58822","58822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669047","2017-01-10","Home Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2016 to Question 54678, when details of the review of the Scrap Metal Dealers Act 2013 and consultation documents will be published on her Department's website; what deadline is in place to ensure stakeholders have adequate time to respond to the consultation; and what steps she is taking to ensure that the consultation process is accessible to small dealers such as Gypsies, Travellers and Roma.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58874","58874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669048","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to encourage international co-operation to tackle the spread of tuberculosis.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58865","58865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669049","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's priority countries are; and which of her Department's country offices will receive reduced support following her Department's recent policy reviews.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58862","58862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669050","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she plans to publish details of funding allocations to multilateral organisations reviewed in the Multilateral Development Review.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58861","58861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669051","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the outcome of the Brussels conference for the Central African Republic on 17 November 2016.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58869","58869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669052","2017-01-11","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to bring forward legislative proposals to amend the International Development (Reporting and Transparency) Act 2006 to reflect the expiration of the Millennium Development Goals and the adoption of the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58844","58844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669053","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Multilateral Development Review, what poverty measures additional to national income multilateral agencies are encouraged to use in reaching investment decisions.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58900","58900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669054","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that her decisions on levels of aid to South Sudan and Yemen do not affect aid decisions made by other countries.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58671","58671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669055","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of trends in the number of people globally living with dementia on the implementation of Sustainable Development Goal 3.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58669","58669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669056","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to provide support to projects intended to foster coexistence between Israelis and Palestinians in the Palestinian territories.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58677","58677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669057","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the creation of an international fund for Israeli-Palestinian peace.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58678","58678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669058","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with Ministerial colleagues on the future allocation of the UK's current contribution to EU development funds.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58679","58679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669059","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to develop a partnership charter with non-governmental organisations.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58680","58680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669060","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to improve its disaggregation of development data by age.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58667","58667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669061","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many contractors working (a) directly for and (b) on projects funded by her Department have been paid more than £400 a day in each financial year since 2012.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58781","58781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669062","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations her Department has made to its international counterparts on water shortages in and around Damascus.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58789","58789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669063","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what information her Department holds on the availability of water in and around the Damascus area.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58798","58798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669064","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to civilians in and around Idlib.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58740","58740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669065","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to consult non-governmental organisations on the next stages of policy development in relation to her Department's recent programme of multilateral and bilateral development reviews.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58995","58995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669066","2017-01-10","Department for International Development","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department will continue to fund (a) the European Commission Development Cooperation Instrument, (b) the European Development Fund and (c) ECHO after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58980","58980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669067","2017-01-10","Department of Health","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prisoners have been diagnosed with mental health problems after their incarceration in the last three years; and what steps his Department is taking to tackle mental health problems during the prisoner rehabilitation process.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59002","59002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669068","2017-01-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost per prisoner is.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59003","59003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669069","2017-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have been convicted of smuggling (a) Inspire magazine, (b) Dabiq magazine and (c) any other piece of proscribed extremist literature into prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59009","59009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669071","2017-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have been found in possession of (a) Inspire magazine, (b) Dabiq magazine and (c) any other piece of proscribed extremist literature in each prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59008","59008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669072","2017-01-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average amount paid to community rehabilitation companies is in (a) Wales and (b) England for the supervision of an offender on a 12-month order.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58883","58883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669073","2017-01-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for the latest year available, how many offenders supervised by the Community Rehabilitation Company in Wales missed (a) two, (b) three, (c) four, (d) five and (e) six or more appointments; and in how many cases in each categories the offenders were arrested and taken back to court.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58884","58884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669074","2017-01-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders supervised by the Community Rehabilitation Company in Wales missed two or more appointments without good reason in 2015.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58885","58885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669075","2017-01-11","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will conduct a public inquiry into the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58930","58930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669076","2017-01-11","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when he was first made aware of the overspend of the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58931","58931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669077","2017-01-11","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether his Department supports the closure of the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58928","58928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669078","2017-01-11","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps he is taking to reduce the cost to the public purse as a result of the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme overspend.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58929","58929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669079","2017-01-11","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions he has had with the First Minister of Northern Ireland on the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58959","58959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669080","2017-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Government's policy is on requiring a debate in the House on a substantive motion prior to any planned deployment of the armed forces.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58695","58695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669081","2017-01-11","Scotland Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will support the introduction of Frank's Law to prevent age discrimination against those aged under 65.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58705","58705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669082","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average waiting time is for a practical driving test in (a) London, (b) England and (c) Hornsey and Wood Green constituency.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58691","58691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669083","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve the efficiency of the process for securing a practical driving test.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58692","58692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669084","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, (a) how much of and (b) on what the £20 million fund managed by Chris Gibb to achieve improvements to rail services has been spent to date.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58763","58763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669085","2017-01-11","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will formally consult the Scottish Government on ship-to-ship transfer proposals that affect Scottish waters.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58934","58934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669086","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of trends in usage of public bus school services.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58901","58901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669087","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Northern Trans-Pennine Routes strategic study: stage 3 report, paragraph 1.4.1, published on 28 November 2016, for what reasons there is an error for the position of the Port of Heysham on the map in figure 1.1.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58881","58881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669088","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the reliability of the Class 37 locomotives that run between Barrow and Preston; and how many journeys were delayed or cancelled in (a) 2016 and (b) 2015 due to engine failure.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58858","58858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669089","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2016 to Question 55749, what progress has been made by his Department's investment board in considering the business case submitted by Southeastern Railway for additional rolling stock.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58809","58809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669090","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of compliance with disability legislation of railway rolling stock operated by Northern in Lancashire and Cumbria.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58800","58800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669091","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the age of railway rolling stock operated by Northern in Lancashire and Cumbria.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58801","58801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669092","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of trends in the cost of public bus services on school services to passengers.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58802","58802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669093","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the cost to passengers of public bus services.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58803","58803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669094","2017-01-11","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Midlands Expressway on usage of the M6 Toll Road.","Biography information for Mr Khalid Mahmood","Mr Khalid Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58818","58818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669095","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will include in his Department's forthcoming Cycling and Walking Investment Strategy a commitment to create new road environment design standards to encourage cycle use among (a) children and young people, (b) women, (c) older people and (d) people with disabilities.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58966","58966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669096","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support the creation of new long-haul air services to airports across the UK to support international trade as part of the new Aviation Policy Framework.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58954","58954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669097","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it is Government policy that the High Speed 2 and Northern Powerhouse rail projects are not developed in isolation; and whether he plans to integrate those two schemes.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58955","58955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669098","2017-01-11","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of road accident casualties that have been (a) seriously and (b) slightly injured that have been unreported to the police in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58963","58963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669099","2017-01-10","Department for Transport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will include in his Department's forthcoming Cycling and Walking Investment Strategy a commitment to review how the planning system (a) supports and (b) fails to support (i) the creation of quality cycling conditions and (ii) improvements to existing cycling conditions.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58965","58965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669100","2017-01-11","Wales Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2016 to Question 46772, what progress has been made on procurement of the Wales and Borders Rail franchise.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58946","58946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669101","2017-01-10","Women and Equalities","2017-01-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when the consultation on caste discrimination announced on 2 September 2016 will commence.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58872","58872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669102","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants in Scotland were covered by the jobseeker's allowance sanctions early warning trial between March and September 2016; and what plans he has to extend that trial across the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58845","58845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669103","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to reform the earnings limit applied to the carer's allowance.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58823","58823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669104","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people not previously in receipt of higher-level disability living allowance were awarded the mobility element of personal independence payments by (a) quarter and (b) region in 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58948","58948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669105","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people previously in receipt of higher-level disability living allowance were awarded the mobility element of personal independence payments by (a) quarter and (b) region in 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58949","58949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669106","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people previously in receipt of higher-level disability living allowance were not awarded the mobility element of personal independence payment by (a) quarter and (b) region in 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58951","58951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669107","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people previously in receipt of higher-level disability living allowance who were not initially awarded the mobility element of personal independence payment were awarded it at review or on appeal by (a) quarter and (b) region in 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58950","58950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669108","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much and what proportion of the Flexible Support Fund was unspent in 2015-16; and how much of the 2016-17 allocation has been spent to date.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58941","58941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669109","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to carry out impact assessments in the areas where jobcentre closures are proposed.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58932","58932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669110","2017-01-11","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the eligibility to free school meals will be of children in households in receipt of Universal Credit, broken down by employment status.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58944","58944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669111","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been out of work who were blind or deaf in each calendar year from 2010 in (a) Sunderland City Council borough, (b) each English region and (c) England.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58890","58890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669112","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been out of work who had a skin condition or epilepsy in each calendar year from 2010 in (a) Sunderland City Council borough, (b) each English region and (c) England.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58891","58891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669113","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people living with musculoskeletal conditions have been out of work in (a) Sunderland City Council borough, (b) each English region and (c) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58892","58892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669114","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have a blood or circulation condition have been out of work in (a) Sunderland City Council borough, (b) each English region and (c) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58893","58893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669115","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have (a) Type 1 and (b) Type 2 diabetes have been out of work in (a) Sunderland City Council borough, (b) each English region and (c) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58894","58894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669116","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with (i) the Department of Health and (ii) Public Health England on developing the evidence base on long-term health conditions, including degenerative and fluctuating health conditions and work outcomes following the publication in November 2016 of the work, health and disability green paper: improving lives.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58886","58886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669117","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobcentre offices in the UK are subject to live planning applications that would change the use of those premises.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58905","58905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669118","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on companies that provide Work Programme services in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58906","58906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669119","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what small business start-up grants are available to people on the Work Programme.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58907","58907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669120","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason annual increases to state pensions are made with reference to the inflation figures from October of the previous year.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58909","58909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669121","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that working and benefits provision is in place in the event that expats living abroad must return to the UK after the UK leaves the EU (a) in general and (b) for those expats who may not have made national insurance contributions in recent years.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58774","58774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669122","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that funding is provided to older people and other vulnerable people so that those people can access adequate supported housing.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58752","58752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669123","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the housing benefit cap on the affordability of housing for claimants living in supported housing.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58753","58753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669124","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to improve access to pensions for self-employed people.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58733","58733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669125","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the uptake of workplace pensions since that scheme's inception.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58734","58734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669126","2017-01-10","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department overpaid in working tax credit claims in the last financial year; and what the estimated cost is of recovering those overpayments.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58735","58735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669127","2017-01-10","HM Treasury","2017-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the estimated amount of unclaimed entitlement to working tax credits was in the last financial year.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58736","58736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669128","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of false self-employment on benefit entitlements.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58737","58737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669129","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who are certified as self-employed in Bolton North East constituency are in receipt of in-work benefits.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58732","58732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669130","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants attending Bridgeton Jobcentre Plus are in receipt of income support.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58693","58693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669131","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect that additional travelling will have on individuals with mobility problems in the event that the Jobcentre Plus office closures in Glasgow go ahead.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58711","58711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669132","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of local public transport networks on people's ability to access alternative jobcentres in the event that Jobcentre Plus office closures in Glasgow go ahead.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58707","58707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669133","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants attending Bridgeton Jobcentre Plus are in receipt of employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58713","58713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669134","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants attending Bridgeton Jobcentre Plus are in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58714","58714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669135","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants attending Bridgeton Jobcentre Plus are in receipt of jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58715","58715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669136","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what effect the recent reassessment of the national living wage has had on the eligibility of (a) an over 25-year old single person, (b) an over 25-year old couple, (c) a single person aged between 21 and 24, (d) a couple aged between 21 and 24, (e) a single person aged between 18 and 20, (f) a couple aged between 18 and 20, (g) a singe person under the age of 18 and (h) a couple under the ages of 18 to claim jobseeker's allowance for up to the quoted 16 hours.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58681","58681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669137","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to respond to the National Audit Office's report on Benefit Sanctions, published on 30 November 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58967","58967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669138","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to change testing criteria for (a) personal independence payments and (b) employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58957","58957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669139","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to put in place greater interim and transitional funding for claimants (a) during and (b) after personal independence payment appeals.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58958","58958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669140","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce the time taken to make payments for (a) personal independence payments and (b) employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58956","58956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669141","2017-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answers of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 5W, what the expenditure for the Work Choice programme was in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58964","58964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669142","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2016 to Question 50587, on state retirement pensions, by what means overseas claimants are audited.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58970","58970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669143","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of disability living allowance have undertaken a reassessment for personal independence payments when over the age of 65 since April 2013.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58972","58972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669144","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of disability living allowance who were reassessed for personal independence payments when over the age of 65 have had their claim disallowed since April 2013.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58973","58973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669145","2017-01-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many unsuccessful applications for personal independence payments were appealed in 2016; and what proportion of those appeals were (a) ruled in favour of the appellant and (b) upheld by the tribunal.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58999","58999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669146","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will amend the Operational Guidance issued to local enterprise partnerships in September 2014 on the allocation of European Structural and Investment Funds (ESIF), to indicate that ESIF and resources should be used to support greater access to adult education, skills training and the labour market for Gypsy, Roma and Traveller groups.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58986","58986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669147","2017-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the reassessment of the national living wage on the eligibility to claim jobseeker's allowance to his Department's quoted up to 16 hours for (a) a single person aged over 25, (b) an old couple aged over 25, (c) a single person aged between 21 and 24, (d) a couple aged between 21 and 24, (e) a single person aged between 18 and 20, (f) a couple aged between 18 and 20, (g) a single person under the age of 18 and (h) a couple under the age of 18.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59000","59000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669148","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2016 to Question 55486, how many of the 687 employers named by his Department for non-compliance with the national minimum wage under the naming and shaming scheme have identified further arrears not included in the sum of arrears for which they were named under the self-correction mechanism; what the total was of those further self-corrected arrears; and to how many workers those further self-corrected arrears were owed.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58981","58981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669149","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2016 to Question 44543, how many (a) warning notices and (b) financial penalties have been issued to respondent employers to date under section 150 of the Small Business, Enterprise and Employment Act 2015 for failure to pay an employment tribunal award; how many of those financial penalties (i) have been paid and (ii) remain unpaid; and how much in previously unpaid awards has been recovered by his Department following (A) the issuing of a warning notice only and (B) the issuing of both a warning notice and a financial penalty.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58968","58968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669150","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2016 to Question 44542, how many financial penalties have been imposed to date on respondent employers for aggravated breach of employment law under section 16 of the Enterprise and Regulatory Reform Act 2013; how many such penalties (a) have been paid and (b) remain unpaid; and what the total sum paid in penalties is.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58969","58969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669151","2017-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions she has had with Ministers of the Scottish Government on the progress of devolving administrative responsibilities for (a) employment tribunals and (b) other relevant tribunals to the Scottish Government.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58712","58712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669152","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish a response to the report published by the Parliamentary Advisory Group on Carbon Capture and Storage prior to the publication of the Government's emissions reduction plan.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58702","58702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669153","2017-01-10","Cabinet Office","2017-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of EU nationals working in each sector of the UK economy.","Biography information for Mr Pat McFadden","Mr Pat McFadden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58686","58686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669154","2017-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2016 to Question 57518, what the strike price comparator is for Hinkley Point C.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58725","58725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669155","2017-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2016 to Question 57518, if his Department will publish the methodology used to calculate strike price comparators for renewable energy technologies.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58726","58726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669156","2017-01-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the correlation between prices in the mobile phones market and the uneven distribution of mobile spectrum.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58746","58746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669157","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the (a) increase in sales, (b) additional investment attracted, (c) creation of jobs and (d) creation of intellectual property resulting from the work of the Small Business Research Initiative in each year since that body was established.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58785","58785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669158","2017-01-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support and further develop tech and digital industries in coastal areas such as Eastbourne.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58777","58777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669159","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many firms have received funding through the Small Business Research Initiative to (a) test an idea and (b) develop a prototype in each year since that body was established.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58786","58786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669160","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Small Business Research Initiative; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58787","58787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669161","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what consideration has been given to supporting charity investment in universities through increasing investment in the Charity Research Support Fund.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58794","58794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669162","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress has been made on establishing and appointing a Small Business Commissioner under the Enterprise Act 2016; and what the timescale is for the appointment of that Commissioner.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58788","58788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669163","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what incentives the Government provides to support biomedical research into the most deadly global diseases.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58902","58902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669164","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many director disqualifications in relation to convictions abroad there have been under section 104 of the Small Business, Enterprise and Employment Act 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58879","58879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669165","2017-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many tonnes of coal the UK has exported in the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58933","58933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669166","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many convictions there have been for general false statement offences under section 1112 of the Companies Act 2006 since 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58808","58808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669167","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many financial penalties have been awarded in relation to Directors' statement and auditor's report to be available for inspection under section 720(5) of the Companies Act 2006 since 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58807","58807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669168","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish his response to the independent report into the consumer protection measures concerning online secondary ticketing facilities, published in May 2016.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58771","58771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669169","2017-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many financial penalties have been awarded in relation to a company's duty to keep a register of secretaries under section 275(6) of the Companies Act 2006 since 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58837","58837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669170","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people work for the breaches team at Companies House (a) in total and (b) as full-time equivalents.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58846","58846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669171","2017-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many financial penalties have been awarded in relation to the direction requiring a company to make appointment under section 156(6) of the Companies Act 2006 since 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58838","58838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669172","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many company officers and Limited Liability Partnership designated members have been fined for offences under sections 21, 22 and 23 of the Company, Limited Liability Partnership and Business (Names and Trading Disclosures) Regulations 2015 since 31 January 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58847","58847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669173","2017-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many financial penalties have been awarded in relation to the register of directors under section 162(6) of the Companies Act 2006 since 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58839","58839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669174","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the total value is of fines collected for companies officers' offences under sections 21, 22 and 23 of the Company, Limited Liability Partnership and Business (Names and Trading Disclosures) Regulations 2015 since 31 January 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58848","58848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669175","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the total value is of fines for companies' offences under sections 21, 22 and 23 of the Company, Limited Liability Partnership and Business (Names and Trading Disclosures) Regulations 2015 since 31 January 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58852","58852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669176","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many registered offices, inspection places and business locations the Companies House Breaches Team has visited in order to verify companies' compliance with sections 21, 22 and 23 of the Company, Limited Liability Partnership and Business (Names and Trading Disclosures) Regulations 2015 since 31 January 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58853","58853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669177","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many registered offices and inspection places there are in relation to sections 21, 22 and 23 of the Company, Limited Liability Partnership and Business (Names and Trading Disclosures) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58850","58850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669178","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many companies have been fined for offences under sections 21, 22 and 23 of the Company, Limited Liability Partnership and Business (Names and Trading Disclosures) Regulations 2015 since 31 January 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58851","58851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669179","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many non-dormant UK companies and Limited Liability Partnerships Companies House Breaches Team monitors for breaches of sections 21, 22 and 23 of the Company, Limited Liability Partnership and Business (Names and Trading Disclosures) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58849","58849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669180","2017-01-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, for what reasons the Government has not joined the World Tourism Organisation.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58871","58871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669181","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many companies the Companies House Breaches Team has investigated for breaches of sections 21, 22 and 23 of the Company, Limited Liability Partnership and Business (Names and Trading Disclosures) Regulations 2015 since 31 January 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58854","58854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669182","2017-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many companies have been found guilty of offences under sections 21, 22 and 23 of the Company, Limited Liability Partnership and Business (Names and Trading Disclosures) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58855","58855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669183","2017-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many financial penalties have been awarded in relation to failure to deliver annual returns under section 858(1) of the Companies Act 2006 since 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58841","58841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669184","2017-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many financial penalties have been awarded in relation to duty to notify registrars of changes under section 167(4) of the Companies Act 2006 since 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58840","58840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669185","2017-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the 10 largest domestic subsidies used by UK industry by virtue of UK membership of EU trading arrangements under the World Trade Organisation definition of aggregate measurement of support are by (a) type of good, (b) sector, (c) quantity of goods affected and (d) estimated value to the UK economy.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58912","58912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669186","2017-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the 10 existing EU tariff rate quotas with the largest economic value for the UK economy are by (a) type of good, (b) sector of the economy, (c) quantity and (d) estimated value for UK industry.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58913","58913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669187","2017-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of whether the UK should negotiate a UK-specific entitlement to the aggregate measurement of support that the EU is allowed under World Trade Organisation rules; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58911","58911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669188","2017-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of whether the UK should agree a division of EU tariff rate quotas before consideration by Parliament of UK-specific World Trade Organisation schedules of concessions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58910","58910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669189","2017-01-10","Department for International Trade","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what value for money assessment his Department has made of the UKTI Events Alliance programme.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58684","58684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669190","2017-01-10","Department for International Trade","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the outcomes have been of the leads generated by the UKTI Events Alliance programme in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58685","58685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669191","2017-01-10","Department for International Trade","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to contract notice 2016/5 166-299652, for what reasons his Department decided to tender for event specialists; and whether his Department considered using trade associations to deliver any of those events.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58690","58690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669192","2017-01-11","Department for International Trade","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how the UK's representative on the Committee of Permanent Representatives was instructed to vote on the proposals to modernise the UK's trade defence instruments.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58975","58975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669193","2017-01-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many trade negotiators his Department has recruited since its creation.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58943","58943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669194","2017-01-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff with negotiation expertise his Department has recruited since June 2016.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58942","58942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669195","2017-01-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which 57 areas of sectoral analysis will feature in the negotiations that the Government is undertaking on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Pat McFadden","Mr Pat McFadden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58659","58659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669196","2017-01-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the options are for the form in which the document containing the Government's plan for the UK leaving the EU will be published before Article 50 is triggered.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58758","58758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669197","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2017-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with UK higher education institutions about the nine per cent drop in applications for medicine courses in UK universities for the 2017-18 academic year.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58859","58859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662780","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people were sent for prosecution for impersonating a candidate and taking the (a) written and (b) practical parts of the driving test for them in each of the last five years and by geographical area.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58403","58403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662781","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people were convicted for impersonating a candidate and taking the (a) written and (b) practical parts of the driving test for them in each of the last five years and by geographical area.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58404","58404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662782","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people were sent for prosecution for using an impersonator to take the (a) written and (b) practical parts of the driving test for them in each of the last five years and by geographical area.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58406","58406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662783","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people were convicted for using an impersonator to take the (a) written and (b) practical parts of the driving test for them in each of the last five years and by geographical area.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58407","58407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662784","2017-01-09","Attorney General","2016-12-20","To ask the Attorney General, whether the Law Officers' Departments permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58444","58444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662785","2017-01-09","Attorney General","2016-12-20","To ask the Attorney General, how many private prosecutions were taken over by the Crown Prosecution Service in each of the last three years for which figures are available; and how many such prosecutions (a) stopped before trial and (b) proceeded to a verdict.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58584","58584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662786","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many private prosecutions have been brought by (a) the National Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Children, (b) the Royal Society for the Protection of Birds, (c) the Royal Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals and (d) individual private citizens in England and Wales in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58585","58585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662787","2017-01-09","Attorney General","2016-12-20","To ask the Attorney General, for what reasons no reference was made in the Government's proposals for the prosecution of ISIS made at the UN on 15 December 2016 to genocide committed against Christians whereas specific reference was made to other minority groups; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58629","58629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662788","2017-01-09","Cabinet Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58445","58445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662789","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will reform the audit requirements for industrial and provident societies in line with similar requirements for companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58437","58437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662790","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58439","58439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662791","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to publish the equality impact analysis of the Autumn Statement 2016 to comply with the Public Sector Equality Duty.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58464","58464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662792","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect on the household income of UK citizens of increasing insurance premium tax from 10 to 12 per cent.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58349","58349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662793","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of UK GDP that will be represented by small business manufacturing in 2020.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58359","58359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662794","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employers were prosecuted in 2009-10 and 2010-11 for failing to pay the National Minimum Wage.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58353","58353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662795","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations his Department has received on the change in the value of secured energy bonds that were offered by CDB Energy; and what steps he is taking to address the implications of that change for investors.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58658","58658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662796","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total amount of benefit and tax credit debt (a) repaid and (b) written-off was in each financial year from 2003-04 to 2015-16 in each region and constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58574","58574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662797","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to publish an updated impact assessment of tax-free childcare to include the changes to eligibility criteria for such childcare announced in the Autumn Statement 2016.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58573","58573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662798","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total amount of benefit and tax credit debt owed was at the end of each financial year from 2003-04 to 2015-16 in each region and constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58575","58575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662799","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2016 to Question 56783, how decisions on the allocation of monies from LIBOR fines between facilities based at MoD sites, MoD events and registered charities were made; and who in his Department was responsible for those decisions.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58513","58513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662800","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department and any arms-length departmental body has spent on (a) staffing, (b) other revenue costs and (c) capital expenditure in the current fiscal year in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58501","58501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662801","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2016 to Question 56783, if he will publish the eligibility criteria for applying for funding from LIBOR fines for military charities.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58514","58514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662802","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people were employed in each HM Revenue and Customs team working on enforcing minimum wage payments in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58599","58599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662803","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) budget and (b) workforce is of each HM Revenue and Customs team responsible for enforcing employment categorisation.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58600","58600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662804","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) budget and (b) planned workforce is of HM Revenue and Customs' employment status and intermediaries team.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58601","58601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662805","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 3.48 of the Autumn Statement 2016, on national minimum wage enforcement, what the (a) budget, (b) staffing capacity and (c) start date is of the additional support targeted at small businesses.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58602","58602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662806","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 3.48 of the Autumn Statement 2016, on national minimum wage enforcement, what the (a) budget, (b) staffing capacity and (c) start date is of the campaign to raise awareness among workers and employers of their rights and responsibilities.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58603","58603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662807","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which areas of protected public expenditure his Department plans to include in the review of public spending priorities and other commitments for the next Parliament announced in paragraph 1.57 of Statement 206.","Biography information for Mr Pat McFadden","Mr Pat McFadden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58598","58598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662808","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that business rates for heat networks are calculated using the receipts and expenditure method of valuation.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58652","58652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662809","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on encouraging the development of heat networks.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58649","58649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662810","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress his Department has made on the roll-out of tax-free childcare; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58655","58655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662811","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from the Northern Ireland Executive on the merits of introducing a windfall tax on profits from the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58651","58651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662812","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support the creation of traditional, street-based, high-density designs in new housing developments.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58654","58654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662813","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate she has made of the number of lease forfeitures that have occurred in the last year.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58653","58653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662814","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to increase the provision of starter homes in Peterborough; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58489","58489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662815","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the report of the review group on Community Infrastructure published in November 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58486","58486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662816","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much local authorities in Yorkshire and the Humber have spent in the current financial year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58510","58510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662817","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans further to devolve (a) community infrastructure levy funding, (b) 100 per cent business rate growth and (c) EU legacy structural funds to the new Cambridgeshire and Peterborough Combined Authority after May 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58483","58483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662818","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to fund social care through new homes bonuses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58515","58515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662819","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the use of vacant building credit in delivering new residential homes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58542","58542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662820","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what applications have been submitted to Lancashire County Council to regenerate land in (a) Morecambe and Lunesdale and (b) Lancaster and Fleetwood constituency.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58441","58441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662821","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what applications have been submitted to Lancashire County Council on regeneration in South Heysham.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58440","58440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662822","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58446","58446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662823","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58447","58447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662824","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make it her policy to review the adequacy of the Electronic Commerce (EC Directive) Regulations 2002 in so far as they relate to social media platforms after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58389","58389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662825","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2016 to Question 56474, if she will provide the answer sought in that Question on what discussions she has had with Ministers of HM Treasury on the potential effect on freelance creative workers of HM Revenue and Customs proposals that self-employed workers update their tax quarterly; and what steps she plans to take to address the concerns of those workers.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58630","58630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662826","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential effect of a 30 per cent cap on mobile spectrum on (a) competition and (b) prices for consumers.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58550","58550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662827","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2016 to Question 48756, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure that its expectations for social media providers to have robust processes in place to deal with abusive content are met.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58499","58499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662828","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the timetable is for the release of data collected by the Libraries Taskforce in relation to statutory and non-statutory public libraries; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58490","58490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662829","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department and its arm's-length departmental bodies has spent on (a) staffing, (b) other revenue costs and (c) capital expenditure in the current financial year in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58625","58625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662830","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of UK's distribution of spectrum on competition in the mobile industry.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58604","58604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662831","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make it her policy to ensure that mobile networks use all of the spectrum holdings available.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58605","58605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662832","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential benefits to Scotland of increasing the equality of spectrum holdings among mobile networks.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58606","58606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662833","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to ensure that the UK's distribution of spectrum ensures (a) coverage and (b) competition across the UK.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58607","58607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662834","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of a phase start for Initial Operational Test and Evaluation for the F35B Lightning II.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58645","58645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662835","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the F35B Lightning II is due to complete air-to-air instrumentation testing before the end of Block 3F testing.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58646","58646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662836","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2016 to Question 57632, what assessment has been made of the identity of the principal competitors for Type 31 frigates in the global export market.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58644","58644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662837","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether F35 Joint Strike Fighters from (a) the Netherlands, (b) Denmark and (c) Norway will be able to operate from UK airfields to conduct exercises.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58642","58642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662838","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2016 to Question 57052, on joint strike fighter aircraft, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect that the ending of the System Development and Demonstration programme will have on the proposed initial operating capability for the UK F-35B in 2018 upon completion of Block 3F testing.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58643","58643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662839","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average time taken is for a case under review by the Iraq Historic Allegations Team before it is resolved.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58583","58583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662840","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average time taken to resolve a case by the Iraq Historic Allegations Team is.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58616","58616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662841","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the sale of UK-manufactured cluster bombs to non-NATO countries between 1980 and 1995.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58374","58374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662842","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department provided training programmes to the Saudi Arabian-led military coalition in (a) air warfare skills and artillery techniques and (b) the use of cluster munitions between 1980 and 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58373","58373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662843","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58448","58448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662844","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Third Tier arrangement between the UK and the US for responding to an accident in the UK involving US nuclear weapons was last reviewed and updated; and what the dates and locations of (a) the last and (b) the next scheduled tabletop and field exercises conducted under the auspices of that arrangement are.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58420","58420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662845","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress the Minister of State for School Standards has made on assessing the potential costs of changing the Schools Admissions Code to provide more flexibility for summer-born children.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58432","58432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662846","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58449","58449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662847","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2016 to Question 55974, on academies: finance, for what reason her Department is not aware of other judgments.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58383","58383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662848","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the mental health assessment pilots for looked-after children announced by her Department in November 2016 will cover both children in care and care leavers.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58370","58370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662849","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Expert Working Group for looked-after children's mental health plans to publish recommendations on mental health assessments for both looked-after children and care leavers.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58371","58371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662850","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions her Department has had with the Department of Health about improving mental health outcomes of care leavers.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58380","58380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662851","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how long Regional Schools Commissioners (RSCs) have taken, by year and by RSC, to find appropriate sponsors for schools from when they are notified that the school is in special measures to having a sponsor taking over that school.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58390","58390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662852","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effect of unmet mental health needs among care leavers on their (a) educational and (b) training and employment outcomes and levels of homelessness.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58376","58376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662853","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase funding for schools with a high concentration of students with special educational needs.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58355","58355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662854","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to attract and retain talented newly-qualified teachers in disadvantaged schools in the North.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58356","58356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662855","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has discussed the levels of sexual harassment occurring on university campuses with the (a) Home Secretary and (b) Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Vulnerability, Safeguarding and Countering Extremism.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58634","58634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662856","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 December 2016 to Question 56818, what evaluation her Department has made of the effectiveness of the teaching of (a) health and nutrition and (b) personal finance advice in schools.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58615","58615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662857","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department holds any information on the levels of sexual harassment occurring on university campuses.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58633","58633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662858","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers have left the profession before retirement in each year since 2010; and how many of those teachers left to teach overseas.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58614","58614"
