"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861130","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to Israeli counterparts on the continued use of live fire by Israeli naval forces against fishermen off the coast of Gaza.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132279","132279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861131","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of (a) girls groomed for sexual exploitation and (b) perpetrators of child sexual exploitation in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132280","132280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861132","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Public and Commercial Services Union on the implications for public safety of the new satellite navigation test.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132281","132281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861133","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to renew the plug-in car grant for electric vehicles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132282","132282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861134","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to regulate in-game purchasing in video games.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132283","132283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861135","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the uptake levels of electric and low-emission vehicles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132284","132284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861136","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to regulate the game mechanics of (a) loot boxes and (b) similar in-game reward mechanisms in video games to ensure fair practices.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132285","132285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861137","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure the disclosure of the odds of winning items in (a) loot boxes and (b) similar variable reward mechanisms on screen at the time of purchase in video games.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132286","132286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861138","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse plans to (a) visit and (b) consider Telford as part of its current investigation into child sexual exploitation in England and Wales.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132287","132287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861139","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the GP to patient ratio was for Coventry and Rugby Clinical Commissioning Group in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132288","132288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861140","2018-03-16","Cabinet Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate the Government has made of the number of eligible people who are not on the electoral register in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132289","132289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861141","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the changes to the eligibility of free school meals under universal credit on child poverty in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132290","132290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861142","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) primary and (b) secondary school pupils in Coventry who will be eligible for free school meals after the introduction of changes to the threshold for free school meals under universal credit.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132291","132291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861143","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children are included on universal credit claims in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132292","132292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861144","2018-03-15","Department for International Trade","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to support small and medium-sized enterprises' to export after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132293","132293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861145","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that retailers pass on the full cost of the five pence charge for plastic carrier bags.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132294","132294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861146","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much money has been raised by the five pence plastic bag levy from each of the ten largest retailers since that policy was introduced.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132295","132295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861147","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to put the prime contract for the Airborne Warning and Control System replacement programme out to tender.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132296","132296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861148","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what level of funding his Department has allocated for the replacement of the RAF’s Airborne Warning and Control System fleet.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132297","132297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861149","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of 5 March 2018 to Question 130173, on Money Laundering: Prosecutions, if he will list the individuals successfully prosecuted under the Money Laundering Regulations 2007 in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132298","132298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861150","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much and what proportion of the revenue raised by the five pence plastic bag levy has been allocated to good causes by each of the ten largest retailers since the introduction of the policy.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132299","132299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861151","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will ensure that the criminal sanctions that apply to offences under the Control of Trade in Endangered Species (Enforcement) Regulations are (a) retained and (b) not downgraded to civil sanctions in the proposed changes to those regulations.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132300","132300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861152","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to research by the Department of Clinical Science at Bergen University, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the findings that exposure to cleaning products can cause as much damage to lung function as smoking 20 cigarettes a day.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132301","132301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861153","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what access detainees in immigration detention centres have to mobile phones, the internet and social media.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132302","132302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861154","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of taking steps to protect cleaners from lung damage due to exposure to cleaning products; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132303","132303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861155","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 131194, how many representations he has received on Northamptonshire County Council's changes to its library provision.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132304","132304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861156","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 131194, on Northamptonshire County Council: Public Libraries, what the timetable is for his Department's decision on whether those representations will be treated as a formal complaint.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132305","132305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861157","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2018 to Question 130540, on Foster Care in England Independent Review, if he will publish the specific evidence reviewed by the Narey Review into Fostering which recommended the addition of Independent Reviewing Officers.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132306","132306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861158","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Minister for Immigration plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Inverness, Nairn, Badenoch and Strathspey dated 25 January 2018 seeking a meeting on behalf of his constituents.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132307","132307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861159","2018-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to respond to the letter of the hon Member for Inverness, Nairn, Badenoch and Strathspey of 4 of December 2017 on unfair delivery charges.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132308","132308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861160","2018-03-16","Cabinet Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many stillbirths were recorded in each month of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132309","132309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861161","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) actual and (b) full time equivalent health visitors who have been employed in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132310","132310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861162","2018-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department has allocated to tackle (a) Islamophobia, (b) sexual orientation discrimination and (c) antisemitism in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132311","132311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861163","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to review the scope of individuals covered by the position of trust terms of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 to include (a) youth workers, (b) sports coaches and (c) ministers of religion.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132312","132312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861164","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS child and adolescent psychiatrists have been employed in Kent in the last two years for which data is available.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132313","132313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861165","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the Hate crime action plan 2016.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132314","132314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861166","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been deemed to be living in in-work poverty in each (a) constituency in Wales and (b) ward in Delyn in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132315","132315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861167","2018-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to prevent the growth of extreme anti-Muslim views in (a) print, (b) broadcast and (c) social media.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132316","132316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861168","2018-03-16","Northern Ireland Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she is taking to restore devolution in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132317","132317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861169","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent from the public purse through the Access to All fund to make improvements to railway stations in each years since 2006.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132318","132318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861170","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, of what factors Network Rail and his Department take account in deciding on allocations of Access to All funding.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132319","132319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861171","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what public funding other than Access to All funding is available for improvements to accessibility at railway stations.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132320","132320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861172","2018-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Housing Delivery Test results which each local authority in England will be required to publish under the National Planning Policy Framework will include specific data on the number of Gypsy sites.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132321","132321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861173","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans his Department has to continue to allocate a financial support grant of £100,000 to the Victim Support homicide team in 2018-2019.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132322","132322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861174","2018-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people are estimated to benefit from the planned rise in the national living wage to £7.83 in Thornbury and Yate constituency.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132323","132323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861175","2018-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people are estimated to benefit from the planned rise in the national living wage to £7.83 in south Gloucestershire.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132324","132324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861176","2018-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy how many people are estimated to benefit from the planned rise in the national living wage to £7.83 in the South West.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132325","132325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861177","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are estimated to benefit from the rise in the tax free personal allowance during the 2017-2018 financial year in Thornbury and Yate constituency.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132326","132326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861178","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are estimated to benefit from the rise in the tax free personal allowance during the 2017-2018 financial year in south Gloucestershire.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132327","132327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861179","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people in the South West who benefited from the increase in the tax free personal allowance in 2017-18.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132328","132328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861180","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment has he made of the effect of changes to free school meals as a result of universal credit on children in Liverpool; and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132329","132329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861181","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which railway stations have received Access for All funding in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132330","132330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861182","2018-03-15","Women and Equalities","2018-03-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she plans to publish the consultation on reform of the Gender Recognition Act 2004 announced on 23 July 2017.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132331","132331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861183","2018-03-15","Women and Equalities","2018-03-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether the public consultation on reform of the Gender Recognition Act 2004 is planned to include a proposal and question on legal recognition for non-binary people.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132332","132332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861184","2018-03-15","Women and Equalities","2018-03-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she plans to hold discussions with trans community groups as part of the the Government's public consultation on reform of the Gender Recognition Act 2004.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132333","132333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861185","2018-03-15","Women and Equalities","2018-03-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many non-binary respondents made submissions to the Government Equalities Office’s nationwide LGBT survey.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132334","132334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861186","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the  legislation passed by the Knesset on 7 March 2018 to enable that country's Minister of Interior to revoke the permanent residency status of Palestinian residents of Jerusalem; and if he will make an assessment of the compatibility of that law with international (a) humanitarian and (b) human rights law.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132335","132335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861187","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of upgrades to the F-35 in the next seven years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132336","132336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861188","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the reasons are for the yellow card system for reporting medical harms not including psycho-social therapies including (a) graded exercise and (b) cognitive behaviour therapy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132337","132337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861189","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for the contract awarded for the provision of health services at HMP Liverpool of the recommendations of the report of the Liverpool Community Health Independent Review, published in January 2018.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132338","132338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861190","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, further to his oral statement of 13 March 2017 on Spring Statement, if he will publish the allocation of the £500 million funding to vulnerable children in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132339","132339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861191","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what percentage of state-funded pupils benefited from a partnership between an independent school and a state-funded school in (a) 2016, and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132340","132340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861192","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to respond to the recommendations of the review conducted by  Dr Bill Kirkup, Report of the Liverpool Community Health Independent Review, published in January 2018.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132341","132341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861193","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2018 to Question 129976 on Refugees, when she plans to publish the evaluation of the implementation of the Post Grant Appointment Service.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132342","132342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861194","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effect of recent increases in the National Living Wage and the personal allowance on the personal incomes of Mid Sussex constituents.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132343","132343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861195","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the potential monies that would accrue to the public purse of the  introduction of revenue-based taxes on multinational companies.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132344","132344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861196","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her oral contribution of 6 March 2017, Official Report, column 560, if she will grant the application made in November 2016 by the hon. Member for Brighton Pavilion to visit Yarl’s Wood immigration detention centre.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132345","132345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861197","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Office, with reference to Children in Military Custody, published in June 2012, how many of that report's recommendations have been implemented by the Government.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132346","132346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861198","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Office, how many people involved in the transfer of Palestinian children out of the West Bank to prisons inside Israel entered the UK in 2017.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132347","132347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861199","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the nationwide trial of the 26-30 railcard was limited to 10,000 such railcards; and whether his Department took steps to ensure that government digital systems could cope with the level of demand.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132348","132348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861200","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for further education provision in Cheshire as a result of the the announcement made on 9 March 2018 of the proposed closure of the Hartford Campus by Warrington and Vale Royal College; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132349","132349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861201","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of access to (a) further and (b) adult education provision in the Cheshire West and Chester area for the academic year 2018-19 as a result of the announcement of the proposed closure of the Hartford campus of Warrington and Vale Royal College in Summer 2018.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132350","132350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861202","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claims in Scotland include a child component.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132351","132351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861203","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households receive universal credit with a child element in Scotland.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132352","132352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861204","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to his Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 131113, on Syria: Armed Conflict, what progress has been made in implementing UN Security Council resolution 2401 since the adoption of the resolution calling for its full and immediate implementation on 5 March 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132353","132353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861205","2018-03-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on the amount of money invested by the Premier League in grassroots football in each year since 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132354","132354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861206","2018-03-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on how the Premier League has distributed its funding for grassroots football projects since the start of the 2016-17 football season.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132355","132355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861207","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he takes to ensure that funds raised by companies through initial public offerings in London do not finance companies under US and EU sanctions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132356","132356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861208","2018-03-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what meetings he or Ministers of his Department have had with (a) the Premier League and (b) the FA on the issue of grassroots football in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132357","132357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861209","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the timetable of three weeks allocated by the Office of Rail and Road for a public consultation to scrutinise Network Rail’s strategic plan for the railways between 2019 and 2024.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132358","132358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861210","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost of ensuring the High Speed Trains on the East Midlands line will be PRM TSI compliant by 2020.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132359","132359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861211","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Network Rail’s procurement framework for Control Period 6 will encourage UK SMEs to tender for work.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132360","132360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861212","2018-03-15","Department for International Development","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress has been made on achieving the 17 sustainable development goals; and what steps her Department is taking to (a) support and (b) collaborate with the nations who have signed up to those goals.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132361","132361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861213","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2018 to Question 128931, on Engineers and Scientists: Visas, for what reason her Department is no longer able to provide the statistics it provided in the Answer of 21 September 2015 to Question 9220 on that same topic.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132362","132362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861214","2018-03-15","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether an announcement on the North West Relief Road and the large local majors scheme is still scheduled to take place in the summer of 2018.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132363","132363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861215","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of electronic vehicles on UK roads by 2028.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132364","132364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861216","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has had discussions with the Home Office on the re-introduction of the alcohol duty escalator; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132365","132365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861217","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £24.8 million allocated to his Department to realise the opportunities from EU exit will be spent.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132366","132366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861218","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the ability of MPAM to respond to correspondence from hon. Members within the service standard of 20 working days.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132367","132367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861219","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £260 million allocated to HMRC to realise the opportunities from EU exit will be spent.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132368","132368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861220","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March to Question 130076, whether her Department collects data on lost data, personal documents and application forms.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132369","132369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861221","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £29.6 million allocated to his Department to realise the opportunities from EU exit will be spent.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132370","132370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861222","2018-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £12.7 million allocated to his Department to realise the opportunities from EU exit will be spent.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132371","132371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861223","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures his Department has in place to provide compensation for lost passports, personal documents and application forms.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132372","132372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861224","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 130076, on Passports: Postal Services, whether it is UK Immigration and Visas policy to return passports to immigration applicants by second class unrecorded post.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132373","132373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861225","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions her Department paid compensation to a victim of wrongful detention and at what total cost in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132374","132374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861226","2018-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects Morpheus will receive a supply of radios to enable them to transmit data from their platforms to other users.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132375","132375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861227","2018-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will reduce business rates for general aviation airfields to reflect their potential contribution to the economy.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132376","132376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861228","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase the number of police officers in (a) England and Wales and (b) Gloucestershire; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132377","132377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861229","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of (a) the number of the kit or replica cars on the road and (b) what proportion of vehicle emissions they represent.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132378","132378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861230","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March to Question 129628, what the strict time limits are on resolving defects where inspected asylum accommodation do not meet the required standards.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132379","132379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861231","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March to Question 129628, what the strict time limits are on resolving defects where inspected asylum accommodation does not meet the required standards.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132380","132380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861232","2018-03-16","Department for International Development","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the level of food security in Ethiopia.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132381","132381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861233","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Road vehicles: improving air quality and safety consultation, published by his Department in February 2018, what estimate he has made of the number of people employed in SMEs in the kit car or replica car industry; and what discussions he has had with those SMEs on his proposals set out in that consultation.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132382","132382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861234","2018-03-15","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of s165 of the Equality Act 2010 in ensuring that wheelchair users are able to hire taxis.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132383","132383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861235","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2018 to Question 129628, how many financial reductions have been applied and at what total cost to providers as a result of inspected asylum accommodation not meeting the required standards in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132384","132384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861236","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase the proportion of (a) leave to remain, (b) indefinite leave to remain and (c) naturalisation applications processed within her Department's service standards.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132385","132385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861237","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times at A&E departments on (a) Fridays and (b) Saturday evenings.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132386","132386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861238","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether (a) his Department and (b) Cifas has undertaken an audit of the bank refusals made in error between January and July 2016 identified by the Independent Chief Inspector of Borders and Immigration; and what steps his Department has taken to lower that error rate.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132387","132387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861239","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for information to be provided to his Department by Cifas for immigration enforcement.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132388","132388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861240","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she received prior to the decision of the Metropolitan Police to use automated facial recognition at Notting Hill Carnival in 2016 and 2017.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132389","132389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861241","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the operational justification for the decision made for the Metropolitan Police to use automated facial recognition at Notting Hill Carnival in 2016 and 2017.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132390","132390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861242","2018-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's policy is on consumers' rights to request a refund if they were not  made aware that they were on an auto-renewal contract for subscription-based services.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132391","132391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861243","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) white, (b) black, (c) Asian and (d) mixed race individuals were on the automated facial recognition watchlist for Notting Hill carnival in 2017.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132392","132392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861244","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of the heightened risk of cancer arising from the consumption of nitrate-processed meats.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132393","132393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861245","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of organ transplants as a result of the roll-out of opt-out only organ donations.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132394","132394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861246","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money has been spent on commissioning non-NHS tier 4 mental health inpatient beds for young people  aged under 18 in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132395","132395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861247","2018-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department is (a) conducting a review and (b) undertaking other work on the deregulation of employment rights.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132396","132396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861248","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has any evidence which shows that homeopathic vets are a risk to animal welfare by using homeopathy as an alternative treatment to pharmaceutical treatment options.","Biography information for David Tredinnick","David Tredinnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132397","132397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861249","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Department for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to ensure that all medical assessment centres have disability access and disabled parking for claimants with mobility issues.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132398","132398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861250","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate he had made of the number of children who will be eligible for 30 hours of funded childcare in the summer term 2018.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132399","132399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861251","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of assessment centres have no (a) disabled parking and (b) disabled access.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132400","132400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861252","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what studies the Government has undertaken to establish the extent to which common veterinary practice is evidence-based.","Biography information for David Tredinnick","David Tredinnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132401","132401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861253","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons she has not added Dupuytren's Contracture to the Industrial Injuries Disablement Benefit list of conditions.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132402","132402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861254","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the cost of adding Dupuytren's Contracture to the list of prescribed diseases.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132403","132403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861255","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will including Dupuytren's Contracture on the list of prescribed diseases.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132404","132404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861256","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions her Department has refused to add a condition to the list of prescribed diseases following a recommendation from the Industrial Injuries Advisory Council.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132405","132405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861257","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations she has received on not including Dupuytren's Contracture on the list of prescribed diseases.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132406","132406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861258","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what organisations she met with when considering the inclusion of Dupuytren's Contracture on the list of prescribed diseases.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132407","132407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861259","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will provide a bespoke HMRC helpline for recipients of a Mineworkers' Pension who have received incorrect tax information.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132408","132408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861260","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will provide a bespoke HMRC helpline for recipients of a Mineworkers' Pension who have received incorrect tax information.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132409","132409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861261","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when HMRC plans to issue revised tax statements to people in receipt of a Mineworkers' Pension who have received incorrect tax information.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132410","132410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861262","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people in receipt of a Mineworkers' Pension who have received incorrect tax information.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132411","132411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861263","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if the Government will make compensation available for the (a) distress caused and (b) additional costs incurred by recipients of a mineworkers pension who have received incorrect tax information.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132412","132412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861264","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to reduce VAT on (a) power walls and (b) other renewable energy products intended for domestic use.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132413","132413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861265","2018-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received from the Trustees of the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme on surplus sharing arrangements in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132414","132414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861266","2018-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment has he made of the benefits of domestic powerwalls as a means of (a) storing energy created by renewables and (b) providing the grid energy to manage peaks in demand.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132415","132415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861267","2018-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the oral contribution of the Hon. Member for Burton of 13 March 2018 whether he plans to publish the notes of his meeting on the Prompt Payment Code.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132416","132416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861268","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2018 to Question 131381 on Children: Day care, for which local authority and for what reasons that disapplication was approved.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132417","132417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861269","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) three and (b) four year olds are eligible for 30 hours funded childcare.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132418","132418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861270","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many 3 and 4 year olds receive the early years Disability Access Fund.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132419","132419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861271","2018-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the oral contribution of hon. Member for Burton of 13 March 2018, what plans he has to ensure that signatories to the Prompt Payment code comply with the requirements of the code.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132420","132420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861272","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many families have (a) registered and (b) re-registered for a 30 hours of funded childcare place for the summer 2018 term prior to the 31 March 2018 deadline.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132421","132421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861273","2018-03-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the average cost of renting a property in (a) the social rented sector and (b) the private rented sector for households on low incomes in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132422","132422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861274","2018-03-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the social housing Green Paper is planned to include measures to increase the supply of social housing.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132423","132423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861275","2018-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to ensure that signatories to the Prompt Payment Code pay all invoices within 30 days.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132424","132424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861276","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a 16-25 bus discount scheme similar to the 16-25 railcard.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132425","132425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861277","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the adequate provision of public transport in rural areas.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132426","132426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861278","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions his Department has had with universities on student mental health services.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132427","132427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861279","2018-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to require signatories to the Prompt Payment Code to ensure that the payment terms in the code are adopted throughout their supply chains.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132428","132428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861280","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals to prevent the import of chicken dosed with the antibiotic colistin after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132429","132429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861281","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to meet representatives of the Association of Educational Psychologists.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132430","132430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861282","2018-03-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many local troubled family co-ordinators there were working as part of the Troubled Families Programme in each year from 2012 to 2017.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132431","132431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861283","2018-03-16","Department for International Trade","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of steel exports to the US by volume that are specialist steel products that the US does not have capability to produce.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132432","132432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861284","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of non-UK doctors not meeting the £55,000 salary threshold to qualify for Tier 2 visas on NHS staffing.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132433","132433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861285","2018-03-16","Department for International Trade","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate his Department had made of the proportion of steel exports to the US by value which are specialist steel products that the US does not or has no capability to produce.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132434","132434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861286","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will commission an independent public inquiry into the abuse of children in Telford with a structure and processes that provide past and current survivors of this abuse with (a) input and control over how and when their voices are heard within the inquiry, (b) full recognition of the trauma that may be associated with a survivor giving evidence and (c) comprehensive support mechanisms; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132435","132435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861287","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on stability in the region of recent violence in Israel and the West Bank.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132436","132436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861288","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of institutionalised radicalism in the Palestinian territories.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132437","132437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861289","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of rocket fire from Gaza into Israel.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132438","132438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861290","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the amount of weapons held by Hezbollah.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132439","132439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861291","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish a list of the private sector companies which are in receipt of diabetes transformation funds.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132440","132440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861292","2018-03-15","Cabinet Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the criteria are for a town to gain city status.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132441","132441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861293","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the devolution of the adult education budget on the development of literacy, numeracy and digital skills.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132442","132442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861294","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what public funding has been provided to the Workers Educational Association in each of the last three years; and what plans the Government has to fund the Workers Educational Association in the future.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132443","132443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/859910","2018-03-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-12","What recent assessment he has made of trends in local authority funding for children's services.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904289","904289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860527","2018-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the liquidation of Carillion on their facilities management contract at the British Museum; whether that contract included clauses to deal with potential liquidation; whether there are plans to bring that work back in-house; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131884","131884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860528","2018-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2018 to Question 123535, on Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Procurement, what the contracts are that his Department holds with those suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131885","131885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860529","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of administering intra-joint injections by ultrasound instead of by x-ray to reduce costs.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131886","131886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860530","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the state of human rights in Morocco.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131887","131887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860531","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss the imprisonment of Ahmed Aliouat with his Moroccan counterpart.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131888","131888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860532","2018-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2018 to Question 126471, on Capita, which contractual obligations Capita has with his Department (a) do and (b) do not flow down to subcontractors.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131889","131889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860533","2018-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2018 to Question 126471, on Capita, on how many occasions his Department has refused to approve a subcontractor proposed by Capita in each year since 2010; what reason was given for each such refusal; and what the name was of each proposed subcontracting company.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131890","131890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860534","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the level of service support that children with eating disorders (a) is not reduced and (b) does not end when those children become adults.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131891","131891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860535","2018-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment OFGEN has made of the level of customer satisfaction with the complaints process for energy companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131892","131892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860536","2018-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to help students afford the cost of renting properties.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131893","131893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860537","2018-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has allocated contingency funding to pay people who are having their personal independence payment claim reviewed by the Government.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131894","131894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860538","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's policy is on Sudan joining the Commonwealth.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131895","131895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860539","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether additional resources have been allocated to (a) the Food Standards Agency and (b) local authorities to allow the inspection of commercial third party assurance providers.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131896","131896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860540","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on implications for (a) the public health regulation of food companies’ exports and (b) those companies' access to the single market after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131897","131897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860541","2018-03-14","Treasury","2018-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether parents of disabled children are entitled to an increase of 40 per cent in the proportional rate of the top-up for tax-free childcare contributions.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131898","131898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860542","2018-03-14","Department for Transport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to review his Department's policy on parking on pavements.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131899","131899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860543","2018-03-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the planned move of Channel 4 out of London.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131900","131900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860544","2018-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for each community rehabilitation company, how many people currently under supervision have had (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four and (e) five or more different designated probation officers.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131901","131901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860545","2018-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent by his Department on (a) focus groups and (b) opinion polling in 2011.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131902","131902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860546","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of refugee families which are reunited in the UK.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131903","131903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860547","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken has been for the office of the Independent Case Examiner to respond to a complaint relating to the equalisation of the state pension age in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131904","131904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860548","2018-03-14","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what is the expected (a) completion and (b) publication date of her Department’s review of the operation of the Psychoactive Substances Act 2016.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131905","131905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860549","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been allocated from the public purse to English for Speakers of Other Languages classes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131906","131906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860550","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been allocated from the public purse to English for Speakers of Other Languages classes in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131907","131907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860551","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of people who are subject to in-work conditionality under universal credit.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131908","131908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860552","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of people who will be subject to in-work conditionality once the roll-out of universal credit is complete.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131909","131909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860553","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which organisation will be responsible for debt recovery from mortgage interest loans and what guidance will be provided to that organisation on responding to elderly and vulnerable claimants.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131910","131910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860554","2018-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government plans to publish its Resources and Waste Strategy for 2018.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131911","131911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860555","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy that all products containing palm oil should be labelled as such to enable consumers to decide whether they wish to buy products containing that ingredient.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131912","131912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860556","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of palm oil production on wildlife and the environment in palm oil producing countries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131913","131913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860557","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128292, on Revenue and Customs: ICT, which contracts the HMRC has let and taken on as part of the Aspire exit; and how the £200 million a year by 2020-21 figure referred to in that Answer was calculated.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131914","131914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860558","2018-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which youth full-time social action programmes have received statutory funding in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131915","131915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860559","2018-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to change the status of full-time volunteers from not being in education, employment or training.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131916","131916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860560","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many victims of modern slavery will potentially be affected by the proposed reduction in weekly subsistence payments.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131917","131917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860561","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff are employed full time in the Modern Slavery Unit; and what estimate she has made of the annual cost to the public purse of those staff.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131918","131918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860562","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the annual Government allocation to the Office of the Independent Anti-Slavery Commissioner was in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, and (c) 2017-18; and what proportion of the Commissioner’s total expenditure this represents in each of those years.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131919","131919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860563","2018-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how his Department defines whether a pension scheme is (a) private and (b) public in calculating benefits eligibility.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131920","131920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860564","2018-03-14","Treasury","2018-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether organisations in Scotland will be able to access funding from the UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131921","131921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860565","2018-03-14","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the number of new regulatory bodies which will be required once the UK leaves the EU; and what the role of each such body will be.","Biography information for Phil Wilson","Phil Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131922","131922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860566","2018-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to review the banding of domestic properties for the purpose of collecting council tax.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131923","131923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860567","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the Coal Authority's most recent estimate is of coal reserves in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131924","131924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860568","2018-03-14","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of Tier 5 (Temporary Worker - Charity Worker) visa applications UK Visas and Immigration has refused in the last four quarters for which information is available.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131925","131925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860569","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance her Department provides to claimants receiving job seekers allowance who volunteer for a Credit Union; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131926","131926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860570","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the 91 sites referenced on page 5 of his Department's document entitled A Better Defence Estate, published in November 2016, how much land has been released for development since the publication of that document; and how many homes have (i) begun and (ii) completed construction on that land since the publication of that document.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131927","131927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860571","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's Written Statement of 6 September 2016, on Defence Estate Rationalisation, HCWS 133, whether he has any revisions to the date by which he expects the 12,565 homes to be built on the land referenced in that statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131928","131928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860572","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2016 to Question 54025, on Ministry of Defence: Capita, if he will update those figures to date.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131929","131929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860573","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that all clinical commissioning groups offer three full cycles of IVF to women under the age of 40 who have been trying to get pregnant for 2 years.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131930","131930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860574","2018-03-14","Treasury","2018-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many members of the Social Care Compliance Scheme there are.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131931","131931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860575","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of Sri Lanka on violence perpetrated against Sri Lanka's Muslim minority.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131932","131932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860576","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of Sri Lanka on the establishment of a country office of the UN Office of the High Commissioner for Human Rights in that country.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131933","131933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860577","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the extent of freedom of religion or belief in Sri Lanka after recent reports of religious-based violence in Kandy.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131934","131934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860578","2018-03-15","Department for International Development","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether officials in her Department have held discussions with the Pakistan Government on the inclusion of religious tolerance in textbooks as part of the Punjab Education Support Programme.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131935","131935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860579","2018-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has plans to increase the funding for basketball at grassroots level across the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131936","131936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860580","2018-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the outstanding money under the Child Maintenance Service's collect and pay system is swiftly collected.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131937","131937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860581","2018-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to prevent parents from accruing arrears under the Child Maintenance Service's collect and pay system.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131938","131938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860582","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the GP to patient ratio for (a) Redbridge Clinical Commissioning Group and (b) other clinical commissioning groups in London; and if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of those GP to patient ratios.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131939","131939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860583","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the GP to patient ratio was for Redbridge Clinical Commissioning Group in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131940","131940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860584","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the Chinese authorities on the demolition of (a) Christian churches, (b) Tibetan Buddhist institutes and (c) religious buildings in China.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131941","131941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860585","2018-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has to the Chinese authorities on the detention of  (a) Uyghur Muslims in Xinjiang, (b) Falun Gong practitioners, (c) Christian leaders, (d) other members of religious minorities and (e) people who defend the right to freedom of religion or belief in that country.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131942","131942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860586","2018-03-15","Cabinet Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate the Government has made of the number of eligible people who are not on the electoral register in (a) the London Borough of Redbridge and (b) each local authority area in London.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131943","131943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860587","2018-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice whether he has had discussions with the governor of HMP Brixton on the removal of Pastor Paul Song from his chaplaincy post at that prison; and if he will take steps to press for that pastor's reinstatement.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131944","131944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860588","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of UK residents who have been not been given access to healthcare due to disputed immigration status in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131945","131945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860589","2018-03-14","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on the lack of access to healthcare for immigrants from West Indian nations due to disputes over their immigration status; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131946","131946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860590","2018-03-14","Cabinet Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111417, on Public Sector: Recruitment, which civil service roles were not identified as suitable for removal of the box under the ban the box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131947","131947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860591","2018-03-14","Cabinet Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111417, on Public Sector: Recruitment. what criteria are used to assess whether a civil service role is suitable for removal of the box under the ban the box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131948","131948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860592","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the Independent Reconfiguration Panels report on the potential downgrading of Huddersfield Royal Infirmary to be made public.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131949","131949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860593","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2018 to Question 130433 and the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128441, whether he plans to make a new estimate of the number of wells projected to be drilled by the shale gas industry in 2025 to replace the estimate which is considered to be out of date.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131950","131950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860594","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2018 to Question 130666, on Fracking: Employment what advice the Department for Energy and Climate Change (a) commissioned and (b) received from the engineering consultancy AMEC on the potential effect on employment from the future development of the shale gas industry; whether his Department has since commissioned any such estimate from an external consultancy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131951","131951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860595","2018-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, in how many instances local authorities have exceeded the six-week limit for using bed and breakfast accommodation for homeless families in the most recent 12 months for which data is available; and how many local authorities have so exceeded that limit in that same period.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131952","131952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860596","2018-03-14","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to use the National Missing Person’s Register as a tool for information sharing between (a) the police (b) children's social care providers and (c) other statutory safeguarding agencies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131953","131953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860597","2018-03-14","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made on establishing a Missing Person’s Register; and what the timetable is for that register going live.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131954","131954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860598","2018-03-14","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Missing Person’s Register will collect information on missing children at risk of (a) child sexual exploitation, (b) child criminal exploitation and (c) child trafficking.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131955","131955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860599","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel have passed each available CBRN course at the Defence Chemical Biological Radiological and Nuclear Centre in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131956","131956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860600","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Army, (b) Royal Air Force and (c) Royal Navy personnel have passed a Defence Chemical Biological Radiological and Nuclear Centre CBRN course; and which courses those personnel have passed.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131957","131957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860601","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the process of transferring CBRN responsibilities from the RAF Regiment to the British Army is planned to be completed.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131958","131958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860602","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel from each service have taken part in Exercise Toxic Dagger in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131959","131959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860603","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many former claimants of disability living allowance who have been unsuccessful in their claim for personal independence payments have been waiting over (a) six weeks, (b) three months and (c) six months for their appeal to be heard in Coventry South constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131960","131960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860604","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of people who have mental health conditions who are receiving personal independence payments in Coventry South constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131961","131961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860605","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who previously qualified for disability living allowance have not been awarded personal independence payments after an assessment by the Independent Assessment Services in Coventry South constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131962","131962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860606","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of knife crime in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry South constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131963","131963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860607","2018-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to consult on post-feed-in tariff policy support for solar power; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131964","131964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860608","2018-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received on the levels of business rates levied on properties used for onsite battery storage; and what assessment he has made of the effect of those levels of business rates on the battery storage sector.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131965","131965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860609","2018-03-15","Cabinet Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what date the London Borough of Bromley (Identification in Polling Stations) Pilot Order 2018 came into force.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131966","131966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860610","2018-03-15","Cabinet Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what date the Gosport Borough Council (Identification in Polling Stations) Pilot Order 2018 came into force.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131967","131967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860611","2018-03-15","Cabinet Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what date the Swindon Borough Council (Identification in Polling Stations) Pilot Order 2018 came into force.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131968","131968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860612","2018-03-15","Cabinet Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what date the Watford Borough Council (Identification in Polling Stations) Pilot Order 2018 came into force.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131969","131969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860613","2018-03-15","Cabinet Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what date the Woking Borough Council (Identification in Polling Stations) Pilot Order 2018 came into force.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131970","131970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860614","2018-03-15","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2018-03-12","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, in respect of the areas where Voter ID pilots are being carried out this spring, and where the Commission plans to evaluate those pilots, what studies of the marked registers from the 2018 local elections will be carried out to understand the effect of such trials on levels of turnout.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131971","131971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860615","2018-03-15","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2018-03-12","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, in respect of the areas where Voter ID pilots are being carried out this spring, and where the Commission plans to evaluate those pilots, what studies of the marked registers from the 2018 local elections will be carried out to understand the differential effect of such trials on levels of turnout between different ethnic groups.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131972","131972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860616","2018-03-15","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2018-03-12","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, in respect of the areas where Voter ID pilots are being carried out this spring, and where the Commission plans to evaluate those pilots, what studies of the marked registers from the 2018 local elections will be carried out to understand the differential effect of such trials on levels of turnout between different ethnic groups.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131973","131973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860617","2018-03-15","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2018-03-12","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, in respect of the areas where Voter ID pilots are being carried out this spring, and where the Commission plans to evaluate those pilots, what steps the Commission is taking to ensure that interviews are carried out not only with electoral registration officers and returning officers but also with people who work for the day as presiding officers in respect of individual polling stations and have personal face-to-face experience of difficulties that electors encounter in those pilot areas.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131974","131974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860618","2018-03-15","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2018-03-12","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, in respect of the areas where Voter ID pilots are being carried out this spring, and where the Commission plans to evaluate those pilots, what steps the Commission is taking to ensure that a representative group of those people who work for the day as presiding officers in respect of individual polling stations who are representative not only the demography of the area but also the particular challenges which have been identified by civil society groups are interviewed.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131975","131975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860619","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to his Answer to of 30 January 2018 to Question 12548, on monitoring of PM1, if he will ensure that more sites in the Particulate Numbers and Concentrations Network monitor PMs of less than 2.5.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131976","131976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860620","2018-03-15","Department for International Trade","2018-03-12","Pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2018 to Question 130861, on Honduras: Electronic Surveillance, if the surveillance equipment has been exported from the UK to Honduras.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131977","131977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860621","2018-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will require operators of waste incineration sites to monitor emissions of particulate matters of less than 2.5.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131978","131978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860622","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of increased electricity interconnection on welfare.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131979","131979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860623","2018-03-14","Cabinet Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to page 8 of his Department's document Regulatory Futures Review, published in January 2018, whether he has received such a report on burdens on smaller regulators.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131980","131980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860624","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2018 to Question 128954, what assessment he has made of the effect of increased electricity interconnection on (a) net employment in and (b) GDP contribution from the electricity generating sector.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131981","131981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860625","2018-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for funeral expenses payments for children under (a) two, (b) five and (c) 18 years have been made in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131982","131982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860626","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Women of 22 February 2018, Official Report, column 328, when he plans to publish his assessment of the effect of period poverty on school absence rates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131983","131983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860627","2018-03-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he consulted the Public Appointments Commissioner on the appointment of the Chair of the Charity Commission before that appointment was publicly announced; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131984","131984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860628","2018-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has held with his counterparts in the Government of Morocco on (a) the work of the UN peacekeeping mission to Western Sahara and (b) proposals for a referendum on Saharawi self-determination.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131985","131985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860629","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to implement the recommendation of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse's Child Migration Programmes Report on establishing a compensation fund for former child migrants.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131986","131986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860630","2018-03-15","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 130823, whether the Government is carrying out a leak inquiry into reports that a BBC journalist received access to a Market Access Assessment in November 2017.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131987","131987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860631","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department plans to comply with the recommendation by the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse's Child Migration Programmes Report that a government scheme for compensation to former child migrants should be established without delay and operational within 12 months.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131988","131988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860632","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to adopt the recommendation by the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse's Child Migration Programmes Report that a Government scheme for compensation to former child migrants should apply to all former child migrants covered by previous Child Migration Programmes.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131989","131989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860633","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to respond to the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse's Child Migration Programmes Report.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131990","131990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860634","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to adopt the recommendation on page 150 of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse's Child Migration Programmes Report, published in March 2018, that no regard be had to any other payments of compensation that have been made in particular cases to former child migrants by previous Child Migration Programmes.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131991","131991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860635","2018-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings of the (a) National Audit Office Investigation report entitled National Lottery funding for good causes, published in December 2017 and (b) Gambling Commission report entitled Gambling participation in 2017, published in February 2018.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131992","131992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860636","2018-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, on how many occasions he or Ministers or staff of his Department met with Camelot representatives since March 2016; and how many of those meetings dealt with the Consultation on Prohibiting Third Party Betting on the Outcome of non-UK EuroMillions.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131993","131993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860637","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the terms that new non-TUPE members of staff were employed on by wholly-owned subsidiaries of NHS trusts in the 2016-17 financial year.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131994","131994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860638","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the access to standard NHS pension arrangements that new non-TUPE staff were granted by wholly-owned subsidiaries of NHS trusts in the 2016-17 financial year.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131995","131995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860639","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has had with employers who use agency contracts on access to bereavement or compassionate leave.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131996","131996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860640","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect on the level of workers' rights of people being employed on agency contracts.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131997","131997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860641","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of people who have been employed as agency workers for (a) less than one year, (b) between one and two years and (c) more than two years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131998","131998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860642","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has provided to NHS trusts on the future hiring of new non-TUPE staff on contracts with their wholly-owned subsidiary companies.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131999","131999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860643","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many new non-TUPE members of staff were hired directly by wholly-owned subsidiaries of NHS trusts in the 2016-17 financial year.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132000","132000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860644","2018-03-14","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) mobile phones and (b) other electronic devices had data extracted from them using (i) self-service kiosks and (ii) and regional hubs by each UK police force in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132001","132001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860645","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which companies have had catering contracts with his Department and its agencies from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132002","132002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860646","2018-03-14","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK police forces have written procedures, regulations or guidelines in place governing the use of mobile phone extraction tools.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132003","132003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860647","2018-03-14","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has received representations on the deletion of mobile phone data extracted from suspects released without charge; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132004","132004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860648","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students taking architecture subjects at degree-level were from (a) the UK, (b) non-UK EU countries and (c) non-EU countries in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132005","132005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860649","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS (a) trusts and (b) foundation trusts made a loss on the treatment of private patients in (i) all and (ii) some of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132006","132006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860650","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much debt was written off by NHS (a) trusts and (b) foundation trusts in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available; and what proportion of that debt related to the treatment of private patients.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132007","132007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860651","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much the NHS received in income from private patients in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132008","132008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860652","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much NHS trusts and foundation trusts paid in clinical negligence compensation to private patients in the last financial year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132009","132009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860653","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has a policy on the price that NHS trusts and foundation trusts are permitted to charge for procedures on private patients; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132010","132010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860654","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have applied to work in a job on the restricted occupation list after waiting over 12 months for their asylum application to be processed; and how many of these applications were granted, in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132011","132011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860655","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS trusts and foundation trusts are able to charge private patients prices that are lower than those set out in the national tariff.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132012","132012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860656","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to increase the level of NHS funding generated by the treatment of private patients.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132013","132013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860657","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS beds are reserved for the use of private patients.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132014","132014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860658","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what (a) profit and (b) loss Frimley Health NHS Foundation Trust made from treating private patients in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132015","132015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860659","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what safeguards his Department puts in place to ensure that NHS patients are not adversely affected by the treatment of private patients in NHS trusts and foundation trusts.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132016","132016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860660","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2018 to Question 129169, on NHS: Loans, which 10 NHS trusts received the highest level of new loans in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132017","132017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860661","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2018 to Question 129169, on NHS: Loans, which 10 NHS trusts had the highest loan balances in 2016-17.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132018","132018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860662","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2018 to Question 129169, on NHS: Loans, which 10 NHS trusts made the highest level of loan repayments in 2016-17.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132019","132019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860663","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of NHS trust (a) Chairs and (b) Chief Executives are women.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132020","132020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860664","2018-03-14","Department for Transport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many UK and Northern Ireland registered fishing vessels are owned by international or European companies in (a) England, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132021","132021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860665","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much the GovernorLine service cost his Department to operate in each of the last five years; and how many people have used that service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132022","132022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860666","2018-03-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what limit has been placed on the number of fixed-odds betting terminals which can be situated in work-place staff canteens.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132023","132023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860667","2018-03-14","Department for Transport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the partnership comprising Arup, SNC-Lavalin Transport Advisory (InterFleet) and EY to provide services to support him with his duties as operator of last resort, was extended when the original two year contract expired in November 2017.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132024","132024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860668","2018-03-14","Department for Transport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Directly Operated Railways has a valid safety certificate under the Railways and Other Guided Transport Systems (Safety) Regulations 2006 and is authorised to work on rail infrastructure, to run trains and to manage stations.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132025","132025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860669","2018-03-14","Department for Transport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place an updated copy of the contracted franchise payment profiles for all train operating companies in the Library.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132026","132026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860670","2018-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) male and (b) female people ordinarily resident in Wales served custodial sentences in England in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132027","132027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860671","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what contingency plans his Department (a) has agreed on and (b) are working on to ensure that the UK's food supply is not affected when the UK exits the EU.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132028","132028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860672","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2018 to Question 130466, Childline: Finance, how much funding his Department has provided to the NSPCC's Childline in each year since the inception of that service.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132029","132029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860673","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2018 to Question 130467, on Childline: Finance, when his Department plans to respond to the NSPCC's Are You There campaign.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132030","132030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860674","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) address the risk of and (b) treat diabetes in people from a Pakistani background living in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132031","132031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860675","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2018 to Question 130484, on Children: Refuges, whether his Department has plans to allocate departmental resources, in addition to those resources that are allocated by local authorities, to children who are resident in a women's refuge with a parent.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132032","132032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860676","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the use of online booking services for GP appointments on the ability of over 75 year olds to access GP care.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132033","132033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860677","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2018 to Question 130484, on Children: Refuges, whether his Department has undertaken any cross-departmental projects with the Department for Housing, Communities and Local Government relating to children living in refuges with a parent.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132034","132034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860678","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to address diabetes and obesity in children.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132035","132035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860679","2018-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2018 to Question 130452, on Housing Benefit: Refuges, when his Department plans to respond to the feedback received through its short-term consultation which closed on 23 January 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132036","132036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860680","2018-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has plans to increase the accountability of coroners to the public; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132037","132037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860681","2018-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has plans to make changes to the system of complaints on the conduct of coroners; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132038","132038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860682","2018-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has plans to make coroners subject to freedom of information requests; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132039","132039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860683","2018-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has plans to change the remit of the Chief Coroner; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132040","132040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860684","2018-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to place a statutory duty on care homes to install fire sprinklers.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132041","132041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860685","2018-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the agenda for the UK UAE Taskforce meeting in London in February 2018 was; who attended that meeting, how long that meeting lasted; and where that meeting was held.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132042","132042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860686","2018-03-14","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) birth and (b) adoptive children with parents who are British citizens have been denied entry to the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132043","132043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860687","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure that all men over 50 year of age have access to prostate tests even when they have no symptoms of prostate cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132044","132044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860688","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police detentions there have been under section 130 of the Mental Health Act 1983 in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132045","132045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860689","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with facial paralysis in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132046","132046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860690","2018-03-14","Treasury","2018-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many firms claimed video games tax relief in each year since its introduction.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132047","132047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860691","2018-03-14","Treasury","2018-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of video games tax relief on (a) employment and b) investment in the video games sector.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132048","132048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860692","2018-03-14","Treasury","2018-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) small and (b) large firms have claimed research and development tax relief in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132049","132049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860693","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment on the effect of the changes to the eligibility of free school meals under universal credit and on child poverty in the North East of England.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132050","132050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860694","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the test for esophageal cancer to be made available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132051","132051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860695","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2018 to Question 128522, how many childcare providers in (a) the North East and (b) England (i) are and (ii) are not offering 30 hours free childcare without extra cost to parents that are eligible for that scheme.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132052","132052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860696","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of funding available to the Welsh agricultural sector came from (a) the UK Government (b) the European Union and (c) other sources in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132053","132053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860697","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with bipolar disorder in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132054","132054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860698","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2018 to Question 130615, when the review of the effect of debt and financial difficulties on people with mental health problems will be (a) completed and (b) published.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132055","132055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860699","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2018 to Question 129636 when the National Service Review of all Children and Young People’s Mental Health Tier 4 services will be (a) completed and (b) published.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132056","132056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860700","2018-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pension, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Glasgow North of 13 December 2017 on his constituent's employment and support allowance application and concerns about a lack of consideration given to mental health and autistic spectrum medical conditions.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132057","132057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860701","2018-03-14","Department for Transport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with Southeastern on its compliance in delivering a minimum train length at all times on the Hastings Line, Paddock Wood Line and Maidstone East Line.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132058","132058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860702","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the net change in in-patient mental health beds has been in (a) Newcastle and (b) the North East of England since 2010.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132059","132059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860703","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to  include blood cancer in the cancer dashboard.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132060","132060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860704","2018-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will implement the recommendations of Lord Lloyd’s report entitled Independent Public Enquiry into Gulf War Illnesses, published in November 2004.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132061","132061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860705","2018-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he last assessed the findings the Lord Lloyd’s report entitled Independent Public Enquiry into Gulf War Illnesses, published in 2004.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132062","132062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860706","2018-03-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much money has been spent on promoting British tourism in (a) Europe, (b) Asia, (c) North America and (d) in total in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132063","132063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860707","2018-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will invest in research to improve recovery outcomes for veterans who have from Gulf War Syndrome.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132064","132064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860708","2018-03-14","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will list the independent studies commissioned by his Department on the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the devolved administrations.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132065","132065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860709","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the abduction of the university Student Council President at Birzeit University in the West Bank on 7 March.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132066","132066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860710","2018-03-14","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with mobile telephone operators on mobile data roaming charges after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132067","132067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860711","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the levels of (a) violence and (b) harassment towards Palestinian university (i) students and (ii) staff in the West Bank; and what recent assessment he has made of the effect of those levels on student education.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132068","132068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860712","2018-03-14","Department for International Trade","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the total amount of exports by (a) volume and (b) value to the Republic of Ireland were in the (i) pharmaceutical and (ii) chemicals sectors in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132069","132069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860713","2018-03-14","Department for International Trade","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the total amount of imports by (a) volume and (b) value from the Irish Republic were in the (i) pharmaceutical and (ii) chemicals sectors in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132070","132070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860714","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the protection of the right to education in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132071","132071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860715","2018-03-14","Department for International Development","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what aid the UK has given to the authorities in Papua New Guinea as a result of the recent earthquake.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132072","132072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860716","2018-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require 118 directory enquiries phone lines to (a) have an automated message stating the call charges prior to connecting and (b) provide customers an opportunity to terminate a call prior to being connected and charged.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132073","132073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860717","2018-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to (a) regulate the cost of calling 118 directory enquiries and (b) set a maximum price cap for each such call.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132074","132074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860718","2018-03-14","Cabinet Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of adults born in the UK to non-UK parents who are permanently living in the UK and who have not established UK citizenship.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132075","132075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860719","2018-03-14","Department for International Development","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support the UK Government has provided to help people affected by the 2017 floods and mudslides in Freetown, Sierra Leone.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132076","132076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860720","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Israeli counterpart on the new legislation passed by the Knesset on 7 March 2018 which allows the Israeli Minister of Interior to revoke the permanent residency status from Palestinian residents of Jerusalem; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132077","132077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860721","2018-03-14","Treasury","2018-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what restrictions are placed on the use of capital receipts gains from Departments' disposals of surplus property; and what guidance his Department provides to departments on the use of capital receipts gains from government disposals of surplus property.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132078","132078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860722","2018-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what restrictions are placed on the use of capital receipts gained from local authorities' disposals of surplus property through the One Public Estate programme; and what guidance his Department provides on the use of capital receipts gained from local authorities' disposals of surplus property through the One Public Estate programme.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132079","132079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860723","2018-03-14","Cabinet Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the total amount of capital receipts received by local authorities as a result of the One Public Estate programme; and if he will provide that same data by local authority area.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132080","132080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860724","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of mature students studying in higher education institutions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132081","132081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860725","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made on negotiations between NHS England and Vertex Pharmaceuticals on access to the drug Orkambi for people with cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132082","132082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860726","2018-03-14","Attorney General","2018-03-12","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132083","132083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860727","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people aged over 21 are (a) encouraged and (b) supported to access higher education in the UK.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132084","132084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860728","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132085","132085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860729","2018-03-14","Cabinet Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132086","132086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860730","2018-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132087","132087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860731","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupil exclusions have been recorded for the London Borough of Haringey in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132088","132088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860732","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the pupil exclusion rate is for (a) Haringey (b) London and (c) England.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132089","132089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860733","2018-03-15","Cabinet Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in the UK are self-employed; and what proportion that number is of (a) people in work and (b) the working age population.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132090","132090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860734","2018-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for Housing and Homelessness, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2018 to Question 127168, on refuges, when her Department plans to announce the allocation of the £1.1million top-up funding.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132091","132091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860735","2018-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of UK nationals who have been arrested for child sex offences overseas in the last five years; and in what countries such nationals have been arrested over that period.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132092","132092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860736","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2018, to Question 129771 in which local authority the 117 alternative provision academies and free schools are located; for which years between 2013 to 2017 those academies have been open; and whether those such academies are new schools or convert academies.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132093","132093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860737","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many instances of bullying have been recorded in the armed forces in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132094","132094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860738","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many instances of homophobic bullying have been recorded in the armed forces in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132095","132095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860739","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many instances of racially-motivated bullying have been recorded in the armed forces in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132096","132096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860740","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many instances of gender-related bullying have been recorded in the armed forces in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132097","132097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860741","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support local councils in developing improved support for carers across (a) Hull West and Hessle constituency and (b) the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132098","132098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860742","2018-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have voluntarily retired from (a) the Army, (b) the Navy and (c) the RAF in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132099","132099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860743","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care what proportion of patients referred to a multidisciplinary diagnostic centre have been (a) suspected of having blood cancer and (b) diagnosed with blood cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132100","132100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860744","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress is being made on reducing the diagnosis times and improving the eventual treatment for endometriosis.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132101","132101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860745","2018-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many apologies for administrative error have been issued by the Independent Case Examiner’s Office in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132102","132102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860746","2018-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints to the Independent Case Examiner’s Office has taken longer than 43 weeks to resolve since being accepted for examination in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132103","132103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860747","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people aged over 21 are encouraged and supported to access higher education.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132104","132104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860748","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many secondary schools in England offered GCSE Music in (a) 2010 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132105","132105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860749","2018-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints about the Independent Case Examiner’s Office have been referred to the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman’s Office in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132106","132106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860750","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Primary Schools in England did not employ a specialist music teacher in (a) 2010 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132107","132107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860751","2018-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant  to his Answer of 27 February to Question 129074, which person or body carries out the monitoring to which he refers; and whether the operator of the waste incineration site is told in advance of the proposed testing.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132108","132108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860752","2018-03-14","Department for International Trade","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 127970, what meetings he, or Ministers in his Department, have had with representatives from (a) Australia, (b) EU, (c) Canada and (d) the US on their trade remedies system.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132109","132109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860753","2018-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February to Question 129074, which person or body carries out the monitoring to which he refers; and whether the operator of the waste incineration site told in advance of the proposed testing.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132110","132110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860754","2018-03-14","Department for Transport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implication for his policies of the report by Oxford Economics on behalf of the Railway Industry Association, published in February 2018.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132111","132111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860755","2018-03-14","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what account the Government will take of the rail supply industry in future trade negotiations with EU and non-EU countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132112","132112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860756","2018-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress  his Department has made in taking forward the proposal to make Lead Local Flood Authorities a Statutory Consultee on planning applications on surface water drainage as consulted upon by his Department in 2014.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132113","132113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860757","2018-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in the Government of Hong Kong on the disqualification of lawmakers from the Legislative Council; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132114","132114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860758","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will enable schools to teach British Sign Language to GCSE level; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132115","132115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860759","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the closure of the Heritage Lottery Fund's Landscape Funding programme on his Department's work to implement the 25 Year Plan for the Environment.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132116","132116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860760","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the amount of funding that was available from the Heritage Lottery Fund for projects that promote biodiversity in 2015/16 and 2016/17.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132117","132117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860761","2018-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) opinion polling in 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132118","132118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860762","2018-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) opinion polling in 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132119","132119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860763","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the level of personal independence payment awards for (a) blind and (b) sight impaired applicants; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132120","132120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860764","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has issued guidance to NHS Property Services on charging clinical commissioning groups for void space in NHS Property Services' properties; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132121","132121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860765","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which Minister of his Department has responsibility for NHS Property Services.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132122","132122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860766","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress NHS Property Services is making on improvements to the NHS Estate in Crawley, Horsham and Mid Sussex constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132123","132123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860767","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the outcome of the review undertaken of the administration and operational effectiveness of NHS Property Services in (a) West Sussex, (b) Mid Sussex and (c) England.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132124","132124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860768","2018-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants  of Support for Mortgage Interest (SMI) received less than two months notice of the closure of SMI.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132125","132125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860769","2018-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the ending of Support for Mortgage Interest (SMI) on (a)  homeowners who are recipients of SMI and (b) mortgage lenders if claimants do not take up the Government loan scheme.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132126","132126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860770","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the state of freedom of religion and belief in Pakistan.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132127","132127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860771","2018-03-15","Department for International Development","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress her Department has made on assisting the Federal Government of Pakistan with drafting a new educational curriculum to ensure the removal of biased content and derogatory language toward religious minorities.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132128","132128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860772","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding has been allocated by his Department to prepare for the UK leaving the EU; and how much of that funding was approved after the issue of a Ministerial direction.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132129","132129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860773","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils at (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in Warrington have recieved free school meals in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132130","132130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860774","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding his Department allocated for preparation projects for the UK leaving the EU was approved in the Spring Supplementary Estimate; and how much of that funding was after the issuing of a Ministerial direction.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132131","132131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860775","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much money from the public purse his Department has spent on the introduction of a new national import control system for animals, animal products and high risk food and feed when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132132","132132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860776","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 131577 on Teachers: Training , what the timetable is for the feasibility study to be completed.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132133","132133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860777","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 02 February 2018 to Question 125731 on Children’s Centres: Standards, what criteria his Department plans to use to assess the quality of children’s centre provision.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132134","132134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860778","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) primary and (b) secondary school pupils in Warrington who will be eligible for free school meals after the introduction of changes to the threshold for free school meals under universal credit.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132135","132135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860779","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information on (a) labour rights and (b) access to advice and remedy is routinely provided to workers during modern slavery operations conducted by Immigration Enforcement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132136","132136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860780","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of illegal working were passed from the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority to Immigration Enforcement in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132137","132137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860781","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information on (a) labour rights and (b) access to advice and remedy is routinely provided to workers who (i) file a complaint with and (ii) are encountered during inspections conducted by HMRC National Living Wage enforcement teams.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132138","132138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860782","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many cases of migrants working undocumented were passed from his Department's national minimum wage team to Immigration Enforcement in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132139","132139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860783","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with a diagnosed mental illness have received benefit sanctions in Warrington North in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132140","132140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860784","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information on (a) labour rights and (b) access to advice and remedy is routinely provided to workers who (i) file a complaint with and (ii) are encountered during inspections conducted by the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132141","132141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860785","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many cases of migrants working undocumented were (a) found and closed and (b) passed from Acas to Immigration Enforcement in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132142","132142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860786","2018-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how his Department plans to use the Statements of Environmental Opportunity from National Character Area profiles to ensure the new environmental land management scheme enhances English landscapes.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132143","132143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860787","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether Acas is permitted to mediate for undocumented workers in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132144","132144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860788","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether Acas is permitted to mediate for workers who are working undocumented in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132145","132145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860789","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what funding has been provided from the public purse to Acas for its helpline in each of the last five years; and how many workers were assisted by Acas in that same period.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132146","132146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860790","2018-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take to help safeguard the future of smaller farms.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132147","132147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860791","2018-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of staff carrying out assessments for personal independence payments have received training in the assessment of mental health conditions and the effect of such conditions on applicants.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132148","132148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860792","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the budget of the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate is for 2018-19; and how many staff it plans to employ during that financial year.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132149","132149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860793","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many workers were assisted by the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132150","132150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860794","2018-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information on (a) labour rights and (b) access to advice and remedy is routinely provided to workers who (i) file a complaint with and (ii) are encountered during inspections conducted by the Health and Safety Executive.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132151","132151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860795","2018-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases of migrants working undocumented were passed from the Health and Safety Executive to Immigration Enforcement in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132152","132152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860796","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 4 December 2017 HCWS309 on Childcare update, what estimate he has made of the total number of two year olds that will be eligible for free childcare once (a) universal credit is fully rolled out and (b) the threshold proposed in that Written Statement is introduced.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132153","132153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860797","2018-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many claims by migrants working undocumented in the UK were taken up by employment tribunals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132154","132154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860798","2018-03-14","Women and Equalities","2018-03-12","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Equality Act 2010 so that women at work are not forced to wear footwear which is damaging to their long term health; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132155","132155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860799","2018-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employment tribunal cases have been brought under equalities legislation (a) in each year since tribunal fees of £1,200 were introduced and (b) in the year prior to the introduction of those fees.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132156","132156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860800","2018-03-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, (a) how many trips were made, (b)  how many nights were stayed, (c) how much was spent, for the purpose of visiting friends and relatives in each of the regions of England in 2017.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132157","132157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860801","2018-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons were involved in the pilot scheme on placing telephones and basic computers into prison cells.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132158","132158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860802","2018-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for each prison involved in the pilot scheme on placing telephones and basic computers into cells, (a) when those items were first put in place, (b) how long that scheme was scheduled to last and (c) when that scheme ended.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132159","132159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860803","2018-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent from the public purse on the pilot scheme on placing telephones and basic computers into prison cells by prison involved in that scheme; and for each prison on what was that money spent.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132160","132160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860804","2018-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data was collected to monitor performance during the pilot scheme on placing telephones and basic computers into prison cells.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132161","132161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860805","2018-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the public purse has been of the pilot scheme on placing telephones and basic computers in prison cells to date.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132162","132162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860806","2018-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the pilot scheme on placing telephones and basic computers into prison cells.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132163","132163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860807","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to expand work experience opportunities for secondary school students from deprived communities.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132164","132164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860808","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Modern Slavery and Implementation Group last met; and what the date is  of its next planned meeting.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132165","132165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860809","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department holds information on the recent incident in Shahdara, Lahore where an allegation of blasphemy was made against a young Christian called Patras Masih; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132166","132166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860810","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department holds information on allegations that the Pubjab Police did not protect Patras Masih from attack by Labaik Ya Rasool Allah party extremists in Shahdara, Lahore on 19 February 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132167","132167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860811","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department holds information on allegations of violence by officers of the Federal Investigation Agency against Patras Masih and his cousin Sajid Masih in Lahore on 23 February 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132168","132168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860812","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department holds information on allegations of coercion by officers of the Federal Investigation Agency towards Sajid Masih to perform a perverse sexual act on his cousin Patras Masih; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132169","132169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860813","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of whether the inquiry proposed by the Government of Pakistan into the conduct of Federal Investigation Agency officers by other officers of that Agency would be sufficiently independent; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132170","132170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860814","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that devolution of the Adult Education Budget does not have a deleterious effect on adult education provision (a) generally and (b) with regard to the role of national providers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132171","132171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860815","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether any adult education providers will retain national contracts with the Education and Skills Funding once the Adult Education Budget is devolved.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132172","132172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860816","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to put in place support to providers who currently have national contracts with the Education and Skills Funding Agency during the transition period of the devolution of the Adult Education Budget; and whether his Department will make funding available for adult education providers during the transition period of the devolution of the Adult Education Budget in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132173","132173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860817","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what arrangements he plans to put in place to support community-based education provision in areas which are outside mayoral combined authorities where the Adult Education Budget is to be devolved.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132174","132174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860818","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations his Department received from providers who have national contracts with the Education and Skills Funding Agency and who will be affected by the devolution of the Adult Education Budget.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132175","132175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860819","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what arrangements the Government plans to put in place from 2018-19 to support adult education providers which operate both in Mayoral Combined Authority areas and also in areas which do not have a devolution deal.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132176","132176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858516","2018-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential benefits of using blockchain technology to store information on (a) food safety and (b) animal welfare; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131771","131771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858517","2018-03-14","Department for International Trade","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many and what proportion of his Department’s cloud hosting contracts have been awarded to (a) hyperscale cloud providers and (b) UK SMEs, and what the value was of those contracts in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131772","131772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858518","2018-03-13","Home Office","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the oral contribution of the hon. Member for Tottenham on 6 March 2018, column 187, Yarl's Wood Detention Centre, for what reason the question on human rights obligations was not answered.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131773","131773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858519","2018-03-14","Treasury","2018-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much compensation has been paid (a) in total, (b) on average for individual claims and (c) to what number of people for failings of the Childcare Service website.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131774","131774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858520","2018-03-14","Home Office","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions took place at the EU Justice and Home Affairs Council of Ministers on 8 and 9 March in Brussels on the Schengen Information System II.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131775","131775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858521","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department has allocated to apprenticeships in each year since 2015; and how much such funding his Department allocated by region.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131776","131776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858522","2018-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cases there were of pulmonary arterial hypertension in England in each of the last 3 years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131777","131777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858523","2018-03-13","Treasury","2018-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was paid out in Lifetime Allowance charges in each year between 2010-2011 to 2017-2018; and what estimate he has made of the amount to be paid in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2019-2020 and (c) 2010-21.","Biography information for Robert Courts","Robert Courts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131778","131778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858524","2018-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which body is responsible for commissioning treatments and services for patients with pulmonary hypertension.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131779","131779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858525","2018-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to decrease the average length of time that it takes to diagnose pulmonary arterial hypertension.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131780","131780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858526","2018-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many clinical commissioning groups offer pulmonary rehabilitation services for patients with pulmonary arterial hypertension.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131781","131781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858527","2018-03-14","Northern Ireland Office","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what her policy is on equal direct access to abortion services for women in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131782","131782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858528","2018-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the European Commission on retaining EU citizenship for UK citizens after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131783","131783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858529","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report of the NCT on The Hidden Half, Bringing postnatal mental illness out of hiding, published in June 2017, what steps his Department is taking to identify post-natal mental health in women.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131784","131784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858530","2018-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the European Commission on associate European citizenship.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131785","131785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858531","2018-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the European Union on retaining EU citizenship for UK citizens in the event that UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131786","131786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858532","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils were entitled to free school meals in (a) Leeds North West Constituency and (b) England in each of the last ten years for which information is available.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131787","131787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858533","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an estimate of the number pupils that will be entitled to free school meals in Leeds North West constituency as a result of his Department's proposals to change the threshold for eligibility for  free school meals eligibility under universal credit.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131788","131788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858534","2018-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps he is taking to ensure that the protection of UK citizen's personal data under EU Charter of Fundamental Rights is maintained after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131789","131789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858535","2018-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether steps he has taken to safeguard deposit payments for licensees who have signed up for property guardianship schemes.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131790","131790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858536","2018-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has to maintain the rights of victims of crime under the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131791","131791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858537","2018-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has to maintain provisions of the Charter of Fundamental Rights in relation to the prevention and combating of trafficking in human beings after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131792","131792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858538","2018-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has to maintain protections in relation to equal pay set out in the Charter of Fundamental Rights after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131793","131793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858539","2018-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has to ensure the maintenance of protections from discrimination in employment on grounds of religion or belief in the Charter of Fundamental Rights after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131794","131794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858540","2018-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has to ensure that the protections from discrimination on the grounds of sexual orientation will be maintained to the standard set out in the Charter of Fundamental Rights.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131795","131795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858541","2018-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has to ensure that the protections from discrimination on the grounds of age will be maintained to the standard set out in the Charter of Fundamental Rights.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131796","131796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858542","2018-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the Government’s policy is on associate EU citizenship for UK nationals in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131797","131797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858543","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's guidance, 30 hours delivery support fund: revenue funding allocations for 2017 to 2018, if he will publish the methodology used to calculate those allocations.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131798","131798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858544","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2018 to Question 125657, whether the £398,250.00 allocated for local authorities in his Department's guidance, 30 hours delivery support fund: grants for local authorities for 2017-18 is the total amount that will be allocated in that time period.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131799","131799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858545","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons fewer than a third of local authorities received a grant from the 2017-2018 delivery support fund; and if he will publish the criteria by which his Department judged whether such a grant would be allocated to successful applicants.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131800","131800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858546","2018-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to implement the proposals resulting from the 2016 Review of the Corporate Insolvency Framework consultation.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131801","131801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858547","2018-03-13","Cabinet Office","2018-03-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2018 to Question 129524 on departmental coordination, whether his Department has targets for the (a) proportion of processes to be converged and (b) timescale for completing that convergent shared service provision.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131802","131802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858548","2018-03-13","Department for Education","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his Answer of 6 March to  Question 129597 on Unemployment: Young People, how many and what proportion of pupils who were (a) eligible for free school meals, (b) not eligible for free school meals, who were (i) included in the Children in Need census, (ii) not included in the Children in Need census, were not in education, employment or training for the whole of academic year 2013-14, three years after finishing key stage 4, in each ethnic group.","Biography information for Alex Burghart","Alex Burghart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131803","131803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858549","2018-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to respond to the letter of the 9 January 2018 from the hon Member for Dewsbury on visiting health care services in Dewsbury constituency.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131804","131804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858550","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding each local authority has received from the 30 hours delivery support fund for the Summer 2018 term.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131805","131805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858551","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what powers the Education Skills Funding Agency have to compulsory purchase land from local authorities for free schools.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131806","131806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858552","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what powers the Education Skills Funding Agency has to compulsory purchase land from private land owners for free school sites.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131807","131807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858553","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Education Skills Funding Agency is required to consult local communities on plans for a new free school before planning permission is sought.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131808","131808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858554","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether people in local communities have the right to object to plans for the establishment of a free school in their area.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131809","131809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858555","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether people in local communities have a statutory right to challenge the purchase of (a) community assets and (b) other community land for the location of free schools.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131810","131810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858556","2018-03-14","Department for Education","2018-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the answer of 8 March 2018 to Question 131079 on Children's Centres, if he will publish the evidence his  Department gathered on children's centres.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131811","131811"
