"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894838","2018-05-02","Treasury","2018-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 April 2018 to Question 136770, on Taxation: Domicil, for what reason the latest figures available are over three yeas old.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139344","139344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894839","2018-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he will publish the (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 versions of the National Atmospheric Emissions Inventory.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139358","139358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894840","2018-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases undertaken by the Financial Investigation Unit have resulted in a financial uplift in payments to resident parents through the Child Maintenance Service in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139533","139533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894841","2018-05-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much housing benefit was claimed in Coventry South constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139381","139381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894842","2018-05-02","Department for Transport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department has allocated to the introduction of autonomous vehicles onto UK roads.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139539","139539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894843","2018-05-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pensioners in Coventry South constituency (a) receive the basic state pension, (b) receive pension credit and (c) are eligible for pension credit but do not claim it.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139382","139382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894844","2018-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much financial assistance was provided by the Government to the organisation Syria Civil Defence in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139383","139383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894845","2018-05-03","Department for International Trade","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what was the value is of UK arms sales to Saudi Arabia since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139384","139384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894846","2018-05-02","Department for International Development","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State of 18 April 2018, Official Report, column 305, if she will publish her Department's policy on orphanages.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139390","139390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894847","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the effect of period poverty on girls in schools.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139369","139369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894848","2018-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of women who are unable to afford sanitary products.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139370","139370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894850","2018-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of dogs with canine distemper; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce incidences of that disease.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139371","139371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894851","2018-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department has issued on the inspection of dogs for distemper on arrival in the UK.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139372","139372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894852","2018-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations he has received from Police and Crime Commissioners on the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals for an offence of attacking service animals.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139373","139373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894853","2018-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to respond to the recommendations in the Trussell Trust report, Is universal credit truly universal?, on foodbank use; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139374","139374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894854","2018-05-03","Treasury","2018-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claims have been made under the non-consensual conception exemption for child tax credit in the Motherwell and Wishaw constituency.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139532","139532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894855","2018-05-03","Home Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress his Department has made on resettling 20,000 Syrian refugees in the UK under the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Resettlement programme by 2020.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139385","139385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894856","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to undertake a review of the cost of call charges to the Healthy Start voucher helpline.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139530","139530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894857","2018-05-02","House of Commons Commission","2018-04-30","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what the reasons are for the introduction in October 2018 of a new system of Members' tours of the Palace of Westminster.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139393","139393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894858","2018-05-02","House of Commons Commission","2018-04-30","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many in-house guides excluding Blue Badge Guides are planned to lose their jobs when the new system of Members' tours of the House is introduced in October 2018.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139394","139394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894859","2018-05-02","House of Commons Commission","2018-04-30","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what training the Commission plans to provide for the new guides for Members' tours to ensure that the level of current expertise and knowledge is maintained.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139395","139395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894860","2018-05-02","House of Commons Commission","2018-04-30","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what qualifications are required for the new guides who will be responsible for Members' tours.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139396","139396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894861","2018-05-02","House of Commons Commission","2018-04-30","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what estimate the Commission has made of the potential (a) cost of and (b) savings from introducing the new system of Members' tours.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139397","139397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894862","2018-05-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to promote the health benefits of eating more fish and incorporating the principles of the Seafood 2040 Strategy into the NHS, care homes, nursing homes and home care.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139534","139534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894863","2018-05-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to support fishing and fish processing communities as part of the Seafood 2040 Strategy.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139535","139535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894864","2018-05-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the future of the UK's involvement in the Galileo programme.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139510","139510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894865","2018-05-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to support the fish supply chain as part of the Seafood 2040 Strategy.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139536","139536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894867","2018-05-03","Department for Transport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to support logistics and transportation infrastructure around fish landing ports as part of the Seafood 2040 Strategy.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139537","139537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894868","2018-05-03","Women and Equalities","2018-04-30","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she plans to implement the dual discrimination provisions set out in s14 of the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139538","139538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894869","2018-05-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will set out the timetable for extending the public lending right to e-book loans.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139413","139413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894870","2018-05-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when his Department plans to publish its response to the consultation on the extension of the public lending right to e-book loans.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139414","139414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894871","2018-05-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support GPs provide to mothers experiencing perinatal mental health problems.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139511","139511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894872","2018-05-03","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions his Department has had with Mayoral Combined Authorities (MCA) on devolving adult education budgets; and what criteria will be used to determine the size of the budget that will be devolved to individual MCAs.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139493","139493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894873","2018-05-03","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to encourage more SMEs in (a) England and (b) Barnsley to take on apprentices.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139494","139494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894874","2018-05-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to bring apprenticeship wages into line with national minimum wage rates for their age group.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139495","139495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894875","2018-05-03","Home Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will introduce legislative proposals to ensure the right of the Windrush generation to remain in the UK.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139609","139609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894876","2018-05-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants on the Youth Obligation offer since April 2017 have moved into employment lasting over six months.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139346","139346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894877","2018-05-03","Department for Transport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the automotive industry on the development of the road to zero strategy.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139504","139504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894878","2018-05-03","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to improve the educational outcomes of vulnerable 16 and 17-year-olds.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139347","139347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894879","2018-05-03","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the quality of educational support provided to 16 and 17-year-olds in need of help or protection.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139348","139348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894880","2018-05-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 27 April 2018 to Question 137389, when she plans for the first performance data from the Work and Health Programme to be published.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139349","139349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894881","2018-05-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the cost of non-domestic renewable heat incentive subsidies was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139521","139521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894882","2018-05-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what circumstances a jobseeker participating in the Work and Health Programme can be made subject to a sanction.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139350","139350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894883","2018-05-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of the total biomass used to produce energy in the last year came from (a) domestically sourced wood and (b) imported wood.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139522","139522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894884","2018-05-03","Department for International Trade","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 26 April 2018 to Question 137004 on Legatum Institute,  between what the purpose was of the meetings between Antonia Romeo and the Legatum Institute between 16 October 2017 and 8 December 2017; whether (a) notes and (b) documentation pertaining to those meetings were (i) produced and (ii) circulated to (A) Ministers and (B) officials in her Department; and whether the Legatum Institute made any proposals on Department or Government policy at those meetings.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139377","139377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894885","2018-05-03","Department for International Development","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking with (a) the UN (b) the UN Office for the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs and (c) other international partners to support displaced people in Afrin, Syria; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139351","139351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894886","2018-05-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made on the effect of the roll-out of universal credit on trends in the level of rent arrears in (a) the Enfield North constituency (b) the London Borough of Enfield and (c) London.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139352","139352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894887","2018-05-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has set a target for the net number of prison officers to be employed in the prison service in the next (a) 12 months and (b) three years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139558","139558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894888","2018-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons and to which prisons his Department has issued improvement orders in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139559","139559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894889","2018-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many improvement orders his Department has issued to each prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139560","139560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894890","2018-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many improvement orders his Department has issued to prisons in each year since 2010; and for what reason each order was issued.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139561","139561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894891","2018-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons have outstanding improvement orders.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139562","139562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894892","2018-05-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers who took voluntary early departure have been re-recruited by HM Prison Service in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139563","139563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894893","2018-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers have taken voluntary early departure in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139564","139564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894894","2018-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average severance package was for a prison officer taking voluntary early departure in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139565","139565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894895","2018-05-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the severance package was for each prison officer who took voluntary early departure and was subsequently re-recruited by HM Prison and Probation Service in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139566","139566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894896","2018-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the value was of severance packages for prison officers that took voluntary early departure and were subsequently re-recruited since after 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139567","139567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894897","2018-05-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the (a) the Secretary of State for Wales and (b) Welsh Government on the design and implementation of the UK Shared Prosperity Fund after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139401","139401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894898","2018-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of making it obligatory for manufacturers to include oxo biodegradation additives in everyday plastic items.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139578","139578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894899","2018-05-03","Department for International Trade","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many applications UK Export Finance has received from (a) Leonardo, (b) Agusta Westland and (c) Selex in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139591","139591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894900","2018-05-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of animal rescue homes in England.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139607","139607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894901","2018-05-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 April to Question 904960 on Animal Welfare, how many animal rescue homes are members of the Association of Dogs and Cats Homes.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139608","139608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894902","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report of the National Childbirth Trust,  The Hidden Half: Bringing postnatal mental illness out of hiding, published in June 2017 and NICE guidance, Postnatal care up to 8 weeks after birth, last updated in February 2015, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all new mothers are asked about their mental health by a GP at six to eights weeks postnatally.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139547","139547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894903","2018-05-03","Department for Transport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effect on community transport services in each parliamentary constituency of the proposals in the Consultation on the use of section 19 and section 22 permits for road passenger transport in Great Britain, published in February 2018.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139461","139461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894904","2018-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of trends in the level of child poverty in London.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139548","139548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894905","2018-05-03","Home Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that doctors from India that have received job offers to work in the NHS are given visas.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139579","139579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894906","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 April 2018 to Question 135864 on Disabled Students' Allowances, what assessment his Department has made of of trends in the level of reliance of disabled students’ on assistive technology.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139378","139378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894907","2018-05-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union on maintaining the single electricity market with the Republic of Ireland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139402","139402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894908","2018-05-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Irish Government on maintaining the single electricity market after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139403","139403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894909","2018-05-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on maintaining the single electricity market with the Republic of Ireland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139404","139404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894910","2018-05-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the potential tariffs that will fall on the UK when importing electricity from the Republic of Ireland in the event that the UK leaves the Single Market and Customs Union.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139405","139405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894911","2018-05-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of levels of energy (a) security and (b) availability in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139406","139406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894912","2018-05-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cases of neonatal herpes there has been in the last three years; and how many of those cases resulted in a death.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139592","139592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894913","2018-05-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU single market and Customs Union on the energy interconnector between the UK and Ireland.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139407","139407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894914","2018-05-02","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with the EU on maintaining membership of the EU’s Internal Energy Market after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139408","139408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894915","2018-05-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will publish the timetable for for introducing Public Lending Right to e-book loans.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139410","139410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894916","2018-05-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of designating neonatal herpes as a notifiable disease.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139593","139593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894917","2018-05-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what his policy is on bringing forward legislative proposals to extend public lending rights to e-book loans.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139411","139411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894918","2018-05-03","Department for Transport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has plans to widen the A1M  between Stevenage and Welwyn.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139448","139448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894919","2018-05-03","Department for Transport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing legislative proposals to issue fines for motorists who park cars on pavements.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139449","139449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894920","2018-05-02","Wales Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the effect of the UK leaving the EU Single Market and Customs Union on the East-West Interconnector.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139409","139409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894921","2018-05-03","Home Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that EU citizens making immigration or residency applications will be able to confirm that their relevant data and documentation is still on file with his Department after June 2021.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139353","139353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894922","2018-05-03","Home Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the total number of additional contact staff his Department will employ to answer EU citizens’ immigration and residence queries.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139354","139354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894923","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has his Department made of the effect of removing the Patient Reported Outcome Measure on hernia repair on the commissioning policies used by Clinical Commissioning Groups.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139583","139583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894924","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  how many inguinal hernia repair procedures has NHS undertaken in each Clinical Commissioning Group in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139584","139584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894925","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance NHS England has issued to Clinical Commissioning Groups for the development of commissioning policies for inguinal hernia repair.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139585","139585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894926","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what criteria is used by Clinical Commissioning Groups to determine commissioning policies for inguinal hernia repair.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139586","139586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894927","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of the recommendation made by Hernia Outcomes Campaign on the introduction of a watchful waiting policy for inguinal hernia surgery in that organisations report, Inguinal Hernia Surgery: Improving Patient Outcomes and Reducing Variation, published in November 2017.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139587","139587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894928","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, in what form will patient outcomes for inguinal hernia patients be recorded as a result of the decision by NHS England to discontinue the patient reported outcome measure for that treatment.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139588","139588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894929","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will respond to the recommendations made in the Hernia Outcomes Campaign’s report, Inguinal Hernia Surgery: Improving Patient Outcomes and Reducing Variation published in November 2017, and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139589","139589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894930","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients underwent inguinal hernia surgery in each region of England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139590","139590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894931","2018-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has conducted an economic impact study on the effect of clean air zones on businesses in (a) Birmingham and (b) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139379","139379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894932","2018-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with small and medium-sized businesses in (a) Birmingham and (b) the West Midlands about the financial effect of proposed clean air zones and associated air quality measures on their businesses.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139380","139380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894933","2018-05-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the levels of bovine tuberculosis in West Sussex.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139342","139342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894934","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has plans to allocate funding for the celebration of Gypsy, Roma and Traveller History Month in schools.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139478","139478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894935","2018-05-03","Department for Transport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons Mobile Batching Concrete Plants are not entitled to operate outside of standard legal gross vehicle weight limits.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139450","139450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894936","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will assess the potential merits of recommending adding to the school curriculum financial education which includes advice on filling out tax forms.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139452","139452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894937","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to tackle educational underachievement in working class areas.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139453","139453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894938","2018-05-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding was allocated from the public purse to museums in 2017-18.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139454","139454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894939","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure greater awareness among parents of the symptoms of autism in children.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139455","139455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894940","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients were referred to a mental health professional on the NHS in 2017.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139456","139456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894941","2018-05-02","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many staff were employed in her Department as of 1 May 2018.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139457","139457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894943","2018-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has a role in tackling credit and debit card fraud; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139459","139459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894944","2018-05-03","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department’s press release, Multi-million fund to boost children's early language skills, published on  30 April 2018, how his Department plans to assess the success of the £5 million scheme run by the Education Endowment Foundation; and whether his Department plans to roll out nationally successful elements of that scheme.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139506","139506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894945","2018-05-03","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department’s press release, Multi-million fund to boost children's early language skills, published on  30 April 2018, what estimate he has made of the number of children who will benefit from the £5 million funding to improve children’s language skills.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139507","139507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894946","2018-05-03","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department’s press release, Multi-million fund to boost children's early language skills, published on 30 April 2018, which areas in the north of England will benefit from the £5 million in funding to be distributed by the Education Endowment Foundation.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139508","139508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894947","2018-05-03","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department’s press release, Multi-million fund to boost children's early language skills, published on 30 April 2018, which local authorities in England will receive funding through the Early Years Social Mobility Peer Review Programme.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139509","139509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894948","2018-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what number and proportion of Gypsies and Travellers undertook a vocational training course whilst in prison for each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139479","139479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894949","2018-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to Italian authorities on safety plans for travelling supporters for the Roma v Liverpool Champions League semi-final second leg in Rome on Wednesday 2 May; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139602","139602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894950","2018-05-03","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 26 April 2018 to Question 136870, on Defence Science and Technology Laboratory: Finance, what estimate he has made of the expected annual running costs of the Chemical Weapons Defence Centre; and whether any additional funding has been allocated for this purpose to the Defence Science and Technology Laboratory for the financial year 2021-22.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139580","139580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894951","2018-05-03","Department for Transport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of existing legislation in ensuring coaches are fitted with tyres and wheels that are safe and do not expose passengers to undue risk of harm.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139398","139398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894952","2018-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to reduce the number of incidents of (a) discrimination and (b) harassment within his Department.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139581","139581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894953","2018-05-03","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent steps has he taken to improve the morale of staff within his Department.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139582","139582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894954","2018-05-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the amount of sick leave taken by staff in his Department due to mental health causes in the last two years for which data is available.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139527","139527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894955","2018-05-03","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the All-Party Parliamentary Group for Education entitled How well do schools prepare children for their future, published in May 2017, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the recommendation that his Department should investigate ways to further professionalise the careers guidance sector.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139471","139471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894956","2018-05-03","Home Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to figure 2 of the Serious Violence Strategy, published in April 2018, if he will publish the figures for (a) homicide, (b) firearms offences and (c) knife crime in each year for which figures are available from 1997-8.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139540","139540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894957","2018-05-02","Department for International Development","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to fund the 2018 Occupied Palestinian Territory Humanitarian Fund administered by the United Nations Office for the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139375","139375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894958","2018-05-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to The Government’s revised mandate to NHS England for 2017-18, what steps he is taking to support NHS England to achieve the goal of a measurable reduction in variation in the management and care for people with diabetes.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139363","139363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894959","2018-05-02","Department for International Development","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 26 April to Question 137118, on Israel: Palestinians, whether any of the organisations she held direct conversations with were (a) Palestinian or (b) groups operating in (i) the West Bank or (ii) Gaza.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139376","139376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894960","2018-05-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the bio-security protocols are for the transport of live animals from TB hot spot to non-hot spot areas.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139343","139343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894961","2018-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how the Government plans to ensure that the four countries of the UK have a coherent approach to cross border environmental issues after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139424","139424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894962","2018-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is reduce the risks of helium balloons and sky lanterns to livestock keepers and the wider agricultural community.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139345","139345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894963","2018-05-03","Department for International Development","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help protect civilians caught up in the Syrian conflict since the UK air strikes of 14 April in that country.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139480","139480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894964","2018-05-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people under the age of 18 have a diagnosis of dementia in (a) England and (b) the North East.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139481","139481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894965","2018-05-03","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the apprenticeship levy in increasing the (a) number and (b) quality of apprenticeships in England since the implementation of that levy.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139482","139482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894966","2018-05-03","Department for International Trade","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 136006, on Legatum Institute, if he will list the meetings and discussions that officials of his Department have had with the Legatum Institute, and what the outcomes of those discussions were.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139483","139483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894967","2018-05-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of housing association properties that are rented at a level above the Government's definition of affordable.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139520","139520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894968","2018-05-08","House of Commons Commission","2018-04-30","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many kilogrammes of food Parliament has discarded in (a) the last week and (b) the last month for which data are available.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139399","139399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894969","2018-05-09","House of Commons Commission","2018-04-30","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what steps the Commission is taking to reduce food waste in Parliament.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139400","139400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894970","2018-05-03","Home Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of the 30 April 2018 to Question 138075, on Biometrics, how the Government plans to improve the independent oversight and the governance of police use of automated facial recognition software.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139541","139541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894971","2018-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution by the  further to the remarks of the Minister for Europe and the Americas on 20 February 2018, Official Report, column 13, how many sq km of sea around the UK Overseas Territories are subject to marine protection.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139445","139445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894972","2018-05-02","Department for Transport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2018 to Question 137533, which (a) training providers and (b) other organisations are licensed by the Maritime and Coastguard Agency to issue those four basic Standards in Training, Certification and Watchkeeping qualifications listed.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139462","139462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894973","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much his Department plans to allocate to the Ending Gang Violence and Exploitation fund in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139542","139542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894974","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much his Department plans to allocate to funding for Young Peoples Advocates in (a) 2018-19 and (b)  2019-20.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139543","139543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894975","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are being taken to improve training for health service professionals dealing with cases of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139418","139418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894976","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much money his Department plans to allocate to (a) future knife crime media campaigns, (b) new local and regional reviews, (c) the test purchase prosecution fund, (d) support for interventions with vulnerable groups, (e) work on police testing kits in respect of corrosive substances, (f) a thematic inspection of police forces in respect of county lines and (g) preventative measures in respect of gang related material on social media (i) 2018-19 and (ii) 2019-20.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139544","139544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894977","2018-05-02","Department for Transport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, in advance of a decision by his Department decision on the business case submitted by Shropshire Council for a North West Relief Road, to be made in the summer of 2018, what opportunities are available to representatives from Shropshire to (a) engage with officials and (b) provide updated information when it becomes available.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139443","139443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894978","2018-05-03","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 136052, on Institute for Apprenticeships, when he plans to provide the answer referred to.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139391","139391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894979","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure better reporting procedures in schools for suspected cases of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139419","139419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894980","2018-05-03","Department for Transport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans to review the compensation arrangements for motorists who received speeding fines while driving on motorways with variable speed limits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139505","139505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894981","2018-05-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when his Department plans to lay statutory instruments before Parliament to extend the Public Lending Right to e-book loans.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139446","139446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894982","2018-05-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the Public Lending Right will be extended to e-book loans in time for the planned implementation date of 1 July 2018.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139447","139447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894983","2018-05-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure equality of access and provision of NHS care for patients with learning disabilities.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139496","139496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894984","2018-05-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he supports the UK offshore wind industry’s ambition to produce one third of UK electricity from offshore wind by 2030.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139549","139549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894985","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support his Department provides to schools to ensure that students and staff are able to (a) identify potential victims of female genital mutilation and (b) deal with such cases sensitively and appropriately.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139420","139420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894986","2018-05-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to implement and monitor progress against the recommendations of the Confidential Inquiry into the Premature Deaths of People with Learning Disabilities, published in 2013.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139497","139497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894987","2018-05-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all NHS staff are aware of and can correctly apply the Mental Capacity Act 2005.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139498","139498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894988","2018-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the roll-out of universal credit on trends in the level of rent arrears in (a) Lewisham borough and (b) London.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139550","139550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894989","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure more effective (a) identification of and (b) support for people who are at high risk of being victims of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139421","139421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894990","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to produce (a) statistics and (b) updated estimates on the prevalence of female genital mutilation (i) nationwide and (ii) by city or region.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139422","139422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894991","2018-05-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the effectiveness of general practitioners in (a) identifying and (b) treating perinatal mental health problems experienced by mothers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139492","139492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894992","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to close the deprivation attainment gap in (a) Lewisham borough and (b) London.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139551","139551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894993","2018-05-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 March 2018 to Question 133905, on World War II: Compensation, what information his Department holds on (a) for what reason the UK signed and (b) who was responsible for the UK signing the Treaty on the Final Settlement with respect to Germany in 1990.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139444","139444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894994","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average amount of (a) revenue and (b) capital funding for pupils in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in (A) Lewisham borough, (B) London and (C) England was in cash terms in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139552","139552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894995","2018-05-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to tackle severe obesity in children.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139604","139604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894996","2018-05-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department is doing to support further research into the prevention of Lyme disease.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139605","139605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894997","2018-05-03","Department for Education","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to allocate revenue raised from the sugar tax to services for severely obese children.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139606","139606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894998","2018-05-02","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the primary functions are of each of the UK's overseas military bases.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139415","139415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894999","2018-05-03","Department for International Development","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what (a) the remit and (b) the priorities of the innovation hub will be; what countries will it focus on; how much funding has been allocated to that project; and from which external organisations or government bodies.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139460","139460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/895000","2018-05-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the public interest is safeguarded in any potential sale of Wembley Stadium.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139523","139523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/895001","2018-05-03","Wales Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether he has sought representations from the Welsh Government on the effect of the UK Government's immigration policies on the ability of the Welsh NHS to (a) recruit and (b) retain staff.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139524","139524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/895002","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many offences involving an airgun were recorded by police in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139545","139545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/895003","2018-05-03","Home Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he intends to respond to Questions 136029 on Immigrants: Commonwealth, tabled by the hon. member for Cardiff Central.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139525","139525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/895004","2018-05-03","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many and what proportion of his Department's staff have had days off sick because of mental illness or stress in each of the last three years; and how many days off that amounted to in each of those years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139463","139463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/895005","2018-05-03","Treasury","2018-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the progress made by the banking sector in ensuring that the needs of vulnerable consumers are met.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139526","139526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/895006","2018-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many cases courts have prepared trial bundles in cases where one or more parties was not represented in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139568","139568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/895007","2018-05-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many cases one or more parents appearing in court hearings on the custody of their children have been unrepresented in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139569","139569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/895008","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department's policy is on the establishment of health and wellbeing hubs in former community hospitals.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139412","139412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/895009","2018-05-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 27 April 2018 to Question 137188 on Marine Protected Areas, whether the derogation under the UK's Treaty of Accession to the EU on exclusive use of the six-nautical-miles and 12-nautical-miles fishing zone will remain in force throughout the implementation period.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139355","139355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/895126","2018-05-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government plans to negotiate associate membership of the European Food Safety Authority for when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905124","905124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893005","2018-05-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Brazilian counterpart on the legal proceedings against former President of Brazil, Lula da Silva; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139047","139047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893006","2018-05-02","Department for International Development","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to report to the Platform on Action Commitments and Transformation set up at the World Humanitarian Summit 2016.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139048","139048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893007","2018-05-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on local communities of the ending of the Parks for People conservation grant scheme.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139041","139041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893008","2018-05-02","Department for International Development","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether (a) the UN and (b) its agencies have requested any increases in UK humanitarian assistance to Internally Displaced Persons in Syria or neighbouring states in 2018 to date.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139049","139049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893009","2018-05-01","Department for International Development","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to supply further humanitarian aid  to Yemen after supplies were destroyed at the port of Hodeidah on 31 March 2018.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139050","139050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893010","2018-05-01","Department for International Development","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with her Saudi counterpart on the pledge of the Saudi Government in January 2018 to donate $1.5 billion to humanitarian agencies in Yemen in coordination with the UN.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139051","139051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893011","2018-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of training provided by the Animal and Plant Health Agency (APHA) to (a) carrier staff and (b) pet checker staff who operate on behalf of the APHA to ensure that they are able to identify fake pet passports used for animals travelling under the Pet Travel Scheme.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139042","139042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893012","2018-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of paying universal credit into a joint bank account on the (a) level of independence of women and (b) balance of power in a relationship between two people sharing such an account.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139032","139032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893013","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to increase the number of girls participating in core STEM subjects after the age of 16.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139033","139033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893014","2018-05-01","Department for Transport","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his Oral Answer 1 March 2018, Official Report, column 945, what progress he is making on the appraisal of the options for the Virgin Trains East Coast franchise.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138948","138948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893015","2018-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of child poverty in the North East.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138949","138949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893016","2018-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs,what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policy of the decision by the German Government in 2017 to cease selling arms to the Saudi Government; and what recent discussions he has had with his German counterpart on that matter.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139052","139052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893017","2018-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policy of the decision by the Norwegian Government in 2017 to cease selling arms to the Saudi Government; and what recent discussions he has had with his Norwegian counterpart on that matter.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139053","139053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893018","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2018 to Question 133056 on social services: minimum wage, how many and what proportion of providers enrolled in the Social Care Compliance Scheme responded to the (a) Deloitte and (b) Frontier Economics and Laing Buisson study on sleep-in back-pay liabilities.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138940","138940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893019","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much of the £1.6 billion announced in Autumn Budget 2017 for allocation in 2018-19 has been used to commission services from (a) NHS Trusts and (b) independent healthcare providers.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139056","139056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893020","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support people diagnosed with foetal alcohol syndrome.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139045","139045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893021","2018-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's summary of responses to its Consultation on the Review of the Non Commercial Movement of Pet Animals Order 2011, what steps he is taking to bring forward legislative proposals to reduce the number of dogs being brought illegally into the UK for sale after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139043","139043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893022","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, under what statute people of the Windrush generation were detained.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138939","138939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893023","2018-05-01","Department for Transport","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to monitor variations in the water table in the area around Stonehenge to ensure that any new roads constructed near to that site do not have a destructive impact on the archaeological remains.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138931","138931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893024","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to amend the regulations in the Poisons Act 1972 on the (a) sale, (b) possession and (c) use of (i) phosphoric acid, (ii) hydrochloric acid, (iii) sodium hydroxide, (iv) ammonia and (v) hydrofluoric acid.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138961","138961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893025","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to Questions 136147, 136148 and 136149, tabled by the hon. Member for Bermondsey and Old Southwark  on 17 April 2018.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138996","138996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893026","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether respite care is a health service or a social care.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138989","138989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893027","2018-05-02","Department for Transport","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions took place with the aviation sector during the preparation of the port connectivity study in relation to the surface access needs of ports and airports.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138990","138990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893028","2018-05-02","Department for Transport","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to remove the Liverpool-Nottingham service from the East Midlands Trains franchise and add it to the TransPennine Express franchise.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138991","138991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893029","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 135134 on legal aid scheme: immigration, how many immigration law access points there are in each region.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139006","139006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893030","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 135134 on legal aid scheme: immigration, in (a) how many areas and (b) which areas were one or fewer compliant tenders received in response to the Legal Aid Agency's recent tender process.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139007","139007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893031","2018-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total real terms change in his Department's expenditure on HM Prison and Probation Service was between (a) 2017-18 to 2018-19 and (b) 2010-11 to 1018-19.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139008","139008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893032","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total real terms change in his Department's expenditure on HM Courts and Tribunals Services was between (a) 2017-18 to 2018-19 and (b) 2010-11 to 2018-19.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139009","139009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893033","2018-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the real terms change in his Department's expenditure on the Youth Justice Board was between (a) 2017-18 and 2018-19 and (b) 2010-11 and 1018-19.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139010","139010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893034","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the real terms change in his Department's expenditure on the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority was between (a) 2017-18 and 2018-19 and (b) 2010-11 and 1018-19.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139011","139011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893035","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the real terms change in his Department's expenditure on the Parole Board was between (a) 2017-18 and 2018-19 and (b) 2010-11 and 1018-19.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139012","139012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893036","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the real terms change in his Department's expenditure on the Criminal Cases Review Commission was between (a) 2017-18 and 2018-19 and (b) 2010-11 and 1018-19.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139013","139013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893037","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the real terms change in his Department's expenditure on the Judicial Appointments Commission was between (a) 2017-18 and 2018-19 and (b) 2010-11 and 1018-19.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139014","139014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893038","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the real terms change in his Department's expenditure on the Office of Legal Complaints was between (a) 2017-18 and 2018-19 and (b) 2010-11 and 1018-19.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139015","139015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893039","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the real terms change in his Department's expenditure on the Legal Services Board was between (a) 2017-18 and 2018-19 and (b) 2010-11 and 1018-19.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139016","139016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893040","2018-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many immigration law legal aid providers there were in each region in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139017","139017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893041","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many immigration law legal aid providers there were in each year since 2010, broken down by procurement area.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139018","139018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893042","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many immigration law legal aid providers there were in each at each access point in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139019","139019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893043","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Windrush generation arrival records were included in the national archive; what arrival dates they covered; and which ports of entry covered.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139023","139023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893044","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department sought advice from the National Archives in advance of the destruction of records on the Windrush generation.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139024","139024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893045","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what advice her Department requested from the National Archives on the (a) disposal and (b) destruction of Windrush generation records in advance of the destruction of those records.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139025","139025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893046","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions Windrush records were used to confirm the immigration status of UK citizens in advance of the disposal of those records; and which (a) agencies of her Department and (b) Ministers of her Department received that information on immigration status.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139026","139026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893047","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who ordered a review of the Windrush papers prior to their disposal; when that review was carried out; and what the criteria for that review were.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139027","139027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893048","2018-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children under the age of 16 had a claim rejected for disability living allowance in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139028","139028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893049","2018-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children under the age of 16 received disability living allowance after a successful appeal.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139029","139029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893050","2018-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children under the age of 16 that were in receipt of disability ilving allowance were not entitled to claim personal independence payment when they reached 16 years of age.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139030","139030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893051","2018-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made on the effect of the roll-out of universal credit on trends in the level of rent arrears in Stoke-on-Trent.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139031","139031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893052","2018-05-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that trading standards officers enforce the Construction Products Regulations.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139005","139005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893053","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether clinical commissioning groups have a statutory duty to provide respite care.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138992","138992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893054","2018-05-01","Department for International Development","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to tackle tuberculosis overseas.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139054","139054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893055","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers over the age of 60 were employed in schools in each year in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138941","138941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893056","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to close the deprivation attainment gap in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138942","138942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893057","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding was provided to each pupil in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England in cash terms each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138943","138943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893058","2018-05-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the implications are for the sale of arms to Israel of the Palestinians killed and injured during the Great Return March in 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138944","138944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893059","2018-05-01","Department for International Trade","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 26 April 2018 to Question 136349, which the IT systems referred to are.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138946","138946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893060","2018-05-02","Department for International Trade","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the Human Rights and Democracy Report 2016, published by the Foreign and Commonwealth Office in July 2017, which countries listed as countries of concern on human rights the Government has authorised arms sales to in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138945","138945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893061","2018-05-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he plans to take to notify hon. Members immediately in the event that he receives formal notification of Comcast’s takeover bid for Sky.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138959","138959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893062","2018-05-01","Department for International Development","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether any representatives from her Department plan to attend the United Nations High-Level Meeting on Tuberculosis and Anti-Microbial Resistance in September 2018.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139055","139055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893063","2018-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations her Department has received from gas and electricity providers on the effect of the introduction of universal credit on levels of debt and arrears; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139040","139040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893064","2018-05-03","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Bridgend dated 8 March on training fatalities in 2016 and Army Annual Fitness Tests.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138958","138958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893065","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when NHS England plans to launch its consultation on Accountable Care Organisations.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138970","138970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893066","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with NHS England on its planned consultation on Accountable Care Organisations.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138971","138971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893067","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure that no Accountable Care Organisation (ACO) contract is awarded until the NHS England consultation on ACOs has been completed.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138972","138972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893068","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2018 to Question HL5353, for what reasons the consultation on the contracting arrangements for Accountable Care Organisations was not launched in March 2018.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138973","138973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893069","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the answer of 20 March 2018, to question 132755 on NHS Finance, how much money will be reprioritised from his Department's budget to provide extra funding for the NHS in 2018-19; and what that money was previously allocated to.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138974","138974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893070","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 1.2 of Refreshing NHS Plans for 2018/19, published by NHS England and NHS Improvement on 2 February 2018, from which of his Department’s budgets he is making a further £540 million available to the NHS through the Mandate; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138975","138975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893071","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with E. coli in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138976","138976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893072","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many trauma cases were recorded in NHS A&E departments in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138977","138977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893073","2018-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who were in receipt of a disability premium and after reaching the age of 20 began claiming Universal Credit have been successful at appeal to be granted the (a) limited capability for work element and (b) limited capability for work related activity element.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139034","139034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893074","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many trauma cases were recorded across all NHS hospitals in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138978","138978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893075","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many adults were recorded as obese in (a) England, (b) London, (c) each primary care trust in London and (d) each London borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138979","138979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893076","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to reduce levels of obesity.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138980","138980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893077","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) heart, (b) lung, (c) liver, (d) kidney and (e) cornea transplant donations there have been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138981","138981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893078","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cases of scurvy there were in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138982","138982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893079","2018-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to make representations to the Government of Bahrain on Hajar Mansoor Hassan’s denial of medication by prison authorities in Isa Town Prison.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139036","139036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893080","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people aged 65 and over suffered a hip fracture as a result of a fall in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138983","138983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893081","2018-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Government of Bahrain on recent punitive measures against Nabeel Rajab in Jau Prison.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139037","139037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893082","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many falls among people aged 65 and over led to a hospital admission in each year since 2009-10; and what the five most frequent types of such falls resulting in such admissions were.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138984","138984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893083","2018-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which UK bodies are tasked with implementing the technical assistance programme in Bahrain funded by the Integrated Activity Fund, and which Bahraini bodies are the beneficiaries of that funding.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139038","139038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893084","2018-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Bahrain on the recent decision of the Bahrain’s Military Court of Cassation to uphold the death sentences of four people of whom three are civilians.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139039","139039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893085","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many nurses were employed in each NHS region in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138985","138985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893086","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the three most common cosmetic surgery operations were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138986","138986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893087","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people had Alzheimer's disease in the last year for which figures are available; and what the cost of their medication was in that year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138987","138987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893088","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average (a) length and (b) cost to the public purse was of a finished admission episode for people admitted to hospitals with fragility fractures in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138988","138988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893089","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the to the answer of 15 January 2016 to question 21522, on Road Traffic Offences: Reviews, when the Government plans to begin its review of driving offences; and whether it plans to complete the full review before consulting on introducing new driving offences.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139046","139046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893090","2018-05-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the Government's policy is on making shared parental pay and paternity pay a right for all employees from their first day of employment.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139035","139035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893091","2018-05-02","Department for Transport","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Article 4 of the 1972 World Heritage Convention, what assessment he has made of whether plans for a new tunnel and flyover at Stonehenge are compliant with the terms of that Convention.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138932","138932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893092","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to uplift armed policing capability and capacity to respond more quickly and effectively to firearms attacks.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138953","138953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893093","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what targets her Department had for the removal of refused applicants for Tier 1 (Entrepreneur) visas in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15, (f) 2015-16, (g) 2016-17 and (h) 2017-18.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138998","138998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893094","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent representations he has received from care home operators on their financial viability.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138933","138933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893095","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent representations he has received from care home operators in West Sussex on their future financial viability.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138934","138934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893096","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information he holds on the number of bed days that were lost due to delayed transfers of care in Brighton and Sussex University Hospitals NHS Trust in 2017.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138935","138935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893097","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what change there was in the level of emergency admissions of older people between 2013-14 and 2016-17 in the Brighton and Sussex University Hospitals NHS Trust.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138936","138936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893098","2018-05-02","Department for Transport","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the ninth report of session 2016-17 of the Women and Equalities Committee, Building for Equality: Disability and the Built Environment, published on 25 April 2017, HC 631, what steps he is taking to ensure that blind and partially sighted people are able to safely navigate shared space areas.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138965","138965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893099","2018-05-02","Department for Transport","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with local authorities in England on making shared space areas accessible for blind and partially sighted people.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138966","138966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893100","2018-05-02","Treasury","2018-04-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to protect customers from the high cost of (a) rent-to-own and (b) doorstep lending products.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138967","138967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893101","2018-05-02","Treasury","2018-04-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department is taking steps to support the Financial Conduct Authority in regulating the high cost credit market.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138968","138968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893102","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many local authorities have submitted a disapplication notice to move more than 0.5 per cent of their schools block funding in line with paragraph 117 of the Schools Revenue Funding 2018 to 2019 Operational Guide published by his Department.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138993","138993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893103","2018-05-02","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2018 to Question 127005, on Ministry of Defence Police, what the (a) agreed size of the Ministry of Defence Police complement and (b) the actual number of officers employed by the Ministry of Defence Police was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138954","138954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893104","2018-05-01","Department for Education","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of schools in England due to lose the maximum amount of 1.5 per cent of their funding per pupil in line with the Minimum Funding Guarantee in 2018-19.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138994","138994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893105","2018-05-02","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to remove the Ministry of Defence Police presence from UK (a) facilities, (b) property and (c) sites which to date have had their protective security ensured by that force.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138955","138955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893106","2018-05-02","Department for Education","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of the site acquisition and construction costs of (a) Hyndburn Studio School, (b) Hull Studio School, (c) The Studio School Luton, (d) Inspire Enterprise Academy, (e) The Midland Studio College Nuneaton, (f) New Campus Basildon Studio School, (g) Kajans Hospitality and Catering Studio College, (h) Create Studio and (i) The Future Tech Studio.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138995","138995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893107","2018-05-02","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to maintain Ministry of Defence Police armed policing capacity.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138956","138956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893108","2018-05-02","Cabinet Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the reasons are for the rise of zero-hours contracts in the UK by 100,000 in 2017 identified in the most recent Office for National Statistics data return.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138969","138969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893109","2018-05-02","Department for Transport","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to Answer 27 April 2018 to Question 137449 on Department of Transport: Procurement, what each of the contracts were for.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138947","138947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893110","2018-05-02","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has sought additional investment in police counter-terrorism capability for the Ministry of Defence Police; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138957","138957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893111","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what annual savings he estimates the courts reform programme will have made by 2021 when that programme is complete.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139020","139020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893112","2018-05-02","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on (a) GDP, (b) the balance of trade, (c) small business growth and (d) large business growth of the Government's policy on leaving the EU Customs Union.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139057","139057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893113","2018-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's policy is on advising claimants who are appealing decisions on employment support allowance whether to apply for universal credit.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138997","138997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893114","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what targets her Department has had in each year since 2010-11 for the removal of applicants who have been refused Tier 1 Investor visas.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138999","138999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893115","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what targets her Department has had in each year since 2010-11 for the removal of applicants who have been refused Tier 1 Graduate Entrepreneur visas.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139000","139000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893116","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what targets her Department has had in each year since 2010-11 for the removal of applicants who have been refused Tier 1 Exceptional Talent visas.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139001","139001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893117","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what targets her Department had for the removal of refused applicants for Tier 2 (General) visas in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15, (f) 2015-16, (g) 2016-17 and (h) 2017-18.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139002","139002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893118","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what targets her Department had for the removal of refused applicants for Tier 4 (Student) visas in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15, (f) 2015-16, (g) 2016-17 and (h) 2017-18.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139003","139003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893119","2018-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will commission within this Parliament research into the effect on children's mental health of living with (a) income poverty, (b) debt, (c) poor housing and (d) in circumstances in which one or more adults have mental health problems.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139021","139021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893120","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what targets her Department has had in each year since 2010-11 for the removal of applicants who have been refused settlement visas.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139004","139004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893121","2018-05-02","Treasury","2018-04-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of all departmental budgets to ensure that they (a) include a sum for investment in tackling children's social and economic inequalities and (b) enable policy collaboration between Departments on social and economic inequalities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139022","139022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893122","2018-05-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to support Ofgem in ensuring that the new RIIO-2 price control framework is tougher on energy network companies.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138960","138960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893123","2018-05-02","Treasury","2018-04-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date he is basing his plans for the (a) disapplication of Air Passenger Duty and (b) replacement of that duty with an air departure tax in Scotland.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138962","138962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893124","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what Ministerial (a) involvement, (b) agreement and (c) direction there was in the setting of removal targets in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138950","138950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893125","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department first introduced removal targets; and if she will publish her Department's removal targets by (a) year and (b) region.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138951","138951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893126","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases are known to (a) Ministers and (b) officials of her Department of people who have been wrongfully (i) deported and (ii) detained.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138952","138952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893127","2018-05-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer to Question 136780, on British Overseas Territories: Marine Protected Areas, which Blue Belt programme activities those payments of Centre for Environment, Fisheries and Aquaculture Science staff salaries were associated with in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138963","138963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893128","2018-05-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer to Question 136780, on British Overseas Territories: Marine Protected Areas, which Blue Belt programme activities those payments of Marine Management Organisation staff salaries were associated with in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138964","138964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893129","2018-05-02","Home Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the High Court Judgment of 10 October 2017, Medical Justice v. Secretary of State, what steps her Department is taking to review the guidance in respect of torture; and with which organisations her Department has consulted on that guidance.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139044","139044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893130","2018-05-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what funding his Department has allocated to diplomatic work in (a) Africa, (b) Europe, (c) USA and (d) Latin America.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138937","138937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893131","2018-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in how many overseas posts do officials in his Department share offices with officials from the Department for International Development.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138938","138938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892107","2018-04-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-26","What assessment he has made of the level of self-sufficiency in food production in England and Wales; and whether he plans to increase that level.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904954","904954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892108","2018-04-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-26","What steps he is taking to improve standards of animal welfare.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904957","904957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892109","2018-04-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-26","What steps he has taken to reduce delays in processing applications for the basic payment scheme.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904958","904958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892110","2018-04-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-26","What steps he is taking to reduce plastic waste in England.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904959","904959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892111","2018-04-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-26","What recent assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the UK food industry.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904961","904961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892112","2018-04-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-26","Whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to improve standards of safety in animal rescue homes.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904960","904960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892140","2018-04-30","Department for Transport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of current incentives to encourage the uptake of electric vehicles.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138458","138458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892141","2018-04-30","Department for Transport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what support is available for local authorities to develop electric vehicle charging infrastructure.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138459","138459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892142","2018-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the accessibility to deaf claimants of the personal independence payment customer satisfaction surveys that are only carried out by telephone.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138493","138493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892143","2018-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment (PIP) review notice letters were sent out to claimants (a) up to one year and (b) over one year in advance of their PIP award expiry date in the last two years; and how many claimants had their PIP award terminated early in that period.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138494","138494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892144","2018-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Yemini counterpart following recent reports of threats made by representatives of the Houthis against the Bahais in that country.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138356","138356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892145","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of reducing the bowel cancer screening age to 50 on a more effective prognosis of that condition; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138357","138357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892146","2018-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in Israel on allowing medical supplies from (a) Israel and (b) elsewhere to be delivered to Gaza.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138358","138358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892147","2018-04-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how his Department determines the interests and wishes of the people of the Western Sahara in establishing whether commercial activity there is legal or otherwise.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138353","138353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892148","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the article entitled Premier League to question clubs over trafficking, published by the Times on 23 April 2018, what assessment he has made of the level of risk of child trafficking within the supply chains of Premier League football clubs; and what steps the Government is taking to tackle modern slavery in sport supply chains.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138393","138393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892149","2018-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on staff of different working conditions between staff directly employed by the NHS and those employed by new wholly-owned subsidiary companies in the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138370","138370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892150","2018-04-30","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what apps his Department has approved for use of mobile phones issued by his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138376","138376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892151","2018-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what apps his Department has approved for use of mobile phones issued by his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138377","138377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892152","2018-04-30","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what apps his Department has approved for use of mobile phones issued by his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138378","138378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892153","2018-04-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what apps his Department has approved for use of mobile phones issued by his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138379","138379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892154","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what apps her Department has approved for use of mobile phones issued by her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138380","138380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892155","2018-04-30","Department for International Development","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what apps her Department has approved for use of mobile phones issued by her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138381","138381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892156","2018-04-30","Department for International Trade","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what apps his Department has approved for use of mobile phones issued by his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138382","138382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892157","2018-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what apps his Department has approved for use on mobile phones issued by his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138383","138383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892158","2018-04-30","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what apps her Department has approved for use on mobile phones issued by her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138384","138384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892159","2018-04-30","Department for Transport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what apps his Department has approved for use on mobile phones issued by his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138385","138385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892160","2018-05-01","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what apps his Department has approved for use on mobile phones issued by his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138386","138386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892161","2018-04-30","Scotland Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what apps his Department has approved for use on mobile phones issued by his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138387","138387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892162","2018-04-30","Wales Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what apps his Department has approved for use on mobile phones issued by his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138388","138388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892163","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what apps his Department has approved for use on mobile phones issued by his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138389","138389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892164","2018-04-30","Department for Transport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, further to oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Transport of 24 April 2018,  Official Report, column 356WH, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on road safety of the decision to eliminate safety targets; and what the killed or seriously injured figures were in each year from 2007 to 2017.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138348","138348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892165","2018-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to tackle low pay.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138424","138424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892166","2018-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to revise the rules governing the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority with regard to the same roof rule in line with the recommendation of the Interim Report of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse, published on 25 April 2018.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138461","138461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892167","2018-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will introduce proposals to revise Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority rules in line with the recommendation of the Interim Report of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse, published on 25 April 2018, so that awards are not automatically rejected in circumstances where an applicant’s criminal convictions are likely to be linked to their child sexual abuse.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138462","138462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892168","2018-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will estimate the potential cost to the public purse of supporting victims and survivors of child sexual abuse in making a civil claim.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138463","138463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892169","2018-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will amend the Civil Procedure Rules to ensure that judges presiding over cases relating to child sexual abuse consider the use of protections for vulnerable witnesses.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138464","138464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892170","2018-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward legislation in line with the recommendation of the Interim Report of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse, published on 25 April 2018 to ensure that victims and survivors of child sexual abuse in civil court cases when they are claiming compensation in relation to the abuse they suffered are afforded the same protections as vulnerable witnesses in criminal court cases.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138465","138465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892171","2018-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will introduce proposals to establish the (a) current levels and (b) effectiveness of public expenditure on services for child victims and adult survivors of child sexual abuse in England in line with the recommendation of the Interim Report of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse, published on 25 April 2018.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138466","138466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892172","2018-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will commission an inspection of compliance with the Victims Code by relevant Departments in relation to victims and survivors of child sexual abuse.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138467","138467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892173","2018-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will implement a national policy for the training and use of chaperones in the treatment of children in healthcare services in response to the recommendation of the Interim Report of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse, published on 25 April 2018.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138468","138468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892174","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will introduce proposals in line with the recommendation of the Interim Report of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse, published on 25 April 2018, to amend the Police Regulations 2003 to include the requirement that a police officer and staff equivalent (a) have operational policing experience in preventing and responding to child sexual abuse and (b) achieve accreditation in the role of the police service in preventing and responding to child sexual abuse to progress to Chief Officer level.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138469","138469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892175","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward proposals for the College of Policing to develop training content and accreditation arrangements for officers on preventing and responding to child sexual abuse in line with the recommendation of the Interim Report of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse, published on 25 April 2018.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138470","138470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892176","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward proposals to prevent complaints relating to child sexual abuse being disapplied by police forces on the grounds that the incident involved took place more than 12 months before the complaint was submitted.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138471","138471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892177","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward proposals to establish (a) levels of public expenditure and (b) measures to assess the effectiveness of that expenditure on services provided by her Department for child victims and adult survivors of child sexual abuse in line with the recommendation of the Interim Report of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse, published on 25 April 2018.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138472","138472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892178","2018-04-30","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will bring forward proposals to establish (a) levels of public expenditure and (b) measures to assess the effectiveness of that expenditure on services provided by his Department for child victims and adult survivors of child sexual abuse in line with the recommendation of the Interim Report of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse, published on 25 April 2018.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138473","138473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892179","2018-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether it is the Government’s policy to seek to stay within the European Emissions Trading Scheme after the scheme’s third trading phase expires on 31 December 2020.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138512","138512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892180","2018-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has plans to negotiate the inclusion of text on climate and energy in the political declaration on the framework for the future relationship that will form part of the European Commission's Draft Agreement on the withdrawal of the UK from the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138513","138513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892181","2018-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that there is continued cooperation with the EU on climate change after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138514","138514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892182","2018-05-01","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many days his Department's Permanent Secretary spent working in HM Treasury at 1 Horse Guards Road in each month since 1 January 2018.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138507","138507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892183","2018-05-01","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many days his Department's Second Permanent Secretary spent working in HM Treasury at 1 Horse Guards Road in each month since 1 January 2018.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138508","138508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892184","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what is the cost to the public purse is of processing an application for indefinite leave to remain.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138521","138521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892185","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers required hospital treatment as a result of an assault at work in 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138496","138496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892186","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers required hospital treatment as a result of an assault at work in the first three months of 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138497","138497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892187","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers that work at prisons rated as Overall performance is of concern were working on detached duty at another prison during January 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138498","138498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892188","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers who work at prisons which are in special measures were working on detached duty at another prison during January 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138499","138499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892189","2018-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) courts and (b) tribunals have closed as a result of leases not being extended in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138500","138500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892190","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time was for an employment tribunal appeal hearing at each employment tribunal hearing venue in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138501","138501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892191","2018-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time was for an employment tribunal appeal hearing to be listed in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138502","138502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892192","2018-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many members of staff resigned from HMP Chelmsford in 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138503","138503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892193","2018-04-30","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2018 to Question 123416 on banks: small businesses, if he will list the options his Department has considered on dispute resolution between small and medium-sized enterprises and banks.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138341","138341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892194","2018-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of her Department's staff have had days off sick because of mental illness or stress in each of the last three years; and how many days off that amounted to in each of those years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138428","138428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892195","2018-05-01","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many and what proportion of his Department's staff have had days off sick because of mental illness or stress in each of the last three years; and how many days off that amounted to in each of those years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138429","138429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892196","2018-05-01","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of his Department's staff have had days off sick because of mental illness or stress in each of the last three years; and how many days off that amounted to in each of those years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138430","138430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892197","2018-05-01","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of his Department's staff have had days off sick because of mental illness or stress in each of the last three years; and how many days off that amounted to in each of those years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138431","138431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892198","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of his Department's staff have had days off sick because of mental illness or stress in each of the last three years; and how many days off that amounted to in each of those years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138432","138432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892199","2018-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many young people have received support through the Youth Obligation; and how many of those people have subsequently gone on to (a) an apprenticeship, (b) a traineeship and (c) a work placement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138342","138342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892200","2018-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of young people have stopped receiving benefits since beginning the Youth Obligation.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138343","138343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892201","2018-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many young people have been sanctioned whilst receiving support through the  Youth Obligation.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138344","138344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892202","2018-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many work coaches have supported claimants on the Youth Obligation to date.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138345","138345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892203","2018-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants are on the Youth Obligation by Jobcentre Plus (a) region and (b) office.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138346","138346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892204","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has plans to encourage Clinical Commissioning Groups to fund transport for vulnerable and disabled patients to events supported by their own social prescribing schemes.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138427","138427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892205","2018-05-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many and what proportion of Basic Payment Scheme payments have been delayed by (a) one, (b) two and (c) three  and (d) more than three months in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138371","138371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892206","2018-05-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the cost per MWh  of energy generated by (a) onshore wind, (b) offshore wind, (c) solar PV, (d) open cycle gas, (e) combine cycle gas and (f) coal in 2020.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138372","138372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892207","2018-05-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of the introduction of safe standing in Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138373","138373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892208","2018-05-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to increase the number of volunteers for (a) amateur and (b) youth sports; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138374","138374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892209","2018-05-01","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many full-time equivalent (a) teachers, (b) teaching assistants and (c) support staff were empolyed in local authority schools in Coventry in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138375","138375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892210","2018-05-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with acquired brain injuries claim (a) high-rate and (b) low-rate Personal Independence Payments and Employment and Support Allowance.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138404","138404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892211","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many medical students there were in each year since 2011 excluding the additional (a) 500 places introduced in  October 2018 and (b) 1000 places introduced in October 2019.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138452","138452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892212","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many full-time equivalent school nurses there were in each January since January 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138453","138453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892213","2018-05-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with acquired brain injuries that claim universal credit also claim (a) limited capability for work and (b) limited capability for work-related activities elements.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138405","138405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892214","2018-05-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to support older people to use digital technology.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138448","138448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892215","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department undertook an Equality Impact Assessment in advance of the decision to destroy documentation relating to the Windrush generation.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138533","138533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892216","2018-05-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking with the Department for Education to promote the teaching of media skills in schools.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138449","138449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892217","2018-05-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking (a) promote and (b) increase the number of sporting opportunities for disabled people.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138450","138450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892218","2018-05-01","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 136096 on Self-employed: Adoption, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies on statutory adoption leave for the self-employed of the request by adoption agencies that adoptive parents spend a minimum of six months at home when a child is first placed.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138509","138509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892219","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 24 April 2018 to Question 136771 on Deportation, when the Home Office Manual of Escorting Safely (HOMES) was developed; how many times HOMES has been reviewed; the last time HOMES was reviewed; and on what dates HOMES was updated.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138365","138365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892220","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of the 24 April to Question 136754 on Immigrants: Detainees, whether the pay rates for immigration-related detainees are consistent throughout the prison service.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138366","138366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892221","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the availability of appointments for women at contraception clinics in England and Wales.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138510","138510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892222","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of the 24 April to Question 136754, what the longest period is for a detainee to have been held; and how many and what proportion of released detainees were subsequently detained within (i) one month of their release and (ii) six months of their release.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138367","138367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892223","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to promote healthcare courses to school leavers.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138451","138451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892224","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timetable is for the introduction of automatic (a) audio and (b) video recording of personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138425","138425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892225","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will made an assessment of the potential merits of ensuring that claimants of  personal independence payments receive a copy of their assessment report.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138426","138426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892226","2018-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of the availability of appointments for abortions in NHS hospital settings for women with complex medical conditions.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138511","138511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892227","2018-04-30","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 April 2018 to Question 136629, whether there a limit on the time between the use of lethal force outside of an armed conflict and the subsequent notification of Parliament.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138368","138368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892228","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer on 24 April 2018 to Question 136628 on Alfie Dingley, when a decision will be reached on the application for a licence that has been submitted.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138369","138369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892229","2018-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will ensure that NICE clarifies its guidance on the entitlement of patients of varying risk to Transcatheter Aortic Valve Implantation.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138577","138577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892230","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the Scottish Government's decision to remove the time-limited definition of terminal illness and to allow the clinical judgment of a registered medical practitioner to determine a terminal diagnosis.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138407","138407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892231","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure safeguards are in place to enable eligible EU citizens to access public funds after the UK leaves the EU and before June 2021.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138349","138349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892232","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of (a) personal independence payment and (b) disability living allowance claimants with (i) Motor Neurone Disease and (ii) Parkinson’s Disease receive the highest rate award.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138408","138408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892233","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that (a) elderly and (b) computer illiterate EU citizens living in the UK are given adequate support to acquire the documentation needed for their immigration status applications before June 2021.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138350","138350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892234","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what grounds she will accept immigration status and residence applications made by EU citizens after the June 2021 deadline.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138351","138351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892235","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the total number of additional staff her Department will need in order to process EU citizens’ immigration and residence status and permanent residency applications ahead of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138352","138352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892236","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to answer Question 135984 tabled on 16 April 2018.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138519","138519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892237","2018-05-01","Department for International Development","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2018 to Question 126095 on Developing Countries: Energy, if he will publish (a) companies, (b) locations and (c) funding allocated in respect of the programme; and whether he has plans to fund additional projects.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138392","138392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892238","2018-04-30","Department for Transport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's policy is on the use of average speed limit cameras on smart motorways (a) at all times and (b)  when a variable speed limit is in force.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138505","138505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892239","2018-04-30","Cabinet Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress the Government has made on the roll-out the ban the box initiative throughout the public sector.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138406","138406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892240","2018-04-30","Department for Transport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's policy is on classifying the A316 as part of the Strategic Road Network.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138506","138506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892241","2018-05-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 21 March 2016 to Question 904216 on Public Libraries: Closures, if he will publish the (a) name and (b) location of the 110 libraries that closed between 2010 and 2016.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138390","138390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892242","2018-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 130769, on Disability Premium, on what date her Department plans to release the ad-hoc statistics publication for employment and support allowance people in receipt of severe and enhanced disability premiums.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138566","138566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892243","2018-04-30","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the defence of reasonable chastisement and punishment is available to (a) nurses and (b) other staff acting in loco parentis in (i) mental health inpatient units and (ii) other health settings charged with the assault of a child in their care.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138474","138474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892244","2018-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timetable is for the Youth Justice Board to confirm the grant allocations for youth offending services for 2018-19;and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138347","138347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892245","2018-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that improving patient access to innovative new medicines is included in the terms of reference for negotiations on the pharmaceutical price regulation scheme.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138517","138517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892246","2018-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the start of negotiations on the pharmaceutical price regulation scheme.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138518","138518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892247","2018-04-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of Hezbollah's weapons arsenal.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138444","138444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892248","2018-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much the Government has spent on repairing potholes across the NHS estate in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138454","138454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892249","2018-04-30","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 135391, how many non-medical help providers have had (a) no payments, (b) fewer than five payments and (c) fewer than 10 payments since the introduction of the Disabled Students Allowance Quality Assurance Group list in April 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138475","138475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892250","2018-04-30","Department for Transport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the data sharing arrangements are between licensing authorities on the licensing of (a) hackney carriages and (b) private hire drivers and operators.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138410","138410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892251","2018-04-30","Department for Transport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to make mandatory the sharing of data on the licensing of hackney carriage and private hire drivers and operators between licencing authorities.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138411","138411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892252","2018-04-30","Department for Transport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent meetings he has had with (a) local authorities and (b) other external stakeholders on the development of data sharing arrangements on the licensing of hackney carriage and private hire drivers and operators between licencing authorities.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138412","138412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892253","2018-05-01","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of applications for 30 hours of free childcare have been processed within seven days in the last three months for which data is available.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138522","138522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892254","2018-04-30","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2018 to Question 135397 and with reference to the report, Local area SEND inspections: one year on, published on 18 October 2017, how many unofficial exclusions were found by the inspections that formed the basis of that report.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138476","138476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892255","2018-04-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of radicalisation in the Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138445","138445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892256","2018-04-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of changes in the level of violence in Israel and the West Bank.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138446","138446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892257","2018-04-30","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the recommendation of the Independent Inquiry Child Sexual Abuse Interim Report, published on 25 April 2018 on introducing arrangements for the registration of staff working in care roles in children’s homes.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138477","138477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892258","2018-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has received from the hospice movement on the effect of proposed increases in NHS pay; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138354","138354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892259","2018-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of proposed NHS pay increases on voluntary sector hospices.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138355","138355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892260","2018-04-30","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to evaluate the performance of the Regional Adoption Agencies.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138478","138478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892261","2018-04-30","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children with development co-ordination disorder there are in primary school.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138479","138479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892262","2018-04-30","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the current pathways for the identification of children at risk of dyspraxia in schools are.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138480","138480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892263","2018-04-30","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the nationally agreed criteria are for the identification, assessment and intervention for dyspraxia; and how adjustments for that condition at GCSE and A levels are determined.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138481","138481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892264","2018-04-30","Cabinet Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people diagnosed with dyspraxia who are (a) unemployed and (b) not in training or further education.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138482","138482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892265","2018-04-30","Cabinet Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of school leavers and adults with dyspraxia who are (a) in work and (b) in training or further education.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138483","138483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892266","2018-04-30","Cabinet Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether any changes will be made to the process for (a) review and (b) oversight of the Consolidated Guidance.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138561","138561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892267","2018-04-30","Cabinet Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government plans to hold a public consultation on potential changes to the Consolidated Guidance.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138562","138562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892268","2018-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of prison officers have (a) 0-1, (b) 1-3, (c) 3-5 (d) 5 -10 and (e) over 10 years of continuous service in the prison service as of January 2018.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138489","138489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892269","2018-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time was to access Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services in each local authority area in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138394","138394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892270","2018-05-01","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of children who received help from schools-based educational psychologists in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138395","138395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892271","2018-05-01","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department provided for schools-based educational psychologists in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138396","138396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892272","2018-04-30","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with EU negotiators on the right of UK citizens living in other EU countries to move freely throughout the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138563","138563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892273","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for the guidance on Police Information Notices in the Authorised Professional Practice guidance on harassment and stalking to be published.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138564","138564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892274","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been detained for periods longer than 28 days at Yarl's Wood Detention Centre since 2010.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138565","138565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892275","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, further to the oral contribution of the Prime Minister of 25 April 2018, Official Report, Column 870, whether the citizenship status will be offered to (a) residents and (b) children of residents of the Chagos Islands that were evicted from those islands between 1967 and 1973 that now reside in the UK.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138492","138492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892276","2018-05-01","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education,  pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 136599 on Education Fellowship Trust (TEFT), if he will list the (a) 10 TEFT schools for which new trusts have been identified but which have not yet been transferred and (b) two TEFT schools for which no new trust has been identified.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138485","138485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892277","2018-05-01","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy schools are awaiting re-brokering as of 26 April 2018.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138486","138486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892278","2018-05-01","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much tax was written off by HMRC for (a) individuals and (b) businesses due to them becoming insolvent and HMRC constituting an unsecured creditor in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138556","138556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892279","2018-04-30","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many schemes have been notified to HMRC under Disclosure of tax avoidance schemes in relation to the Employment Allowance avoidance scheme set out in the guidance issued by HMRC on 29th June 2015.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138557","138557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892280","2018-05-01","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Advanced Thin Capitalisation Agreements have been agreed to in each month in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138558","138558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892281","2018-04-30","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many opinions the General Anti-Abuse Rule Advisory Panel has published in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138559","138559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892282","2018-05-01","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of cases referred to the General Anti-Abuse Rule Advisory Panel by HMRC resulted in positive determinations in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138560","138560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892283","2018-05-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to Questions 245 to 259 of his evidence to the Treasury Committee on 25 April 2018 on local authorities, how he defines the term at risk to categorise that level of financial sustainability of local authorities in England; what terms other than at risk he uses to categorise the levels of financial sustainability of local authorities in England; and how many local authorities in England have been defined as (a) at risk and (b) any other level he uses to categorise levels of financial sustainability.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138439","138439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892284","2018-05-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to Questions 245 to 259 of his evidence to the Treasury Committee on 25 April 2018 on local authority funding, whether he has conducted a risk assessment of the (a) short-term and (b) long-term financial ability of local authorities to meet the need for local services.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138440","138440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892285","2018-05-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to Questions 245 to 259 of his evidence to the Treasury Committee on 25 April 2018 on The Work of the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what drivers of cost he has identified among local authorities in England.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138441","138441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892286","2018-04-30","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish the revised guidance notes relating to the Enterprise Investment Scheme following changes announced in Autumn Budget 2017.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138578","138578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892287","2018-04-30","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to RD5 on page 29 of the Research and Development Tax Credits Statistics report, published in September 2017, whether HMRC is able to provide a supplementary table that breaks down the regional adoption of the tax relief by parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138487","138487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892288","2018-05-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to oral evidence given to the Treasury Committee on 25 April 2018, HC 424 and the Local Government Association's response to the Housing, Communities and Local Government report into business rates, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of local government finance in maintaining vital services.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138442","138442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892289","2018-05-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the (a) short-term and (b) long-term financial sustainability of local authorities' provision of public services.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138443","138443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892290","2018-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) enforcement and (b) effectiveness of the published acceptable limits for formaldehyde both within and released from MDF wood used in furniture.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138488","138488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892291","2018-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much legal aid was spent on advice relating to (a) housing benefits, (b) welfare benefits and (c) other benefits in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138504","138504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892292","2018-04-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on adherence to international humanitarian law when responding to Palestinian protests on Gaza’s borders.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138409","138409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892293","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the target was for the removal of immigrants from (a) Scotland and (b) Northern Ireland in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138490","138490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892294","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-UK nationals have been removed from (a) Scotland and (b) Northern Ireland; and for what reasons each of those people were removed in each month of each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138491","138491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892295","2018-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with foetal alcohol syndrome in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138537","138537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892296","2018-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to eliminate the use of single-use plastic cutlery.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138538","138538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892297","2018-04-30","Attorney General","2018-04-26","To ask the Attorney General, what steps his Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138539","138539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892298","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many mobile phone masts are being built under the Emergency Services Network in High Peak.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138567","138567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892299","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of jobs listed on Universal Jobmatch are open to (a) part-time or flexible hours and (b) full-time hours.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138523","138523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892300","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will list the location of mobile phone masts being built under the Emergency Services Network in High Peak.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138568","138568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892301","2018-04-30","Cabinet Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138540","138540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892302","2018-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics .","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138541","138541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892303","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department provides to employers on posting part-time vacancies including job share roles on the Universal Jobmatch website.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138524","138524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892304","2018-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support is available to social care providers to implement the change in guidance on the national minimum wage and national living wage for sleep-in shifts for care workers.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138447","138447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892305","2018-04-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics .","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138542","138542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892306","2018-04-30","Department for Education","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138543","138543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892307","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many responsible carers and lone parents in receipt of legacy benefits and universal credit have received a sanction for not applying for a sufficient number of jobs using the Universal Jobmatch website.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138525","138525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892308","2018-04-30","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps his Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics .","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138544","138544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892309","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of whether there is a sufficient number of part-time vacancies on the Universal Jobmatch site suitable for carers and lone parents with pre-school aged children who will be required to look for work in order to receive universal credit.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138526","138526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892310","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of whether there is a sufficient number of vacancies advertised on the Universal Jobmatch site for responsible carers and lone parents with children aged between five and 12 years old who are required to look for work of at least 25 per hours per week in order to receive universal credit.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138527","138527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892311","2018-04-30","Department for International Development","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development,  what steps her Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics .","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138545","138545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892312","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether responsible carers and lone parents in receipt of legacy benefits and universal credit are required to use the Universal Jobmatch site to look for work; and whether activity on that site can be used as a measure of a claimant actively seeking work.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138528","138528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892313","2018-04-30","Department for International Trade","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138546","138546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892314","2018-05-01","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many mobile phone mast sites being built under the Emergency Services Network in High Peak have (a) been granted planning approval, (b) entered the build phase and (c) are live as of 1 April 2018.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138569","138569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892315","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of universal credit rules on a mother's ability to return to work.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138529","138529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892316","2018-04-30","Department for Transport","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138547","138547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892317","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many mobile phone mast sites being built under the Emergency Services Network in High Peak (a) are being built with the capacity for multi-occupancy and (b) have a confirmed second tenant.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138570","138570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892318","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics .","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138548","138548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892319","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the universal credit income taper and work allowances on gender equality in the labour market.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138530","138530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892320","2018-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics .","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138549","138549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892321","2018-04-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs,  what steps his Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics .","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138550","138550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892322","2018-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the universal credit income taper and work allowances on women returning to work after childbirth.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138531","138531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892323","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many mobile phone mast sites funded by the public purse are being built under the Emergency Services Network in High Peak.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138571","138571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892324","2018-04-30","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138551","138551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892325","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138552","138552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892326","2018-04-30","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138553","138553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892327","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will list the locations of mobile phone mast sites funded by the public purse being built under the Emergency Services Network in High Peak.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138572","138572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892328","2018-04-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken to reduce its use of single-use plastics ..","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138554","138554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892329","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many mobile phone mast sites being funded by the public purse built under the Emergency Services Network in High Peak have (a) been granted planning approval, (b) entered the build phase and (c) are live as of 1 April 2018.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138573","138573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892330","2018-04-30","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many reported incidents of lasers attacks on military aircraft operating in UK airspace have been recorded by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138398","138398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892331","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many mobile phone mast sites funded by the public purse and being built under the Emergency Services Network in High Peak are (a) being built with the capacity for multi-occupancy and (b) have a confirmed second tenant.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138574","138574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892332","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much will spent from the public purse on each mobile phone mast site being built under the Emergency Services Network in High Peak.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138575","138575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892333","2018-04-30","Scotland Office","2018-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he plans to visit a food bank in May 2018.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138534","138534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892334","2018-05-01","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what track and trace system will be in operation for cigarettes, other tobacco products such as IQOS and substitutes such as e-cigarettes after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138455","138455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892335","2018-05-01","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for that reasons the UK has not ratified the WHO Protocol to Eliminate the Illicit Trade in Tobacco Products.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138456","138456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892336","2018-04-30","Treasury","2018-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what system is in place to monitor potential fraud in the collection of the sugar tax.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138457","138457"
