"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89585","2014-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the policy document entitled, Helping households to cut their energy bills, supporting pages on smart meters, updated online on 24 July 2014, who receives the benefits of £17.1 billion for the installation of smart meters in homes; and what form those benefits take.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207543","207543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89586","2014-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of households with an energy performance certificate of (a) A, (b) B, (c) C, (d) D, (e) E, (f) F and (g) G are (i) owner-occupied, (ii) private rented, (iii) local authority and (iv) housing association households.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207539","207539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89587","2014-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the effect on the UK economy of the supply of gas from Russia to Europe being cut off.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207362","207362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89588","2014-09-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much has been allocated to each local authority area under the Green Deal Home Improvement Fund.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207444","207444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89589","2014-09-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to refund people who paid for a Green Deal assessment prior to the exhaustion of the fund.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207445","207445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89590","2014-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, under what timetable her Department plans to phase-out use of telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, 0844 and 0843 in accordance with the Cabinet Office guidance on customer service lines published in December 2013 and (b) 03 and 08, where 03 is the primary number under a dual numbering system.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207453","207453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89591","2014-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many farms in Cumbria which received payments under the (a) Hill Livestock Compensatory Allowance, (b) Sheep Annual Premium Scheme, (c) Hill Farm Allowance and (d) Uplands Entry Level Stewardship Scheme in each of the last 30 years; and what aggregate local payments were made under each scheme in each such year.","Biography information for Rory Stewart","Rory Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207462","207462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89592","2014-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will establish a scheme to provide affordable insurance cover for leasehold dwellings and small businesses in areas at high risk of flooding modelled on the existing Flood Re scheme for freehold dwellings.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207550","207550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89593","2014-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer to Lord Rooker of 11 August 2014, HL1378, on the food supply networks review, for what reasons Professor Elliott's final report on horsemeat fraud and the food supply networks review has not yet been published; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207528","207528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89594","2014-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many new EU directives and regulations have been transposed into UK law by her Department since May 2010.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207259","207259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89595","2014-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to publish the review led by Professor Elliott into the food system and food contamination.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207532","207532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89596","2014-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will introduce new guidelines to protect the welfare of dogs in cars; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207134","207134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89597","2014-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will commission a study to assess the extent of mis-stunning at the point of animal slaughter in the UK.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207157","207157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89598","2014-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department spent on the purchase of televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207214","207214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89599","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on the purchase of televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207215","207215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89600","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Tuvalu; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207228","207228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89601","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Tonga; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207227","207227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89602","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help protect people living in ISIS-controlled areas of Iraq.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207202","207202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89603","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Dominica; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207206","207206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89604","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in the Solomon Islands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207226","207226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89605","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to secure the release of the Nigerian schoolgirls kidnapped by Boko Haram in April 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207392","207392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89606","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Saudi counterpart on the imprisonment of Waleed Abu al-Khair.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207391","207391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89607","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the alleged torture of Waleed Abu al-Khair while imprisoned in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207390","207390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89608","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Brunei; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207191","207191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89609","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Antigua and Barbuda; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207192","207192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89610","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Malaysia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207189","207189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89611","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Pakistan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207190","207190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89612","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Tanzania; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207234","207234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89613","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Kenya; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207231","207231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89614","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Cameroon; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207229","207229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89615","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Belize; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207205","207205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89616","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Mauritius; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207232","207232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89617","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Zambia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207236","207236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89618","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Bangladesh; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207237","207237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89619","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Grenada; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207238","207238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89620","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Jamaica; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207239","207239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89621","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Swaziland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207233","207233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89622","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Uganda; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207235","207235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89623","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in St Kitts and Nevis; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207240","207240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89624","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Papua New Guinea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207248","207248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89625","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the merits of the appointment of a team of experts led by the UN Office of the High Commissioner for Human Rights to assist the investigation into alleged abuses in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207273","207273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89626","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Sri Lanka; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207245","207245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89627","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Barbados; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207246","207246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89628","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Nauru; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207247","207247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89629","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether anyone from his Department will attend the third international Conference on the Humanitarian Consequences of Nuclear Weapons in Vienna in December; and what discussions he has had with international counterparts about that Conference.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207351","207351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89630","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) British citizens, (b) British residents holding dual passports and (c) British residents holding foreign passports who left the UK in 2014 to fight for the (i) Israeli Defence Force in Gaza, (ii) Koma Komalên Kurdistan in Syria and Iraq and (iii) ISIS Islamic State in Syria and Iraq in 2014; and what his policy is in each such case.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207355","207355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89631","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the validity of reports that the so-called Bahrain 13 were tortured during 2011.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207345","207345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89632","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what meetings Ministers in his Department have had with civil society or religious groups based in the UK which have discussed the situation in Israel and Palestine since 1 July 2014; which organisations attended each such meeting; and when each such meeting took place.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207285","207285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89633","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what fines have been levied on the UK Government for non-compliance with EU directives since November 2012.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207280","207280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89634","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to international organisations on the protection of Christians in those parts of Iraq controlled by ISIL.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207277","207277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89635","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Ghana; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207230","207230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89636","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the safety of Christians in those parts of Iraq controlled by ISIL.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207276","207276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89637","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Singapore; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207244","207244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89638","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Samoa; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207249","207249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89639","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Sierra Leone; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207086","207086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89640","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in St Vincent and the Grenadines; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207087","207087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89641","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Kiribati; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207083","207083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89642","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in the Seychelles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207084","207084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89643","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Nigeria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207085","207085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89644","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in St Lucia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207082","207082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89645","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Guyana; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207093","207093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89646","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Trinidad and Tobago; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207094","207094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89647","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in the Cook Islands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207095","207095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89648","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the use of components for Paveway II bombs manufactured by Raytheon in Scotland by Israeli military forces during Operation Protective Edge.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207102","207102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89649","2014-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reason the UK abstained from voting on the motion entitled, Ensuring respect for international law in the Occupied Palestinian Territory, including East Jerusalem at the 21st Special Session of the UN Human Rights Council.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207437","207437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89650","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Botswana; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207141","207141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89651","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Malawi; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207168","207168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89652","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in Namibia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207169","207169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89653","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in India; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207170","207170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89654","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote LGBT rights in the Maldives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207171","207171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89655","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 July 2014, Official Report, column 1050W, on the Middle East, when his Department will conduct a full assessment of whether Israeli military action during Operation Protective Edge has complied with its international legal obligations.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207156","207156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89656","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the political activities of MQM in Pakistan.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207126","207126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89657","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of whether recent Israeli military operations in Gaza are in breach of international law.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207151","207151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89658","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many new EU directives and regulations have been transposed into UK law by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207260","207260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89659","2014-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the proposals for a lasting ceasefire in Gaza.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207522","207522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89660","2014-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which HM embassies and high commissions have a designated contact for the strategy for supporting human rights defenders working on issues related to business and human rights.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207472","207472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89661","2014-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with which companies (a) Ministers in his Department and (b) HM embassies and high commissions have discussed the UK Action Plan on Business and Human Rights in the last year.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207473","207473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89662","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Kurdistan Regional Government or its representatives in the UK on the situation in that region.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207428","207428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89663","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2014, Official Report, column 726-8W, on Conflict Resolution: Females, if he will place in the Library copies of the minutes of the inter-departmental meetings referenced in that Answer.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207409","207409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89664","2014-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to improve access to remedies for victims of human rights abuses involving UK business operating overseas.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207475","207475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89665","2014-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effects of the Government's Action Plan on Business and Human Rights in the last year on the (a) conduct, planning and composition of Ministerial-led trade delegations and (b) operations overseas of British businesses.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207474","207474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89666","2014-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department has provided to help UK businesses uphold their responsibilities to international human rights in the last year.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207476","207476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89667","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress his Department has made on exploring potential funding options for the Causeway British-Irish Exchange Programme.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207497","207497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89668","2014-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the Foreign Affairs Committee's recommendation in the Fifth Report of Session 2013-14, The UK's Relations with Saudi Arabia and Bahrain, HC 88, paragraph 214, that Bahrain should be designated as a country of concern if no significant progress had been made by the start of 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207489","207489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89669","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Saudi Arabia on each of the executions by public beheading carried out in that country in August 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207513","207513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89670","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Saudi government about the funding of ISIS by Saudi citizens since 2012.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207360","207360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89671","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the human rights situation in Iran; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207297","207297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89672","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the safety of Christians in those parts of Iraq currently controlled by ISIL.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207424","207424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89673","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what meetings he or Ministers in his Department have had with civil society or religious groups based in the UK to discuss the situation in Israel and Palestine since the start of July 2014; and which such groups have met on what dates.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207414","207414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89674","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to international bodies on the protection of Christians in those parts of Iraq currently controlled by ISIL.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207425","207425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89675","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to protect Christians in northern Iraq.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207401","207401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89676","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the situation for Christians in northern Iraq.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207402","207402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89677","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that foreign nationals pay for healthcare they receive in the UK.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207406","207406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89678","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department is giving to King's College London to work on developing the MAP vaccine for Crohn's disease from animal testing to human trials.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207417","207417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89679","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS staff were employed on administrative tasks in (a) 2010 and (b) 2014; and what proportion of the total NHS wage bill they represented in each year.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207369","207369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89680","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many incidents in which non-patient egg donors had (a) severe ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome and (b) ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome were categorised as (i) Grade A incidents and (ii) Grade B incidents in each year since 2009 for which records are available.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207298","207298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89681","2014-09-03","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on making it easier for licensed medication drugs to be used for off-patent treatments.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207483","207483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89682","2014-09-03","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP surgeries which receive income from the minimum price income guarantee are in areas which are high on the deprivation index.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207477","207477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89683","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that patients with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD) have access to oxygen therapy when travelling abroad; for what reason the NHS contractor in England no longer provides that service; and if his Department will instruct the contractor to fully inform COPD patients about the provision of oxygen therapy when they are travelling abroad.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207504","207504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89684","2014-09-03","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse is of freezing the withdrawal of the minimum price income guarantee from GP practices which receive it as of 1 August 2014.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207478","207478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89685","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many of the NHS trusts involved in the Sign up to safety campaign have a policy of stocking medicines for the treatment of Parkinson's disease in their emergency medications cupboards.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207495","207495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89686","2014-09-03","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the definition of e-cigarettes as tobacco products under the terms of the Framework Convention on Tobacco Control.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207464","207464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89687","2014-09-03","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on precautionary measures to protect against the spread of the Ebola virus.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207467","207467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89688","2014-09-03","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish his Department's impact assessment relating to the consultation into standardised tobacco packaging in a wider range of languages.","Biography information for Richard Harrington","Richard Harrington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207457","207457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89689","2014-09-03","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training and guidance on the Ebola virus has been issued to staff at airports and ports in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207466","207466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89690","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to improve compliance in (a) hospitals and (b) care homes with the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence guidelines that people with Parkinson's disease should have their medication given at appropriate times and should be allowed to self-administer if necessary.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207493","207493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89691","2014-09-03","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department is giving to clinical commissioning groups to process retrospective continuing care claims.","Biography information for Richard Harrington","Richard Harrington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207458","207458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89692","2014-09-03","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent reports he has received of food contamination at chicken abattoirs in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207468","207468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89693","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the new NHS safety action team plans to take to reduce avoidable harm resulting from delays or omissions in medication for hospital patients with Parkinson's disease.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207494","207494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89694","2014-09-03","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, under what timetable his Department plans to phase-out use of telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, 0844 and 0843 in accordance with the Cabinet Office guidance on customer service lines published in December 2013 and (b) 03 and 08, where 03 is the primary number under a dual numbering system.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207452","207452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89695","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many new EU directives and regulations have been transposed into UK law by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207261","207261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89696","2014-09-03","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress clinical commissioning groups have made in (a) processing retrospective continuing care claims and (b) the payment of compensation to affected families.","Biography information for Richard Harrington","Richard Harrington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207531","207531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89697","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ask the Food Standards Agency to assess the level of food contamination at chicken abattoirs in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207147","207147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89698","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support research into neuroblastoma.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207129","207129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89699","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of ambulances in (a) the East Midlands and (b) High Peak constituency failed to respond within their targeted response times in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207318","207318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89700","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulance calls from (a) the East Midlands and (b) High Peak constituency were responded to in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207319","207319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89701","2014-09-03","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the number of avoidable deaths from breast cancer and to improve survival rates for that disease.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207436","207436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89702","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received regarding the General Dental Council's proposed increase to the annual retention fee for dentists.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207132","207132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89703","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has plans to create a nationally agreed structure for medical teachers.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207155","207155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89704","2014-09-03","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to create an effective national mechanism for payment for the academic development of medical teachers.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207442","207442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89705","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve public awareness of neuroblastoma.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207162","207162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89706","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps (a) his Department and (b) NHS England have taken to ensure that accessible information is produced about multiple sclerosis treatment options.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207186","207186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89707","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of progress on the Cancer Strategy target of saving an additional 5,000 lives from cancer per year by 2014-15.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207197","207197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89708","2014-09-03","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of whether payments mechanisms to medical schools in the form of SIFT funding are resulting in general practices being underpaid.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207441","207441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89709","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on research into fybromyalgia in the last three years; and what guidance his Department gives on support to be given through the NHS for fybromyalgia sufferers.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207313","207313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89710","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cycles of IVF treatment are offered free of charge to patients by each clinical commissioning group in England.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207079","207079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89711","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that regular reviews of treatment and care by multiple sclerosis (MS) specialists are available for all people with MS in England.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207243","207243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89712","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the levels of patient satisfaction with the NHS Choose and Book service.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207283","207283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89713","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department is providing to King's College London to assist the development of the MAP vaccine for Crohn's disease from animal testing to human trials.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207271","207271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89714","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with (a) NHS bodies and (b) patients' groups on the effectiveness of the NHS Choose and Book service.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207282","207282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89715","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of appointments booked through the NHS Choose and Book service in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207281","207281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89716","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the practicality and safety of the recycling of prosthesis components issued by the NHS.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207347","207347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89717","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of repairs to prostheses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207348","207348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89718","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 12 May 2014, Official Report, column 406W, on Standardised Packaging for Tobacco Independent Review, how much was spent under each cost-heading during the life of the Review.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207354","207354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89719","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of fybromyalgia sufferers in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207312","207312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89720","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the provision of licensed treatments for multiple sclerosis in the NHS in England; and if he will take steps to increase the availability of such treatments.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207242","207242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89721","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many requests have been made by dental practices in England for their Unit of Dental Activity price to be increased in the latest period for which figures are available; and how many such requests have been granted.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207204","207204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89722","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Palliative Care Funding Review pilots are due to report.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207198","207198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89723","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps (a) his Department and (b) NHS England are taking to address weaknesses in cancer patient experience and staff engagement.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207199","207199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89724","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to increase the role of people with multiple sclerosis in decision-making processes relating to their treatment.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207193","207193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89725","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that NHS staff can access training and development on providing care with dignity and respect.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207200","207200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89726","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that all people with relapsing remitting multiple sclerosis are invited to talk with a specialist about potential treatment options arising from new disease-modifying drugs.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207203","207203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89727","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on the purchase of televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207216","207216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89728","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on the purchase of televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207217","207217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89729","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she intends to take to implement the recommendations made in the Independent Inquiry into child sexual exploitation in Rotherham from 1997 to 2013.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207397","207397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89730","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what analysis her Department has undertaken of the reasons for visa refusals arising from unconditional and conditional offers of student places; and if she will place this analysis in the Library.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207346","207346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89731","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff have been transferred to HM Passport Office from other Government departments and agencies in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207328","207328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89732","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much UK Border Force and its predecessor bodies has spent on infrastructure at Stansted Airport in the last five years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207275","207275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89733","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK Border Force personnel have been deployed at (a) Gatwick, (b) Heathrow, (c) Luton, (d) Stansted and (e) Southend airport in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207274","207274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89734","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the UK Border Force is taking to reduce queuing and improve the passenger experience at Stansted Airport.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207268","207268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89735","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contingency plans are in place to handle electronic failures at e-passport gates at Stansted Airport.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207269","207269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89736","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department will publish the review of the operation of sections 135 and 136 of the Mental Health Act 1983 in England and Wales.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207125","207125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89737","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she proposes to take to improve the efficiency of the process of returning passports to applicants within the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207146","207146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89738","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Tier 1 post-study work visas were issued in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011 and (d) 2012.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207121","207121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89739","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Tier 2 General Visas have been issued to international students since the withdrawal of the Tier 1 Post-Study Work Visa.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207120","207120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89740","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of the West Midlands Police and Crime Commissioner by-election held on 21 August 2014.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207187","207187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89741","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost of paying compensation for missing passports dispatched within the UK from her Department and departmental offices in 2013-14.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207154","207154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89742","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of whether it would be cost-effective and secure to allow visa applicants within the UK the option of collecting documents from a designated office instead of relying on second class post.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207148","207148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89743","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many new EU directives and regulations have been transposed into UK law by her Department since May 2010.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207262","207262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89744","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reports her Department has commissioned into child abuse in the last 25 years; and what steps her Department took in response to the conclusions and recommendations in each such report.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207502","207502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89745","2014-09-03","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to prevent UK nationals joining IS.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207525","207525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89746","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department provides support to people with (a) disability and (b) other special needs in meeting the cost of acquiring a Security Industry Authority licence.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207499","207499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89747","2014-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many joint search warrants have been applied for by the police and another applicant and issued by the courts in England and Wales in the last five years; and who the other applicant was in each such case.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207544","207544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89748","2014-09-03","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, under what timetable her Department plans to phase-out the use of telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, 0844 and 0843 in accordance with the Cabinet Office guidance on customer service lines published in December 2013 and (b) 03 and 08, where 03 is the primary number under a dual numbering system.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207454","207454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89749","2014-09-03","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many individuals have been granted limited leave to remain with no recourse to public funds in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207459","207459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89750","2014-09-03","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what legal costs have been incurred by her Department for costs associated with the recent Raytheon e-borders arbitration tribunal.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207485","207485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89751","2014-09-03","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what meetings the Minister for Security and Immigration has had with the Chief Executive and senior officials of HM Passport Service since November 2013.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207490","207490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89752","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of whether the cost of acquiring the Security Industry Authority licence acts as a barrier to people entering the private investigation trade.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207498","207498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89753","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to tackle the problem of companies offering bogus or limited alternatives to the Security Industry Authority licence.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207500","207500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89754","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many University-sponsored Graduate Entrepreneur Tier 1 visas have been issued since 6 April 2013.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207372","207372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89755","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many small and medium-sized enterprises in each (a) district, (b) county and (c) unitary authority hold a Tier 2 general sponsor licence.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207370","207370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89756","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many employers in the creative industries, as defined in the Government's 2001 Creative Industries Mapping  Document, hold a Tier 2 general sponsor licence.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207371","207371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89757","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people resident within the ML postcode area were (a) issued with passports for collection and (b) called for interviews at offices outside Scotland in each of the last four years for which information is available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207359","207359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89758","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the nationality and gender was of each suspected victim of trafficking referred to the Trafficking Victim Support Scheme operated by the Salvation Army in August 2014; in which (a) region and (b) county each of the suspected victims was found; which agency referred each person to the Scheme; in which town was the shelter to which they were placed for the relevant period; and what contact is had with each victim after they exit the shelter to ensure they are not re-trafficked.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207358","207358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89759","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many grants of settlement were given to Tier 1 (Post Study Work) visa holders since 2009; and what the countries of origin were of those granted settlement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207375","207375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89760","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the full Standard Occupational Code groups for all international students employed under the former Tier 1 Post Study Work visa for 2011 referrred to in her Department's Impact Assessment, Reform of the Points Based Student System, published on 1 June 2011.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207378","207378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89761","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether staff answering calls to the UK Visas and Immigration MPs' Hotline who are not directly employed by the Home Office receive the same training and have access to the same information as staff who are directly employed.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207384","207384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89762","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of staff answering enquiries to the UK Visas and Immigration MPs' Hotline have been directly employed by the Home Office in the last six months.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207385","207385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89763","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contingency plans are in place to handle electronic failures at e-passport gates at Stansted Airport.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207423","207423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89764","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have been deported to other European countries in each of the last four years.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207405","207405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89765","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much UK Border Force has spent at Stansted Airport in the last five years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207422","207422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89766","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish her Department's assessment of the effect of the Tier-1 Post Study Work route on domestic graduate unemployment levels; and what steps she took to ascertain the effect on employment amongst that group before her decision to close that scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207413","207413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89767","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK Border Force personnel have been deployed at (a) Gatwick, (b) Heathrow, (c) Luton, (d) Stansted and (e) Southend airports in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207421","207421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89768","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps UK Border Force took to reduce queuing and improve the passenger experience at Stansted Airport in the last summer.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207420","207420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89769","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that all victims of domestic violence are given equal protection irrespective of gender or sexual orientation.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207382","207382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89770","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what private companies have been contracted to answer enquiries to the UK Visas and Immigration MPs' Hotline in the last six months.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207386","207386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89771","2014-09-02","House of Commons Commission","2014-08-29","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, how much the House of Commons Commission spent on the purchase of televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207218","207218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89772","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on the purchase of televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207219","207219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89773","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what humanitarian and medical support the Government is providing to the population of Gaza.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207241","207241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89774","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure vulnerable people in Gambia are not affected by the decision of the EU to suspend aid to that country.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207272","207272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89775","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, under what timetable her Department plans to phase out use of telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, 0844 and 0843 in accordance with the Cabinet Office guidance on customer service lines published in December 2013 and (b) 03 and 08, where 03 is the primary number under a dual numbering system.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207287","207287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89776","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Syria.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207135","207135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89777","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports she has received on (a) the humanitarian situation in the Central African Republic and (b) the humanitarian implications of broader insecurity in the Sahel.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207137","207137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89778","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what policies and programmes her Department has to tackle female genital mutilation and early forced marriage; and what progress has been made in this area following the Prime Minister's Girl Summit held in July 2014.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207136","207136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89779","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many young people are involved in the International Citizens Service in (a) Brighton and Hove, (b) East Sussex and (c) South East England; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207139","207139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89780","2014-09-03","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which companies in Tanzania have received how much in funding from her Department since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207440","207440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89781","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress has been made in the negotiations towards achieving a post-2015 set of millennium development goals; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207140","207140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89782","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to help the Philippines recover and build resilience after Typhoon Haiyan.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207138","207138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89783","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the UK is taking to end aid dependency in countries which receive UK aid; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207088","207088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89784","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effects on her Department's aid programme in Nepal of the formation of the new government in that country.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207089","207089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89785","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to provide humanitarian assistance in Eastern Ukraine; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207090","207090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89786","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that vulnerable people in Gambia are not affected by deteriorating conditions as a result of the suspension of aid and human rights violations.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207416","207416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89787","2014-09-02","Department for International Development","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many new EU directives and regulations have been transposed into UK law by her Department since May 2010.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207263","207263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89788","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new EU directives and regulations have been transposed into UK law by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207264","207264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89789","2014-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department will publish the review of all driving offences and penalties announced on 6 May 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207530","207530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89790","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 10 October 2013, Official Report, column 377W, on courts: Sunderland, what progress has been made on plans to rebuild Sunderland court.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207412","207412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89791","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent on building, refurbishment and maintenance in Crawley Magistrates' Court in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207403","207403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89792","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders in each prison in England and Wales were eligible for unemployment pay as set out in paragraph 2.2.1 of Prison Service Order 4460 in the last (a) week, (b) month and (c) year for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207336","207336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89793","2014-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions since May 2010 a Rule 43 ruling has been used in coronial verdicts.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207456","207456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89794","2014-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what type of statutory instrument he plans to introduce to bring the temporary exemption for insolvency litigation under the Legal Aid Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 to an end in April 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207439","207439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89795","2014-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether an impact assessment has been carried out on the amount of reduced income that creditors will receive as a result of the proposed end of the temporary exemption for insolvency litigation under the Legal Aid Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 which is planned for April 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207438","207438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89796","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many repeat juvenile offenders in (a) South Staffordshire constituency, (b) Staffordshire and (c) Wolverhampton were cautioned or sentenced for recordable offences in each of the last five years; and how many and what proportion of total offences were attributable to such offenders in that period.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207310","207310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89797","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, under what timetable his Department plans to phase out use of telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, 0844 and 0843 in accordance with the Cabinet Office guidance on customer service lines published in December 2013 and (b) 03 and 08, where 03 is the primary number under a dual numbering system.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207291","207291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89798","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many repeat offenders in (a) South Staffordshire constituency, (b) Staffordshire and (c) Wolverhampton were cautioned or sentenced for recordable offences in each of the last five years; and how many and what proportion of total offences were attributable to such offenders in that period.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207309","207309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89799","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many determinate sentence prisoners with more than two years to serve to their earliest release date were moved to open prisons in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2011-12.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207334","207334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89800","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was paid in unemployment pay to offenders in each prison in England and Wales under paragraph 2.2.1 of Prison Service Order 4460 in the last (a) week, (b) month and (c) year for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207335","207335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89801","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women aged 18 years and above from each ethnic group were sentenced to custody for a first offence, broken down by (a) offence type and (b) sentence length in the last two full years for which data is available.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207307","207307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89802","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisoners in each prison in England and Wales were working in industrial activity in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207329","207329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89803","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much the National Offender Management Service spent on subsidising its retail canteen service contract in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207330","207330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89804","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on the purchase of televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207220","207220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89805","2014-09-02","Leader of the House","2014-08-29","To ask the Leader of the House, how much his Office spent on the purchase of televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207221","207221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89806","2014-09-02","Northern Ireland Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department spent on the purchase of televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207222","207222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89807","2014-09-02","Northern Ireland Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, under what timetable her Department plans to phase out use of telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, 0844 and 0843 in accordance with the Cabinet Office guidance on customer service lines published in December 2013 and (b) 03 and 08, where 03 is the primary number under a dual numbering system.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207290","207290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89808","2014-09-02","Northern Ireland Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress has been made on extending the Warm Homes Discount Scheme to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207152","207152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89809","2014-09-02","Prime Minister","2014-08-29","To ask the Prime Minister, what meetings he has had with civil society or religious groups based in the UK which have discussed the situation in Israel and Palestine since 1 July 2014; which organisations he has met; and when each such meeting took place.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207286","207286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89810","2014-09-02","Prime Minister","2014-08-29","To ask the Prime Minister, what meetings he had with civil society or religious groups based in the UK to discuss the situation in Israel and Palestine since the start of July 2014; and what the name of each such group and the date of each meeting was.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207415","207415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89811","2014-09-02","Public Accounts Commission","2014-08-29","To ask the Chairman of the Public Accounts Commission, how much the Public Accounts Commission spent on televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207145","207145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89812","2014-09-02","Scotland Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on the purchase of televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207223","207223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89813","2014-09-02","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2014-08-29","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, how much the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority spent on televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207142","207142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89814","2014-09-02","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-08-29","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how much the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission spent on televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207144","207144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89815","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many driving licence (a) applications and (b) renewals breached the target timeframe for processing in each of the last five years; and in how many such cases the breach arose as a result of delays in medical assessments.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207167","207167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89816","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the current level of compliance is with the Merchant Shipping (Emergency Equipment Lockers for Ro/Ro Passenger Ships) Regulations 1988 amongst ship owners operating licensed passenger ferry services from UK ports; what the penalties are for non-compliance; and if he will publish a list of all instances of non-compliance with these regulations recorded by the Maritime and Coastguard Agency since 1988.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207127","207127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89817","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions he has met representatives of the insurance industry in the last 12 months; and what issues were discussed at those meetings.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207149","207149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89818","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the process is for the review of the National Rail Conditions of Carriage; when that review will be completed; and whether there will be consultation with (a) consumer groups and (b) the general public about the outcome of that review.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207166","207166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89819","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Maritime and Coastguard Agency's (MCA) annual budget was for promoting the UK Shipping Register internationally to encourage ship owners to register their ships in the UK in each year since 2009-10; and what the MCA's budget is for such work in 2015-16.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207097","207097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89820","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many recorded hit and run incidents where the driver was (a) caught and (b) not caught there have been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207106","207106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89821","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many officials from the UK Chamber of Shipping have been seconded to work in his Department since May 2010; and in what areas of maritime policy each such member of staff has been so employed.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207103","207103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89822","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a charge of killing or injuring someone through a hit and run.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207099","207099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89823","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fixed penalty notices were issued in each region and constituent part of the UK for use of hand-held mobile telephones whilst driving in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207100","207100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89824","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many recorded hit and run incidents involving (a) injury and (b) death there have been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207107","207107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89825","2014-09-02","Home Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many traffic police officers were employed in each police force area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207101","207101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89826","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many overseas visit trips (a) Ministers, (b) officials in his Department and (c) officials from the Maritime and Coastguard Agency have undertaken in each year since 2009-10 to promote the UK Shipping Register to ship owners; and what the (i) destination and (ii) cost was of each such trip.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207104","207104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89827","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Maritime and Coastguard Agency's (MCA) annual budget for promoting seafarer safety to ship owners operating in the UK was in each year since 2009-10; and what the MCA's budget for such work is in 2015-16.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207105","207105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89828","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drivers charged with dangerous driving offences were made to surrender their licence as a condition of bail in the last year.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207113","207113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89829","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department has allocated to each local authority in the West Midlands for road improvement in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207314","207314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89830","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the current level of compliance is with the (a) Merchant Shipping (Weighing of Goods Vehicles and other Cargo) Regulations 1988, (b) Merchant Shipping (Weighing of Goods Vehicles and other Cargo) (Amendment) Regulations 1989 and (c) Merchant Shipping (Weighing of Goods Vehicles and other Cargo) (Application to non-UK Ships) Regulations 1989 at each UK port licensed to operate passenger ferry services.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207124","207124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89831","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the current target timeframe is for processing of driving licence (a) applications and (b) renewals; and whether the same timeframe applies in the case of licences that have a medical test as part of the application.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207185","207185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89832","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on the purchase of televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207224","207224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89833","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many driving licence (a) applications and (b) renewals the DVLA has received in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207184","207184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89834","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, under what timetable his Department plans to phase out use of telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, 0844 and 0843 in accordance with the Cabinet Office guidance on customer service lines published in December 2013 and (b) 03 and 08, where 03 is the primary number under a dual numbering system.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207289","207289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89835","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the request under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 of 10 February 2014, reference F0001198, for what reasons the Maritime and Coastguard Agency cannot attribute incidents to any particular Maritime Rescue Coordination Centre.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207419","207419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89836","2014-09-03","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what sanctions are taken against Network Rail when engineering works overrun causing disruption to the rail network.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207448","207448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89837","2014-09-03","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps are being taken to minimise the overrunning of engineering works on the London Liverpool Street - Chelmsford - Colchester - Ipswich railway line.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207449","207449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89838","2014-09-03","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what sanctions have been imposed on Network Rail as a result of engineering works overrunning and causing disruption to the rail service on the London Liverpool Street - Chelmsford - Colchester - Ipswich railway line in the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207446","207446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89839","2014-09-03","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions engineering works carried out by Network Rail on the London Liverpool Street - Chelmsford - Colchester - Ipswich railway line have overrun causing disruption to the service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207447","207447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89840","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department's Review of Motoring Offences will be published.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207433","207433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89841","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many new EU directives and regulations have been transposed into UK law by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207265","207265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89842","2014-09-02","Department for Transport","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the request to his Department under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 of 10 February 2014, ref. F0001198, for what reasons the Maritime and Coastguard Agency cannot attribute incidents to any particular Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207536","207536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89843","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department monitors the number of employment and support allowance claims which are awaiting action by (a) a work capability assessment provider and (b) his Department.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207549","207549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89844","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is his Department's policy to permit jobseeker's allownce claimants who follow their advisor's instructions to attend a jobcentre course instead of signing on to be sanctioned or have their claim stopped because they did not sign on.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207548","207548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89845","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new EU directives and regulations have been transposed into UK law by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207267","207267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89846","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have been moved to contribution-based employment and support allowance (ESA) from a combination of incapacity benefit and income support since ESA was introduced.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207511","207511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89847","2014-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 8 April 2014, Official Report, column 220W, on the Work Programme, what the cost is of paying a second attachment fee for persons transferred from Newcastle College to new providers; and what other additional costs his Department incurs as a result of that transfer.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207491","207491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89848","2014-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many computers have been installed for use in Jobcentre Plus offices in the UK in 2014-15; and what estimate he has made of the number of computers so installed by the end of the current financial year.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207488","207488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89849","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease (a) have applied for personal independence payments (PIPs), (b) are receiving PIPs and (c) have been refused PIPs.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207496","207496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89850","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has taken steps to inform people moving to contribution-based employment and support allowance that they may no longer be entitled to free dental care, eye care and prescriptions.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207507","207507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89851","2014-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many mandatory reconsideration periods for employment and support allowance his Department has conducted to date; what the outcomes were of each such case; and what the (a) shortest, (b) average and (c) longest periods were.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207486","207486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89852","2014-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what average length of time his Department takes to process applications for hardship payments; and what targets he has set for the processing of such claims.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207487","207487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89853","2014-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will undertake a separate impact assessment of the closure of the Independent Living Fund on demand for (a) NHS and (b) social care services.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207484","207484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89854","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to assist employment and support allowance claimants with medical costs including dental care, eye care and prescriptions.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207506","207506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89855","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with (a) individuals and (b) organisations on employment and support allowance and eligibility for free dental care, eye care and prescriptions.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207505","207505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89856","2014-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time was between (a) an employment and support allowance applicant submitting an ESA 50 questionnaire and undergoing a work capability assessment, (b) an employment and support allowance applicant undergoing a work capability assessment and advice being submitted to a decision-maker and (c) advice being submitted to a decision-maker and a decision being issued to an employment and support allowance applicant in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207460","207460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89857","2014-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether people with mental health conditions may be refused disability benefits on the grounds that their condition does not require the use of aides.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207471","207471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89858","2014-09-02","Cabinet Office","2014-08-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the current claimant rate is for jobseeker's allowance in Thirsk and Malton constituency.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207427","207427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89859","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when applications for personal independence payment will be able to be made online.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207418","207418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89860","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress has been made on making statistics on mandatory reconsiderations for jobseeker's allowance and employment and support allowance publicly available.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207337","207337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89861","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints have been (a) made and (b) upheld against the Children and Family Court Advisory and Support Service in the last three years.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207300","207300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89862","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the comparative performance of Capita and Atos in conducting personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207332","207332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89863","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, under what timetable his Department plans to phase out use of telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, 0844 and 0843 in accordance with the Cabinet Office guidance on customer service lines published in December 2013 and (b) 03 and 08, where 03 is the primary number under a dual numbering system.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207288","207288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89864","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment (a) registrations and (b) decisions were made in the (i) KA and (ii) PA postcode areas between April 2013 and March 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207333","207333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89865","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the average waiting time for personal independence payments assessments in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207356","207356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89866","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of applicants for personal independence payments who have waited longer than 26 weeks for an assessment in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207357","207357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89867","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what mean length of time between a personal independence payment claim being registered and a decision being made was on (a) claims not made under special rules for terminally ill people and (b) claims made under special rules for terminally ill people where the decision was taken between April 2013 and March 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207331","207331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89868","2014-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints have been made against the Children and Family Court Advisory and Support Service in the last three years; and how many such complaints have been upheld.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207284","207284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89869","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial information is sent to his Department from individual local authorities on the administrative costs incurred in the preparation for, and the processing of, the under-occupancy penalty; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Charles Kennedy","Mr Charles Kennedy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207327","207327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89870","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when applications for personal independent payment will be available online.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207270","207270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89871","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial gain his Department has made arising from the use of telephone lines which are not free to call in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207183","207183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89872","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people received a reduced rate of incapacity benefit as a result of receiving a pension income of more than £85 in 2013-14.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207182","207182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89873","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people received a reduced rate of employment and support allowance as a result of receiving a pension income of more than £85 in 2013-14.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207181","207181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89874","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much expenditure his Department allocated to universal credit (a) between April 2013 and May 2014 and (b) to date.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207112","207112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89875","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the effects of the under-occupancy penalty on social housing tenants in (a) Brighton and Hove and (b) East Sussex; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207092","207092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89876","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the effects of the benefits cap on reducing unemployment in Brighton, Kemptown constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207091","207091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89877","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2014, Official Report, column 180W, on social security benefits, if he will conduct an estimate of the saving to the public purse generated by the reduction of (a) employment and support allowance and (b) incapacity benefit for individuals in receipt of a pension income of more than £85 per week in 2013-14.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207081","207081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89878","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an estimate of (a) the amount of savings accruing to the public purse through penalties incurred on housing benefit arising from the under occupancy penalty to date and (b) the amount paid in discretionary housing payments in that time.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207317","207317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89879","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what right of appeal claimants will have against reports and decisions made through doorstep interviews where their benefits are affected; and by what legislative means that system of appeals will be introduced.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207153","207153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89880","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) work capability assessments and (b) personal independence payment assessments has been undertaken by Atos in (i) the South West, (ii) Gloucestershire and (iii) Gloucester in the last 12 months; and how many assessments resulted in the claimant being found fit for work.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207128","207128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89881","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what performance targets his Department has set for Atos's contract under the work capability assessment; and whether such targets have been met.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207158","207158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89882","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of Atos's performance in carrying out personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207159","207159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89883","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many medically qualified staff have been employed by Atos in (a) Gloucestershire and (b) Gloucester in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207160","207160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89884","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time is which a caller to a Department for Work and Pensions telephone line which is not free to call is made to wait while on hold, when listening to a pre-recorded message or selecting options at the start of a telephone call; and what the financial gain is to his Department from the charge levied for a call of that length.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207173","207173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89885","2014-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will take steps to work with HM Treasury to ensure that, where future savings in the attendance allowance budget result from greater numbers of care home residents starting to qualify for local authority-funded care, those savings could be used to help local authorities with their wider responsibilities to meet care and support needs.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207196","207196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89888","2014-09-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of his Department's Universal Jobmatch website.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905114","905114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89889","2014-09-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the employment outcomes of people affected by the benefit cap.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905116","905116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89890","2014-09-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the operation of the under-occupancy penalty so that it applies only when suitable alternative accommodation is readily available.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905118","905118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89891","2014-09-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-08-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how long the average wait for an assessment for a personal independence payment was on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905122","905122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89992","2014-09-02","HM Treasury","2014-08-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has made to institutions of the EU on the cap on bank bonuses.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905051","905051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/89993","2014-09-02","HM Treasury","2014-08-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the level of employment.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905064","905064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90102","2014-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with Qatar's Supreme Committee for Delivery and Legacy on the safety and wellbeing of migrant workers preparing that country for the 2022 World Cup.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905136","905136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90106","2014-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-08-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to address the treatment of workers in Qatar during the construction of World Cup 2022 venues.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905123","905123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90234","2014-09-02","HM Treasury","2014-08-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has for future funding for a new M6 South road link to the M54.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905046","905046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90399","2014-09-03","Department for International Development","2014-08-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what help she plans to give to children in Gaza who require support to deal with trauma related to bombing.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905131","905131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90400","2014-09-03","Department for International Development","2014-08-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, for what reasons she decided to end her Department's role in the Bost Agricultural Business Park project in Afghanistan in 2012.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905132","905132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79203","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of international harmonisation of the 700 MHz band of radio spectrum on domestic small and medium-sized enterprises operating within (a) the programme making and special events sector and (b) the creative industries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206818","206818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79204","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what requirements there are for delivery partners to monitor the gender of (a) applicants for and (b) recipients of government-backed (i) grants and (ii) loan schemes.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206824","206824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79205","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of applicants for (a) grants or (b) loans underwritten by the Government were female in the last five years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206825","206825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79206","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of recipients of (a) grants or (b) loans underwritten by the Government were female in the last five years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206822","206822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79207","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings in the last year between financial sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials in his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206895","206895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79208","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings in the last year between agricultural sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials in his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206896","206896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79209","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings in the last year between pharmaceutical sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials in his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206897","206897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79210","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings in the last year between chemical sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials in his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206898","206898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79211","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings in the last year between manufacturing sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials in his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206899","206899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79212","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings in the last year between energy sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials in his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206900","206900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79213","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings in the last year between insurance sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials in his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206901","206901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79214","2014-09-01","Cabinet Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which government departments do not pay all employees the living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation; and how much less than the living wage those departments pay.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206840","206840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79215","2014-09-04","Cabinet Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what arrangements his Department has put in place for the public recognition of acts of heroism by private citizens; if he will make it his policy to apply these to the women who confronted the killers of Fusilier Lee Rigby and who sought to help the attacked soldier; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206872","206872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79216","2014-09-01","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-22","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what steps he is taking to increase voter turnout in local elections among 18 to 25 year-olds.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206863","206863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79217","2014-09-01","HM Treasury","2014-07-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has received any requests from the Welsh Government for loans or grants for the construction of the Circuit of Wales.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206834","206834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79218","2014-09-01","HM Treasury","2014-07-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2014, Official Report, column 355W, on consumers: protection, what assessment he has made of the effect on consumers of the limits on the Financial Conduct Authority's powers to issue fines in cases which involve (a) breaches before April 2014 and (b) investigations begun by other agencies before April 2014.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206826","206826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79219","2014-09-01","HM Treasury","2014-07-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the likely reduction to the block grant for Northern Ireland in the current financial year arising from lack of progress on welfare reform difficulties.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206837","206837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79220","2014-09-01","Department for Transport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of (a) taking the Highways Agency out of public ownership and (b) rebranding the Highways Agency, including (i) the replacement of uniforms and equipment of the staff of the Highways Agency and (ii) the replacement of liveries on the vehicles operated by the Highways Agency.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206862","206862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79221","2014-09-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what powers his Department has made available to councils to deal with illegal Traveller sites; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206832","206832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79222","2014-09-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities in England and Wales have been required to increase the amount of housing they will permit in their local plans.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206853","206853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79223","2014-09-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many houses have been completed in each local authority area in each of the last five years; how many such houses are affordable houses built under a section 106 agreement; and what proportion of the total number of houses on each scheme built in that time are houses built under section 106 agreements.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206859","206859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79224","2014-09-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities have a Community Infrastructure Levy (a) approved and (b) in operation.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206860","206860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79225","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the costs likely to be incurred by the programme making and special effects sector through having to complete research and development into new equipment of the re-allocation of the 700 MHz band; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206823","206823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79226","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will request Ofcom to undertake an independent analysis of (a) the need of mobile network operators to be granted access to additional radio spectrum and (b) the quantity of spectrum currently allocated to mobile network operators of which they are not making use to provide mobile connectivity for consumers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206819","206819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79227","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the validity of mobile network operators' requirement for access to an increased quantity of radio spectrum; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206820","206820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79228","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, for what reason his Department did not identify an alternative spectrum for use by the programme making and special events sector before the proposals to withdraw this sector's access to the 700 MHz band of radio spectrum; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206821","206821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79229","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the efficiency with which mobile companies make use of the radio spectrum to which they currently have access; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206817","206817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79230","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the BBC Trust on accounting for the BBC's contribution to spending on local television.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206835","206835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79231","2014-09-01","Department for Education","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2014, Official Report, column 63W, on teachers: offences against, what information her Department holds and in what format on cases considered by the National College for Teaching and Leadership.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206836","206836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79232","2014-09-01","Department for Education","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who the approved Academy sponsors for primary and secondary schools are in Sheffield.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206858","206858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79233","2014-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she has any plans to introduce minimum welfare requirements for keeping pet rabbits.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206868","206868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79234","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in how many meetings in the last year between financial sector professionals and Ministers or Senior officials in his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206902","206902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79235","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in how many meetings in the last year between agricultural sector professionals and Ministers or Senior officials in his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206903","206903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79236","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in how many meetings in the last year between pharmaceutical sector professionals and Ministers or Senior officials in his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206904","206904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79237","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in how many meetings in the last year between chemical sector professionals and Ministers or Senior officials in his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206905","206905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79238","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in how many meetings in the last year between insurance sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials of his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206879","206879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79239","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to resolve the situation in Gaza and the West Bank.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206861","206861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79240","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to ensure that the UN-led MINUSCA peacekeeping mission in the Central African Republic is well-resourced and fully deployed with the UN authorised number of troops by September 2014.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206850","206850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79241","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received on the right to self-determination of Palestinian people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206864","206864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79242","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to publicise internationally the UK's position on the conflict in Gaza.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206865","206865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79243","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to protect residents of Gaza and the West Bank.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206866","206866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79244","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government is giving to the European Union Force's presence in the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206841","206841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79245","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the support that people at the end of life receive so that they can die in their preferred place of care.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206833","206833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79246","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the number of paramedics and emergency care assistants employed by the East of England Ambulance Trust.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206854","206854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79247","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average amount a full-time NHS worker spends on car parking on NHS sites each year.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206831","206831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79248","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of NHS dentistry contracts that were in place between 1 April 2013 and 31 March 2014; and what the (a) name and (b) location was of each provider.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206851","206851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79249","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what changes there were in the number of people diagnosed with diabetes between 2004 and 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206839","206839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79250","2014-09-01","Home Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letter to her dated 17 June 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms S Rasheed.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206847","206847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79251","2014-09-01","Home Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letter to her dated 16 June 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr F M Bondoki.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206848","206848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79252","2014-09-01","Home Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letter to her dated 10 June 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms Zabada Begum.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206849","206849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79253","2014-09-01","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-22","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what the arrangements were for the selection of the recommended candidate to be Clerk of the House and Chief Executive on each of the last three occasions; and who was on the interviewing board in what capacity on each such occasion.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206827","206827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79254","2014-09-01","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-22","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer to the right hon. Member for Chelmsford of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 725-6W, on Clerk of the House, who initiated the changes to the previous arrangements.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206828","206828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79255","2014-09-01","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-22","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, whether Mr Speaker has a casting vote on the interviewing board for the selection of a recommended candidate to be Clerk of the House and Chief Executive.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206829","206829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79256","2014-09-01","Department for International Development","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will increase financial aid for Palestine.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206867","206867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79257","2014-09-01","Department for International Development","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she will make any changes to aid allocations as a result of the violence in Gaza.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206838","206838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79258","2014-09-01","Prime Minister","2014-07-22","To ask the Prime Minister, when he expects to recommend to HM The Queen a person to be appointed Clerk of the House and Chief Executive of the House of Commons.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206830","206830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79259","2014-09-01","Department for Transport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to prevent the Highways Agency keeping motorways out of action for any longer than necessary in the aftermath of incidents.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206842","206842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79260","2014-09-01","Department for Transport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve the management of traffic in the aftermath of motorway incidents.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206843","206843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79261","2014-09-01","Department for Transport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding he is making available to improve the reliability of rail signalling.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206844","206844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79262","2014-09-01","Department for Transport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Network Rail on improving rail signalling.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206845","206845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79263","2014-09-01","Department for Transport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what future discussions he has planned with Network Rail on improving rail signalling.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206846","206846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79264","2014-09-01","Department for Transport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will issue sanctions against Network Rail for its performance in granting access to tracks for rail operators.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206855","206855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79265","2014-09-01","Department for Transport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that Network Rail improves service reliability.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206856","206856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79266","2014-09-01","Department for Transport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Network Rail on improved performance of services between London and Clacton.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206852","206852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79267","2014-09-01","Wales Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions his Department has had with the Welsh Government on State Aid rules and the Circuit of Wales.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206857","206857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79268","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on mutually-recognised standards in financial services as part of negotiations on the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206894","206894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79269","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on the investor state dispute settlement mechanism in the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206910","206910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79270","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with trades unions on the inclusion of an investor state dispute settlement mechanism in the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206913","206913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79271","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with consumer groups on the inclusion of an investor state dispute settlement mechanism in the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206914","206914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79272","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with health campaigners on the inclusion of an investor state dispute settlement mechanism in the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206915","206915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79273","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with environmental campaigners on the inclusion of an investor state dispute settlement mechanism in the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206916","206916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79274","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on consumers of the inclusion of an investor state dispute settlement mechanism in the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206911","206911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79275","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether cross-border use of personal data is being discussed as part of the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206920","206920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79276","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which existing regulations will not be part of the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206921","206921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79277","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether negotiators are discussing (a) the harmonisation of standards between the EU and US and (b) mutual recognition of standards between the EU and US in the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206922","206922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79278","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will give a formal response to the report published by LSE Enterprise entitled, Costs and Benefits of an EU-US Investment Protection Treaty.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206923","206923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79279","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the rigorousness of the US judicial system towards business; and under what circumstances he would support a dispute settlement mechanism being included in the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206924","206924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79280","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will give hon. Members access to the draft text of the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206925","206925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79281","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on small and medium-sized enterprises operating within the (a) programme making and special events sector and (b) creative industries of reallocation of the 700 MHz band of radio spectrum to use by mobile network operators; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206943","206943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79282","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the corporate events and conference industry of a loss of access by wireless microphone users to the 700 MHz band of radio spectrum; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206944","206944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79283","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answer of 11 December 2013, Official Report, column 247W, on students: loans, how many complaints (a) he and (b) the Office of Fair Trading has received about changes to the conditions of student loans sold to Erudio Student Loans Limited for loan holders (i) nationally and (ii) in Greater Manchester; what steps he has taken to remind Erudio of its responsibility to uphold the original conditions of the loan; what guidance he has issued to purchasers of the student loan book on how student loans impact credit ratings; and if he will place in the Library a copy of that guidance.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206948","206948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79284","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that no rogue batches of e-cigarettes and liquid reach the UK market.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206977","206977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79285","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to announce the implementation of industry standards for those e-cigarettes regulated as consumer products.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206978","206978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79286","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when his Department plans to make a decision about future funding of students and recognition of courses at the 23 private colleges which it suspended from recruiting further students in November 2014.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207043","207043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79287","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what guidance his Department has issued to the 23 private colleges which it suspended from recruiting further students in November 2013 on their ability to advertise and recruit students to commence courses in September 2014.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207044","207044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79288","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has to widen access to and inclusion in further and higher education for mature, disadvantaged and other harder to reach students.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207045","207045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79289","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what allowance his Department makes for the proportion of mature, disadvantage and harder to reach students any college has on its student rolls when assessing the adequacy of the college's student attendance rates.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207046","207046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79290","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans his Department has for increasing the role of private colleges in provision of further and higher education; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207047","207047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79291","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether any official in his Department amended, or caused to be amended, the report of the Internal Audit Investigation Team which visited the London School of Science and Technology between 30 June and 2 July 2014; who made such amendments; and what amendments were so made.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207048","207048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79292","2014-09-01","Cabinet Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Brigg and Goole constituency who are paid at a rate below the living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207032","207032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79293","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings in the last year between financial sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials of his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206880","206880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79294","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings in the last year between agricultural sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials of his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206881","206881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79295","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings in the last year between pharmaceutical sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials of his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206882","206882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79296","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings in the last year between chemical sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials of his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206883","206883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79297","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings in the last year between manufacturing sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials of his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206884","206884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79298","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings in the last year between energy sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials of his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206885","206885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79299","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in how many meetings in the last year between insurance sector professionals and Ministers or senior officials of his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206886","206886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79300","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the continuation to the UK economy by (a) West End theatres, (b) the UK theatre industry and (c) the Programme Making and Special Events (PMSE) sector of a loss of access by the PMSE sector to the 700 MHz band of radio spectrum; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206936","206936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79301","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the economic contribution to the UK economy of (a) West End theatres, (b) the UK theatre industry and (c) the Programme Making and Special Events sector in each year since 2004; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206937","206937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79302","2014-09-01","HM Treasury","2014-07-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has made to the European Commission on the removal of VAT on sanitary products; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206878","206878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79303","2014-09-01","HM Treasury","2014-07-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will introduce legislative proposals to require all retail banks to offer a secure automated messaging services for customers.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206966","206966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79304","2014-09-01","HM Treasury","2014-07-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will request the Financial Policy Committee (FPC) of the Bank of England to provide them with their most recent assessment of risks to UK financial stability arising from investment in high-carbon assets; and if he will place in the Library that request and the FPC response.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207056","207056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79305","2014-09-01","HM Treasury","2014-07-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many leaflets produced by his Department promoting the Government's policy on the Scottish independence referendum have had to be amended, altered or destroyed; and at what cost to the public purse.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207049","207049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79306","2014-09-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many first-time buyers have (a) bought properties in Worcester and (b) been helped by the help-to-buy scheme to purchase properties in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206968","206968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79307","2014-09-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have had with counterparts in the Department for Education on his Department's Information Sharing Guidelines and child protection.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206972","206972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79308","2014-09-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he will update his Department's Information Sharing Guidance.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206970","206970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79309","2014-09-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his Department's Information Sharing Guidelines on providing professionals with information about sharing data in the interests of child protection; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206971","206971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79310","2014-09-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government has taken to implement the EU proposal to replace the royal coat of arms with the EU emblem on birth, death and marriage certificates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206993","206993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79311","2014-09-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new homes Tendring Council must allow for in its local plan.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206877","206877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79312","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on (a) places of worship and (b) community centres of loss of access by wireless microphone users to the 700 MHz band of radio spectrum; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206934","206934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79313","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the (a) film industry and (b) television production industry of a loss of access by wireless microphone users to the 700 MHz band of radio spectrum; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206945","206945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79314","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his policy is on the development by ISPs and copyright owners of Creative Content UK, a programme of education about legal entertainment services, and alerts to subscribers found to have been uploading content illegally online; and what effects he expects the development to have on the implementation of the Digital Economy Act 2010.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206927","206927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79315","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he expects that the Triennial Review of the British Film Institute will be published.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206926","206926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79316","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the programme making and special events (PMSE) sector of a loss of access by PMSE users to the 700 MHz band of radio spectrum; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206947","206947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79317","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the UK's ability to host future major sporting or cultural events of a loss of access by programme making and special events users to the 700 MHz band of radio spectrum; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206946","206946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79318","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much the National Lottery Distribution Fund has allocated to each parliamentary constituency in Scotland in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206973","206973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79319","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the research being conducted by Lincoln University on fixed odds betting terminals will assess the potentially addictive nature of those machines.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207030","207030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79320","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the research being conducted by Lincoln University on fixed odds betting terminals will help determine an appropriate stake level for those machines.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207031","207031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79321","2014-09-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many complaints the Service Personnel and Veterans Agency received in each year since 2010; and whether those complaints have been categorised.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207037","207037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79322","2014-09-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the guideline period is in which an application for an armed forces pension should be (a) processed and (b) delivered; and how many applications have exceeded that guideline period to date.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207035","207035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79323","2014-09-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what checks and balances he put in place to ensure that the Service Personnel and Veterans Agency was accountable to his Department.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207038","207038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79324","2014-09-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when designing the application process for the armed forces pension, what weight his Department gave to the ease of use of the system.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207036","207036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79325","2014-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of the RAF Air Show at RAF Waddington on (a) the public profile of the RAF, (b) public interest in the RAF and (c) money raised for RAF charities; and what plans he has for the future of the air show at RAF Waddington.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207015","207015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79326","2014-09-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what checks and balances he has put in place to ensure that Veterans UK is accountable to his Department.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207033","207033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79327","2014-09-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many complaints Veterans UK has received since its creation; and whether those complaints have been categorised.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207034","207034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79328","2014-09-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of the integration of the Storm Shadow missile on the Typhoon aircraft.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206989","206989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79329","2014-09-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of expanding the capabilities of the Sentinel R.1.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206985","206985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79330","2014-09-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what consideration his Department has given to integrating the Brimstone 2 missile onto Apache AH.1 attack helicopters MQ-9 Reaper unmanned aerial vehicles.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206984","206984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79331","2014-09-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the introduction of the (a) Heavy and (b) Light Future Anti-Surface Guided Weapon Systems on AW159 Wildcat Helicopters; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206994","206994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79332","2014-09-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of the new common jamming pod for the Tornado aircraft; and when the requirement for that pod was first identified.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206987","206987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79333","2014-09-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what communication (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have had with the Boeing Company regarding the lease of four P-8A aircraft.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206988","206988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79334","2014-09-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many medical downgrades there have been in the Submarine Service since the removal of retention and recruitment pay, in each month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207018","207018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79335","2014-09-01","Department for Education","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching staff were dismissed as a result of unsatisfactory attendance in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207000","207000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79336","2014-09-01","Department for Education","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure that the national curriculum highlights the importance of British history.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207001","207001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79337","2014-09-01","Department for Education","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much financial and in-kind support, including staff time, has been provided to each of the events entitled the Academies Show held in London and Birmingham since May 2010; and what the cost was of (a) venue hire, (b) catering, (c) promotion and advertising, (d) presentations, (e) work performed by officials in his Department in preparing, promoting and visiting these events and (f) other costs in respect of those events.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206999","206999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79338","2014-09-01","Department for Education","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to retain the international GCSE on school league tables in order to encourage take-up of that qualification.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207008","207008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79339","2014-09-01","Department for Education","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children under the age of 16 have been excluded from school as a result of possession of illegal substances in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206952","206952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79340","2014-09-01","Department for Education","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she made for planning purposes of the number of initial teacher training (ITT) places that would be offered by all ITT providers in (a) early years, (b) primary and (c) specialist subjects in 2014-15; and what estimate she has made of the number of people who will take up ITT places in those categories in that period.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206928","206928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79341","2014-09-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on (a) schools and (b) universities of loss of access by wireless microphone users to the 700 MHz band of radio spectrum; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206935","206935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79342","2014-09-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he has made an assessment of the potential effect of automatic energy imports from the US to the EU arising from the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations on EU carbon emission targets.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206908","206908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79343","2014-09-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding from the Green Deal has (a) Tivium Limited, (b) Green Deal Marketing Services Limited, (c) Tivium Green Deal Installers Limited and (d) Nationwide Green Deal Installers Limited received; and whether the actions of the directors of each company are under investigation.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206961","206961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79344","2014-09-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to ensure that Green Deal companies employed by the Government are not making nuisance calls under the contract.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206980","206980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79345","2014-09-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had on the maintenance of the current 20-year duration support level for accredited solar PV plants and the Renewables Obligation order; what his policy is on this matter; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206960","206960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79346","2014-09-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2014, Official Report, column 178W, on dairy farming, how many complaints her Department has received on the Dairy Code of Conduct.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206975","206975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79347","2014-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many enforcement notices were served under the Weeds Act 1959 in respect of ragwort in each of the last three years; and to whom they were served in each such year.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206870","206870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79348","2014-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the code of practice on how to prevent the spread of ragwort published in July 2004.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206871","206871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79349","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to improve trade relations with the Republic of Macedonia.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206950","206950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79350","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that DG Trade in the European Commission meets more public interest groups from the UK to discuss the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206917","206917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79351","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that DG Trade in the European Commission meets more trades unions from the UK to discuss the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206919","206919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79352","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that DG Trade in the European Commission meets more environmental interest groups from the UK to discuss the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206918","206918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79353","2014-09-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received from his counterpart in (a) South Africa, (b) Ecuador, (c) India and (d) Indonesia on the investor state dispute mechanism in the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206909","206909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79354","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in how many meetings in the last year between energy sector professionals and Ministers or Senior officials in his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206907","206907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79355","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in how many meetings in the last year between manufacturing sector professionals and Ministers or Senior officials in his Department the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership has been discussed.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206906","206906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79356","2014-09-01","Department for International Development","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much energy prices on St Helena have increased in each of the last four years; and what estimate she has made of the likely change in such prices in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206990","206990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79357","2014-09-01","Department for International Development","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of (a) the current cost of transporting a container of goods to St Helena and (b) the future cost of transporting a container of goods after the RMS St Helena has been decommissioned.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206992","206992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79358","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on imposing sanctions against Russia in relation to that country's response to the crash of the Malaysian Airlines flight MH17 in Ukraine.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206986","206986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79359","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will place in the Library a copy of the commercial tuna-fishing licences sold by the British Indian Ocean Territory Government in 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206998","206998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79360","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that West Nile virus is not introduced from the US to Ascension Island.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206997","206997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79361","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart on the crash of Malaysian Airlines flight MH17 in Ukraine.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206995","206995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79362","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that British Embassy staff in Iraq make contact with Danny Fitzsimon, who is held prisoner in that country.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207002","207002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79363","2014-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage the Iraq government to sign the Ministry of Justice's draft Prison Transfer Agreement.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207014","207014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79364","2014-09-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Ukrainian government on assisting Ukrainian nationals to obtain external passports.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207039","207039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79365","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to introduce the meningitis B vaccine.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207051","207051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79366","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has made any plans for the future of the Colindale Health Protection Agency site.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207040","207040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79367","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on top-level pay at the General Dental Council.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207017","207017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79368","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will meet with the author of Mindfulness in Clinician Therapeutic Relationships to discuss the ways in which mindfulness-based practices can be disseminated to NHS staff for the purposes of improving staff well-being and patient care.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207041","207041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79369","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many paramedics were working in each ambulance service in England in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207054","207054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79370","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the article Mindfulness in Clinician Therapeutic Relationships by Razzaque et al. published in the Journal Mindfulness, Volume 4, September 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207042","207042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79371","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to make employment a clinical commissioning group outcome indicator; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207022","207022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79372","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis among healthcare professionals.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207026","207026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79373","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients with idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis in England and Wales are currently considered eligible for lung transplantation.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207027","207027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79374","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the current safe staff-to-patient ratio on elderly and dementia wards in the Mid Yorkshire NHS trust.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207012","207012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79375","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding his Department has designated for research into idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis in 2014-15.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207028","207028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79376","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what processes are in place to ensure that idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis patients in the NHS and their families have access to high quality information about that condition.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207029","207029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79377","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what procedures his Department has put in place to deal with the consequences of a failure by the General Dental Council to meet key tests set by the Professional Standards Authority.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207016","207016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79378","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2014, Official Report, column 1007W, on radiotherapy, when data relating to individual funding requests per indication for radiotherapy treatment made to NHS England and the number of such requests refused will be available from NHS England.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206964","206964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79379","2014-09-02","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the General Dental Council on its proposal to increase the annual retention fee by 64 per cent; and what his Department's response is to that proposal.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207011","207011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79380","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to respond to the British Dental Association's recent letter to him expressing concern at the regulatory ability of the General Dental Council and condemning its proposed annual retention fee increase of 64 per cent.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207010","207010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79381","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that rural, remote and small settings will continue to receive milk under the Nursery Milk scheme.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206967","206967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79382","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2014, Official Report, column 1007W, on radiotherapy, in what respects University College Hospital London has failed to meet NHS England's service specifications for gamma knife services.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206965","206965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79383","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made towards meeting the commitment in the Government's 2010 cancer strategy of saving an additional 5,000 lives from cancer each year.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207003","207003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79384","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the prevalence and efficacy of the procurement and use of off-patent drugs in the NHS.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206976","206976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79385","2014-09-01","Cabinet Office","2014-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women are known to have died of ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206969","206969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79386","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Mid Yorkshire Hospitals NHS Trust has spent on hiring temporary nursing staff in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206981","206981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79387","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Mid Yorkshire Hospitals NHS Trust has spent on permanent nursing staff in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206982","206982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79388","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many serious health events have been recorded per thousand (a) e-cigarette users, (b) users of nicotine replacement therapies and (c) users of the Champix form of varenicline in the last year.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206979","206979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79389","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will investigate the reasons why NHS England is instructing hospitals with patients presenting as clinically urgent to treat such patients with innovative radiotherapy at the hospital's financial risk while it decides whether to fund the patient; and if he will issue guidelines on how hospitals which have followed that instruction will receive reimbursement for such expenditure if NHS England subsequently refuses to fund the treatment.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206974","206974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79390","2014-09-01","Department of Health","2014-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2014, Official Report, columns 766-7W on NHS: funding, if he will estimate the cost of the challenge posed by the pressures posed by the pressures of an aging population and the cost of new investment.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206873","206873"
