"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946942","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2018 to Question 165696, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on funding any pay rise recommended by the 2018 report of the School Teachers' Review Body.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167376","167376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946943","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has spent on bus services in (a) Barnsley and (b) South Yorkshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167345","167345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946944","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of recent trends in bus usage in Barnsley, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167346","167346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946945","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure access to justice for people facing disability discrimination in (a) employment and (b) education.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167347","167347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946946","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that legal aid solicitors have the capacity to meet the demand for their services in relation to complex asylum cases.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167396","167396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946947","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect on contributions to the public purse of the implications of increases in the building of social rented housing for (a) construction sector contributions to the economy and the exchequer, (b) the cost of temporary accommodation provision, (c) welfare spending, (d) income, corporation and council tax receipts and (e) any other factors.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167292","167292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946948","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to set up a New Homes Ombudsman to monitor and regulate new housing standards.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167293","167293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946949","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on support for victims of sexual violence to secure employment and training opportunities.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167341","167341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946950","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2018 Question 158653, when he plans to publish the scientific advice commissioned by his Department on the corrosive products and concentration limits set out in Schedule 1 of the Bill.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167105","167105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946951","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many acute non-consultant-led mental health beds there were in the NHS in England in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167230","167230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946952","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of acute consultant-led mental health beds in the NHS in England are now classified as non-consultant-led beds as a result of changes to reporting data in 2013-14.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167231","167231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946953","2018-09-04","Prime Minister","2018-07-23","To ask the Prime Minister, when her office plans fully to respond to the letters of the hon. Member for Brent Central of (a) 18 April 2018 on Windrush landing cards, (b) 20 April 2018 on next steps to address the Windrush scandal, (c) 30 April 2018 on deportation flights and (d) 18 May 2018 on the lack of responses to previous letters of the hon. Member for Brent Central.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167214","167214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946954","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is the policy of the Government that EU member states should apply UK tariffs and trade policy at the EU border for goods intended for the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167106","167106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946955","2018-09-04","Women and Equalities","2018-07-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many civil servants are employed by the Government Equalities Office.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167215","167215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946956","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on overall public spending per capita in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167348","167348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946957","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, by what date she plans for claimants of employment and support allowance who have been underpaid to have received all the back-payments due to them.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167107","167107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946958","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has plans to extend the maximum length of monthly back-pay recipients of industrial injuries disablement benefit can receive if they are subject to an administrative error by her Department, and will she make a statement.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167349","167349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946959","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her Department’s policy is in taking into consideration awards made by the medical appeals tribunal when deciding on benefit entitlement.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167350","167350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946960","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much money has been spent from the public purse on universal credit complaint resolution since that benefit was established.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167360","167360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946961","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to pay compensation to people who are in debt as a result of employment support allowance underpayments.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167108","167108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946962","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of pay-freezes on staff of his Department who remain on legacy shift arrangements.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167351","167351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946963","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the fitness for purpose of the universal credit IT system; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167109","167109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946964","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 July 2018 to Question 162042 on Mental Health Services: Acute Beds, what classifications his Department has used for acute mental health beds for data purposes since 2009.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167232","167232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946965","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has plans to collect information on the total number of acute mental health beds in the NHS in England.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167233","167233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946966","2018-09-04","Department for International Development","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to (a) assist the development of the IT sector in the Occupied Palestinian Territories and (b) foster links between UK and Palestinian companies.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167103","167103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946967","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of (a) 16-65 year olds and (b) people over 65 receive hearing aids on the NHS.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167317","167317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946968","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) dual and (b) UK-only UK nationals have had their UK citizenship revoked in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167155","167155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946969","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Emir of Qatar on improving working conditions and valuing the human rights of workers in Qatar.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167399","167399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946970","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the waste of prescription medicine.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167318","167318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946971","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the oral evidence of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Children and Families to the Education Committee on Accountability hearings on 18 July 2018, Q1389, HC 341, what evidence he was referring to when he stated that 30 per cent of care leavers end up as adults in prison.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167291","167291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946972","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2018 to Question 155916 on Social Rented Housing: Construction, whether information on homes developed on surplus public land which has been sold off as part of the Public Land Housing Programme will include figures specifically relating to social rented homes and not just figures for affordable homes when published.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167357","167357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946973","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many additional university places have been created at (a) Russell Group and (b) non-Russell Group universities since the lifting of the cap on undergraduate numbers.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167319","167319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946974","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that buildings constructed for (a) elderly and (b) vulnerable people have more than one lift and such people are not trapped in their homes if one lift breaks down; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167238","167238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946975","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils who are (a) eligible and (b) not eligible for free school meals have taken up English Baccalaureate subjects in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167320","167320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946976","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which UK companies are participating in the Autonomous Last Mile Resupply project.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167179","167179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946977","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information he holds on the (a) number of pupils in each ethnic group who have taken subjects in the English Baccalaureate and (b) grades that those pupils have achieved since the introduction of that qualification.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167321","167321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946978","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2018 to Question 165655, on prisons, whether the 10,000 additional places will (a) add to current capacity, (b) replace some existing capacity or (c) achieve a combination of replacing existing capacity and increasing current capacity.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167333","167333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946979","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the remit is of the Royal Air Force's Rapid Capabilities Office.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167180","167180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946980","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to publish its response to the consultation entitled Land Registry: moving operations to the private sector public consultation, published in March 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167313","167313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946981","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the prescription charge is affordable for people on low incomes who pay those charges.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167322","167322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946982","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which units within the (a) Royal Navy and (b) Army are the primary agencies within those respective bodies for identifying and investigating innovative solutions to future combat requirements.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167181","167181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946983","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the quantum of change is for the prescription charge in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167323","167323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946984","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the proportion of young people diagnosed with chronic illnesses in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167324","167324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946985","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to investigate the potential uses of directed energy on future UK armed forces platforms.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167182","167182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946986","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department issues to help people better understand their diabetes.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167325","167325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946987","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Statement of 18 July on employment and support allowance, WS877, what estimate she has made of the number of people who have been underpaid in (a) Doncaster and )b) South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167122","167122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946988","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what correspondence his Department has received from Hampshire County Council in respect of the devolution proposal made by the three Solent authorities.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167366","167366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946989","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help reduce the number of young people with mental health issues.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167326","167326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946990","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of people have taken up smoking in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167327","167327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946991","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase early screening for cancer diagnosis.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167328","167328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946992","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure greater consistency in the accuracy of decision making for all nationalities of asylum applicants.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167307","167307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946993","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 13 and 20 July to Questions 161175 and 164445, for what reasons the Government did not provide an estimate of the economic cost of the disruption caused by the rail timetable changes introduced on (a) Northern Rail and (b) Govia Thameslink Railway from 20 May 2018.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167289","167289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946994","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on procuring fleet support ships for the Royal Fleet Auxiliary; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167314","167314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946995","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress his Department has made on procuring Type 31e frigates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167315","167315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946996","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to restrict the competition of the Royal Fleet Auxiliary support ships being procured to UK-only bidders; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167316","167316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946997","2018-09-04","Cabinet Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had with the  (a) CBI, (b) Institute of Directors and (c) EEF on the Government's White Paper on the UK's future relationship with the EU, Cm 9593.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167255","167255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946998","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to publish the Institute of Business Ethics 2017 report on culture, values and behaviours at Her Majesty’s Inspectorate of Constabulary and Fire and Rescue Services.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167110","167110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946999","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many colleges in England offer music at A-Level.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167404","167404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947000","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department issues to rail freight operators on idling in residential areas.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167377","167377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947001","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has held with HS2 Limited on whether rail lines through Oxford will be used by freight services for the movement of construction materials for HS2.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167378","167378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947002","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Rail Delivery Group on that organisation’s air quality impact study.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167379","167379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947003","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2017 to Question 115264 on Railways: Freight, whether the air quality impact study undertaken by the Rail Delivery Group’s freight air quality group has been published.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167380","167380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947004","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will issue guidance to (a) Network Rail and (b) rail operating companies on speed limits for freight trains during night time hours in residential areas.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167381","167381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947005","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make his policy to electrify the East-West rail line between Oxford and Cambridge.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167382","167382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947006","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for a decision to be made on the future electrification of the railway line between Oxford and Didcot Parkway.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167383","167383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947007","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to deliver the electrification of freight services running through Oxford.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167384","167384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947008","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has held with Network Rail on (a) planned changes in the volume of rail freight and (b) the (i) length of freight trains (ii) weight of freight trains and (iii) the type of cargo being transported on freight trains passing through Oxford in the next five years.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167385","167385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947009","2018-09-04","Cabinet Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff of each grade work in the Cabinet Office Europe Unit.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167256","167256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947010","2018-09-04","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2018 to Question 165163 on Political Parties: Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of (a) controls and (b) transparency regulations on donations from the (i) the US and (ii) other countries outside of the UK and the Republic of Ireland to political parties in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167386","167386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947011","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has undertaken an impact assessment on the potential beneficial effects of regulating the dispensing of special medicinal products in England.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167294","167294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947012","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, to list meetings of his Department attended by (a) staff of Global Council and (b) the European Round Table of Industrialists.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167257","167257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947013","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what proportion of business meetings arranged by the Directorate of Communications and Stakeholders were with small or small and medium enterprises in each year since his Department was established.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167258","167258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947014","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish a list of the names and addresses of all state-maintained academies which have been constructed via a Private Finance Initiative or PF2 programme.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167263","167263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947015","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether (a) he, (b) his permanent Secretary or (c) Ministers of his Department plan to meet representatives of (i) Beatty, (ii) Barclays, (iii) Dalmore Capital, (iv) Equitix, (v) Innisfree, (vi) Interserve, (vii) Semperian and (viii) Veolia before April 2019.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167264","167264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947016","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue has been raised for the public purse as a result of the application of VAT on sanitary products in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167265","167265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947017","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the (a) formal and (b) informal reporting lines are between staff of his Department and HM Treasury.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167259","167259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947018","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many fines of what level have been issued to how many dentists by the NHS Business Services Authority for providing FP17 forms without the address of a patient.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167266","167266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947019","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the (a) formal and (b) informal reporting lines are between staff of his Department and the Cabinet Office Europe Unit.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167260","167260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947020","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the names and locations are of all schools constructed under the Building Schools for the Future programme and funded by means of a PFI or PF2 programme.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167267","167267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947021","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will instruct Highways England to consider lane widening as part of its proposals to introduce variable speed limits through motorway emergency works.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167290","167290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947022","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, to list each external economist who has met staff of his Department's Planning and Analysis Directorate.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167261","167261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947023","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, to list every external economic report that his Department's Planning and Analysis Directorate has analysed for Ministers since his Department was formed.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167262","167262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947024","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what impact assessment his Department has carried out in respect of the implications of the Court of Justice of the European Union's judgment of 12 April 2018, reference C-323/17, for the conservation of natural habitats and proposed revisions to the final National Planning Policy Framework; and if he will place a copy of that assessment in the Library.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167123","167123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947025","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to update the revised final National Planning Policy Framework to incorporate the Court of Justice of the European Union's judgment of 12 April 2018, reference C-323/17, on the conservation of natural habitats; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167124","167124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947026","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what statutory or non-statutory guidance is issued by his Department to local authorities on the process of asset transferring playing pitches to community sports clubs; if he will place a copy of such guidance in the Library; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167125","167125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947027","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what statutory or non-statutory guidance is issued by his Department to local authorities on the provision and maintenance of playing pitches; if he can place a copy of that guidance in the Library; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167126","167126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947028","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what processes are in place for local authorities to ensure that Academy schools sports facilities can be accessed by third party individuals or organisations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167127","167127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947029","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the number of playing pitches in each local authority area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167128","167128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947030","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities (a) directly manage the maintenance of playing pitches and (b) indirectly manage the maintenance of such pitches by using a third party service provider; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167129","167129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947031","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which agencies and other public bodies accountable to him will not have published their annual report and accounts for 2017-2018 by 31 July 2018; and what the reasons are for each such body not having done so by that date.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167130","167130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947032","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which agencies and other public bodies accountable to him will not have published their annual report and accounts for 2017-2018 by 31 July 2018; and what the reasons are for each such body not having done so by that date.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167131","167131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947033","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which agencies and other public bodies accountable to him will not have published their annual report and accounts for 2017-2018 by 31 July 2018; and what the reasons are for each such body not having done so by that date.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167132","167132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947034","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-23","to ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which agencies and other public bodies accountable to him will not have published their annual report and accounts for 2017-2018 by 31 July 2018; and what the reasons are for each such body not having done so by that date.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167133","167133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947035","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which agencies and other public bodies accountable to him will not have published their annual report and accounts for 2017-2018 by 31 July 2018; and what the reasons are for each such body not having done so by that date.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167134","167134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947036","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which agencies and other public bodies accountable to him will not have published their annual report and accounts for 2017-2018 by 31 July 2018; and what the reasons are for each such body not having done so by that date.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167135","167135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947037","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which agencies and other public bodies accountable to him will not have published their annual report and accounts for 2017-2018 by 31 July 2018; and what the reasons are for each such body not having done so by that date.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167136","167136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947038","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has received representations on the origin of 20 skinless human bodies being exhibited at the National Exhibition Centre in Birmingham; and what information his Department holds on consents obtained for the (a) transportation and (b) exhibition of those bodies.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167240","167240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947039","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the £780 million investment in the East Coast Main Line announced on 23 July 2018, whether that funding has been ring-fenced for investment in that line; to what specific projects that funding is planned to be allocated; and what the timetable is for each of those projects so funded.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167274","167274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947040","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps he has taken to help mitigate delays on (a) Thameslink, (b) Northern and (c) other commuter trains into London.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167188","167188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947041","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what further steps he plans to take to improve air quality for residents of London.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167189","167189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947042","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will take steps to ensure that policing budgets maintain alignment with inflation year-on-year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167190","167190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947043","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the planned closure of half of London's police stations does not impact negatively on work to reduce crime levels.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167191","167191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947044","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of putting in place provisions for temporary housing to reduce homelessness in London.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167192","167192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947045","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to improve the accessibility of the Help to Buy scheme for lower-income citizens.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167193","167193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947046","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proportion of homes built in London in the last twelve months his Department classes as affordable housing.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167194","167194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947047","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of the tri-borough merger among the police forces in Havering, Redbridge and Barking and Dagenham.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167195","167195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947048","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the implications of allowing home care assistants to administer controlled drugs without supervision; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167196","167196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947049","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated on covering the legal costs of private prosecutors in the event that the private prosecution fails in the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167197","167197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947050","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department last reviewed its policy of reimbursing private prosecutors' costs from the public purse in the event that the private prosecution fails.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167198","167198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947051","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of private prosecutions initiated in the last five years were the result of law enforcement agencies having declined to take prosecutions forward.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167199","167199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947052","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of children in the London Borough of Havering who will be made homeless in 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167200","167200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947053","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding has been allocated from the public purse for estate regeneration in the Greater London Authority area in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167201","167201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947054","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the most recent information which his Department holds on the average class size in schools in (a) England and (b) London is.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167202","167202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947055","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to tackle moped-enabled crime in London.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167203","167203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947056","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps he is taking to prevent acid attacks in London.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167204","167204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947057","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the participation of the (a) City of London Police and (b) Metropolitan Police Service in Operation Sceptre.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167205","167205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947058","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of the pothole action fund is planned to be allocated to London borough councils.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167206","167206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947059","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the growth of the bike and scooter share scheme in London.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167207","167207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947060","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to tackle any disparities in education and skill levels between London and other regions of the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167208","167208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947061","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many ambulances called in the London Borough of Havering have responded outside the (a) Category A and (b) Category C response time target in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167209","167209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947062","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of children under the age of 18 who are living in the London Borough of Havering who have been subjected to a forced marriage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167210","167210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947063","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he plans to take to ensure security arrangements are in place for the Euro 2020 games taking place at Wembley Stadium.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167211","167211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947064","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of children under the age of 18 living in the London Borough of Havering who have (a) undergone female genital mutilation in the UK, (b)  undergone female genital mutilation abroad and (c) who have been subjected to a forced marriage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167212","167212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945511","2018-07-24","Department for International Trade","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the value of increased British business that will accrue as a result of the opening of the new office of his Department in Minneapolis in the US.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166468","166468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945512","2018-07-24","Department for International Trade","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the value of increased British business that will accrue as a result of the opening of the new office of his Department in Raleigh in the US.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166469","166469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945513","2018-07-24","Department for International Trade","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the value of increased British business that will accrue as a result of the opening of the new office of his Department in San Diego in the US.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166470","166470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945514","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of violence carried out by settlers in East Jerusalem and the West Bank; and what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on that violence.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166440","166440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945515","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children excluded for 2017-18 were children with special educational needs or disabilities; and what proportion of such children were excluded by their schools for the reason given as Other.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166506","166506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945516","2018-07-24","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what contingency plans he is making in relation to UK freight transport using UK ports in the event that (a) no deal with the EU is reached, (b) multi-lateral or bi-lateral driving permits are not honoured after the UK leaves the EU and (c) there is a delay in the number of trained staff being available to adequately cope with the additional customs demands at ports after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166507","166507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945517","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the volume of non-recyclable plastic produced in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166498","166498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945518","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the volume of non-recyclable plastic sent to landfill in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166499","166499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945519","2018-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans to bring forward legislative proposals for the regulation of security of tenure for residential boats.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166492","166492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945520","2018-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of universal credit claimants who did not qualify for a payment as a result of receiving two wage payments during an assessment period in each of the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166475","166475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945521","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on designating water companies as responsible and impartial statutory consultees in the planning system.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166505","166505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945522","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the implementation of higher maximum penalties for animal cruelty.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166493","166493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945523","2018-07-24","Church Commissioners","2018-07-20","To ask the right Hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what assessment he has made of whether proposed recommendations by the Cathedrals Working Group on winding-up provisions in the event of a cathedral’s insolvency could result in creditors receiving less than they would otherwise.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166471","166471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945524","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel from each service are based in each local authority of the UK.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166472","166472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945525","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the the task and finish group on Taxi and Private Hire vehicle licensing plans to report on its findings.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166500","166500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945526","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the gap between demand and funding for health services for disabled children and their families; what steps he is taking to address any such gap; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166433","166433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945527","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the gap between demand and provision of social care services for disabled children and their families; what steps he is taking to address any such gap; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166434","166434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945528","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the UK retains its medical scientists after the European Medicines Agency moves from London to Amsterdam.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166442","166442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945529","2018-09-04","Department for International Development","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department is planning to send emergency aid to refugees to South Sudan as a result of violence in that region.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166443","166443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945530","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will establish a disabled children’s fund to improve early intervention services such as short breaks for disabled children.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166435","166435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945531","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will establish a disabled children’s fund to improve health services for disabled children.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166436","166436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945532","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces veterans who have served in the Duke of Lancaster's Regiment (King's, Lancashire and Border) (LANCS) have received treatment for post-traumatic stress disorder  in the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166444","166444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945533","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking with rail operators to ensure that the electrification of the Preston to Manchester via Bolton line experiences no delays.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166445","166445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945534","2018-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the digital and tech sector of the UK leaving the EU without a data adequacy arrangement in place.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166465","166465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945535","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of prosecutions for fly tipping in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166467","166467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945536","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government has taken to support the oil heating industry in their work to develop a low carbon liquid fuel alternative to kerosene.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166477","166477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945537","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Public Accounts Committee report on renewable heat incentive in Great Britain published on 16 May 2018, what steps his Department is taking to identify low cost heat alternatives for off-grid homes.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166478","166478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945538","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for the Fire and Rescue Services since the Winter Hill moorland fire in Lancashire.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166446","166446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945539","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he plans to take to help preserve juvenile cod fishing stocks after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166447","166447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945540","2018-07-24","Home Office","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how he plans to commemorate Anti-slavery Day on 18 October 2018.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166448","166448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945541","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has been taking to reduce water consumption since May 2018.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166449","166449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945542","2018-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has had discussions with the Football Association to discourage football clubs from accepting betting companies as their shirt sponsor.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166450","166450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945543","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made an assessment of the of the effect the implementation of self-service checkouts by retailers on levels of employment.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166451","166451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945544","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 19 July 2018 to Question 164389, what proportion of applications to use Adult Psychiatric Morbidity Survey 2014 data received a decision more than three months after  submission in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166479","166479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945545","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many pensioners were admitted to hospital with malnutrition in (a) Lancashire Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (b) East Lancashire NHS Foundation Trust in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166452","166452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945546","2018-07-24","Home Office","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to tackle the use of drones over (a) power plants and (b) prisons.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166453","166453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945547","2018-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions there have been for thefts relating to self-service checkouts in the (a) Lancashire Constabulary, (b) Greater Manchester Police and (c) Merseyside Police areas in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166454","166454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945548","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prevent the growth of bacteria in water as a result of dog fouling.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166455","166455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945549","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Department for Health has plans to introduce a National Incontinence Strategy.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166456","166456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945550","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress has been made on the re-basing of the British Army from Germany to the UK.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166473","166473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945551","2018-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the amount of funding allocated from the public purse to (a) fibre broadband installation and (b) mobile phone signal installations to improve digital connectivity in Gloucester.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166480","166480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945552","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that boron is not included in play slime.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166457","166457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945553","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupil premium students attended grammar schools in Gloucester in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166481","166481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945554","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many units of Service Family Accommodation in Germany are currently occupied by Service personnel.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166474","166474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945555","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to ban glitter.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166458","166458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945556","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary schools have been established on grammar school sites as a linked or feeder school (a) during 2017 and (b) since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166482","166482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945557","2018-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the agreed service waiting time for HM Courts and Tribunals Service cases are in England; and what proportion of cases met that target in (a) England and (c) Gloucestershire in 2017.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166483","166483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945558","2018-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress has been made in supporting people with disabilities into work since May 2015.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166484","166484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945559","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what target his Department has set for receiving a GP appointment; and what the average waiting time is for a GP appointment in (a) England and (b) Gloucestershire in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166485","166485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945560","2018-07-24","Department for International Trade","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he plans to allocate more departmental resources to South East Asia in order to increase trading opportunities in that region.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166486","166486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945561","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many nurses were employed by NHS Trusts in Gloucestershire in the last financial year; and how many nurses (a) left and (b) retired in that time period.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166487","166487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945562","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many foreign nationals from (a) EU and (b) non-EU countries are employed by Gloucestershire’s NHS Trusts.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166488","166488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945563","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to put out to tender the preliminary outline design for the proposed Gloucester to Cheltenham cycle route; and what the timeframe is for the announcement of the successful bidder for that tender.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166489","166489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945564","2018-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of local festivals on the growth of local tourism.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166490","166490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945565","2018-07-24","Women and Equalities","2018-07-20","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the Female FTSE Board Report 2018, published by Cranfield University in July 2018, what steps the Government is taking to support more women into business leadership positions; and what local initiatives the Government Equalities Office is supporting to inspire more women into public life.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166491","166491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945566","2018-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what analysis his Department has made of the economic impact of broadband blackspots in (a) London and (b) Vauxhall constituency.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166438","166438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945567","2018-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to tackle broadband blackspots in London.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166439","166439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945568","2018-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of UK television advertising related to junk food products in 2017.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166509","166509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945569","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which Multi-Academy Trusts are being considered for the re-brokerage on University Academy Warrington; and what criteria his Department will use to decide on a preferred Trust.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166441","166441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945570","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the Government has to increase support for unpaid carers.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166466","166466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945571","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made on the effect of junk food advertising on childhood obesity.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166510","166510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945572","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many times he and Ministers of his Department have formally met with the Welsh Government since the announcement that his Department will be overseeing the Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166494","166494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945573","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans for the UK wide frameworks on agriculture to cover a joint agreement on the permissibility of the allocation of subsidies to farms that are not commercially viable independent of subsidies.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166495","166495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945574","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the devolved administrations on his Department's research into the link between junk food advertising and childhood obesity.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166511","166511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945575","2018-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the devolved administrations on the potential merits of extending junk food advertising restrictions.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166512","166512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945576","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 June 2018 to Question 155260 on rail strikes, whether South Western Railway has made an application in the last 12 months to reimburse the company for revenues lost as a result of official industrial action.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166508","166508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945577","2018-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number and proportion of universal credit claims started but not completed.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166515","166515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945578","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that food safety standards remain closely aligned with the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166437","166437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945579","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 106098, how much of his Department's budget allocated to 16 to 19-year old education was reallocated to other budgets in the financial year 2017-18.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166476","166476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945580","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential for large-scale hydrogen conversion projects to support the UK to meet its de-carbonisation targets.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166496","166496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945581","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps is he taking to support research and development for large-scale hydrogen conversion projects.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166497","166497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945582","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the financial sustainability of childcare provision in the private, voluntary and independent early education sector.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166501","166501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945583","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local authorities have provided business rate relief to private, voluntary and independent childcare providers.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166502","166502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945584","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to increase recruitment and retention in the childcare sector.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166503","166503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945585","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what in-school support is provided for children suffering from (a) bowel and (b) bladder cancer.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166504","166504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945586","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for (a) secondary schools and (b) primary schools in (i) Jarrow constituency, (ii) South Tyneside and (iii) the North East.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166459","166459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945587","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has held with Nexus on the proposed replacement of the Tyne and Wear Metro train fleet.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166460","166460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945588","2018-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an estimate of the number of people using food banks in the North East.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166461","166461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945589","2018-07-24","Cabinet Office","2018-07-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people in the North East who are in insecure jobs.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166462","166462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945590","2018-07-24","Home Office","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the increase in the level of reported crime in South Tyneside between April 2017 and March 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166463","166463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945591","2018-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve mental health support for (a) veterans and (b) serving Military personnel in North East England.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166464","166464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945592","2018-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the timescale is for issuing new licences to mobile networks.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166513","166513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945593","2018-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to help eliminate not spots.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166514","166514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945594","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce rates of childhood obesity.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906611","906611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944640","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of trends in the level of under-age pregnancies among females in social care in Coventry since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166063","166063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944641","2018-07-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if his Department will make an assessment of the effect of allegations made against the campaigns (a) Vote Leave and (b) BeLeave by the (i) Electoral Commission and (ii) Observer on negotiations with the EU on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166049","166049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944642","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether universal credit payments will be made for a looked after child for periods that the child has returned home temporarily.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166270","166270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944643","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department provides on deciding whether a full-time carer should be expected to look for work despite their caring responsibilities or be placed in the no-conditionality group under regulation 89 (b) of the universal credit regulations.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166271","166271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944644","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has made a recent assessment of the capacity of Coventry City Council to discharge its statutory responsibilities to vulnerable children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166064","166064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944645","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department is providing assistance to local authorities to meet the demand for children’s services in rural areas around Coventry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166065","166065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944646","2018-07-24","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what powers are available to local authorities to require (a) organisations and (b) individuals to (i) clear and (ii) tidy industrial sites where anti-social behaviour is having a detrimental effect on local residents.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166137","166137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944647","2018-07-24","Department for International Trade","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the Initial Assessment of the UK National Contact Point for the OECD Guidelines for Multinational Enterprises of 15 June on a complaint against PwC, what assessment the Government has made reports of claims from PwC that it was not required to investigate whether Palestinian Authority funding was used to pay convicted terrorists.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166052","166052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944648","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of the creation of the Antarctic Ocean Sanctuary for tackling (a) over-fishing, (b) plastic pollution and (c) climate change.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166056","166056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944649","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the yearly variation in the number of applications granted for refugee status from refugees from Eritrea in the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166057","166057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944650","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his Department's monitoring of the disposal of plastic exported to China for recycling.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166058","166058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944651","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the technological changes needed for a reduction in maximum stake on fixed odds betting terminals to be completed.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166245","166245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944652","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to publish a land warfare strategy.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166110","166110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944653","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Pet Travel Scheme, when his Department last reviewed the effectiveness of the Animal and Plant Health Agency's Required Method of Operation process with Eurotunnel, P&O, DFDS and other carriers.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166121","166121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944654","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the level of water stress in each water company area throughout England.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166066","166066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944655","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the value of assets held by water companies throughout England in each year since 1989.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166067","166067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944656","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will commission research into the effects of motorbike related noise on rural and urban communities.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166084","166084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944657","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has commissioned research on the causes of work poverty in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166246","166246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944658","2018-07-24","Treasury","2018-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an estimate of how much money would be generated annually were the soft drinks levy to be extended to milk-based drinks; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166105","166105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944659","2018-07-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to article 4 of Regulation (EC) No 1071/2009, what (a) discussions his Department has had with the EU and (b) his policy is on the occupational status of UK transport managers residing in the UK and working for a road transport operator based in the EU 27 after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166050","166050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944660","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Prime Minister's oral contribution on 18 July 2018, Official Report, col 408, if he will ensure that the Windrush report commissioned by Sir Alex Allan is published promptly without redactions or deletions and made available to hon. Members.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166085","166085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944661","2018-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of the replacement of Aspergers with Autistic Spectrum Disorder in the fifth edition of the Diagnosis and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders on the ability of people with Aspergers to claim personal independence payment and employment support allowance as a result of being required to secure a new diagnosis when proving that their condition affects their daily living.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166213","166213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944662","2018-07-24","Department for International Trade","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the White Paper entitled The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, published in July 2018, Cm 9593, what assessments has been made of the feasibility of accession to the Comprehensive and Progressive Agreement for Trans-Pacific Partnership.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166107","166107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944663","2018-07-24","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to his Answer of 6 July 2018 to Question 160244 on Immigration Controls: Airports, if he will publish that data in the same format as his response to Freedom of Information request reference 41762.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166200","166200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944664","2018-07-24","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will change his service level agreements with UK Border Force in response to findings from the Airport Operators Association that passengers expect to wait less than half the current maximum waiting time at passport control.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166201","166201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944665","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has plans to increase the immigration health surcharge.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166130","166130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944666","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the amount paid in business rates by (a) private, (b) volunteering and (c)independent childcare providers in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166217","166217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944667","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are eligible for 30 hours free childcare in north each Lincolnshire.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166218","166218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944668","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the future launch of the S-80-class submarine by the Spanish Navy, what steps he is taking to ensure that Spain respects the national territorial waters around Gibraltar.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166131","166131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944669","2018-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants have made contact with her Department to request a reduction in the amount deducted from their standard allowance; and how many of those requests were accepted.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166272","166272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944670","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will assess the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to prohibit the export of live animals from the UK for research procedures abroad.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166148","166148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944671","2018-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which (a) local authority areas and (b) constituencies have an average download speed for fixed broadband services of less than 30 Mbps.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166106","166106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944672","2018-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether standards equal to or higher than those in the EU directive banning animal-tested cosmetics will remain in place as part of any preferential trade agreement that the UK agrees.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166149","166149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944673","2018-07-24","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases there were of people being identified as an adult at risk in immigration detention between 1 August 2017 and 10 July 2018 by (a) level of risk and (b) month.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166053","166053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944674","2018-07-24","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people identified as an adult at risk between 1 August 2017 and 10 July 2018 resulted from a Rule 35 Report by (a) levels of risk and (b) month.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166054","166054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944675","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are being taken to improve (a) diagnosis, (b) awareness and (c) treatment of Ehlers-Danios Syndrome.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166257","166257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944676","2018-07-24","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many decisions to release people identified as an adult at risk from immigration detention were made between 1 August 2017 and 10 July 2018, by (a) levels of risk and (b) month.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166055","166055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944677","2018-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will respond to Early Day Motion 1492, on human rights in Colombia.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166212","166212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944678","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, who will represent the Government at the UN high level meeting on non-communicable diseases in September; and what the Government's expected outcomes for that meeting are.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166195","166195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944679","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to prepare for the UN high level meeting on non-communicable diseases in September.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166196","166196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944680","2018-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the obligation local authorities to give due care and support to tenants who are to be evicted, including those with known mental ill-health.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166109","166109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944681","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) GPs and (b) other health professionals have adequate training for the early diagnosis of Lyme Disease.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166156","166156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944682","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were excluded from school in (a) London and (b) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166051","166051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944683","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the reduction in wage growth between March and May 2018.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166277","166277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944684","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Departments policies of the conclusion of the Office for Budget Responsibility's Fiscal Sustainability Report that tax rises or budget cuts are necessary to deliver the proposed funding increases for the NHS.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166278","166278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944685","2018-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has made an assessment of the effect of benefit sanctions on the mental health of claimants.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166197","166197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944686","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 33 of the Fiscal sustainability report – July 2018, published by the Office of Budget Responsibility on 17 July 2018, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies that Brexit is more likely to weaken the public finances than strengthen them over the medium term.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166279","166279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944687","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he Department has made an assessment of the effect of the imposition on benefits sanctions on the mental health of claimants with an existing mental health condition.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166198","166198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944688","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of (a) employment support allowance, (b) universal credit and (c) jobseeker's allowance in Scotland with a declared mental health problem have been subject to a benefits sanction since 2015.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166199","166199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944689","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's announcement of 18 July 2018 on the new medal to recognise the fight against Daesh, if he publish the countries where UK personnel in receipt of the medal (a) are based and (b) have been based.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166111","166111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944690","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Llanelli dated 28 June 2018 on his Department's plan to award the contract for the Defence Fire and Rescue Service to Capita.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166112","166112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944691","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has he made of the financial effect on the NHS of the introduction of the General Data Protection Regulation.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166138","166138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944692","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the final agreed price was for the sale of HMS Ocean to the Brazilian Government.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166285","166285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944693","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the agreed payment schedule is for the purchase of HMS Ocean by the Brazilian Government.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166286","166286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944694","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the NHS has taken to maintain patient records in a suitable format to reduce the time it takes staff to comply with subject access requests resulting from the General Data Protection Regulation.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166139","166139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944695","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his oral contribution of 17 July 2018, Official Report, column 241, how many academics were consulted as part of the development of the Combat Air Strategy; and how many of those academics were women.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166113","166113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944697","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department plans to appoint a new Minister for Defence Procurement.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166114","166114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944698","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what infrastructure projects were built in (a) 2017 and (b) 2008 using Private Finance 2; and how much funding there was for each such project.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166220","166220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944699","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average cost per applicant is for her Department of an appeal against an initial refusal to grant a personal independence payment.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166251","166251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944700","2018-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2018 on Question 163539 on Jobcentres: Peterlee, if he will undertake a review of the Peterlee Jobcentre Physical Security Survey in relation to (a) data protection and (b) the suitability of the open plan office.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166140","166140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944701","2018-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's announcement entitled Crackdown on rogue bailiffs, published on 2 April 2018 what the timeline is for the call for evidence to be launched.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166250","166250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944702","2018-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her Department's key performance indicators are to assess whether the universal credit system is functioning effectively.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166141","166141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944703","2018-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's announcement, Major new prison reform programme unveiled, published on 9 November 2015, what the timeframe is for each prison to open; and the number of prisons for which (a) work has begun (b) contracts been signed and (c) a decision on the finance mechanism has been made.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166223","166223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944704","2018-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans to review the legal definitions for the offences of (a) careless and (b) dangerous driving.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166208","166208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944705","2018-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of international broadcasting companies based in the UK that broadcast to the rest of the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166209","166209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944706","2018-07-24","Department for International Trade","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many free trade agreements with non-EU countries the Department plans to have signed by the 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166210","166210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944707","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect the recent decline of season tickets sales will have on the current franchise model.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166211","166211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944708","2018-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps the Government has taken to promote UN efforts to resolve the political crisis in Nicaragua.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166216","166216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944709","2018-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to respond to the letter of 21 June 2018 of the hon. Member for Greenwich and Woolwich on Woolwich Barracks.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166232","166232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944710","2018-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to help promote the sport of women's rugby.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166176","166176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944711","2018-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to promote the discussion of mental health concerns among young athletes.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166177","166177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944712","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Oil and Gas Authority on the effect on the terms and conditions of employment for offshore workers of Chevron’s sale of its oil and gas platforms and satellites in the Central North Sea; and what estimate he has made of the number of offshore staff will be affected by that sale.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166157","166157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944713","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Clinical Commissioning Groups have adequate funding to maintain the provision of NHS-funded acupuncture services.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166178","166178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944714","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many contractor staff are employed on the (a) Alba, (b) Alder, (c) Captain, (d) Elgin/Franklin, (e) Erskine, (f) Jade and (g) Britannia platforms in the Central North Sea.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166158","166158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944715","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many directly employed staff are working on the (a) Alba, (b) Alder, (c) Captain, (d) Elgin/Franklin, (e) Erskine, (f) Jade and (g) Britannia platforms in the Central North Sea.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166159","166159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944716","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 10 of the UKCS Decommissioning - 2018 Cost Estimate Report published by the Oil and Gas Authority in June 2018, if he will make an updated estimate of the total cost of onshore recycling and disposal of decommissioned offshore infrastructure from the Central North Sea.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166160","166160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944717","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the UKCS Decommissioning - 2018 Cost Estimate Report published by the Oil and Gas Authority in June 2018, what his latest estimate is of employment levels in the offshore decommissioning industry in each year from 2018 to 2025.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166161","166161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944718","2018-07-24","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Government's withdrawal agreement on freight transport and UK ports.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166253","166253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944719","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2018 to Question 158755 on Digital Technology: South Yorkshire, how much of that British Business Bank funding has been allocated to South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166179","166179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944720","2018-07-24","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what progress he has made on agreements for (a) bi-lateral and (b) multi-lateral haulage and driving permits after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166254","166254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944721","2018-07-24","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he plans to have with representatives of the (a) Freight Transport Association and (b) Trades Unions on the Government's plans for (i) customs arrangements and (ii) freight and haulage in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166255","166255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944722","2018-07-24","Treasury","2018-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the additional (a) customs and (b) security resources required to maintain frictionless trade through UK ports after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166256","166256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944723","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the provision of systematic screening for Lynch Syndrome for people diagnosed with bowel cancer in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166180","166180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944724","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for secondary schools in South East London.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166243","166243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944725","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for primary schools in South East London.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166244","166244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944726","2018-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the letter from the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Courts of 6 July 2018 to the non. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South and the hon. Member for Sunderland Central, whether the £825,000 will be reinvested in Sunderland Magistrates’ Court as a result of the decision to relinquish land held on Farringdon Row.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166155","166155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944727","2018-07-23","Department for International Development","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has plans to support the the allocation of additional funding to the Global Financing Facility for Every Woman and Every Child.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166175","166175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944728","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 July 2018 to Question 159025 on Child Support and Social Security Benefits, how many First-tier tribunal cases relating social security claims were for (a) personal independence payment and (b) employment support allowance in the Inverclyde constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166221","166221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944729","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Estonia, (b) Latvia and (c) Lithuania on re-tasking of the NATO Baltic air-policing mission to an air defence posture mission.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166086","166086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944730","2018-07-24","Treasury","2018-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people were eligible for the disabled worker element of Working Tax Credit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166273","166273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944731","2018-07-24","Treasury","2018-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households with disabled children were eligible for the Disabled Child element of Child Tax Credit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166274","166274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944732","2018-07-24","Treasury","2018-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households received both the disabled worker element of Working Tax Credit and Disabled Child element of Child Tax Credit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166275","166275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944733","2018-07-24","Treasury","2018-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households in receipt of the disabled worker element of Working Tax Credit also received Child Tax Credit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166276","166276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944734","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's latest estimate is of the remaining recoverable oil and gas deposits under the (a) North, (b) Central and (c) Southern North Sea.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166143","166143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944735","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the level of (a) exploration and (b) drilling activity in the North Sea since January 2017.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166144","166144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944736","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the 21st Century Exploration Roadmap Palaeozoic Project on the exploitation of viable oil and gas deposits under the UK Continental Shelf; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166145","166145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944737","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish the (a) public and (b) private sources of funding for the  21st Century Exploration Roadmap Palaeozoic Project undertaken by the Oil and Gas Authority and British Geological Survey between November 2014 and May 2016.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166146","166146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944738","2018-07-24","Treasury","2018-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse of was decommissioning projects in the (a) Northern, (b) Central and (c) Southern North Sea in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse in each North Sea region in 2018.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166147","166147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944739","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's document, Permanent and fixed-period exclusions in England: 2016 to 2017, if he will make an assessment of the reasons why pupils with SEN support have a permanent exclusion rate that is six times higher than the rate for pupils with no SEN; and if he will institute a specific programme for families of pupils with SEN to ensure that their children are given the most suitable means of advice and support following such expulsions.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166230","166230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944740","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's document, Permanent and fixed-period exclusions in England: 2016 to 2017, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons why (a) Black Caribbean pupils had a permanent exclusion rate nearly three times higher than the school population as a whole, (b) pupils of Gypsy/Roma and Traveller of Irish Heritage ethnic groups had the highest rates of both permanent exclusions and (c) pupils known to be eligible for and claiming free school meals accounted for 40 per cent of all permanent exclusions.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166231","166231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944741","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with (a) trades unions and (b) the oil and gas authority on employment standards in the offshore decommissioning industry.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166173","166173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944742","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the UKCS Decommissioning 2018 Cost Estimate Report by the Oil and Gas Authority, what assessment he has made of trends in the cost of labour associated with decommissioning projects.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166174","166174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944743","2018-07-24","Wales Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will list all the consultation events or meetings he has had with (a) the Welsh Assembly, (b) Welsh local authorities, (c) Welsh businesses, (d) Welsh hon. Members and (e) any other Welsh stakeholders on the proposed UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166081","166081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944744","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much each nation and region of the UK received per capita in EU structural funding for the (a) 2007-13 and (b) 2014-2020 reporting periods.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166082","166082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944745","2018-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library a copy of the consultation process on proposed funding mechanisms which will replace EU structural funding after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166083","166083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944746","2018-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Israeli Government on the (a) passage of the Nation State Law by the Israeli Knesset and (b) implications of that law on the rights and status of minority groups.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166059","166059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944747","2018-07-24","Department for International Development","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of the funding shortfall for the United Nations Relief and Works Agency for Palestinian Refugees on front line services in (a) the West Bank, (b) Gaza, (c) Jordan, (d) Lebanon and (e) Syria.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166060","166060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944748","2018-07-24","Department for International Development","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent estimate she has made of the number of refugees who have been displaced from Yarmouk refugee camp; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166061","166061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944749","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 79 of the July 2018 White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm 9593, whether he has estimated the number of UK armed forces personnel that will be required to host an Operational Headquarters.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166087","166087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944750","2018-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 77 of the July 2018 White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm 9593, whether he plans to assign UK armed forces personnel to the European Union's Military Planning and Conduct Capability as part of the Government's proposals set out in that paragraph.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166088","166088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944751","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 19 July 2018 to Question 164427 on learning disability: nurses, in what format his Department collects data.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166168","166168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944752","2018-07-24","Treasury","2018-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to promote personal savings and investments in (a) the North East and (b) England.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166169","166169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944753","2018-07-24","Treasury","2018-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has identified costs in addition to the estimation of a settlement of £35-39 billion that the UK will need to pay as a result of leaving the EU.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166170","166170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944754","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) timescale and (b) scope is of the research his Department is conducting on Traffic Regulation Orders in relation to pavement parking.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166171","166171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944755","2018-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 80 of the July 2018 White Paper, The future relationship between the UK and the EU, Cm 9593, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the operations of the Five Eyes intelligence alliance of UK involvement in EU operational planning.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166089","166089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944756","2018-07-24","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 July 2018 to Question 161101, Home Office: Members, whether his Department is satisfied that an MP has the authority to act for a constituent when consent is given verbally by that individual.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166077","166077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944757","2018-07-24","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children have been held in immigration detention centres in the UK in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166045","166045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944758","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on noise pollution over Camberwell and Peckham constituency of the construction of a third runway at Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166046","166046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944759","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of establishing a legally binding noise threshold at Heathrow airport.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166047","166047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944760","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to extend the ultra-low emission but scheme to coach operators.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166125","166125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944761","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the extent to which coach travel contributes to improvements in air quality; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166126","166126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944762","2018-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to commence the provisions of the Guardianship (Missing Persons) Act 2017.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166048","166048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944763","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, in which local authority areas in (a) London and (b) England outside London the number of bus journeys per head of population has increased since 2011.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166127","166127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944764","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many buses free Wi-Fi is available (a) in London and (b) elsewhere in England.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166128","166128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944765","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the importance of the Bus Service Operators Grant on the stability of local bus services.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166129","166129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944766","2018-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the distribution of land allocations between settlers and Palestinians in the West Bank.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166062","166062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944767","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that food products which are contaminated with listeria are more easily identified and prevented from being put on sale to the public.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166284","166284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944768","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, by what date his Department plans the construction of HMP Glen Parva to have been concluded.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166224","166224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944769","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the date is by which the contract to build HMP Glen Parva will be put out to tender; and what will the timeline for that tender process is planned to be.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166225","166225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944770","2018-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what model of private finance his Department plans to use in the contract to build HMP Glen Parva.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166226","166226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944771","2018-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the lifetime cost of the building of HMP Glen Parva.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166227","166227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944772","2018-07-24","Treasury","2018-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many renting households have paid stamp duty land tax (SDLT) in each of the last five years; and how much SDLT has been paid by such households in total.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166079","166079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944773","2018-07-24","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when and how the Government plans to set out its contingency plans to tackle delay and disruption at UK ports to ensure that (a) security is unaffected (b) the welfare of logistics workers is fully considered and (c) UK industries reliant on just-in-time deliveries importing fresh produce are not adversely affected as a consequence of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166252","166252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944774","2018-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish a list of the non-executive appointments made by his Department between April 2018 and March 2019 including (a) the name of the person appointed and the role to which they have been appointed, (b) the date and term of their appointment, (c) their compensation, (d) whether they have declared any conflicts of interest or political activity, (e) who was responsible for managing the process of appointment, (f) what the expected time commitment of the role is and (g) whether the appointment was made in line with the processes laid down by the Commissioner for Public Appointments.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166228","166228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944775","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy schools are in receipt of a termination notice; how long each academy has been waiting to be re-brokered; how many academies have agreed to voluntary re-brokering; and how long each academy with that status has been waiting for a new sponsor.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166183","166183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944776","2018-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will credit to victims of modern slavery the National Insurance contributions that were unpaid during the period of their slavery.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166104","166104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944777","2018-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Written Statement of 19 July 2018, Modernising Defence Programme - Update, HCWS883, for what reasons only headline conclusions from that programme have been published.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166090","166090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944778","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure the Defence equipment plan is affordable.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166091","166091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944779","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of his Department's ability to make the remaining £8.1 billion saving from its equipment plan by 2027.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166092","166092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944780","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons expenditure on equipment support is falling when major new equipment is being brought into service.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166093","166093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944781","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the ability of his Department to deliver the re-baselined cost of £6.2 billion for production of the two new aircraft carriers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166094","166094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944782","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timeframe is for his Department to publish the detailed data on the cost of (a) supporting and (b) operating UK F-35 aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166095","166095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944783","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that the cost to the public purse of the four Dreadnought class nuclear ballistic missile submarines does not exceed the £31 billion budget.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166096","166096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944784","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to increase staff retention rates in UK schools.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166258","166258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944785","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people with Arthritis have adequate access to (a) aids and (b) adaptations that enable them to live independently.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166259","166259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944786","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to tackle the backlog in maintenance work on the defence estate.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166097","166097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944787","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Scottish armed forces veterans have died as a result of suicide in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166247","166247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944788","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on realising £1 billion of savings between 2016-17 and 2020-21 as a result of sales of the MoD estate.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166098","166098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944789","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has any plans to publish periodic statistics on the rates of suicide for (a) serving and (b) former serving armed forces personnel.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166248","166248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944790","2018-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will put forward a resolution to the United Nations Security Council calling for an investigation into the activities of the Myanmar military.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166260","166260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944791","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that former armed forces personnel are able to access metal health services.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166249","166249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944792","2018-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government,  whether his Department plans to make an assessment of the adequacy of the Check, Challenge, Appeal system in England.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166261","166261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944793","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking in improve satisfaction rates for Service Family Accommodation.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166099","166099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944794","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies in the event that the target of 144,200 trained regular armed forces personnel by 2020 is not met.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166100","166100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944795","2018-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with US officials on the status of British prisoner Kris Maharaj.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166262","166262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944796","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the need for specific services designed to address the ongoing physiological damage of people affected by forced adoption.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166263","166263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944797","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he plans to take to ensure that records of adoptions are more easily accessible by relevant parties.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166264","166264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944798","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps is he taking to fill gaps in the 102 specialist armed forces pinch point trades where there are shortfalls in skilled personnel.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166101","166101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944799","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the debate of 12 July 2018 on forced adoption in the UK, Official Report, column 1187, whether the Government plans to make an apology for the practice of forced adoption in UK history.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166265","166265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944800","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how his Department plans to respond to the results of the Armed Forces continuous attitude survey that only 40 per cent of regular personnel are satisfied with service life.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166102","166102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944801","2018-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received representations on allegations of the Israeli Government's refusal to grant residency permits and visas to foreign nationals who have made their home and livelihood in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166266","166266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944802","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information he holds on recent reports of refusal by Israel to grant residency permits and visas to foreign nationals who live in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166267","166267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944803","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on access to the Occupied Palestinian Territories for international visitors.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166268","166268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944804","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will seek assurances from Israeli immigration officials that access to the Occupied Palestinian Territories for international visitors will remain unhindered.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166269","166269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944805","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many local authority maintained schools which have failed an Ofsted inspection receiving an inadequate judgement are still waiting for an academy sponsor to be confirmed; and how many of those schools have been waiting (a) less than 9 months, (b) between 9 and 18 months, (c) 2 years, (d) 3 years and (e) over 3 years; and how many such schools are in the process of being issued an academy order.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166184","166184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944806","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the potential costs of setting up UK bodies to carry on the functions of EU agencies in his Department's area of responsibility in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166203","166203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944807","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what contingency budget his Department has been provided with in order to set up UK bodies to carry on the functions of EU agencies in his Department's area of responsibility in the event of the UK leaving the EU without an agreement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166204","166204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944808","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what arrangements are being made to secure accommodation for UK bodies set up to carry on the functions of EU agencies in his Department's area of responsibility in the event of the UK leaving the EU without an agreement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166205","166205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944809","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the potential costs of associate membership of EU agencies in his Department's area of responsibility when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166206","166206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944810","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the (a) administration costs, (b) grant funding, (c) staff, (d) accommodation and (e) budget required by existing UK bodies to which he plans to transfer the functions of EU agencies in his Department's area of responsibility in the event of the UK leaving the EU without agreement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166207","166207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944811","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department spent on advertising the position for Chair of the Social Mobility Commission; how that money was spent; how much funding is being spent on advertising for the role of Social Mobility Commissioners; and how that funding is being spent.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166185","166185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944812","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made in establishing domestic equivalents to the European Maritime Safety Agency information systems currently used by the Maritime and Coastguard Agency to regulate the safety of (a) passengers, (b) merchant seafarers, (c) merchant ships and (d) the marine environment in the UK; and whether the domestic equivalent for each of those is on course to be operational by March 2019.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166150","166150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944813","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the (a) costs to the public purse of and (b) delivery date for the domestic equivalents to European Maritime Safety Agency information systems which the Maritime and Coastguard Agency currently uses to carry out its regulatory responsibilities.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166151","166151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944814","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff in (a) his Department, (b) other Government departments, (c) executive agencies and (d) external bodies have worked on (i) aviation, (ii) roads, (ii) rail and (iv) maritime issues arising from the UK’s departure from the European Union since July 2016.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166152","166152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944815","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport,  what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for the Home Department on the role of Border Force officials in promoting seafarers’ rights on foreign registered vessels regularly working on routes from or between UK ports.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166153","166153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944816","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vessels were detained in UK ports after port state control inspection by Maritime and Coastguard Agency officials in each year since 2015; and if he will list the five most common grounds for detention in each of those years.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166154","166154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944817","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he last met the Mayor of London to discuss the regeneration of the Royal Docks.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166132","166132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944818","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will convene a meeting with the (a) Mayor of London, (b) Mayor of Newham and (c) local hon Members to discuss the regeneration of Silvertown Quays.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166133","166133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944819","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what is the cost was of changing branding and livery to LNER following the collapse of Virgin Trains East Coast.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166142","166142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944820","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools have been rated by Ofsted as inadequate for (a) two years, (b) three years, (c) four years, (d) five  years and (e) more than six years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166186","166186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944821","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools have been rated by Ofsted as requires improvement for (a) two years, (b) three years, (c) four years, (d) five  years and (e) more than six years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166187","166187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944822","2018-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 19 July 2018, HCWS883 on the Modernising Defence Programme, whether the publication of the Modernising Defence Programme is planned to be accompanied by an oral statement.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166115","166115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944823","2018-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 19 July 2018, HCWS883 on the Modernising Defence Programme, how many phases he intends the Modernising Defence Programme to have.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166116","166116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944824","2018-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 19 July 2018, HCWS883 on the Modernising Defence Programme, how much financial headroom his Department plans to find for additional modernisation.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166117","166117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944825","2018-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 19 July 2018, HCWS883 on the Modernising Defence Programme, when his Department plans to publish a defence technology framework.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166118","166118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944826","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how he plans to control immigration to the UK from the EU while while also protecting the uninhibited movement of people between Ireland and the UK under the Common Travel Area.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166134","166134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944827","2018-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's consultation on Modernising Defence Programme, which was launched on 5 March 2018, when his Department plans to publish the consultation outcome of that consultation.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166119","166119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944828","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the likelihood of immigrants from the EU using the uninhibited movement of people under the Common Travel Area to gain access to the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166135","166135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944829","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has undertaken an impact assessment of the risks associated with the roll-out smart motorways.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166172","166172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944830","2018-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support her Department provides to people fleeing abuse from their home where they have a financial interest such as a mortgage and are therefore unable to claim the housing benefit element of universal credit.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166214","166214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944831","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the potential future use of alternative fuels to reduce emissions.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166280","166280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944832","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children (a) with special education needs, (b) in care and (c) on a child protection plan attended (i) maintained nursery schools, (ii) nursery classes and (iii) private, voluntary and independent early years provision in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166188","166188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944833","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of offering incentives for the adoption of fuel converters that lower the total amount of emissions produced by a vehicle.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166281","166281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944834","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has for increased border control at Welsh ports in the event of EU migrants using the uninhibited movement of people under the Common Travel Area to gain access to the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166136","166136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944835","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on introducing measures to provide tax relief for armed forces personnel stationed in Scotland who are subject to that administration's tax rates.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166282","166282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944836","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that colleges remain sufficiently protected from cyber-attack should any college choose to opt out of the forthcoming Jisc subscription.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166080","166080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944837","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether recent reviews of the defence estate have identified any necessary improvements works to current accommodation in Scotland.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166283","166283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944838","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the (a) 2019 Loan Charge and (b) IR35 reforms on the NHS.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166122","166122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944839","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of locum doctors who are affected by the 2019 Loan Charge.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166123","166123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944840","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, hat estimate he has made of the number of NHS Trusts that rely on blanket IR35 assessments of non-payroll NHS staff.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166124","166124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944841","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) maintained nursery schools, (b) nursery classes in maintained schools, (c) private, independent and voluntary sector early years provision and (d) childminders are rated (i) inadequate, (ii) requires improvement, (iii) good and (iv) outstanding.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166189","166189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944842","2018-07-24","Department for International Development","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to tackle the persecution of the Tawerga in Libya.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166190","166190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944843","2018-07-24","Department for International Development","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department is providing to the Tawerga that are currently displaced in the UN-supported Qararet al-Qatef camp.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166191","166191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944844","2018-07-24","Department for International Development","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is offering to people from the Tawerga community that have been displaced outside Libya as a result of the actions of the Libyan government.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166192","166192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944845","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Libyan Government on the rights of the Tawerga people to return to their homeland in Libya.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166193","166193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944846","2018-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the International Criminal Court on the investigation of people implicated in possible crimes against humanity against the Tawergha community.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166194","166194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944847","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether planned Royal Navy Type 31 frigates will be able to operate in the extreme climate conditions found in northern waters and the arctic region.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166103","166103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944848","2018-07-24","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the oral evidence of the Prime Minister of 18 July 2018 to the Liaison Committee, when the Government plans to publish 70 technical notices for businesses and families setting out how to prepare for a no-deal scenario for the UK leaving the EU; and how many of those notes have been completed.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166181","166181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944849","2018-07-24","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the oral evidence of the Prime Minister of 18 July 2018 to the Liaison Committee, if he will publish the titles of the 70 technical notices for businesses and families setting out how to prepare for a no-deal scenario for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166182","166182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944850","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will agree to calls from representatives and organisations in the Western Isles that the wreck of HMY Iolaire be designated a protected place under the Protection of Military Remains Act 1986.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166120","166120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944851","2018-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to publish its response to the consultation on strengthening consumer redress in housing.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166078","166078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944852","2018-07-24","Cabinet Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of days of sick leave taken for reasons of mental health in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166202","166202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944853","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to Answer of 15 June 2018 to Question 152799 and Answer of 02 July 2018 to Question 157791 on Special Protection Areas: Birds, on what date her Department received the results of the public consultations and associated recommendations of Natural England for the Flamborough and Filey Coast, the Bowland Fells and the Solent and Dorset Coast potential Special Protection Areas; what the other site designation priorities were that have caused delays to the decision to classify each site; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166215","166215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944854","2018-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what date Right hon Member for Uxbridge vacated the grace and favour apartments he occupied as Foreign Secretary.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166108","166108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944855","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the potential benefits of a greater uptake in electric bikes for (a) older people, (b) people on low incomes and (c) people with mobility problems.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166233","166233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944856","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of updating the Cycle to Work Scheme guidance to facilitate a greater uptake in electric bikes.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166234","166234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944857","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to secure access to EU organ transplant networks and databases after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166229","166229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944858","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the financial benefits for the public purse of the Cycle to Work Scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166235","166235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944859","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2018 to Question 163590 on London North Eastern Railway, what other advertising campaigns have been undertaken for the LNER branding; and if he will list the (a) locations of such advertising and (b) expenditure for each such location.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166222","166222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944860","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to allow pharmacy payment processes to include internet-only dispensing models.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166162","166162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944861","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the potential savings from digital-first pharmacy services.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166163","166163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944862","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has met with (a) the Scottish Government and (b) representatives of the Scottish fishing industry to discuss (i) domestic skills, (ii) training and (iii) recruitment in the Scottish fishing industry.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166236","166236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944863","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on (a) medicines adherence and (b) error rates in repeat prescription dispensing of digital-first pharmacy services.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166164","166164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944864","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Scottish Government on the Seafood 2040 framework and the relevance of its recommendations for the Scottish fishing industry.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166237","166237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944865","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department’s policy is on funding for the seafood processing sector after the conclusion of the 2014-2020 European Marine and Fisheries Fund.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166238","166238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944866","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to spend the remaining £6.4 million from the 2014-2020 European Marine and Fisheries Fund.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166239","166239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944867","2018-07-24","Department for Education","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of removing children with special educational needs and disabilities (SEND) from their SEND school on the educational outcomes of such children.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Mr John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166068","166068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944868","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing ring-fenced funding for arts, culture and media projects to incentivise greater diversity.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166165","166165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944869","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of the £4.9 million from the 2014-2020 European Marine and Fisheries Fund that his Department has spent on support for the seafood processing sector has been spent in Scotland (a) directly and (b) through the Barnett formula.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166240","166240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944870","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will require the BBC to publish the proportion of people it employs working (a) on-screen and (b) off-screen who are BAME.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166166","166166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944871","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the Scottish Government on support for the Scottish seafood processing sector.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166241","166241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944872","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department’s policy is on common frameworks facilitating cross-border trade and cross-border supply chains in the fishing industry between the constituent parts of the UK.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166242","166242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944873","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been stopped and searched in the last five years; and of those people, how many have been subsequently (a) arrested and (b) convicted.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Mr John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166069","166069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944874","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to introduce ring-fenced funding for arts, culture and media projects to incentivise greater diversity.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166167","166167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944875","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with representatives at (a) the BBC, (b) Channel Four and (c) private sector broadcasters on promoting diversity in those organisations.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166296","166296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944876","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on tackling hare coursing in Lincolnshire.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Mr John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166070","166070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944877","2018-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 5 July 2018 to Question 158768, whether his letter to the Competition and Markets Authority expressed the view that the assessment of the proposed merger of ASDA and Sainsbury's must also consider the potential effect of that merger on the high street.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Mr John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166071","166071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944878","2018-07-24","Department for Transport","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Network Rail on its vegetation management plan.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Mr John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166072","166072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944879","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential effect of a ban on electronic collars in containment systems on the number of domestic cats killed on the road.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Mr John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166073","166073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944880","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to reintroduce a seasonal agricultural  workers scheme.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Mr John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166074","166074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944881","2018-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Booker takeover by Tesco on small farmers and growers.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Mr John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166075","166075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944882","2018-07-23","Department for International Trade","2018-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many times (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have met with Lebanese officials to discuss trade with that country after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Mr John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166076","166076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943812","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health of 18 April 2018, Official Report, column 190WH, on Austerity: Life Expectancy, if he will publish the evidence referred to relating to other European countries.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165638","165638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943813","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women were sentenced to prison for less than (a) two weeks, (b) one month, (c) three months, (d) six months, (e) one year; and how many women were given a custodial sentence in 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165645","165645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943814","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2018 to Question 154763 on Young Offender Institutions: Education, what estimate he has made of the cost of collecting that information.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165646","165646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943815","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the role of the National Centre for Sports and Exercise Medicine in Sheffield in the future of the NHS.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165639","165639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943816","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of clinical appointments provided at the NHS clinics co-located on the sites of the National Centre for Sports and Exercise Medicine in Sheffield in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165640","165640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943817","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many maintenance requests in total have been outstanding throughout the prison estate on 1 January in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165647","165647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943818","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many total maintenance requests have been outstanding in each prison on 1 January in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165648","165648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943819","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to help small businesses cover the costs of making the mandated transition to online VAT returns in April 2019.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165614","165614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943820","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the provision of training for prisoners in HMYOI Deerbolt.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165649","165649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943821","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the provision of training for prisoners in HMYOI Doncaster.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165650","165650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943822","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the provision of training for prisoners in HMYOI Werrington.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165651","165651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943823","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the provision of training for prisoners in HMYOI Wetherby.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165652","165652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943824","2018-07-23","House of Commons Commission","2018-07-18","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, whether the Commission holds information on the number of security passes to access the Parliamentary estate held by (a) males and (b) females working for hon. Members as Parliamentary Assistants or Researchers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165458","165458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943825","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's press release, Crackdown on rogue bailiffs, published on 2 April 2018, on how many occasions (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have met with representatives of the bailiff industry to discuss bailiff reform.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165459","165459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943826","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to meet debt advice charities to discuss the scope of the upcoming call for evidence on bailiff reform announced by his Department on 2 April 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165460","165460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943827","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's press release, Crackdown on rogue bailiffs, published on 2 April 2018, when his Department plans to launch its call for evidence.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165461","165461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943828","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure immigration authorities adequately assess the safety risks of returning people to (a) Sudan and (b) South Sudan; and whether his Department undertakes monitoring of such people after their return to those countries.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165448","165448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943829","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the social enterprise Livewell South West will receive additional resource from the planned increase in funding for Agenda for Change.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165714","165714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943830","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the 2018 report by ICAN, Bercow: Ten Years On, what plans he has to make sure that the special interest group convened by Public Health England to identify key mental health prevention evidence and its relevance to practice and to highlight gaps and make recommendations for these to be addressed through further research includes an expert in speech, language and communication and the links with mental health.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165670","165670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943831","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the the forthcoming victims strategy addresses the concerns raised by victims about the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority of (a) same roof and (b) rules on access to the compensation scheme by people with unspent convictions.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165653","165653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943832","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what lessons his Department has learned from the construction of HMP Berwyn for future prison construction.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165654","165654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943833","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will assess the potential merits of ensuring that farm support payments are dependent on farmers improving performance against animal welfare standards after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165543","165543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943834","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people with multiple sclerosis who scored 12 points under PIP mobility activity 2 moving around descriptor (e) can stand and then move more than 1 metre but no more than 20 metres, either aided or unaided were (a) new claimants and (b) reassessments in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165668","165668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943835","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to update the guidance on the 2017 money laundering regulations for estate agents.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165681","165681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943836","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the agenda was for the meeting between the Minister of State for Local Government and the leader of Somerset County Council in July 2018.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165479","165479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943837","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for the Ministry of Justice of 2 July 2018, Official Report, column 100, what criteria his Department has used to determine that 10,000 prison places will lead to the accommodation of 20,000 prisoners.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165655","165655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943838","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that women are able to get on to waiting lists for rape crisis centres.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165674","165674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943839","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the effect of recent changes in the level of funding for early education on the number of nursery places available for children with special educational needs in Wandsworth; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165675","165675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943840","2018-07-23","Cabinet Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 9.5 of the Ministerial Code, what steps he is taking to ensure that a copy of the text of an oral statement is shown to the Opposition shortly before it is made; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165676","165676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943841","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received representations on the arrest of an Iranian diplomat in Germany on charges related to a foiled plot against the Iran Freedom – The Alternative gathering on 30 June 2018 in Paris; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165541","165541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943842","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential perpetrators of the plot against the Iran Freedom – The Alternative gathering on 30 June 2018 in Paris.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165542","165542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943843","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he is having with NHS England to ensure that consultants are aware of the licensing process for access to medical cannabis.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165715","165715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943844","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to create an aggravated offence of attacking shopkeepers who refuse to sell a corrosive substance or sharp weapon.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165641","165641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943845","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons his Department agreed to provide funding for the policing costs of the recent visit by President Donald Trump to Police Scotland; and whether an assessment was made of providing such funding for police forces in England and Wales.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165642","165642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943846","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of police officers who were on duty for the purpose of policing the recent visit by President Donald Trump.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165643","165643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943847","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to reduce the number of animals that one person can transport to the UK under the Pet Travel Scheme after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165544","165544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943848","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 112175, how many officials of his Department are working with colleagues across government to inform plans for the UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165591","165591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943849","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2018 to Question 163522 on Electronic Commerce: EU Law, what the expiry date will be for the implementation period.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165476","165476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943850","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of money rail franchises have paid out in compensation to ticket holders in each of the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165615","165615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943851","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he is taking steps to ensure that charities are consulted on the development of the UK Shared Prosperity Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165592","165592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943852","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Spanish counterpart on an independence referendum for Catalonia.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165621","165621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943853","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of student finance provision for students who began their university course as an international student but were subsequently granted indefinite leave to remain while still studying.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165451","165451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943854","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will bring forward proposals to enable international students who are granted indefinite leave to remain while undertaking a degree to access student loans.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165452","165452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943855","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the compatibility of the Hong Kong Government's ban on the Hong Kong Special Administration Region National Party with the human rights guarantees contained in the Sino-British Joint Declaration.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165442","165442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943856","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the implications for policing in (a) Merseyside and (b) England and Wales of an increase in crimes recorded and a fall in criminal charges brought since 2014-15.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165628","165628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943857","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of implications for his policies on criteria for transitional funding in the first two years for areas having a devolved adult education budget of the WEA's latest impact report on its disadvantaged students.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165468","165468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943858","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of trends in staffing levels in prisons over the last five years.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165528","165528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943859","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the recommendations of the report Ignoring the alarms: How NHS eating disorder services are failing patients, published by the  Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman in December 2017, what progress Health Education England has made on tackling the gaps in the provision of (a) education, (b) training and (c) numbers of eating disorder specialists in the NHS.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165489","165489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943860","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report, Ignoring the alarms: How NHS eating disorder services are failing patients, published by the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman in December 2018, what progress (a) his Department and (b) NHS England have made on reviewing the existing (i) quality and (ii) availability of adult eating disorder services to achieve parity with child and adolescent services.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165490","165490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943861","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report, Ignoring the alarms: How NHS eating disorder services are failing patients, published by the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman in December 2018, what progress NICE has made on including co-ordination of services in its new quality standard for eating disorders.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165491","165491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943862","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report, Ignoring the alarms: How NHS eating disorder services are failing patients, published in December 2017, what steps (a) NHS Improvement and (b) NHS England have taken to (i) improve and ii) better co-ordinate eating disorder services.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165492","165492"
