"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15744","2013-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much inward foreign direct investment did UK Trade and Investment and its private sector partners attracted into London during (a) the last 12 months and (b) the last two years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170801","170801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15745","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what alternative arrangements, if any, will be required to enable the transmission of controlled substances upon opting out of Council Decision 2001/419/JHA; what her policy is on putting in place such alternative arrangements and whether they should differ from the provisions of the Council Decision; and what assessment she has made of whether these arrangements would be put in place.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170809","170809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15746","2013-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether Council Framework Decision 2001/413/JHA has required any alteration to law or practice in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170802","170802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15747","2013-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the UK complies with all the requirements of Council Framework Decision 2000/383/JHA, as amended; and whether the Government intends to maintain the laws implementing these requirements once the Framework Decision ceases to bind the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170803","170803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15748","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the UK public funds has been of transmissions carried out under Council Decision 2001/419/ JHA in the last year; and what the purpose was of each of these transmissions.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170810","170810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15749","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to UK public funds has been in each of the last five years of complying with Joint Action 97/339/JHA.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170804","170804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15750","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with which EU member states the UK does not have bilateral or multilateral agreements on matters covered by Joint Action 97/339/JHA; and whether the UK would seek to establish such agreements with these member states upon opting out of this measure.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170805","170805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15751","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether co-operation which is undertaken under the provisions of Joint Action 98/699/JHA will be maintained following a UK opt out from that Joint Action; and what the cost has been to UK public funds in each of the last five years of this co-operation.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170811","170811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15752","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the importance of Joint Action 96/610/JHA in counter-terrorism co-operation between the UK and other EU member states.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170806","170806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15753","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times UK authorities have made use of the directory under Joint Action 96/610/JHA in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170807","170807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15754","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the UK complies with the obligations relating to judicial training under Joint Action 98/699/JHA.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170812","170812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15755","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the cost of producing and maintaining the guide required by Joint Action 98/699/JHA.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170813","170813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15756","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many prosecutions have been facilitated in the UK through Joint Action 96/699/JHA.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170778","170778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15757","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether existing policy and practice in matters covered by Joint Action 97/372/JHA, including co-operation with other member states, will alter as a result of the UK opting out of the Joint Action.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170814","170814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15758","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how frequently information exchange involving the UK is conducted on the basis of Joint Action 96/699/JHA; and what the cost has been to UK public funds in each of the last five years of such information exchange.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170779","170779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15759","2013-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of the Government's Work Programme.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170822","170822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15760","2013-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason it is his Department's policy not to employ Jobcentre Plus staff to implement its Work Programme.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170823","170823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15761","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to UK public funds has been in each of the last five years of co-operation with other member states undertaken under the provisions of Joint Action 96/750/JHA.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170815","170815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15762","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether existing policy and practice in matters covered by Joint Action 96/750/JHA, including co-operation with other member states, will alter as a result of the UK opting out of this measure.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170816","170816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15763","2013-10-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, for what reason she has recently declined an invitation to meet representatives of the Musicians' Union and Equity.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170781","170781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15764","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the UK has taken to assure the EU that the UK is compliant with Joint Action 96/750/JHA.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170817","170817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15765","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Joint Action 96/698/JHA, with which business organisations the Government and its agencies have memoranda of understanding.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170782","170782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15766","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what UK legislative or operational measures, if any, would be necessary to satisfy the requirements of Joint Action 96/750/JHA that do not accord with existing policy or practice.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170818","170818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15767","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government intends to maintain and periodically review the memoranda of understanding required by Joint Action 96/698/JHA irrespective of the UK's participation in the Joint Action.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170783","170783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15768","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which provisions of Joint Action 96/750/JHA do not accord with existing UK policy or practice.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170819","170819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15769","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government last reviewed the effectiveness of the memoranda of understanding required by Joint Action 96/698/JHA; and what manpower this took.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170784","170784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15770","2013-10-14","Department of Health","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the Congenital Heart Disease Review to follow the recommendations of the Independent Reconfiguration Panel and to take account of the outcome of the judicial review case brought against the Joint Committee of Primary Care Trusts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170785","170785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15771","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, through what means, if any, the information currently exchanged through Joint Action 96/699/JHA will be exchanged with other member states assuming that the UK ceases to be bound by this Joint Action.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170820","170820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15777","2013-10-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dairy farms in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK have ceased to operate in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170701","170701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15778","2013-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what total cost has been incurred by local authorities in presenting a defence in planning appeals which have resulted in their initial decisions being overturned by the planning inspector since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170702","170702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15779","2013-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning appeals have resulted in local authority decisions being overturned by the planning inspector in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170703","170703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15780","2013-10-15","Department for Transport","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total cost to the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency is of processing a payment for a 12 months tax disc by credit card.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170704","170704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15781","2013-10-15","Department for Transport","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase access to public transport in rural areas.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170705","170705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15782","2013-10-15","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what his policy is on participation by police officers in political campaigning.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 900470","900470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15784","2013-10-14","Department for Education","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress he has made on ensuring that all young people have the chance to learn an instrument and receive top quality music education.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170567","170567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15785","2013-10-14","Department for Education","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department has provided for music education for each pupil in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170569","170569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15786","2013-10-14","HM Treasury","2013-10-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of royalty income from petroleum exploration and development licences in the UK in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170581","170581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15787","2013-10-14","HM Treasury","2013-10-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of increasing the minimum wage by £1,000 each year on (a) pay as you earn contributions, (b) employer's National Insurance contributions, (c) employee's National Insurance contributions and (d) tax credits.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170572","170572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15788","2013-10-14","Cabinet Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average real wage level in Wales was in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170607","170607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15789","2013-10-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-10-09","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, which local authorities have taken part in City Deals to date; and what freedoms and funding have been given as part of each such City Deal.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170590","170590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15790","2013-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to secure the release of South Yard, HM Dockyard Devonport to the Homes and Community Agency; and by when such a transfer will take place.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170591","170591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15791","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with her European counterparts on establishing a co-ordinated European resettlement programme for the most vulnerable refugees from the Syrian conflict.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170594","170594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15792","2013-10-14","Department of Health","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the Food Standards Agency's ability to monitor cadmium in imported cocoa.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170595","170595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15793","2013-10-14","Department for Education","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to reduce bureaucracy on (a) new and (b) established academies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170616","170616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15794","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, following the High Court judgment of 5 July 2013 on the minimum income threshold for spouses or partners and children applying in the family route, what guidance her Department has issued regarding passports and other documents that have been submitted with applications made under Appendix FM to the Immigration Rules that have been subject to the hold on decision-making.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170617","170617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15795","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, following the High Court judgment of 5 July 2013 on the minimum income threshold for spouses or partners and children applying in the family route, (a) how many applications made under Appendix FM to the Immigration Rules have been subject to the hold on decision-making and (b) how many such applications have been received by visa application centres outside the UK.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170618","170618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15796","2013-10-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 October 2013, Official Report, column 201W, Broadband: Rossendale, how many premises in Rossendale and Darwen constituency are included in the 1800 premises passed to date; and what proportion of the premises in Lancashire, Blackpool and Blackburn with Darwen are in Rossendale and Darwen constituency.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170619","170619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15797","2013-10-14","Department of Health","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Chief Medical Officer is obliged to publish details of meetings in the same manner as Ministers publish ministerial diaries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170641","170641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15798","2013-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons the Senior President of the Tribunals will no longer prepare an annual report on the performance of decision making in his Department.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170642","170642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15799","2013-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations he has received on removing the duty of the Senior President of Tribunals to report on the standards of decision-making by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170643","170643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15800","2013-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of additional security measures which were given consideration but not adopted at Camp Bastion before September 2012.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170637","170637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15801","2013-10-14","HM Treasury","2013-10-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what has been the cost to the public purse of the legal challenge brought by his Department against the proposal to limit bonuses paid to those in the financial sector; which legal firms have been engaged in respect of this case; what their daily rate is for (a) solicitors and (b) barristers; and if he will make a weekly report to Parliament on the ongoing costs of this case.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170638","170638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15802","2013-10-14","Cabinet Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether it remains the policy of the Government to respond to reports from Select Committees of the House within two months.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170665","170665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15803","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many immigration raids were carried out on businesses in (a) Rupert Street, (b) Wardour Street, (c) Dansey Place, (d) Macclesfield Street, (e) Gerrard Street, (f) Horse and Dolphin Yard, (g) Gerrard Place, (h) Newport Place, (i) Little Newport Street, (j) Leicester Place, (k) Leicester Court, (l) Leicester Street and (m) Lisle Street in London W1 between 1 January and 30 September 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170650","170650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15804","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many immigration raids were carried out on businesses in (a) Rupert Street, (b) Wardour Street, (c) Dansey Place, (d) Macclesfield Street, (e) Gerrard Street, (f) Horse and Dolphin Yard, (g) Gerrard Place, (h) Newport Place, (i) Little Newport Street, (j) Leicester Place, (k) Leicester Court, (l) Leicester Street and (m) Lisle Street in London W1 between 1 January and 30 September 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170651","170651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15805","2013-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the health problems in Iraq arising from the use of uranium-depleted munitions and the nerve agent Sarin during the first and second Gulf wars; and what steps his Department is taking to tackle such health issues in an effective and appropriate way.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170685","170685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15806","2013-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where each Army unit that has been withdrawn from Germany is being re-based.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170679","170679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15807","2013-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions power to a nuclear submarine's reactor cooling systems has failed when in port in each submarine base in the last 20 years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170726","170726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15808","2013-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has plans to provide training on drones to African-led International Support Mission to Mali.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170713","170713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15809","2013-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people lived in private rental accommodation in England in September (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170748","170748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15810","2013-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with farming bodies to protect the yellowhammer in the UK; and what incentives exist for habitat improvement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170741","170741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15811","2013-10-14","Department of Health","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the British Medical Association on side effects of the use of sun beds.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170757","170757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15812","2013-10-14","Department for International Development","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support the UK is providing to Lebanon and Jordan to cope with the large numbers of refugees from Syria.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170758","170758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15813","2013-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the responsibilities of trading standards and a local authority's licensing department are with regards to the regulation of pet shops.","Biography information for Laura Sandys","Laura Sandys","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170723","170723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15814","2013-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make a statement regarding the proposed removal of the Union Flag from meat packaged in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170790","170790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15815","2013-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with which foreign companies, investors, sovereign wealth funds and governments UK Trade and Investment worked to secure inward investment into London during (a) 2011 and (b) 2012.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170796","170796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15816","2013-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which foreign companies, investors, sovereign wealth funds and/or governments UK Trade and Investment and their private sector partners are currently working with to secure inward investment into London.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170797","170797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15817","2013-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many private sector companies deliver the Government's Work Programme; and what the cost to the public purse has been of those companies' involvement.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170821","170821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15818","2013-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what advice he has sought from (a) English Heritage, (b) the Advisory Panel on the Archaeology of Burials in England and (c) other bodies or experts on (i) whether he has power to amend the terms of the licence issued to the University of Leicester Archaeology Department to dig for the remains of King Richard III and (ii) other related matters; and if he will place in the Library copies of all the advice he has received on this matter.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170780","170780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16006","2013-10-15","Women and Equalities","2013-10-09","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps he is taking to increase the number of women elected to Parliament.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 900473","900473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16254","2013-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the Exchequer received in income from petroleum exploration and development licences on land in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11 and (c) 2011-12.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170580","170580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16255","2013-10-14","Cabinet Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the number of workers in the offshore oil and gas industry who are currently employed on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170654","170654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16256","2013-10-14","Cabinet Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the number of workers in the offshore oil and gas industry who are employed using daily agreements with (a) employers and (b) employment agencies.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170655","170655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/16257","2013-10-14","Cabinet Office","2013-10-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many workers in the (a) rail, (b) maritime and (c) offshore oil and gas industry are currently classified as self-employed.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170657","170657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15310","2013-10-10","Department for Transport","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department had with (a) the Council of Mortgage Lenders and (b) the National Federation of Estate Agents whilst devising the compensation proposals for those affected by Phase One of the High Speed 2 scheme.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170215","170215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15311","2013-10-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will estimate the average cost to domestic electricity customers in (a) Greater Manchester, (b) Oxfordshire and (c) Surrey who consumed 3.300 kWh of electricity in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170216","170216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15312","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients in Greater Manchester with non-urgent hospital appointments have waited for over two hours for an ambulance since April 2013.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170217","170217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15313","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients in Greater Manchester with non-urgent hospital appointments have been taken to hospital in a taxi because no ambulances were available since April 2013.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170218","170218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15314","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints about Arriva Transport Solutions have been received by Greater Manchester Ambulance service in each month since April 2013.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170219","170219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15315","2013-10-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to UK Export Finance's Annual Report and Accounts for 2012-13, how many of the 138 transactions listed in that report are covered by the Recommendation of the Council on Common Approaches for officially supported export credits and environmental and social due diligence (The Common Approaches) that governs the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development export credit agencies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170220","170220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15316","2013-10-10","Department for Transport","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that the planned feasibility study of improvements for the A303/A30/A358 corridor will consider these routes as one whole corridor in which the A358 and A30 elements meet different but complementary growth and resilience needs of strategic importance to the South West.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170221","170221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15317","2013-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of (a) prospects for the collapse of the North Korean government and (b) the potential consequences of the collapse of the North Korean government; and what plans his Department has produced to respond to any such consequences.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170222","170222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15318","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent by Greater Manchester Ambulance service on taxis for patients since April 2013.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170223","170223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15319","2013-10-10","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many anti-social behaviour orders have been issued to people in Manchester in each year since their introducion.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170225","170225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15320","2013-10-10","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many instances of anti-social behaviour by people in Manchester have been reported in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170226","170226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15321","2013-10-10","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests to exercise her discretion in granting leave to remain on compassionate grounds she has received since May 2010; and how many individuals have been granted exceptional leave to remain as a result.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170227","170227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15322","2013-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to calculate the loss to farmers as a consequence of outbreaks of bovine tuberculosis.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170228","170228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15323","2013-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what evidence is used by his Department to calculate compensation for animals destroyed as a result of a positive test for bovine tuberculosis; and where that evidence is published.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170229","170229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15324","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that blind and partially sighted people are adequately assessed in work capability assessments.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170230","170230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15325","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) military and ex-military primary amputees, (b) civilian primary amputees, (c) military and ex-military established amputees and (d) civilian established amputees there are in England.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170231","170231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15326","2013-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints the Legal Ombudsman decided not to investigate because they were submitted out of time in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170232","170232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15327","2013-10-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much was provided in (a) financial guarantees and (b) other support for UK exports through UK Export Finance in (i) 2009-10, (ii) 2010-11, (iii) 2011-12 and (iv) 2012-13.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170233","170233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15328","2013-10-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether any products sold legally as non-harmonised food supplements in other EU member states have been prohibited from sale in the UK despite mutual recognition being cited.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170234","170234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15329","2013-10-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what grounds there are for prohibiting products sold lawfully as non-harmonised food supplements in other member states from being sold in the UK under mutual recognition.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170235","170235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15330","2013-10-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the progress of retailers in implementing guidelines on the display of newspapers and magazines featuring age sensitive content following the Bailey review; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170236","170236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15331","2013-10-10","Department for Transport","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will review (a) its policy of requiring HGV drivers to avoid areas with bridge restrictions of 7.5 tons and (b) the use of satellite navigation systems on such routes.","Biography information for Jessica Lee","Jessica Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170238","170238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15332","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to promote regular sight tests.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170239","170239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15333","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of temporal arteritis.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170240","170240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15334","2013-10-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding her Department makes available for community internet television broadcasting.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170242","170242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15335","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to receive a reply to her letter of 2 September 2013 to the interim director general of UK Visas and Immigration on behalf of a constituent, CTS ref B23798/13.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170246","170246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15336","2013-10-14","Department for Education","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how poverty among five, six and seven year olds will be measured and recorded following the announcement that every child in this age group will now qualify for free school meals.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170247","170247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15337","2013-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many coroners are above the judicial retirement age; and what estimate he has made of the average age of such coroners.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170248","170248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15338","2013-10-14","HM Treasury","2013-10-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish in an anonymised table the range of charitable gifts donated by the top 1,000 donors and subsequently claimed against tax.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170249","170249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15339","2013-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reasons his Department provided indirect funding to the Migration Observatory in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170250","170250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15340","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of the ceremonial uniform worn by HM Chief Inspector of Constabulary; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170251","170251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15341","2013-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of including the Postcode Address File in the privatisation of Royal Mail on businesses and public bodies.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170252","170252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15342","2013-10-14","Department for Education","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effects of mid-course changes to GCSE qualifications on (a) schools and (b) students taking such examinations in the current academic year.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170253","170253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15343","2013-10-14","Department for Education","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will extend eligibility for free bus travel for school students aged over 16, following the implementation of the increased compulsory participation age.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170254","170254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15344","2013-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the implications for the policy of the Natural Environment Research Council on funding for fossil fuel exploration and extraction of the findings of Working Group 1 of the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change, published on 27 September 2013, on the upper limits on the amount of cumulative carbon dioxide emissions from anthropogenic sources compatible with limiting global warming to below two degrees celsius global temperature rise; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170255","170255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15345","2013-10-14","HM Treasury","2013-10-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the written answer of 29 August 2013, Official Report, column 988W, on Air Passenger Duty, if he will introduce an official definition of aviation hub.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170256","170256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15346","2013-10-14","Department for International Development","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make a statement about plans for the G20 Anti-Corruption Working Group.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170393","170393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15347","2013-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, who has owned the Drill Hall in Newport, Isle of Wight since it was constructed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170394","170394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15348","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assurances she has received on whether all evidence presented to the Independent Police Complaints Commission from (a) South Yorkshire Police and (b) Norman Bettison relating to the Hillsborough disaster is complete.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170395","170395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15349","2013-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will assess what implications there may be for his policy of the recent report published by the International Humanist and Ethical Union entitled, Freedom of Thought 2012: A Global Report on Discrimination Against Humanists, Atheists and the Non-religious.","Biography information for Angie Bray","Angie Bray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170396","170396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15350","2013-10-14","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on establishing a ring-fenced fund for rare disease drugs.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170399","170399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15351","2013-10-14","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request that the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence take steps to assess treatments for rare conditions differently to less rare conditions.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170400","170400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15352","2013-10-14","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that specialist centres are appropriately equipped to treat (a) muscular dystrophy and (b) similar conditions.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170401","170401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15353","2013-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with the Minister for Social Development in the Northern Ireland Executive on the effects of the implementation of welfare reform in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170402","170402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15354","2013-10-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to introduce the Renewable Heat Incentive for residential properties; and when he expects that grant to be available.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170243","170243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15355","2013-10-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which food supplements have been introduced into the UK under mutual recognition since 2005.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170244","170244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15356","2013-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent representations he has received on the late submission of complaints to the Legal Ombudsman; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170245","170245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15357","2013-10-17","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with (a) the Prime Minister, (b) the Deputy Prime Minister and (c) other Cabinet colleagues on the appointment of junior Ministers to her Department (i) prior to and (ii) since the recent reshuffle.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170257","170257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15358","2013-10-17","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Ministers in her Department have (a) responsibility for and (b) access to classified information in connection with the Security Service; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170258","170258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15359","2013-10-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the additional cost to the UK cement industry of the cross sectoral correction factor for Phase III of the EU Emissions Trading System.","Biography information for Mark Pawsey","Mark Pawsey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170260","170260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15360","2013-10-10","Department for Transport","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department is conducting into aerotoxic syndrome.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170382","170382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15361","2013-10-10","HM Treasury","2013-10-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many mutual assistance in recovery of debt demands have been made by the German tax authorities against UK tax residents in the last five years.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170383","170383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15362","2013-10-10","Department for International Development","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if there are plans financially to support UK-based INGO initiatives that support market-led initiatives for the Great Himalayan Trail.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170385","170385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15363","2013-10-10","Department for Transport","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on the future role of open access rail operators.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170386","170386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15364","2013-10-10","Attorney General","2013-10-08","To ask the Attorney General, with what proportion of local government social services departments the Crown Prosecution Service has protocol agreements for the disclosure of third-party evidence.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170387","170387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15365","2013-10-10","Attorney General","2013-10-08","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of prosecution witnesses attended court (a) one time and (b) at all in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170388","170388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15366","2013-10-10","Attorney General","2013-10-08","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of prosecution witnesses in each Crown Prosecution Service area attended court (a) on time and (b) at all in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170389","170389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15367","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many businesses in (a) the UK and (b) Bolton North East constituency have taken part in the wage incentive scheme since the introduction of the Youth Contract.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170391","170391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15368","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the primary aim of the Fundamental Review of Allocations Policy is.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170262","170262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15369","2013-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the availability of commercial loans to businesses and individuals operating in the rural economy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170406","170406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15370","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department provided guidance to the Advisory Committee on Resource Allocation whilst it was revising the funding formula during the Fundamental Review of Allocations Policy.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170263","170263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15371","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to maximise the use of locally (a) grown and (b) supplied food in NHS hospitals.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170407","170407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15372","2013-10-10","HM Treasury","2013-10-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make a statement on HM Treasury's approval of bonuses paid to employees of Lloyds Banking Group and the Royal Bank of Scotland.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170264","170264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15373","2013-10-10","Department for Education","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to maximise the use of locally (a) grown and (b) supplied foods in schools; and whether the introduction of universal free school meals in infant schools will include requirements or incentives to utilise such products.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170408","170408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15374","2013-10-10","Prime Minister","2013-10-08","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will publish the terms of reference and scope of Sir Jeremy Heywood's inquiry into youth unemployment; and when he expects this inquiry to report.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170409","170409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15375","2013-10-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects to launch a consultation on measures to regulate the use of zero-hour contracts.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170410","170410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15376","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps will be taken to encourage greater use of and support for self-monitoring in clinical commissioning groups across England.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170266","170266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15377","2013-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what length of the English coastal path is currently available for public access; what proportion this represents of the eventual complete path; and when he expects the full length of the path to be publicly accessible.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170411","170411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15378","2013-10-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received in respect of Hibu following suspension of its shares in July 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170415","170415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15379","2013-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that local authority affordable housing targets are met.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170267","170267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15380","2013-10-10","HM Treasury","2013-10-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the level of competitiveness of savings products.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170416","170416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15381","2013-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations he has received from Raytheon regarding a Maritime Patrol version of the Sentinel R.1 aircraft.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170413","170413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15382","2013-10-10","Department for International Development","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effects of the (a) demolition by Egypt of the tunnels into Gaza and (b) reduced access through Rafah on the daily supplies of food, fuel, construction materials and medicines entering Gaza.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170268","170268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15383","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England has the authority to transfer a patient's care from one NHS provider to another if the patient is satisfied with his or her current provider.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170414","170414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15384","2013-10-10","HM Treasury","2013-10-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take following Barclays' decision to cease providing money transfer services to Somalia to ensure there are robust measures against suspected money laundering between the UK and Somalia.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170418","170418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15385","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the compatibility of the decision of NHS England to transfer brain tumour patients undergoing treatment at the National Hospital for Neurology and Neurosurgery to another provider with his Department's policy on patient choice.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170420","170420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15386","2013-10-10","Department for International Development","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations she has made to her Israeli counterparts on increasing the flow of food, fuel and medicines into Gaza from Israel through Kerem Shalom.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170380","170380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15387","2013-10-10","Department for Education","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were assessed as having profound and multiple learning difficulties in (a) the UK, (b) North West England, (c) Cheshire, (d) Merseyside and (e) the Wirral in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170419","170419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15388","2013-10-10","Department for International Development","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effects of Israel's restrictions on Palestinian fishing boats off Gaza on the (a) income and (b) nutritional status of Palestinians.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170381","170381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15389","2013-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total amount spent on legal aid in each of the last five years was.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170426","170426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15390","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseeker's allowance claimants were sanctioned on more than one occasion in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170421","170421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15391","2013-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with officials and Ministers in the Welsh Government in the last 12 months on the Domestic Fire Safety (Wales) Measure 2011.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170436","170436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15392","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the sub-group of the specialised cancer CRG which is scoping out current indications for molecular testing in patients will be (a) appointed and (b) operational.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170422","170422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15393","2013-10-10","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many calls the police 101 service has received in each month from its launch to date.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170428","170428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15394","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to ESOL courses for claimants of jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170429","170429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15395","2013-10-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funds her Department makes available to refurbish privately-owned seafront piers.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170423","170423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15396","2013-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he last spoke to his fire advisor on the installation of fire sprinklers in domestic properties.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170437","170437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15397","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of phone calls received by the 0800 055 6688 Jobcentre Plus telephone line came from mobile telephones in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170424","170424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15398","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employees in (a) Britain and (b) Bolton North East constituency have taken part in the wage incentive scheme since the introduction of the Youth Contract.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170430","170430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15399","2013-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funds his Department makes available to refurbish privately-owned seafront piers.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170425","170425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15400","2013-10-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with Welsh Government ministers on the privatisation of the Royal Mail.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170438","170438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15401","2013-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what weapons systems are planned to be included in the Type 26 Global Combat Ship.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170431","170431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15402","2013-10-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-10-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment his Department has made of the financial value of volunteering and unpaid care by staff of his Office.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170439","170439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15403","2013-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what unmanned aircraft system and rotor systems are planned to be included in the Type 26 Global Combat Ship.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170432","170432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15404","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the financial value of volunteering and unpaid care by staff of his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170440","170440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15405","2013-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Type 26 Global Combat ships are planned to be built; and when the first ceremonial cutting of metal will take place.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170433","170433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15406","2013-10-10","Cabinet Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were employed in each (a) county and (b) constituency in North Wales in the (i) 2001 and (ii) 2011 Census figures.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170441","170441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15407","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of applications for disability living allowance were rejected in each month from May 2013 to September 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170446","170446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15408","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the costs to GP practices of informing patients of the disclosure of data and their rights to withhold information under the care.data arrangements.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170434","170434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15409","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims for disability living allowance were rejected in each of the last (a) six months and (b) five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170447","170447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15410","2013-10-10","Wales Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with officials and Ministers in the Welsh Government in the last 12 months on the Domestic Fire Safety (Wales) Measure 2011.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170435","170435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15411","2013-10-10","Leader of the House","2013-10-08","To ask the Leader of the House, when he plans to respond to the letter of the hon. Member for Bolton North East dated 30 July 2013 on his policy for responding to e-petitions that have passed 10,000 signatures.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170448","170448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15412","2013-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many registered intermediaries were appointed for children in cases involving (a) sexual offences and (b) other offences in the last three years for which data are available at (i) pre-police interview, (ii) pre-trial and (iii) trial broken down by (A) age, (B) geography and (C) impairment group.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170443","170443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15413","2013-10-10","Attorney General","2013-10-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many finalised defendant prosecutions were prosecuted under charges relating to sexual offences involving a victim under 18 years of age (a) for the last three years for which data are available and (b) since January 2013.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170444","170444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15414","2013-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Type 26 Global Combat Ship will be completed and come into service.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170445","170445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15415","2013-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that rural communities have adequate access to public transport.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170450","170450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15416","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to respond to the NHS Confederation report, Urgent and Emergency Care: An accident waiting to happen?; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170451","170451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15417","2013-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent conversations he has had with the Secretary of State for (a) Energy and Climate Change and (b) Business, Innovation and Skills on the findings of the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) fifth assessment report published on 27 September 2013 on the upper amounts of cumulative carbon dioxide emissions from anthropogenic sources compatible with limiting global warming to below two degrees celsius global temperature rise; if he will make an assessment of implications of the IPCC's findings on upper amounts of cumulative carbon dioxide emissions on the proportion of known fossil fuel reserves that can be exploited (i) globally and (ii) domestically; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170488","170488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15418","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170459","170459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15419","2013-10-10","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the ability of households in receipt of support under section 4 of the Asylum Act 1999 to access a landline telephone.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170489","170489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15420","2013-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170453","170453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15421","2013-10-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the revised codes of practice of the trade associations representing the payday and short-term loan industry published on 25 July 2012.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170490","170490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15422","2013-10-10","HM Treasury","2013-10-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170454","170454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15423","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what processes are in place to identify households that will potentially be affected by the household benefit cap.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170491","170491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15424","2013-10-14","HM Treasury","2013-10-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether consideration has been given to introducing a protected minimum balance in the use of continuous payment authorities as is in force for bank arrestments in Scotland under the Bankruptcy and Diligence etc. (Scotland) Act 2007.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170476","170476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15425","2013-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the security situation in Peshawar, Pakistan following recent violence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170455","170455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15426","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether individuals who have been affected by the household benefit cap were offered early access to the Work Programme.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170492","170492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15427","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in the London Borough of Brent have had their benefits reduced as a result of the household benefit cap.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170493","170493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15428","2013-10-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170452","170452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15429","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulances have been in operation in the Liverpool city-region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170495","170495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15430","2013-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he expects the Government's review of the fourth Carbon Budget to be completed.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170478","170478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15431","2013-10-14","HM Treasury","2013-10-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fees were paid to banks advising on the sale of Government shares in Lloyds Banking Group.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170479","170479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15432","2013-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with the Moroccan ambassador the report that the bodies of eight Saharawi, including two children who were extrajudicially executed by the Moroccan armed forces in 1976 have been found and that no information on any of the eight cases was revealed by the Equality and Reconciliation Commission.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170498","170498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15433","2013-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much of the £200 million of Government funding allocated to the Green Deal in November 2011 has been spent to date.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170480","170480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15434","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions have taken place with ministerial counterparts in the devolved regions regarding the ratification of the decision by the Clinical Priorities Grouping in respect of the Soliris form of Eculizumab taken in July 2013.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170497","170497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15435","2013-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will (a) raise with the Moroccan ambassador and (b) instruct the UK ambassador in Rabat to investigate the violent break-up of a demonstration by unemployed Saharawi graduates on 31 August 2013 in El Aauin, Western Sahara and allegations of beatings leading to hospitalisation.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170499","170499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15436","2013-10-14","Department for International Development","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when her Department will release new details of (a) how the Catalytic Fund will function, including how funds can be accessed, (b) what types of activities the funding can be used for and (c) what countries must do to access the funds.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170481","170481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15437","2013-10-14","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what date his Department was informed of a likely underspend in budgets of Merseyside primary care trusts in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170519","170519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15438","2013-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how he will ensure that a part of the money paid by the EU under the new protocol to the EU-Morocco Fisheries Partnership Agreement will be for the benefit of the indigenous people of Western Sahara.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170501","170501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15439","2013-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2013, Official Report, column 128W, on Central Sussex College, what conclusions were drawn from the urgent review of the financial situation of Central Sussex College; and what further steps have since been taken.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170482","170482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15440","2013-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to his Answer of 18 July 2013, Official Report, column 859W, on biofuels, how many microgrammes of small particulates (PM2.5) per cubic metre of air he expects emissions from biomass combustion to add to the atmosphere in the UK in 2020 (a) net of fuels displaced by biomass and (b) not net of fuels displaced by biomass.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170509","170509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15441","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in (a) Liverpool, Walton constituency, (b) Liverpool and (c) England have been granted work permits since May 2010.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170510","170510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15442","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to publicise the implications for patients of the introduction of the care.data system.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170503","170503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15443","2013-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the proportion of heat generated by heat pumps that can be considered as renewable according to existing regulations.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170484","170484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15444","2013-10-14","Department for Transport","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total length in kilometres of the HS2/HS1 link is (a) tunnelled and (b) above ground.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170521","170521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15445","2013-10-10","Department for Education","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170504","170504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15446","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consultation he has undertaken with the public and GPs over the introduction of the care.data system.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170505","170505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15447","2013-10-14","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many fitness to practise cases being dealt with by the Nursing and Midwifery Council have been outstanding for (a) over 12 months and (b) over two years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170511","170511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15448","2013-10-10","Department for Education","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the median cost of providing education for a child with profound and multiple learning difficulties in England was in the most recent year for which figures are available; and what the range of such costs was.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170506","170506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15449","2013-10-14","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Nursing and Midwifery Council about improvements to its practice and procedures; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170512","170512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15450","2013-10-14","Department for International Development","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department will ensure that nutrition indicators in the post-2015 framework reflect both chronic and acute malnutrition and are measured in a way that ensures that vulnerable groups and populations are not missed.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170477","170477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15451","2013-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the administrative burden placed on UK farmers applying for the single farm payment compared to those in other EU member states; and if he will bring forward proposals to reduce that burden.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170507","170507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15452","2013-10-14","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many fitness to practise cases dealt with the Nursing and Midwifery Council have been referred under section 29 of the National Health Service Reform and Health Care Professions Act in (a) the last 12 months and (b) the last two years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170513","170513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15453","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will ensure that any reports into allegations of sexual assault at Yarl's Wood immigration removal centre that have previously been or will in the future be produced by Serco are made available to the public.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170514","170514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15454","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures are in place to (a) ensure women detained for immigration purposes are protected from sexual assault and harassment and (b) facilitate immigration detainees to report incidences of sexual assault and harassment on the immigration detention estate.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170516","170516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15455","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the suitability of detaining women for immigration purposes following the allegations of sexual assault at Yarl's Wood immigration removal centre.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170517","170517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15456","2013-10-14","Department for Education","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the current education curriculum at AFC Harrogate (namely functional skills at Level 1 in English and mathematics and a level 2 IT certificate) meets the requirements for compulsory education of 16 to 18 year olds.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170523","170523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15457","2013-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts announced to be closing since May 2010 have been disposed of; and how much has been generated in capital receipts from their disposal.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170518","170518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15458","2013-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department intends to make GCSE English and mathematics at grades A*-C a compulsory component of Phase 1 training for recruits at AFC Harrogate; what estimate his Department has made of the cost of doing so; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170524","170524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15459","2013-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much is spent each year on Probation Trust building; which companies provide such premises; and when the contract governing the occupancy of such building is next due for renewal.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170384","170384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15460","2013-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Army recruits who left before the end of their Phase 2 training enlisted at (a) age 16 and (b) age 17, in the five most recent full financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170527","170527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15461","2013-10-14","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many foreign doctors were employed by the NHS on 30 September 2012.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170528","170528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15462","2013-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress he has made in implementing section 139 of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170404","170404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15463","2013-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has written off in unpaid fines in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170405","170405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15464","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provisions are in place to prevent foreign nationals who have previously been served with an anti-social behaviour order within the UK from returning to the UK from another EU country.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170538","170538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15465","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many finished admission episodes involving patients with an obesity-related illness there were in each of the last three financial years; and what the (a) gender and (b) age group of each such patient was.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170533","170533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15466","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in each (a) socio-economic, (b) ethnic and (c) age-group underwent weight-loss operations in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170534","170534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15467","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people under the age of 18 had each type of surgical treatment for obesity in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170535","170535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15468","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals of each EU nationality who have previously been served with an anti-social behaviour order within the UK have been refused entry to the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170539","170539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15469","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of (a) Romanian, (b) Bulgarian, (c) Polish and (d) Lithuanian nationals who enter the UK by air and leave within 24 hours of arrival; what proportion of such people commit criminal offences while in the UK; and what security checks are in place at airports to prevent foreign nationals from entering the UK for this purpose.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170540","170540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15470","2013-10-14","HM Treasury","2013-10-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what annual total tonnage of aggregates exempt from the aggregates levy was registered or claimed in each year from 2002 to 2012.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170541","170541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15471","2013-10-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what statistics his Department is collecting on the number of people employed on zero-hour contracts as part of its review of the use of such contracts; at what geographical levels and for which sectors those statistics will be collected; and when those statistics will be published.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170537","170537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15472","2013-10-14","HM Treasury","2013-10-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the annual total tonnage of aggregates on which the aggregates levy was paid was in Northern Ireland in each year from 2002 to 2012.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170542","170542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15473","2013-10-10","Department for International Development","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department is providing to victims of violence in Peshawar, Pakistan.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170456","170456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15474","2013-10-14","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the effects of public disorder in summer 2013 on the economy in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170543","170543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15475","2013-10-10","Department for International Development","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of progress in eradicating polio in Peshawar, Pakistan; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170457","170457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15476","2013-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to commission a reassessment of the appropriateness of the Lariam form of Mefloquine to protect service personnel against malaria; and if he will make a statement on recent reports of the adverse side-effects of such medication.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170486","170486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15477","2013-10-10","Department for International Development","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the role that the UK-based Pakistani diaspora in the UK can have in promoting polio vaccination campaigns in Pakistan.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170458","170458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15478","2013-10-17","Prime Minister","2013-10-08","To ask the Prime Minister, what mechanisms are in place to ensure that an individual whom it is proposed to appoint to sensitive ministerial positions is screened for reliability in the handling of classified information; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170487","170487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15479","2013-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170460","170460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15480","2013-10-10","Department for Transport","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170461","170461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15481","2013-10-10","Scotland Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170462","170462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15482","2013-10-10","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by her Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170463","170463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15483","2013-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170464","170464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15484","2013-10-10","Department for International Development","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by her Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170465","170465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15485","2013-10-10","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by her Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170466","170466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15486","2013-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170467","170467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15487","2013-10-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by her Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170468","170468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15488","2013-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170469","170469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15489","2013-10-10","Cabinet Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170470","170470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15490","2013-10-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170471","170471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15491","2013-10-10","Attorney General","2013-10-08","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by the Law Officers' Departments received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170472","170472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15492","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170473","170473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15493","2013-10-10","Wales Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by his Department received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170474","170474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15494","2013-10-10","Women and Equalities","2013-10-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what proportion of (a) disabled and (b) all other staff employed by the Government Equalities Office received each level of performance rating in their end of year performance assessment for 2012-13.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170475","170475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15495","2013-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) nationality and (b) gender was of each suspected victim of trafficking referred to the Trafficking Victim Support Scheme operated by the Salvation Army in September 2013; in which (i) region, (ii) country and (iii) parliamentary constituency each of the suspected victims was found; and which agency referred each person to the scheme.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170485","170485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15496","2013-10-14","Department for Education","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of schools have had building works commence on site under his Department's Priority Schools Building Programme since that programme was announced.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170559","170559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15497","2013-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of UK job vacancies filled by non-UK EU applicants through the First Eures Job job mobility scheme in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170563","170563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15498","2013-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff in his Department, other than those employed at pathfinder jobcentres, are currently involved in processing universal credit applications.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170549","170549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15499","2013-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people who will be in receipt of universal credit by April 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170550","170550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15500","2013-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what date he expects the universal credit portal to be able to accept all new applications for working age benefits.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170551","170551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15501","2013-10-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policy of the draft decision of the Aarhus Convention Compliance Committee on the UK's National Renewable Energy Action Plan published in July 2013.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170544","170544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15502","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the costs to the NHS of people on long-term warfarin having to attend regular GP or hospital appointments for simple blood tests.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170545","170545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15503","2013-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to publish updates of the data contained in his Department's publication, Employment and Support Allowance - Incapacity Benefits Reassessments: Outcomes of Work Capability Assessments, Great Britain, published in March 2012, broken down by geographical area.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170552","170552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15504","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential annual cost savings to the NHS of people with diabetes being able to self-monitor their blood glucose levels.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170546","170546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15505","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that all clinical commissioning groups have policies in place allowing people on long-term warfarin to (a) self-test their INR levels and (b) self-managed their warfarin therapy if they choose to do so.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170547","170547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15506","2013-10-14","Department for Education","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to share back office services with other Government departments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170553","170553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15507","2013-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what career transition support is available to personnel leaving the armed forces; and if he will list the specific courses and training available to such personnel.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170548","170548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15508","2013-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has for training of F35 Joint Strike fighter pilots; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170554","170554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15509","2013-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) funding and (b) marketing support the Government provides to the sparkling wine growing industry in the south east.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170555","170555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15510","2013-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many trees were killed by (a) acute oak decline, (b) Asian longhorn beetle, (c) chalara dieback of ash, (d) chestnut blight and (e) dothistroma needle blight in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170556","170556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15511","2013-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many trees were killed by (a) great spruce bark beetle, dendroctonus micans, (b) horse chestnut leaf miner, cameraria ohridella, (c) oak pinhole borer, platypus cylindrus, (d) oak processionary moth, thaumetopoea processionea, and (e) phytophthora alni in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170557","170557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15512","2013-10-14","Department for Transport","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) fastest and (b) average journey time (i) is and (ii) will be after completion of High Speed 2 between London and (A) Sandwell and Dudley and (B) Wolverhampton; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170558","170558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15525","2013-10-10","Cabinet Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Committee on the Grant of Honours, Decorations and Medals will next meet.","Biography information for James Wharton","James Wharton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170213","170213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15526","2013-10-10","Cabinet Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent representations he has received on the frequency of meetings of the Committee on the Grant of Honours, Decorations and Medals.","Biography information for James Wharton","James Wharton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170214","170214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15527","2013-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many businesses in (a) Greater Manchester and (b) the North West were liable to pay business rates in the last financial year.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170224","170224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15528","2013-10-10","Department for Education","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to ensure that students in sixth form colleges receive the same benefits and entitlements as students pursuing A level courses in FE colleges and 11 to 18 schools.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170237","170237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15529","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been paid by the Government in severance packages to former Care Quality Commission executives since May 2010; when such payments were made; and who authorised each such payment.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170241","170241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15530","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what current level of English language proficiency is required for those arriving on (a) ICT Long term staff, (b) ICT Short term staff, (c) ICT Graduate Trainee and (d) ICT Skills Transfer visas; and what such levels will be following the upcoming implementation of changes to immigration rules announced on 6 September 2013.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170397","170397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15531","2013-10-14","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support sufferers of muscular dystrophy.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170398","170398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15532","2013-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of providing (a) accommodation and (b) IT infrastructure, (c) mandated disabled access requirements and (d) other appropriate facilities for HQ 4th Infantry Brigade and HQ North East (AF Bde HQ) at (i) Imphal Barracks in York and (ii) Catterick Garrison.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170403","170403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15533","2013-10-17","Cabinet Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment she has made of the circumstances surrounding the death of Dr David Kelly in 2003.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170259","170259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15534","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) the UK and (b) Bolton North East constituency claimed in-work credit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170390","170390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15535","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of telephone calls to the 0800 055 6688 Jobcentre Plus telephone line is.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170392","170392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15536","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate what real terms changes in financial allocations would be faced by Rotherham CCG if the recommendations of Fundamental Review of Allocations Policy in the NHS were adopted.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170261","170261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15537","2013-10-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what inspection and enforcement measures his Department has put in place to ensure that wind farm developers abide by development regulations.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170265","170265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15538","2013-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the final unmanned aerial vehicle MQ-9 Reapers will be delivered to the UK; how many Reapers will be sent to Afghanistan; and when such a transfer will take place.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170412","170412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15539","2013-10-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if she will establish a music licensing and collections agency for the devolved regions.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170417","170417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15540","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0870, (b) 0845 and (c) 0800 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170427","170427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15541","2013-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 13 July 2011, Official Report, column 323W, on bail, if he will publish figures for the most recent period for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170442","170442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15542","2013-10-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-10-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, which local authorities have submitted bids for funding to assist with the implementation of individual electoral registration; and how much funding each authority has received.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170449","170449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15543","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in the London Borough of Brent have been affected by the recent changes to the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170494","170494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15544","2013-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2013, Official Report, columns 725-6W, on courts: Wales, what progress he has made centrally collating information on the number of litigants in person in civil and family court cases since 1 April 2013.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170496","170496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15545","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the number of individuals likely to be affected by a move to provide pension equality for same sex couples; and what assessment she has made of the cost of such a move.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170500","170500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15546","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many individuals were arrested and charged by Merseyside police for anti-social behaviour offences from 2003 to the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170520","170520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15547","2013-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, by what mechanism he will ensure that Saharawi will be employed on the EU vessels fishing under the new protocol to the EU-Morocco Fisheries Partnership Agreement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170502","170502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15548","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2013, Official Report, column 921W, on food banks: voucher schemes, which organisations his Department consulted in designing the New Food Bank Signposting Slip issued by Jobcentre Plus staff to clients; and when each was consulted.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170508","170508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15549","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will investigate allegations of sexual assault at Yarl's Wood immigration removal centre.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170515","170515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15550","2013-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the average fee charged by English higher education institutions in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14 (i) including the effect of reduced fees and bursaries and (ii) excluding the effect of reduced fees and bursaries.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170522","170522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15551","2013-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what his latest estimate of the cost to consumers of the Energy Company Obligation is; and how that figure compares to his Department's original estimate.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170529","170529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15552","2013-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of army recruits who dropped out of training before the end of Phase 2 had GCSEs at grades D-G in (a) English and (b) mathematics in the five most recent full financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170525","170525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15553","2013-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of army recruits who dropped out of training before the end of Phase 2 had GCSEs at Grades A*-C in (a) English and (b) mathematics in the five most recent full financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170526","170526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15554","2013-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which benefits were claimed by people under the age of 25 in each of the last four financial years; and what proportion of such claimants were (a) registered as sick or disabled and (b) lone parents.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170532","170532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15555","2013-10-10","Department of Health","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the youngest age of a patient who underwent surgical treatment for obesity was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170536","170536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15556","2013-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many badgers have been killed to date under his Department's cull programme; how that figure compares to the Department's targets and forecasts; and who is responsible for determining the criteria against which the effectiveness of the culls will be judged.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170564","170564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15772","2013-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many parents in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK have been in arrears with their Child Support Agency payments for a period of (i) under six months, (ii) under a year and (iii) over a year in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170530","170530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15773","2013-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many parents in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK have been registered with the Child Support Agency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170531","170531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15774","2013-10-14","Home Office","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visa applications have been processed in (a) under three months, (b) under six months, (c) under a year, (d) under 18 months and (e) over 18 months in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170560","170560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15775","2013-10-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) homes and (b) businesses in (i) Ribble Valley constituency, (ii) Lancashire and (iii) the UK have access to high speed broadband.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170561","170561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15776","2013-10-14","Department for Transport","2013-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many rural bus services in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK have been (i) reduced and (ii) removed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170562","170562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/15783","2013-10-14","HM Treasury","2013-10-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to ring-fence mortgage guarantee scheme money for properties with local occupancy restrictions.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170483","170483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14699","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has discussed the acquisition, development and deployment of unmanned aerial vehicles with his counterpart in Turkey.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169706","169706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14700","2013-10-09","Department for International Development","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has any plans to use drones as part of its humanitarian and development work.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169707","169707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14701","2013-10-09","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether she has had any discussions about the acquisition and deployment of unmanned aerial vehicles by the Police Service of Northern Ireland in relation to the policing of (a) the recent G8 summit and (b) public order disturbances arising from parades.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169708","169708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14702","2013-10-09","Home Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what purpose and on how many occasions in each of the last five years the UK Border Agency has used drones.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169709","169709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14703","2013-10-09","Prime Minister","2013-10-07","To ask the Prime Minister, which Minister has lead responsibility for the regulation and operation of drones in civil airspace.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169710","169710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14704","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has any plans to use unmanned aerial vehicles over Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169711","169711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14705","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many legal professionals in his Department provide advice to personnel operating drones in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169712","169712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14706","2013-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what purpose, at what location and on how many occasions his Department has used drones in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169713","169713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14707","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2013, Official Report, column 14W, on Gulf States, whether Royal Air Force support to the US in the Gulf includes intelligence provision and analysis for the purposes of drone strikes.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169714","169714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14708","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will assess the potential effects of the Co-operative Bank's capital action plan on 13 per cent perpetual subordinated bondholders.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169725","169725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14709","2013-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which organisations have taken over ownership of each court building closed but not disposed of on the open market since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169735","169735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14710","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will assess the effects of decisions taken by the Prudential Regulation Authority on the value of the Co-operative Bank's 13 per cent perpetual subordinated bondholders.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169726","169726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14711","2013-10-09","Department for International Development","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to ensure that her Department's funding goes to humanitarian agencies that can commit to separating their funds between USAID and non-USAID donors.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169755","169755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14712","2013-10-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what powers he has to ensure that local planning authorities' estimates of the need for additional houses in their area are based on accurate estimates of that need; and what steps he is empowered to take if such estimates are found to be inaccurate.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169745","169745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14713","2013-10-09","Department for International Development","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to tackle gender inequality and promote women's participation in political and public life.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169727","169727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14714","2013-10-09","Cabinet Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average weekly gross earnings of full-time employed (a) men and (b) women in (i) Wrexham constituency, (ii) North Wales and (iii) England were in (A) cash terms and (B) constant prices in each year since 2006-07.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169736","169736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14715","2013-10-09","Department for Education","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage children to take part in school sports.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169715","169715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14716","2013-10-09","Scotland Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, when he last met representatives of the largest six energy providers in Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169746","169746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14717","2013-10-09","Department for International Development","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that UK Government funds are used to support agencies that provide non-discriminatory care for conflict rape victims regardless of local or national laws.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169756","169756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14718","2013-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of sentencing for crimes involving the abuse of animals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169728","169728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14719","2013-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to improve the conviction rates in cases of alleged rape and sexual violence.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169716","169716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14720","2013-10-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress her Department has made on plans for Tavistock to become the key eastern visitor centre for the Cornwall and West Devon Mining Landscape World Heritage Site.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169729","169729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14721","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what processes are in place to support and encourage those under 18's recruited to the armed forces to report (a) sexual harassment, (b) sexual assault and (c) rape by (i) an instructor, (ii) another recruit and (iii) a senior officer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169737","169737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14722","2013-10-09","Home Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to reinstate the ban on Gujarat's Chief Minister, Narendra Modi, entering the UK.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169730","169730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14723","2013-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much is spent each month on each court building which has been closed but not disposed of since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169738","169738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14724","2013-10-09","Home Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many members of the Association of Chief Police Officers are (a) subject to misconduct inquiries and (b) on long-term sick leave.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169757","169757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14725","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what procedures are followed when a patient disputes a medical diagnosis on their NHS record; what rights of appeal a patient has in such circumstances; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169747","169747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14726","2013-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of his Department's former library currently resides within other Government institutions; what measures are being planned to restore this material to his Department; what proportion of the Library material has been sold; what revenue was generated from such sales; what the assessed value of that material was; what proportion of the material has been destroyed; and what the replacement value of such destroyed or sold material is.","Biography information for Mr Brian Binley","Mr Brian Binley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169731","169731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14727","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the provision of mental health services in Haringey.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169765","169765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14728","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of English domiciled students at English higher education institutions were aged (a) under 22, (b) 22 to 25, (c) 26 to 30 and (d) over 30 in each year since 2001.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169717","169717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14729","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost of testing aborted foetuses to ascertain their gender and the nature of any disability from which they suffered; what consideration he (a) has given and (b) plans to give to monitoring to ensure effective implementation of the law on abortion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169739","169739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14730","2013-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) fined and (b) jailed for non-payment of council tax in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169748","169748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14731","2013-10-09","Home Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers there are in each of the 43 forces as of 1 September 2013; and how many such officers (a) have been arrested in their career, (b) are currently subject to misconduct inquiries and (c) are on long-term sick leave.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169758","169758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14732","2013-10-09","Home Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking in conjunction with the devolved administrations and police forces to tackle crime in habitats affecting wildlife in the UK.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169766","169766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14733","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many dementia patients under the age of 65 there are in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) East Lancashire.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169749","169749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14734","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent estimate he has made of the RAB change to be applied to student loans for students commencing studies in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169718","169718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14735","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many care homes suitable for dementia patients under the age of 65 there are in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) East Lancashire.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169750","169750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14736","2013-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking in response to the Fourth United Nations Conference on Women: Platform for Action which called for governments to take steps to eliminate all forms of discrimination against the girl child which result in harmful and unethical practices such as prenatal sex selection, compounded by the increasing use of technologies to determine foetal sex resulting in abortion of female foetuses; what recent representations he has received on prenatal sex selection and abortion; what response his Department made to such representations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169732","169732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14737","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure adequate provision of care services for dementia patients under the age of 65.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169751","169751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14738","2013-10-09","Home Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding her Department is providing to police forces and specialist units for tackling crime in habitats affecting wildlife in the UK in (a) 2013-14 and (b) each of the next two financial years.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169767","169767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14739","2013-10-09","Department for International Development","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make representations to her US counterpart on that country lifting its prohibition on the supply of humanitarian aid to women raped in war.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169759","169759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14740","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people under the age of 65 were diagnosed with dementia in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169752","169752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14741","2013-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department made of (a) the medical purpose and (b) the potential effect on people's willingness to be honest with their doctors about addiction problems of the application made by his Department to access drug treatment data of NHS patients in order to link it to information about employment and benefits claims; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169740","169740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14742","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) UK domiciled and (b) English domiciled students received (i) maintenance grants and (ii) loans and were (A) living at home and (B) living away from home in each year since 2001.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169719","169719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14743","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will set out full details of the methodology and indicators used by his Department to allocate EU structural funds to UK regions between 2005 and 2010.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169753","169753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14744","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with Lyme Disease in each region of the UK in each of the last three years; and what steps his Department has taken to prevent the spread of Lyme Disease in that time.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169760","169760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14745","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what protocol is in place for the diagnosis and treatment of Lyme Disease.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169761","169761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14746","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many full-time students at English higher education institutions were (a) living away from home and (b) living at home in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169720","169720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14747","2013-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which court buildings closed since May 2010 have been disposed of (a) on the open market and (b) through an alternative route.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169733","169733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14748","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the expected overall yield from the UK-Swiss Confederation Taxation Co-operation Agreement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169768","169768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14749","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research into Lyme Disease his Department plans to commission in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169762","169762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14750","2013-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which court buildings announced for closure since May 2010 have been (a) disposed of and (b) not disposed of.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169734","169734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14751","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, under what circumstances abortions can be performed on the grounds that the foetus is female; what the form and timescale is of the investigation into reports of abortions being performed on the grounds that the foetus is female; whether that investigation will cover all abortion clinics in the UK; whether the relevant police forces and prosecuting authorities have been informed of those reports; whether doctors suspected of having falsified abortion referral forms or having performed abortions on the grounds that the foetus is female will be referred to the General Medical Council and the relevant police authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169754","169754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14752","2013-10-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on council tax rates for empty properties and empowering local authorities to pursue compulsory purchase on long-term empty properties.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169742","169742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14753","2013-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much (a) income support, (b) housing benefit, (c) employment and support allowance and (d) jobseeker's allowance was paid late due to administrative error by his Department in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169763","169763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14754","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions the in-house option has been exercised for contract renewal options for the Defence Infrastructure Organisation in the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169722","169722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14755","2013-10-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what guidance his Department has issued on the distance that offshore wind farms should be placed from the coast.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169775","169775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14756","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the UK-Swiss Confederation Taxation Co-operation Agreement, how many UK citizens have been identified as moving funds outside that Agreement's jurisdiction prior to it coming into effect on 1 January 2013; whether that number is in line with HM Treasury's previous forecasts; and to which locations such funds have been moved.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169769","169769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14757","2013-10-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the planning process takes account of potential effects on health of noise from wind farms; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169776","169776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14758","2013-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many health and safety inspections of cooling towers have been completed since May 2010.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169764","169764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14759","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many UK citizens have been exempted from the UK-Swiss Confederation Taxation Co-operation Agreement owing to their non-domiciled status.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169770","169770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14760","2013-10-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what powers he has to ensure that local planning authorities' estimates of the need for additional pitches for Gypsies and Travellers in their area are based upon accurate estimates of this need; and what steps he is empowered to take if such estimates are found to be inaccurate.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169743","169743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14761","2013-10-09","Department for Education","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to transfer the cost of historic private finance initiative deals to those schools that have opted out of their local authority arrangements to become academies or free schools.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169777","169777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14762","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the UK-Swiss Confederation Taxation Co-operation Agreement, how many UK citizens have elected to make voluntary disclosures to HM Revenue and Customs to date.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169771","169771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14763","2013-10-09","Department for International Development","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of the UK's annual aid to Kenya has been used to help people who were internally displaced by violence connected to elections in 2007 and 2008 in each year since 2007; how many of those displaced persons are still living in camps; and what steps her Department is taking to assist such persons.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169724","169724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14764","2013-10-09","Department for Education","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department spent on the Government Carbon Offsetting Framework in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169855","169855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14765","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department plans to review its policy of not having a dedicated budget to market or directly promote 24+ advanced learning loans to potential applicants.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169778","169778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14766","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many UK citizens have been identified as the beneficial owners of (a) domiciliary companies or assets and (b) other similar complex structures following the introduction of the UK-Swiss Confederation Taxation Co-operation Agreement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169772","169772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14767","2013-10-09","Wales Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department spent on the Government Carbon Offsetting Framework in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169856","169856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14768","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department spent on the Government Carbon Offsetting Framework in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169857","169857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14769","2013-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to support recent peace talks between Israeli and Palestinian leaders.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169779","169779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14770","2013-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on the Government Carbon Offsetting Framework in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169858","169858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14771","2013-10-09","Scotland Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on the Government Carbon Offsetting Framework in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169859","169859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14772","2013-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on peace talks between Israel and the Palestinians; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169780","169780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14773","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on the Government Carbon Offsetting Framework in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169860","169860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14774","2013-10-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what provisions of the Offshore Energy Strategic Environmental Assessment 2 apply to offshore wind energy sites developed in the Round 3 tranche.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169773","169773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14775","2013-10-09","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department spent on the Government Carbon Offsetting Framework in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169861","169861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14776","2013-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on the Government Carbon Offsetting Framework in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169862","169862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14777","2013-10-09","Department for International Development","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on the Government Carbon Offsetting Framework in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169863","169863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14778","2013-10-09","Cabinet Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much money his Department spent on the Government Carbon Offsetting Framework in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169865","169865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14779","2013-10-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department spent on the Government Carbon Offsetting Framework in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169864","169864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14780","2013-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answers of 25 April 2013, Official Report, columns 1298-1302W, if he will provide the latest data available on the number of offenders cautioned for and found guilty of (a) possession of drugs offences and (b) cannabis posession offences in England and Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169781","169781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14781","2013-10-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether contracts let in the Round 3 tranche of offshore wind energy contracts will be subject to the provisions of the EU (a) procurement and (b) utilities directives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169774","169774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14782","2013-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what controls there are on arms sold by UK firms to the UAE to prevent them being passed on to Egypt.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169866","169866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14783","2013-10-09","Attorney General","2013-10-07","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the Answer of 14 March 2013, Official Report, columns 17-8W, on drugs: prosecutions, if he will provide the latest available data on the number of offences charged for supply and possession in the last complete financial year.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169782","169782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14784","2013-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the case of the five schoolboys from the village of Hares in Palestine who were arrested by the Israeli authorities in March 2013.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169867","169867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14785","2013-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any UK arms have been sent to Egypt (a) directly and (b) via another source since 30 July 2013.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169868","169868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14786","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what notice the Land Registry aimed to give of overriding interests being registered under Section 117 of the Land Registration Act 2002 in order to allow appeals against such registrations in advance of the 13 October 2013 deadline.","Biography information for Patrick Mercer","Patrick Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169783","169783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14787","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what conditions the Government attaches to countries receiving debt relief.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169966","169966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14788","2013-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in which month his Department plans to publish the response to its consultation on reducing the number and costs of whiplash claims.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169784","169784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14789","2013-10-09","Department for Education","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to ensure that Prospects is a suitable provider of early years education inspections and can deliver value for money.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169967","169967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14790","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on the smoke-free homes and cars campaign in spring 2013.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169869","169869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14791","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what countries are currently receiving debt-relief from the UK as part of the (a) Heavily Indebted Poor Countries Initiative and (b) Multilateral Debt Relief Initiative.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169968","169968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14792","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what return on investment his Department receives from the £54.2 million it has spent on energy saving measures to date.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169969","169969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14793","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department plans to measure the effectiveness of the recent smoke-free homes and cars campaign.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169870","169870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14794","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department saves each year through meeting its Greening Government targets by March 2015.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169970","169970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14795","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent support the (a) Export Credits Guarantee Department and (b) UK Trade & Investment have given to UK companies that wish to do business in Ethiopia.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169795","169795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14796","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what returns on investment his Department has achieved through energy saving policies to date.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169971","169971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14797","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to increase competition across rail markets and lower barriers to open access rail competition on (a) the West Coast Main Line and (b) other rail lines.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169871","169871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14798","2013-10-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the effect of the European Union Emissions Trading Scheme on household energy prices.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169796","169796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14799","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what criteria exist for the awarding of bonuses to Met Office staff.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169972","169972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14800","2013-10-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many homes in Wrexham constituency have received insulation under his Department's energy efficiency programmes in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169797","169797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14801","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the contribution of open-access operators on the East Coast Main Line in support of the franchised operator.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169872","169872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14802","2013-10-09","Department for Education","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the financial saving of social workers working with families to retain their children rather than taking them in to care; and how many troubled families are supported in England and Wales in this manner.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169973","169973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14803","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) monetary value of loans given to entrepreneurs based in Wrexham under the start-up loans scheme.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169798","169798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14804","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on increasing the ability of open access operators to make a greater contribution to the UK's railways.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169873","169873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14805","2013-10-09","Cabinet Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he hs made of recent trends in female employment in (a) Wrexham constituency and (b) Wales.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169799","169799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14806","2013-10-09","Home Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the (a) number of false accusations of child sex offences made each year and (b) amount of police time consequently not spent pursuing genuine cases.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169974","169974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14807","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to boost capacity utilisation on the (a) East Coast Main Line and (b) West Coast Main Line to allow more services to exist which may compete with the franchised operator.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169874","169874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14808","2013-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the average weekly number of job applications submitted by each jobseeker in (a) Wrexham constituency and (b) Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169800","169800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14809","2013-10-09","Cabinet Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in (a) Wrexham constituency and (b) Wales were paid only the minimum wage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169801","169801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14810","2013-10-09","Department for Education","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of hours of annual safeguarding training received each year on average by (a) primary, (b) secondary and (c) post-16 teaching staff in England.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169975","169975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14811","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department has commissioned since 2010 on the effect of reducing speed limits from 30 mph to 20 mph.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169802","169802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14812","2013-10-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the carbon footprint produced by shale gas.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169959","169959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14813","2013-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that the protections offered by the Mental Capacity Act 2008 are available to those in HM prisons.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169803","169803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14814","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons military dogs were put down at the end of their service in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169815","169815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14815","2013-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the proportion of jobseeker's allowance claimants who (a) are in receipt of contributory jobseeker's allowance and (b) have exhausted eligibility for contributory jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169804","169804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14816","2013-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's policy is on the proposed exploration for oil by SOCO International PLC in the Virunga National Park and World Heritage Site, Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169960","169960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14817","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what provisions are made for military working dogs that are (a) healthy, (b) have an illness and (c) injured at the end of their service.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169816","169816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14818","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment HM Revenue and Customs made of its chances of success in litigation under the law as it stood prior to bringing forward the legislative proposals announced in Budget Note 66 on 12 March 2008.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169785","169785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14819","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans Companies House has to move towards digital data collection and publishing.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169825","169825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14820","2013-10-09","Home Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost of (a) purchasing and (b) deploying the Home Office-approved handheld device for use at a police station to enforce the law relating to drug driving is.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169961","169961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14821","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if Companies House plans to publish a strategy document on its future role, structure and activities.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169826","169826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14822","2013-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the use of captive bolt gun and the legislation allowing its use against dogs.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169835","169835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14823","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on the incidence of aerotoxic syndrome.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169962","169962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14824","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether Companies House intends to become a fully open public register.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169827","169827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14825","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what options are considered before deciding to put down military working dogs  at the end of their service and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169817","169817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14826","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2013, Official Report, column 960W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, whether his Department has carried out training in unmanned aerial vehicles in conjunction with a European military within his Department's reserved airspace areas in the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169786","169786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14827","2013-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many transporters have been involved with the export of livestock from the UK for further fattening or slaughter in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169828","169828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14828","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many UK-based (a) pilots, (b) cabin crew have reported to his Department symptoms of neurological damage alleged to have arisen from aerotoxic syndrome.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169963","169963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14829","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, who within his Department takes the final decision to put down military working dogs at the end of their service and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169818","169818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14830","2013-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will list (a) the research projects fully funded or partly funded by his Department, (b) the project dates, (c) the report titles and (d) any grants issued for studies into the control of cereal aphids without the use of insecticide sprays or seed treatments since 1997.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169836","169836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14831","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will investigate the number of military working dogs put down at the end of their service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169819","169819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14832","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many petrol suppliers in Northern Ireland have supplied evidence in relation to the extension of the fuel rebate scheme to remote inland areas; and from which areas such evidence was received.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169964","169964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14833","2013-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the proportion of employment and support allowance claimants who (a) are in receipt of contributory employment and support allowance and (b) have exhausted eligibility for contributory employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169805","169805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14834","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the scientific paper by Sándor Spisák et al entitled Complete Genes Pass from food to human blood published on 30 July 2013.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169787","169787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14835","2013-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Ports, Harbours and Piers Clauses Act 1847 to allow discretion by individual port authorities to ban or control the live export of animals through a port.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169829","169829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14836","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what legal framework is currently in place to control the number of military working dogs that are put down; what plans he has to amend this framework; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169820","169820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14837","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the evidence received from petrol suppliers in Northern Ireland regarding the extension of the fuel rebate scheme to remote inland areas.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169965","169965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14838","2013-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential for the non-GM blight resistance potatoes bred by the Sárvári Research Trust to reduce the input of agrochemicals and irrigation water in the production of potatoes in the UK.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169837","169837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14839","2013-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the proportion of jobseeker's allowance claimants who have been out of work for more than 12 months.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169806","169806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14840","2013-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to support families who struggle to pay funeral costs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Evans","Jonathan Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169830","169830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14841","2013-10-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to lower the interest rate on Green Deal finance packages.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169788","169788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14842","2013-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate his Department has made of the rate of non-take up of means-tested benefits.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169807","169807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14843","2013-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research his Department has commissioned into the cost effectiveness of GM crops compared to conventionally bred varieties; and if he will provide the (a) conclusions and (b) cost of each such project.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169838","169838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14844","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the (a) advertisement, (b) schedule of the placement of the advertisement, (c) detail of the interview process, (d) members of the interview panel and (e) all the applicants for the newly appointed Chairman of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169821","169821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14845","2013-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research his Department has funded on the effectiveness of different approaches to tackling vitamin A deficiency in the Global South including GM, conventional plant breeding, vitamin supplements and diet diversification.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169831","169831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14846","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has developed plans that will allow the transfer or conversion of funds in child trust funds into junior ISAs.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169839","169839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14847","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Deparment will consult the National Audit Office in advance on the value for money implications on the public finances of Government guarantees for the debt financing of the expansion of Heathrow airport.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169789","169789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14848","2013-10-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many wind farm developers did not have the relevant licences to erect wind turbines over 10mw in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169808","169808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14849","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he will publish the results of the consultation on transferring child trust fund accounts into junior ISAs.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169840","169840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14850","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to introduce the new formula proposed by the Fundamental Review of Allocations Policy.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169809","169809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14851","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place (a) a copy of the contract for Sir David Higgins, the newly-appointed Chairman of HS2 Ltd, and (b) details of his remuneration and pension package in the Library.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169822","169822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14852","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the level of support currently available for people with hearing loss; and what steps he will take to support additional measures for those with hearing loss.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169832","169832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14853","2013-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent progress he has made on improving community sentences.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169790","169790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14854","2013-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many probation staff in England and Wales have been trained in sections 2A and 4A of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169841","169841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14855","2013-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether a course of conduct is taken into account by a court when sentencing for a stalking-related offence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169842","169842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14856","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish financial details of the severance agreement with the outgoing Chairman of HS2 Ltd.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169823","169823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14857","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the previous weighting for deprivation within the capitation formula has been removed or substantially downgraded in the new formula.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169810","169810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14858","2013-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what stage of development GM golden rice has reached in terms of (a) its risk assessment on health and the environment and (b) its efficacy in tackling vitamin A deficiency.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169833","169833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14859","2013-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of press freedom in Bahrain.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169843","169843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14860","2013-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the detention of Ahmed Humaidan in Bahrain.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169844","169844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14861","2013-10-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if Companies House will publish a fully open register which is accessible to the general public without charge.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169824","169824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14862","2013-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research his Department has conducted on the effect of the development of glyphosate-resistant weeds in (a) the UK, (b) the EU and (c) other countries and the effect of such developments on the costs of production.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169834","169834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14863","2013-10-09","Cabinet Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many UK citizens visited Mauritius in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169811","169811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14864","2013-10-09","Cabinet Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in (a) Wrexham constituency and (b) Wales live in private rented accommodation.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169791","169791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14865","2013-10-09","Cabinet Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Mauritians are currently resident in the UK.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169812","169812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14866","2013-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the detention of Mohamed Sudayf and  Hussain Hubail in Bahrain.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169845","169845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14867","2013-10-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of when offshore wind will reach grid parity.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169792","169792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14868","2013-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Mauritian government on joint efforts to reduce piracy in the Indian Ocean.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169813","169813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14869","2013-10-09","Department of Health","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the net value is of the property portfolio (a) managed and (b) owned by NHS Property Services Ltd.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169895","169895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14870","2013-10-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of when solar PV will reach grid parity.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169793","169793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14871","2013-10-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of when onshore wind will reach grid parity.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169794","169794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14872","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the role of open access competition on the annual premium paid by the East Coast Main Line franchise.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169875","169875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14873","2013-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of military working dogs were (a) put down and (b) re-homed at the end of their service in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169814","169814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14874","2013-10-09","Department for International Development","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on consolidating the Great Himalaya Trail Development Programme into the Nepal Market Development programme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169896","169896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14875","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to promote open access across the rail market.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169876","169876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14876","2013-10-09","Department for International Development","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what level of aid has been given to Ethiopia in the last five years.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169886","169886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14877","2013-10-09","HM Treasury","2013-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the Gift Aid system will be affected by the introduction of a variable rate of income tax in Scotland as mandated in the Scotland Act 2012.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169846","169846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14878","2013-10-09","Department for International Development","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which projects her Department is funding in Nepal; and which non-governmental organisations are involved in each such project.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169897","169897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14879","2013-10-16","Department for Education","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason gender identity was included in the February draft of the National Curriculum Framework document as a characteristic obligating teachers in their duties under equal opportunities legislation, but was not included in the July draft of that document.","Biography information for Baroness Burt of Solihull","Lorely Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 170204","170204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14880","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to better underpin (a) new entrants to the UK's railways and (b) open access operators.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169877","169877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14881","2013-10-09","Home Office","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on the Government Carbon Offsetting Framework in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169898","169898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14882","2013-10-09","Department for Education","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department spent on promoting safe swimming in schools in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169847","169847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14883","2013-10-09","Department for Transport","2013-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy that his Department collates information on the number of available training roles for UK ratings in the previous year for inclusion in the annual Seafarer Statistics publication.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 169887","169887"
