"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140633","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department has provided support to Africa Trade Ltd.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279400","279400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140634","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department has provided support to Africa House London Ltd.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279401","279401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140635","2019-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment she has made of the potential merits of supporting a ban on lethal autonomous weapons systems.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279386","279386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140636","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether freedom of movement for EU nationals to and from the UK will end if the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279357","279357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140637","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with toilet tissue manufacturers on (a) increasing the amount of recycled pulp used in that tissue and (b) investing in more sustainable alternatives to paper-based products.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279387","279387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140638","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing a complete ban on single-use plastic bags.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279388","279388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140639","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he has taken to engage with businesses in order to assess their levels of satisfaction with the Tradeshow Access Programme.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279479","279479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139848","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government plans to provide financial support to Montserrat for the building of a new Parliament building.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278432","278432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140088","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","What steps he is taking to help ensure the provision of new rolling stock on the east coast main line.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912039","912039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140089","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","What progress he has made on introducing a hybrid Bill to secure the powers to deliver phase 2b of High Speed Two; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912041","912041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140090","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","If he will allocate additional funding to improve roads outside the major road network and the strategic road network.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912043","912043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140091","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","What progress has been made on the proposed dualling of the A27 east of Lewes to Eastbourne.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912044","912044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140092","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","What progress he has made on helping to ensure that flights between the UK and Europe continue after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912045","912045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140093","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","What progress he has made on helping to ensure that flights between the UK and Europe continue after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Sir Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912046","912046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140094","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","What progress he has made on opening new stations on the rail network.","Biography information for Vicky Ford","Vicky Ford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912048","912048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140099","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve local authority support for vulnerable children.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912085","912085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140158","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans for devolution in Greater Lincolnshire.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912083","912083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140159","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the take-up of the healthy start scheme.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279060","279060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140160","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the cumulative years experience of teachers working in prisons in (a) 2010 (b) 2015 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279091","279091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140161","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the findings of the Institute for Strategic Dialogue’s report, The Great Replacement: the violent consequences of mainstreamed extremism, published in July 2019 on the great replacement conspiracy theory.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278941","278941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140162","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have paid Employment Tribunal Fees during the operation of that policy.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279092","279092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140163","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Recorders have sat to hear cases in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279093","279093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140164","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish the letters sent by the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State and Minister for Small Business, Consumers and Corporate Responsibility to online platforms on the matter of second hand recalled tumble dryers being sold on their platforms.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279088","279088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140165","2019-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2019 to Question 276284 on Government Departments: Digital Technology, if he will publish that information before the summer recess.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279145","279145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140166","2019-07-23","Cabinet Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2019 to Question 276281 on Huawei: 5G, if he will meet with operators to raise cybersecurity CNI standards.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279146","279146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140167","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 274430 and with reference to the Building Research Establishment document quoted, for what reason that methodology of selecting information referred to in para 2.2 and page 5 has been used and what the timetable is for publishing the full review that his Department is commissioning on that methodology.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278900","278900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140168","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether (a) a different or (b) an amended method of assessing the performance of Canetis GasSaver compared with other flue gas heat recovery technology has been used.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278901","278901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140169","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2019 to Question 276197 on Buildings: Insulation, in the event that high-pressure laminate cladding fails a BS 8414 test for the same reasons aluminium composite material (ACM) cladding did, whether he would still consider ACM cladding to be wholly exceptional.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279061","279061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140170","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will respond to the recommendations in the report entitled Call for Action: Inquiry into heart attack and stroke, published by the all-party Parliamentary group on women’s health in July 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279083","279083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140171","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve (a) outcomes, (b) early identification and (c) treatment of heart attack and stroke for women.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279084","279084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140172","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Written Statement of 26 March 2019, HCWS1449, whether the interim findings of the Adrian Smith Review on the design of UK funding schemes for international collaboration, innovation and curiosity-driven blue-skies research will be published before Parliament rises on 25 July 2019.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278976","278976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140173","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the European Commission on whether funding for research partners in UK-led research consortia would be provided by (a) the UK or (b) the EU if the UK chooses to associate to the next EU Framework Programme as a third country.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278977","278977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140174","2019-07-23","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for administrative reviews have been made to the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278978","278978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140175","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits in extending consumer protection law to cover further education courses.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279134","279134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140176","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the sale of beer brewed by small independent breweries in pubs on tourism in the UK.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279135","279135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140177","2019-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will place in the Library the correspondence between the BBC and his Department from the date of the 2017 General Election on the Conservative Party's Election Manifesto pledge to maintain pensioner benefits and the policy of transferring responsibility for free TV licences for over 75s to the BBC.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278927","278927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140178","2019-07-22","Cabinet Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals on the recommendations of the boundary review.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278961","278961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140179","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of sexual offences committed on university campuses in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278962","278962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140180","2019-07-22","Cabinet Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to celebrate UK independence day on 31 October 2019.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278882","278882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140181","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to reduce the use of antibiotics in chicken farming.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278963","278963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140182","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to issue commemorative (a) stamps and (b) coins to mark the UK leaving the EU on 31 October 2019.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278883","278883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140183","2019-07-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent assessment the Government has made of the UK's level of preparedness in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal on 31 October 2019.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278884","278884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140184","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has written to all suppliers of heat networks asking them to sign up to the Heat Trust.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279152","279152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140185","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of sewage releases by water companies in the last three months.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278964","278964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140186","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many sewage releases there were by water company in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278965","278965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140187","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make the sub-letting of residential property a criminal offence.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278966","278966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140188","2019-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 May 2019 to Question 237584, if she will place in the Library a copy of letter from the Minister for Disabled People clarifying previous answers on the ministerial requirement to amend the wording of the ESA65B letter to claimants’ doctors.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278886","278886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140189","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to allocate additional funding to the NHS in increase spending on (a) infrastructure, (b) the NHS workforce and (c) public health.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278967","278967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140190","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much was spent by the NHS on settling compensation claims in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278968","278968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140191","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many requests for vehicle owner information have been made by overseas enforcement agencies in each of the last five years by country.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278969","278969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140192","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many alternative fuelled cars have been registered in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278970","278970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140193","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to require UK registered ferry operators to pay the Minimum Wage to all employees.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278971","278971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140194","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received from unions on UK registered ferry operators paying staff less than the Minimum Wage.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278972","278972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140195","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints HMRC has received of employers (a) advertising unpaid internships and (b) not paying the minimum wage in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279153","279153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140196","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Turkish counterpart on reports of exploration and drilling vessels entering the Cyprus exclusive economic zone.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278973","278973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140197","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his EU counterparts on Turkish exploration and drilling vessels entering the Cyprus exclusive economic zone.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278974","278974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140198","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how the Government-backed British business bank will help support small businesses in North Cornwall constituency.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279103","279103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140199","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase the number of electric car charging points in North Cornwall.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279104","279104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140200","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much of the £2 billion investment in the Post Office network has been spent in North Cornwall.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279105","279105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140201","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how North Cornwall can bid for the National Centre for Computing funding of £84 million.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279106","279106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140202","2019-07-23","Department for International Development","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the findings of the UNESCO report entitled Meeting commitments: are countries on track to achieve sustainable development goal four that more than 220 million children, adolescents and youth will not be in school in 2030.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278887","278887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140203","2019-07-23","Department for International Development","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the findings of the UNSECO report entitled Beyond commitments how do countries implement SDG 4, published on 8 July 2019.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278888","278888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140204","2019-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the May 2019 High Court judgment, when she plans to deliver transitional and ongoing payments for people who have lost the Severe Disability Premium since moving onto universal credit.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278934","278934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140205","2019-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with representations of Amazon on (a) the number of NHS ambulance responses to that company's warehouses in the last three years and (b) working conditions at those warehouses.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278935","278935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140206","2019-07-23","Department for International Development","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the findings of UNSECO in its report, Global education monitoring report 2019 – gender report: Building bridges for gender equality.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278889","278889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140207","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons his Department will not allow additional Transport for Wales train services to serve Bristol Temple Meads station.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278936","278936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140208","2019-07-23","Department for International Development","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to integrate nutrition into all areas of its work on UK Aid; and what discussions has he had with (a) his international counterparts and (b) international aid agencies on the merits of integrating nutrition into all areas of international aid work.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278937","278937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140209","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions there have been between Vertex Pharmaceuticals and NHS England with on cystic fibrosis medicines.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278928","278928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140210","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will set a deadline for NHS England and Vertex Pharmaceuticals to come to an agreement to enable access to cystic fibrosis medicines produced by that company.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278929","278929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140211","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to work with faith leaders to help tackle the Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278890","278890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140212","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the proportion of looked-after children that have (a) run away and (b) gone missing from homes and hostels not subject to the children’s homes regulations since 2014.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279124","279124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140213","2019-07-23","House of Commons Commission","2019-07-18","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many complaints have been made against Members since the introduction of the Independent Complaints and Grievance Scheme.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279075","279075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140214","2019-07-23","House of Commons Commission","2019-07-18","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many complaints against Members have been resolved since the introduction of the Independent Complaints and Grievance Scheme.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279076","279076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140215","2019-07-22","House of Commons Commission","2019-07-18","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what sanctions have been imposed on hon. Members since the introduction of the Independent Complaints and Grievance Scheme.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279077","279077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140216","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment he has made of the humanitarian situation in (a) southern Idlib and (b) northern Hama; and what steps his Department is taking to help alleviate the humanitarian situation in those regions.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278891","278891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140217","2019-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking further to the Disability Confident Scheme and the Disability Confident Toolkit to ensure people with autism spectrum conditions are supported within the workplace through (a) peer and (b) mentor support.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279085","279085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140218","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the safety implications of failing to renew the UK’s current exemption from Standard European Rules of Air on vertical separation from cloud in Class D airspace for aircraft operating under Visual Flight Rules.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278940","278940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140219","2019-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking, in addition to the Disability Confident Scheme and the Disability Confident Toolkit, to ensure people with autism spectrum conditions are supported in the workplace in relation to the working environment and their sensory needs.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279086","279086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140220","2019-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will offer people with autistic spectrum conditions of working age access to interview training  designed and delivered by individuals with extensive knowledge of autism spectrum conditions through Jobcentres.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279087","279087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140221","2019-07-22","House of Commons Commission","2019-07-18","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what range of sanctions against hon. Members are available for complaints upheld under the Independent Complaints and Grievance Scheme.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279078","279078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140222","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of people refused emergency housing each night in (a) Greater London, (b) the London Borough of Lambeth and (c) England in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279007","279007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140223","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of people living in accommodation that is unsuitable for their health needs or disabilities in (a) Greater London (b) the London Borough of Lambeth and (c) England.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279008","279008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140224","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to respond to the recommendations in the all-party Parliamentary group on adoption and permanence’s report entitled Investing in Families, published 16 July 2019.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279068","279068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140225","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of people that are living in council accommodation with combustible cladding in (a) Greater London, (b) the London Borough of Lambeth and (c) England.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279009","279009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140226","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his Department’s most recent estimate is for the proportion of housing transfer requests that are motivated out of (a) crime and (b) fear of violence in (i) the UK, (ii) Greater London and (iii) the London Borough of Lambeth.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279010","279010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140227","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what research his Department has conducted on the potential effect on public health of upgrading infrastructure to support 5G.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279011","279011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140228","2019-07-23","Treasury","2019-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) businesses and (b) companies (i) have an Economic Operator Registration and Identification (EORI) number, (ii) require an EORI number but do not have one and (iii) have applied for an EORI number and not received one.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279012","279012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140229","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of children who are at risk of experiencing hunger during the school summer holidays in 2019.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278892","278892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140230","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department is providing to families with children who are at risk of experiencing hunger during the school summer holidays in 2019.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278893","278893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140231","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to increase support for catalytic chemical recycling and upcycling to realise the ambition of zero plastic waste.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278919","278919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140232","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 229177 on visas: married people, if he will collate and publish figures for (a) the number of applications submitted under Appendix FM where the sponsor did not meet the financial requirement but argued that there were exceptional circumstances pertaining to their case and (b) the number of applications that were successful.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278926","278926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140233","2019-07-23","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many licences for the cultivation of industrial hemp are in effect in the UK.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279071","279071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140234","2019-07-23","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many licences for the cultivation of industrial hemp are in effect in Scotland.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279072","279072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140235","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of providing upfront financial support for childcare to parents claiming universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278894","278894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140236","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the average waiting time for the completion of disabled facilities grants in (a) each district council and (b) every unitary authority area in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279143","279143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140237","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 July 2019 to Question 273310 on HIV Infection: Drugs, whether work has started on future commissioning of PrEP; and which individuals will be involved in that work.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278896","278896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140238","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 July 2019 to Question 273310 on HIV Infection: Drugs, if he will take steps to ensure that all commissioning routes are considered before April 2020 so that the patients currently on the impact trial do not face a hard end to the treatment in September 2020.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278897","278897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140239","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 July 2019 to Question 273310 on HIV Infection: Drugs, if he will take steps to ensure that commissioning routes are established before September 2020.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278898","278898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140240","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 July 2019 to Question 273310 on HIV Infection: Drugs, if he will make it his policy to implement a long term plan for PrEP before the impact trial ends in September 2020.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278899","278899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140241","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to increase the accessibility of childcare in Merseyside.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278895","278895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140242","2019-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the two-child limit for universal credit and tax credits on disabled parents with more than two children.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278905","278905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140243","2019-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to work with (a) charities and (b) advice centres to improve the advice and support provided to disabled people completing applications and undergoing assessments for benefits.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278906","278906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140244","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress the Government has made in planning for farm payments in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279013","279013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140245","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of giving people a monthly allowance to spend on fresh, healthy and locally sourced food in a bid to (a) tackle obesity and (b) support the farming industry.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278920","278920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140246","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for receiving rural development funding in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279014","279014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140247","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, whether his Department has implemented the parts of the plan entitled, Handling civil legal cases that involve EU countries if there’s no Brexit deal.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279015","279015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140248","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for exporting GM food and animal products in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279016","279016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140249","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for for exporting objects of cultural interest in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279017","279017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140250","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for labelling tobacco products and e-cigarettes in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279018","279018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140251","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for travelling with a European Firearms Pass in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279019","279019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140252","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for control on mercury in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279020","279020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140253","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for control on persistent organic pollutants in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279021","279021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140254","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for broadcasting and video on demand in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279022","279022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140255","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for copyright in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279023","279023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140256","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department has taken to assess how the Pensions Dashboard could connect into private pension schemes using a federated Digital Identity.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278951","278951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140257","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for exhaustion of intellectual property rights in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279024","279024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140258","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for merger review and anti-competitive activity in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279025","279025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140259","2019-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when the Financial Services and Markets Act 2000 on legislation.gov.uk will be updated to ensure the version available accurately represents the legislation in its current form.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279144","279144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140260","2019-07-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessments the Government has made of the potential effects on (a) the economy, (b) policing and (c) public safety of the UK not leaving the EU; and if they will publish those assessments.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278949","278949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140261","2019-07-23","Cabinet Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what civil contingency plans are in place in the event that the UK does not leave the EU; and if he will publish those plans.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278950","278950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140262","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2019 to Question 267773 on Buildings: Insulation, whether his Department's engagement with (a) local authorities, (b) housing associations and (c) industry includes requests for information on the number of buildings covered in HPL cladding.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279136","279136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140263","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July to Question 273766 on Magistrates' Courts: Greater London, what the utilisation rates were for the adult courts only.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278938","278938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140264","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July to Question 273769 on Family Courts, who the person is on the panel that represents male victims.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278939","278939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140265","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2019 to Question 262396 on Buildings: Insulation, whether his Department took steps to estimate the number of buildings with HPL cladding after the failed BS8414 fire test on that cladding.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279137","279137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140266","2019-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when her Department will announce the preferred bidder for the Future Service Delivery Contract.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279107","279107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140267","2019-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Future Service Delivery Contract will include the (a) War Pension Scheme, (b) Armed Forces Compensation Scheme and (c) Medals Office.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279108","279108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140268","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of staff at the Defence Business Services office at Tomlinson House, Norcross are (a) part-time, (b) female, (c) over 50 years old and (d) disabled.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279109","279109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140269","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people living with dementia are aged over 75.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279141","279141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140270","2019-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect on the delivery of veteran services of the closure of Tomlinson House, Norcross.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279110","279110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140271","2019-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who are eligible for but do not claim pension credit live with dementia.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279142","279142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140272","2019-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment she has made of the compatibility of outsourcing veteran services with the Armed Forces Covenant.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279111","279111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140273","2019-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many subject access requests have been made to her Department in each of the last four quarters.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279112","279112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140274","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many subject access requests made to her Department in each of the last four quarters were complied with within the 28-day time limit.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279113","279113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140275","2019-07-23","Scotland Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will make a comparative assessment of total public spending per capita in Scotland with that in (a) Northamptonshire and (b) England, in the latest period for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278931","278931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140276","2019-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of preventing social media users from seeing how many likes posts have to support the mental health of people who use those media.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278921","278921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140277","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2019 to Question 262396 on Buildings: Insulation, what type of combustible insulation was combined with HPL cladding for the BS8414 test.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279138","279138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140278","2019-07-22","Church Commissioners","2019-07-18","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England plans to take to implement the decision taken at the General Synod in July 2019 in relation to the motion on Tackling Serious Youth Violence.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279089","279089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140279","2019-07-22","Church Commissioners","2019-07-18","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England’s Education Department is taking to implement the decision taken at the General Synod in July 2019 in relation to the motion on tackling serious youth violence in schools; and what guidance it is planning to issue to youth workers.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279090","279090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140280","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to Ministerial Statement, Building safety update, HCWS1757, whether the British Standard 8414 test on Class B, fire retardant, high pressure laminate rainscreen with a non-combustible rock fibre insulation carried out by the Fire Protection Association on behalf of his Department was only carried out once in June and July 2019.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279062","279062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140281","2019-07-23","Department for International Trade","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to his Department's consultations on trade negotiations with (a) the US, (b) Australia, (c) New Zealand and (d) potential accession to the Comprehensive and Progressive Agreement for Trans-Pacific Partnership, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of (i) farming unions and (ii) trades unions during the consultation period.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278944","278944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140282","2019-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women in prison gave birth in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279094","279094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140283","2019-07-23","Department for International Trade","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what formal consultation his Department had with the Welsh Government during the consultation period on (a) trade negotiations with (i) the US, (ii) Australia, and (iii) New Zealand and (b) potential accession to the Comprehensive and Progressive Agreement for Trans-Pacific Partnership.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278945","278945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140284","2019-07-23","Department for International Trade","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the economic merits of potential trade agreements between the UK and (a) the US, (b) Australia and (c) New Zealand compared to the EU’s proposed free trade agreements with those countries.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278946","278946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140285","2019-07-23","Department for International Trade","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the potential economic merits of the UK acceding to the Comprehensive and Progressive Agreement for Trans-Pacific Partnership with the benefits of the UK's membership of the European Single Market.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278947","278947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140286","2019-07-23","Department for International Trade","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the potential environmental merits of the UK acceding to the Comprehensive and Progressive Agreement for Trans-Pacific Partnership with the UK's membership of the European Single Market.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278948","278948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140288","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 18 July 2019, HCWS1757 on Building safety update, whether building owners should ensure that High Pressure Laminate panels of a European classification of Class C or D or European classification of Class B when combined with combustible insulation should be removed from buildings.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279063","279063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140289","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of (a) the volume of traffic passing through the village of Farthinghoe on the A422 and (b) the effect on the wider local route network when the A422 is closed.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278988","278988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140290","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the cost, including design and construction, of a bypass for the village of Farthinghoe on the A422.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278989","278989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140291","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 18 July 2019, on  HCWS1757 on Building safety update, for what reasons his Department's data collection exercise is not covering high risk buildings other than residential blocks.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279064","279064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140292","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with officials at Highways England and Northamptonshire Highways on the benefits to the wider local route network of a bypass on the A422 at the village of Farthinghoe.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278990","278990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140293","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to prepare for the creation of the Major Road Network in Northamptonshire; what assessment he has made of the effect of the designation of the A422 as part of that network on the wider local route network (a) with the Farthinghoe bypass on the A422 and (b) without the Farthinghoe bypass.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278991","278991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140294","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will visit the village of Farthinghoe to discuss with local residents the potential merits of the Farthinghoe bypass.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278992","278992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140295","2019-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will introduce targets for the waiting time for a universal credit appeal case to be heard by a tribunal.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278908","278908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140296","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department plans to make an assessment of whether combustible materials in the roof contributed to the spread of the fire at the Premier Inn near Cribbs Causeway on 18 July 2019.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279065","279065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140297","2019-07-23","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the Government plans to provide funding to the Loughs Agency after the UK leaves the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278924","278924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140298","2019-07-23","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the Government will continue to provide financial support to Tourism Ireland after the UK leaves the EU; what the level of current financial support is; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278925","278925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140299","2019-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to bring the Protocol to the North Atlantic Treaty on the Accession of the Republic of North Macedonia before the House for ratification.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278881","278881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140300","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has for the public procurement of sheep meat in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278952","278952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140301","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of preventing imports of sheep meat into the UK in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278953","278953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140302","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of residential drug recovery services for women in County Durham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278956","278956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140303","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the timetable is for listing the UK as a third country for the purposes of exporting sheep meat to the EU in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278954","278954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140304","2019-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have spent time in segregation by prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279095","279095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140305","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of potential demand for UK produced sheep meat in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278955","278955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140306","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) average length of time and (b) longest number of days was that a prisoner spent in segregation in each prison in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279096","279096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140307","2019-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours of purposeful activity per prisoner were recorded on average in (a) each prison rated in the 2017-18 performance rating as performance is of serious concern and (b) each prisons that was rated as exceptional performance.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279097","279097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140308","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to improve its procedures for implementing the recommendations made by HM Chief Inspector of Prisons.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279098","279098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140309","2019-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 273816 on Prisons: Education, what the value by lot is of Dynamic Purchasing System contracts awarded to date.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279099","279099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140310","2019-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 273816 on Prisons: Education, which providers have been awarded Dynamic Purchasing System contracts to date.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279100","279100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140311","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 273816, how enabling a governor to determine (a) what the curriculum is, (b) how it is delivered, and (c) who delivers it will ensure a consistent approach to delivery.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279101","279101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140312","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government has taken to ensure that recommendations for improvements made by HM Chief Inspector of Prisons are addressed.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279102","279102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140313","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of exams on the mental health of (a) sixth-form, (b) secondary, and (c) primary school students.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279114","279114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140314","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of (a) sixth-form, (b) secondary, and (c) primary school students received mental health referrals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279115","279115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140315","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of (a) sixth-form, (b) secondary, and (c) primary school students started mental health treatment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279116","279116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140316","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of (a) sixth-form, (b) secondary, and (c) primary school students were waiting to start mental health treatment at the start of each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279117","279117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140317","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time was for (a) sixth-form, (b) secondary, and (c) primary school students for mental health treatment after receiving a referral in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279118","279118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140318","2019-07-23","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on improving access to mental health services in order to reduce the number of mental health related incidents attended to by the police.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278957","278957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140319","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of school students attempting suicide after receiving a mental health referral but before starting treatment in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279119","279119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140320","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of (a) sixth-form, (b) secondary, and (c) primary schools offer (i) counselling services and (ii) access to counselling support.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279120","279120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140321","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of (a) community, (b) academy, (c) grammar and (d) independent school students were given special consideration in exams due to mental health problems in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279121","279121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140322","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of children in year (a) nine (b) 10 and (c) 11 were permanently excluded from a school in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279122","279122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140323","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of children in year (a) nine, (b) 10 and (c) 11 left full-time education after permanent exclusion from a school in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279123","279123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140324","2019-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if she will publish the terms of the review of the Reserve Forces and Cadets Association undertaken by Mr Rob Sullivan.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278902","278902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140325","2019-07-23","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much time is allocated for new police recruits to receive mental health training prior to their first deployment.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278958","278958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140326","2019-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timeframe is for the publication of the review on Reserve Forces and Cadets Association.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278903","278903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140327","2019-07-23","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much time is allocated to police officers for continuing professional development in mental health training.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278959","278959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140328","2019-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions she has had with the Chairman of the Reserve Forces and Cadets Association on the contribution that associations make to the defence of the realm; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278904","278904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140329","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the (a) CEO, (b) Accountable Officers and (c) chief nurses of the CCGs rated as inadequate in NHS England’s assessment framework on the performance of those CCGs; what measures have been agreed to help ensure improvement of the performance of those CCGs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278885","278885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140330","2019-07-23","Treasury","2019-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many responses his Department received to its consultation on restricting exit payments in the public sector.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278975","278975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140331","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will undertake a review of the effectiveness of prosecutions under the Protection Against Cruel Tethering Act 1988; what steps the Government is taking to ensure the implementation of adequate protections for tethered horses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278918","278918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140332","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2019 to Question 260035, how many tumour profiling tests to guide adjuvant chemotherapy decisions for early breast cancer were delivered in each (a) NHS Trust and (b) Genomic Laboratory Hub for the most recent 12 months for which data are available.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279073","279073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140333","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2019 to Question 260033, what annual assessment is planned for the activity undertaken through the Genomic Laboratory infrastructure; and whether that information will be made public.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279074","279074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140334","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cessations of bus services (a) his Department and (b) Traffic Commissioners were notified of in 2018-19; and where in the UK those cessations were.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278942","278942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140335","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will increase the (a) funding for and (b) provision of residential drug treatment services.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278960","278960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140336","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of pupils who experience bowel and bladder problems; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the needs of those pupils are met.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279070","279070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140337","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which alternative locations to High Legh were considered as part of the planning for a junction to join Northern Powerhouse Rail to High Speed Two.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278979","278979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140338","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time for patients attending the accident and emergency departments at (a) Sherwood Forest and (b) Nottingham University hospitals was in the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278943","278943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140339","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons High Legh was chosen as the location for joining Northern Powerhouse Rail to High Speed Two.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278980","278980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140340","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to ensure that the requirements of Northern Powerhouse Rail are addressed in the High Speed Rail Two: Phase 2b Design refinement consultation; and if he will publish the requirements that have been considered and prioritised.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278981","278981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140341","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of alternative routes for Northern Powerhouse Rail to (a) link and (b) not link to High Speed Two.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278982","278982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140342","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings of the 11 July 2019 Road Safety Foundation report that (a) local road safety in the UK has major structural weaknesses and (b) the lack of funding may compromise the ability of councils to fulfil their legal duties.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279066","279066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140343","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to hold a consultation on the Northern Powerhouse rail route.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278983","278983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140344","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the franchise for East Midlands Trains stipulates that the new rolling stock for that route should be manufactured by a company that is based in the UK.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279067","279067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140345","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the consequences of the October 31 deadline for the UK leaving the EU on (a) stockpiling and (b) cashflows in the manufacturing sector.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278995","278995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140346","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the adequacy manufacturing businesses' preparations for the UK leaving the EU without an agreement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278996","278996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140347","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the proposed east to west Northern Powerhouse Rail is a Y-shape rather than a direct line between Manchester and Liverpool; what assessment he has made of whether the distance is further between (a) Liverpool and Manchester and (b) Liverpool and Leeds using the proposed Y- shaped line; and what estimate he has made of the extra time each such journey will take as a result of that proposal.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278984","278984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140348","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support UK manufacturers prepare for the possibility of the UK leaving the EU without an agreement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278997","278997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140349","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons there are no direct Northern rail services between Liverpool and Newcastle.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278985","278985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140350","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure access to warehousing for manufacturers in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278998","278998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140351","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of how the changes to the rules on social security entitlements for mixed aged couples will affect local authority council tax reduction schemes given the protected status of pensioners in such schemes.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279147","279147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140352","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the manufacturing sector on preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278999","278999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140353","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of 5G on data used in meteorology; and what steps he will take to ensure that 5G does not interfere with weather forecasting.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279000","279000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140354","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2019 to Question 242826, what the timescale is for the publication of the consultation on regulatory proposals regarding consumer Internet of Things security.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279001","279001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140355","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has to cap ground rents for existing leaseholders.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279125","279125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140356","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many single parents with dependent children are in receipt of severe disability premium in their income-related employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279148","279148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140357","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of requiring universities in England to use contextual admissions tools to widen participation in higher education.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278922","278922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140358","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households with no one in work receive the (a) disabled child element and (b) the disabled child element but not the severely disabled child element in their child tax credit.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279149","279149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140359","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what impact assessments the Government has undertaken on capping ground rents for existing leaseholders, and what cap values were used in those assessments.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279126","279126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140360","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps he has taken to widen access to the highest performing schools in England and Wales.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278923","278923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140361","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many single parents who are not in work receive (a) the disabled child element and (b) the disabled child element but not the severely disabled child element in their child tax credit.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279150","279150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140362","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of Official Development Assistance allocated to his Department is spent on independent schools; and what other programmes are funded by that Assistance.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279002","279002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140363","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of universal credit mandatory reconsiderations where the claimant was (a) represented and (b) not represented were successful; what proportion of unsuccessful mandatory reconsiderations where the claimant was (a) represented and (b) not represented were appealed; and how many of those appeals were successful.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279151","279151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140364","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answers of 16 May 2019 to Question 255325 and Question 255326 on mental health in prisons, whether the number of prison officers trained in the new suicide and self-harm reduction training is 14,000 or 24,000.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279003","279003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140365","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 16 May 2019 to Question 255326 on death and self-harm in prisons, whether key workers supporting new prisoners are mandated to undertake suicide and self-harm prevention training.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279004","279004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140366","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with Sir Mike Richards on workforce requirements to support the implementation of breast screening recommendations in the Independent Review of National Screening Programmes in England.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279127","279127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140367","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the core spending power per dwelling for Barnsley council was in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279128","279128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140368","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of children in reception class in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire, (c) Yorkshire and the Humber, and (d) England have been classified as (i) overweight and (ii) obese in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279129","279129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140369","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of children in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire, (c) Yorkshire and the Humber, and (d) England have been classified as (i) overweight and (ii) obese in Year 6 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279130","279130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140370","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire, (c) Yorkshire and the Humber, and (d) England have been classified as (i) overweight and (ii) obese in Year 11 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279131","279131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140371","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of children in Year 11 in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire, (c) Yorkshire and the Humber, and (d) England have been classified as (i) overweight and (ii) obese in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279132","279132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140372","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of adults in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire, (c) Yorkshire and the Humber, and (d) England have been classified as (i) overweight and (ii) obese in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279133","279133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140373","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of applications received in each of the last twelve months for Leave to Remain extension application as a Tier 1 Highly Skilled general migrant; and how of those cases were concluded within eight weeks.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279030","279030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140374","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons the processing of extension applications may exceed the eight-week agreed service standard; and with what frequency that standard has been exceeded in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279031","279031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140375","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the reasons are that qualify an extension application as complex.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279032","279032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140376","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to support the (a) use and (b) production of renewable (i) energy and (ii) infrastructure in each nation and region of the UK.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279033","279033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140377","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many applications were submitted to the Feed-In Tariff scheme in each of the last nine years in each region and nation of the UK.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279034","279034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140378","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the amount of money distributed in (a) generation and (b) export tariffs under the Feed-In Tariffs scheme in each of the last nine years in each nation and region of the UK.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279035","279035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140379","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the (a) closure of the Feed-in Tariff scheme and (b) proposed introduction of the smart export guarantee scheme on the use of microgeneration technologies by residents.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279036","279036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140380","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the number of (a) students training to be citizenship education teachers and (b) schools providing GCSE citizenship education as an option.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278986","278986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140381","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has plans to make citizenship education a priority subject for teacher training.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278987","278987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140382","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to reduce rates of absence among pupils that are (a) eligible free school meals, (b) have special educational needs and (c) are of the Irish Heritage and Gypsy/Roma ethnic groups in each London Borough.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279037","279037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140383","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the proportion of adults without qualifications in (a) London and (b) Hounslow Borough.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279038","279038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140384","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement, Building safety update, HCWS1757, by what date the data will be collected; what (a) funding and (b) resources he has allocated to the collection of that data; what data will be collected; and if he will publish the results of that data collection.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279139","279139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140385","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of (a) the UK and (b) other EU countries in translating public sector investment in R&D into private sector investment in R&D; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279005","279005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140386","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the get help to retrain scheme, whether the digital service will include the assessment of adults' (a) qualifications and (b) skills.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278909","278909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140387","2019-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training his Department provides to prison officers on Rule 39 in relation to private legal post.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278993","278993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140388","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of (a) public and (b) private sector R&D spend figures; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279006","279006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140389","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the office for students on registration fees for further education colleges.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278910","278910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140390","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to maintain support for small-scale renewable heat generation beyond the termination of the Domestic Renewable Heat Initiative in March 2021.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279039","279039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140391","2019-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints have been made in the last three years in relation the breach of Rule 39; and what steps his Department has taken to resolve those complaints.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278994","278994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140392","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the projected undistributed expenditure in relation to the Feed-In Tariff scheme as a result of the early closure of that scheme.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279040","279040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140393","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the roll-out of the Get Help to Retrain scheme (a) in the Liverpool City Region and (b) to all eligible adults in England by 2020.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278911","278911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140394","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the office for students registration fees on the financial viability of further education colleges.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278912","278912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140395","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the introduction of a separate office for students registration fee banding for stand alone further education colleges.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278913","278913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140396","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2019 to Question 276204, on the Holiday Activities and Food Research Fund, what funding organisations that unsuccessfully bid for funding from that fund can apply for to feed children.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279069","279069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140397","2019-07-23","Cabinet Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether there is a protocol in place to inform Members when Departments change (a) correspondence, (b) secretarial and (c) ministerial e-mail addresses.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278915","278915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140398","2019-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the merits of twice monthly universal credit payments in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278916","278916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140399","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what comparative estimate he has made the proportion of non-UK EU citizens who have applied to the settled status scheme  in (a) Wales and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279079","279079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140400","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the average time it takes for a new business to become fully operational in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278917","278917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140401","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what contingency funding he has allocated for the (a) slaughter, (b) burial and (c) disposal of lamb carcasses in the event that there is a decrease in the export of lamb if the UK leaves the EU without an agreement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279080","279080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140402","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding his Department has allocated for contingency plans in the event that the UK leaves the EU without an agreement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279081","279081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140403","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what level of funding his Department has allocated to contingency planning at the ports (a) Holyhead and (b) Pembroke Dock in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279082","279082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140404","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2019 to Question 272722 on High Rise Flats: Insulation, whether the tests have started; how many tests are due to take place; and when all the tests are due to be completed.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279140","279140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140405","2019-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many disability qualified members of tribunals there are and what the qualifications are for those roles; and if he will she make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278914","278914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140406","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279041","279041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140407","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the overcharging of medicines to the NHS.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279026","279026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140408","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department is aware that synacthen has recently increased in cost from £2.70 per vial to £38 per vial; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279027","279027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140409","2019-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 18 July 2019 on Defence Fire and Rescue Project, HCWS1758, what the total cost was to his Department of the legal challenge from Serco Ltd.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278932","278932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140410","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that there is no duplication of animal testing for chemical registrations in the event that the UK leaves the EU without an agreement.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278930","278930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140411","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department will use the Health Service Products (Provision and Disclosure of Information) Regulations 2018 to prevent price inflation of medicines.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279028","279028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140412","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle the promotion of red listed drugs to non-specialist healthcare professionals by pharmaceutical companies.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279029","279029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140413","2019-07-22","Attorney General","2019-07-18","To ask the Attorney General, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279042","279042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140414","2019-07-22","Cabinet Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279043","279043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140415","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279044","279044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140416","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in her Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279045","279045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140417","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279046","279046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140418","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279047","279047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140419","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279048","279048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140420","2019-07-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279049","279049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140421","2019-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to  Written Statement of 18 July 2019 on Defence Fire and Rescue Project, HCWS1758, for what reasons her Department decided that that project will improve safety for firefighter personnel.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278933","278933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140422","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279050","279050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140423","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279051","279051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140424","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279052","279052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140425","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279053","279053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140426","2019-07-22","Department for International Trade","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279054","279054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140427","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279055","279055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140428","2019-07-22","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in her Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279056","279056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140429","2019-07-22","Scotland Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279057","279057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140430","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279058","279058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140431","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279059","279059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140432","2019-07-22","Wales Office","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in his Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279154","279154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140433","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many BAME staff are employed at (a) grade 7, (b) grade 5 and (c) grade 3 in her Department.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279155","279155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139279","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential environmental effects of the disturbance of deep-sea carbon stores through deep-sea mining.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277680","277680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139651","2019-07-17","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","What recent discussions he has had with his (a) European and (b) other international counterparts on the humanitarian crisis in Venezuela.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911993","911993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139652","2019-07-17","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","What progress his Department has made on achieving sustainable development goal 4 on education for children.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911994","911994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139653","2019-07-17","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","What steps he is taking to improve English literacy throughout the Commonwealth.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911995","911995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139654","2019-07-17","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","What recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the humanitarian situation on the US-Mexico border.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911998","911998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139655","2019-07-17","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","What support his Department provides to victims of forced displacement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911999","911999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139656","2019-07-17","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","What steps he is taking to ensure that UK aid to the Occupied Palestinian Territories facilitates peacebuilding with Israel.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912000","912000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139668","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to minimise aircraft noise for people living close to Stansted airport's 04 and 22 runway approaches.","Biography information for Mrs Kemi Badenoch","Mrs Kemi Badenoch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278570","278570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139669","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding he plans to make available for the delivery of the forthcoming green paper on prevention.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278539","278539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139670","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the forthcoming green paper on prevention will include (a) a full analysis of the budget needed to implement the content of that paper and (b) an indication of the sources of funding to deliver the content of that paper.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278540","278540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139671","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the forthcoming green paper on prevention will include a commitment to fully fund local authority public health services.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278541","278541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139672","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the forthcoming green paper on prevention will include commitments on (a) HIV infection and (b) sexual health.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278542","278542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139673","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the take-up of the flu vaccination among people most at risk of flu.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278543","278543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139674","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the Government plans to publish its green paper on prevention.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278544","278544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139675","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the French Government's approach to returning African cultural artefacts to their countries of origin, including the joint development of secure museums in those countries, what assessment he has had made of the potential merits of the UK adopting a similar approach to   the return of artefacts held by UK museums.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278486","278486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139676","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the announcement by the French Development Agency of €1 billion in equity and €1 billion in loans being made available to African entrepreneurs through the programme Choose Africa, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the UK adopting a similar scheme.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278487","278487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139677","2019-07-22","Cabinet Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many contractors employed by the Cabinet Office have been paid more than £750 per day in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278363","278363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139678","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the role of free ports in tackling global tax avoidance and evasion.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278534","278534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139679","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","[Suggested redraft] To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of farms at risk of closing down as a result of a new systems of agricultural payments as outlined in the Government's policy paper of 12 September 2018 on health and harmony: the future for food, farming and the environment in a green Brexit, what the size of those farms are; and the type of farming undertaken by those farms.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278334","278334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139680","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled, Business Management Practices on Farms, England 2016/17, published by his Department in February 2018, what steps he is taking to increase the number of farm businesses that undertake (a) business and (b) land management planning; and what assessment he has made of the effect of new Environmental Land Management system as outlined in the statement of 12 September 2018 on the ability of farmers to produce land management plans.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278335","278335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139681","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what measures will be included in a future environmental land management scheme as outlined in the policy statement of 12 September 2018 on health and harmony: the future for food farming and the environment in a green Brexit, to ensure all farm businesses can create land management plans and participate in the new payment schemes.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278336","278336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139682","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what measures will be included in a future environmental land management scheme as outlined in the policy statement of 12 September 2018 on health and harmony: the future for food farming and the environment in a green Brexit, to promote farm cluster working and landscape-scale enhancement projects.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278337","278337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139683","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) extent and (b) appropriateness of the use of Eritrean airfields and ports by the militaries of Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates to support their operations in Yemen.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278387","278387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139684","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of public health funding for smoking cessation services in County Durham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278474","278474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139685","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS England's Commissioner-based Cancer Waiting Times for May 2019 (Provisional), published on 11 July 2019, for what reason the NHS Durham Dales, Easington and Sedgefield Clinical Commissioning Group is not meeting the target for patients to receive their first cancer treatment within 62 days of an urgent GP referral.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278475","278475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139686","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the number of notified bodies to service medical devices under the terms of the Medical Devices Regulation.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278523","278523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139687","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to protect Local Welfare Assistance schemes in England.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278615","278615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139688","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with (a) NHS England and (b) Bristol City Council on the routine commissioning of PrEP in Bristol.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278545","278545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139689","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many applications for Standard NHS Continuing Healthcare were completed in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, (c) 2017-18 and (d) 2018-19.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278451","278451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139690","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many assessments for Standard NHS Continuing Healthcare were completed in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, (c) 2017-18 and (d) 2018-19.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278452","278452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139691","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people were assessed as eligible for Standard NHS Continuing Healthcare in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, (c) 2017-18 and (d) 2018-19.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278453","278453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139692","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to prevent UK sports teams engaging in promotional work with the gambling industry aimed at young people under 18 years-old in other countries.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278590","278590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139693","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will make an assessment of the effect on trends in the level of high street footfall of William Hill's recent announcement to close branches throughout the UK.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278547","278547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139694","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 275103 on Carbon Emissions: EU Countries, what dates have been set as targets for net zero emissions by (a) Finland, (b) Denmark, (c) Germany and (d) Portugal.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278338","278338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139695","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans his Department has to monitor, track and publish the proportion of its education spending allocated for delivery by (a) public and (b) private providers.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278583","278583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139696","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","If his Department will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the findings of the UN Special Rapporteur on the right to education presented to the UN Human Rights Council in July 2019 that stated that public-private partnerships in education that focus on involving private actors for service delivery have empirically largely failed, in particular in fragile countries.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278584","278584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139697","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Department for International Trade's draft tariff schedule, Temporary rates of custom duty, published on 13 March 2019, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on livestock farmers in the event that the EU matches the tariff on sheep meat proposed in that draft tariff schedule in the event that the UK leaves the EU without an agreement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278535","278535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139698","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 272120, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of the statement in BRE's paper of 7 February 2018, that there is therefore an increased risk that boilers will in fact be non-compliant.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278339","278339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139699","2019-07-22","Department for International Trade","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the potential merits of negotiating as part of a trade agreement between the UK and the US a change in the level of actionable limits for foreign bodies in food sold in the US.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278536","278536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139700","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with Astrazeneca and Avara Avlon about the (a) three year guarantee on enhanced redundancy payments and terms for staff agreed as part of the sale of the company for £1 in December 2016 and the (b) collapse of Avara Avalon.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278449","278449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139701","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of welfare changes on disabled people in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278483","278483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139702","2019-07-22","Cabinet Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the value of trade (a) exports and (b) imports between the UK and the Irish Republic in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278395","278395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139703","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his South African counterpart on potentially changing the travel advice for UK nationals in the Cape Town area due to recent violence.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278396","278396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139704","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to hold discussions with his North Macedonian counterpart on that country's application to join NATO.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278397","278397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139705","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the British Medical Association and other representative bodies on proposals to mitigate the effect of pension taxation on the NHS.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278568","278568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139706","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Steppe Inn at the British Embassy in Ulaanbaatar to promote UK soft power.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278359","278359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139707","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Government of Peru on freedom of the press and the role of investigative journalists in that country.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278360","278360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139708","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the (a) Government of Albania and (b) political parties in Albania on the boycott of that country's Parliament by opposition parties.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278361","278361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139709","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to include the Women’s World Cup Football Finals in the Listed Events category for free to air sports viewing.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278362","278362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139710","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to support developing countries' national plans to deliver universal health coverage.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278415","278415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139711","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the UK has plans to be a signatory to the Hong Kong International Convention for the Safe and Environmentally Sound Recycling of Ships.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278447","278447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139712","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether his Department has plans to encourage governments of developing countries to invest five per cent of GDP in primary healthcare.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278416","278416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139713","2019-07-22","Scotland Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he plans to visit a food bank in August 2019.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278581","278581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139714","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate the Government has made of the number of illegal seaborne migrants that have crossed the Short Straits (a) from 1 October to 31 December 2018, (b) from 1 January to 31 March 2019 and (c) since 1 April 2019.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278443","278443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139715","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 May 2019 to Question 251240 on 101 Calls: Fees and Charges, whether (a) that review has concluded and (b) he plans to place a copy of that review in the Library.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278582","278582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139716","2019-07-22","Department for International Trade","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of average price reduction on non-EU goods into the UK from setting a new UK tariff schedule on exit from the EU.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278326","278326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139717","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of goods from non-EU countries are held at EU borders for physical checks.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278327","278327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139718","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) maximum and (b) average reduction in per pupil funding for a state secondary school was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278328","278328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139719","2019-07-22","Cabinet Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to tackle third party websites from posing as Government entities.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278442","278442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139720","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what minimum per pupil sum is for a state secondary school to provide each pupil with a good quality education.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278329","278329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139721","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what financial support his Department provides to local authorities for investment in waste and recycling facilities.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278601","278601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139722","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what R&D support his Department provides to small- and medium-sized enterprises for innovation in packaging.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278602","278602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139723","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the cost to the public purse of the introduction of separate food waste collections throughout England.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278603","278603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139724","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many local waste collection authorities own arms-length commercial waste collection services.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278604","278604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139725","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans the Government has to tackle agricultural plastic pollution.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278605","278605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139726","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what funding the Government plans to allocate to the modernisation of the UK steel industry.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278606","278606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139727","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of Local Plans that include a requirement on new homes to be accessible and adaptable.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278563","278563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139728","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to improve access to housing for (a) older and (b) disabled people.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278564","278564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139729","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding his Department has made available to waste disposal authorities for the prevention of methane emissions from closed landfill sites.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278607","278607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139730","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential (a) financial and (b) environmental merits of an incineration tax for household waste.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278608","278608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139731","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on revenue of a tax on virgin materials including on plastics.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278609","278609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139732","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much has been spent on tackling waste crime in the last five years.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278610","278610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139733","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much revenue has been raised from fines for fly-tipping in the last five years.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278611","278611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139734","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what financial support was available to re-useable nappy schemes in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278612","278612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139735","2019-07-22","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the Equality Commission for Northern Ireland's recruitment criteria as a result of the composition of new commissioners announced in June 2019.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278398","278398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139736","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to provide (a) advice, (b) support and (c) services for small business owners looking to grow their business.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278354","278354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139737","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that small business owners are aware of the advice, support, and services available from the Government to help them grow their business.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278355","278355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139738","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on volumes of food waste collected in the event of local authorities introducing food waste collections separate to other waste collections.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278340","278340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139739","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2019 to Question 259124 on Livestock: Animal Welfare, what plans his Department has to introduce benchmark incentives for farmers to maintain and enhance animal health standards.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278450","278450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139740","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to lower the corporation tax rate for small businesses.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278356","278356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139741","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of scrapping quarterly reporting for businesses with a turnover of under £85,000.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278357","278357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139742","2019-07-22","Attorney General","2019-07-17","To ask the Attorney General, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278364","278364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139743","2019-07-22","Cabinet Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278365","278365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139744","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278366","278366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139745","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278367","278367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139746","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278368","278368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139747","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278369","278369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139748","2019-07-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278370","278370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139749","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278371","278371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139750","2019-07-22","Department for International Trade","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278372","278372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139751","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278373","278373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139752","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the (a) Chancellor of the Exchequer and (b) Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on ensuring the UK Shared Prosperity Fund contributes to the achievement of the goals set out in the 25 Year Environment Plan.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278577","278577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139753","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278374","278374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139754","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278375","278375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139755","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support small businesses in towns and small cities.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278358","278358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139756","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278376","278376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139757","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278377","278377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139758","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much time off in lieu has been taken staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278378","278378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139759","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278379","278379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139760","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278380","278380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139761","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278381","278381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139762","2019-07-22","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much time off in lieu has been taken by staff in her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278382","278382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139763","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 274560, what the driving test centre service standard travel distance criteria is; what the locations are of the test centres that each of the 19 closed test centres merged with; and which test centres those closed test centres have merged with.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278524","278524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139764","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government plans to make a commitment to the Global Polio Eradication Initiative at its pledging conference in Abu Dhabi in November 2019.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278585","278585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139765","2019-07-22","Department for International Trade","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the potential response from the EU on the Government's plan to maintain zero tariffs on (a) eggs, (b) cereals, (c) fruit and (d) vegetables imported into the UK in the event that the UK leaves the EU without an agreement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278537","278537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139766","2019-07-22","Department for International Trade","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of tariffs imposed by the EU on the competitiveness of the UK's export of (a) eggs, (b) cereals, (c) fruit and (d) vegetables to the EU; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of such tariffs on the agricultural sector.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278538","278538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139767","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of two-factor payment authentication on (a) consumers and (b) businesses.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278491","278491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139768","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that humanitarian workers globally can carry out their roles without risk of attack.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278492","278492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139769","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that families and young people have access to the help they need when faced with a financial crisis.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278493","278493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139770","2019-07-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many technical notices on ensuring that citizens and businesses have the information they require to prepare for the UK leaving the EU have been withdrawn; and for what reasons have those notices been withdrawn.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278494","278494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139771","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which parts of the Government’s plan for Connecting Facility Energy funding in the event that the UK leaving the EU without a deal (a) have and (b) have not been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278495","278495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139772","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which parts of the Government’s plan for European Regional Development funding in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal (a) have and (b) have not been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278496","278496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139773","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which parts of the Government’s plan for European Social Fund grants in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal (a) have and (b) have not been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278497","278497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139774","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which parts of the Government’s plan for European Territorial Cooperation funding in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal (a) have and (b) have not been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278498","278498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139775","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which parts of the Government’s plan for Funding for UK LIFE projects in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal (a) have and (b) have not been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278499","278499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139776","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which parts of the Government’s plan for Horizon 2020 funding in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal (a) have and (b) have not been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278500","278500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139777","2019-07-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which parts of the Government’s plan for the guarantee of EU-Funded programmes in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal (a) have and (b) have not been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278501","278501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139778","2019-07-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which parts of the Government’s plan for British Overseas Territories funding in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal (a) have and (b) have not been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278502","278502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139779","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to help local authorities tackle eutrophication.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278586","278586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139780","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what nationwide strategy is in place to tackle the effects of eutrophication.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278587","278587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139781","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) practices participating in and (b) children who have benefitted from the Starting Well scheme since its launch in spring 2018.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278528","278528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139782","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the interim evaluation of the Starting Well Scheme will be published.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278529","278529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139783","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of children under the age of five were seen by an NHS dentist in England in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18 and (c) 2018-19.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278530","278530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139784","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of dental practices who have participated in the Starting Well Core scheme since its launch.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278531","278531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139785","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, in which areas of England has the Starting Well Core scheme been made available to NHS dental practices.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278532","278532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139786","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure all local authorities in England take part in Public Health England’s Oral Health Survey of five-year-old children 2019.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278533","278533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139787","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the rail industry is accountable to Government.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278597","278597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139788","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 272127, which organisation completed the evaluation; and if he will place a copy of the evaluation in the Library.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278333","278333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139789","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his oral contribution of 16 July 2019, Official Report, column 663, what the timeframe is for his Department to respond to the consultation on shared parental leave for the self-employed.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278392","278392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139790","2019-07-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effects of the UK leaving the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal on inter-continental travel.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278503","278503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139791","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that medical workers in Gaza can perform their humanitarian functions without risk of attack.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278454","278454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139792","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that people responsible for attacks on humanitarian workers are held to account.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278455","278455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139793","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the extent to which the Israeli Government’s internal investigations into the killings of Palestinian health workers comply with international standards of independence, impartiality, promptness, thoroughness and transparency.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278456","278456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139794","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of a decrease in the number of people immigrating to the UK after the UK leaves the EU on house prices.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278504","278504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139795","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to reduce the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on labour shortages.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278505","278505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139796","2019-07-22","Department for International Trade","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to protect foreign investment in the UK ahead of the the UK leaving the EU on 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278506","278506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139797","2019-07-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to trade between the UK and the EU after the UK leaves the EU on employment in the trade sector.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278507","278507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139798","2019-07-22","Women and Equalities","2019-07-17","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities,  whether her Department has made an assessment of any potential discrepancies in rates of pay between heterosexual and non-heterosexual workers.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278331","278331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139799","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase the number of electric car charging points (a) throughout the UK and (b) in Gloucestershire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278342","278342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139800","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education what the adult education budget is for (a) financial year 2019-20 and (b) academic year 2019-20; and what proportion of that budget is devolved to the seven combined authorities in England.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278476","278476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139801","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will launch an independent inquiry into family courts in England and Wales to establish (a) how victims of domestic violence are treated, (b) whether the process under which parents convicted of domestic violence are given access to children is adequate and (c) whether the courts should be more transparent in their handling of domestic violence cases and the protection of children involved in such cases.","Biography information for Suella Braverman","Suella Braverman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278552","278552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139802","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 270730 on Prisons: Industrial Health and Safety, whether all prison staff who are not directly employed by HMPPS have access to (a) occupational health services, (b) employee assistance programmes, (c) trauma support services and (d) personal well-being zones.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278444","278444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139803","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 270730 on Prisons: Industrial Health and Safety, what assessment he has made of risk to prison staff who are (a) directly employed by HMPPS and (b) contractors of (i) exposure to new psychoactive substances, (ii) assaults with excreta and (iii) other assaults.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278445","278445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139804","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 270730 on Prisons: Industrial Health and Safety, what steps he is taking to support the physical, emotional and social well-being of prison staff who are not directly employed by HMPPS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278446","278446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139805","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the (a) effect on and (b) risks to the environment of deep sea mining; and if he will make it his policy to pursue a moratorium.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278457","278457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139806","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the creation of national recovery network maps to identify (a) the location of wildlife and (b) where wildlife should be in the future.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278400","278400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139807","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer on 5 February 2019 to Question 213318 on UK Seabed Resources: Pacific Ocean, if he will publish the domestic licenses granted by the Government for the Clarion-Clipperton Fracture Zone.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278458","278458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139808","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the oral evidence given by his Department’s Chief Scientist Professor Gideon Henderson to the Environmental Audit Committee on 16 October 2018, what the implications are for his policies of the statement that deep sea mining will do substantial damage to that local environment on the seabed, and that is pretty much unavoidable; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278459","278459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139809","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many computers are operating Windows 7 across the NHS.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278598","278598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139810","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to end UK Government sponsorship of deep sea mining exploration licences; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278460","278460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139811","2019-07-22","Cabinet Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of computers in the public sector that are using  Windows 7; and whether his Department has set a deadline for the withdrawal of Windows 7 in advance of Microsofts' end of support for that operating system.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278599","278599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139812","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the introduction of a registration scheme for private-rented accommodation to ensure that it meets minimum energy efficiency standards.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278401","278401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139813","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training her Department provides to Jobcentre Plus staff on economic abuse as a form of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278514","278514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139814","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department collects on needs of claimants of universal credit that are survivors of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278515","278515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139815","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress she has made on the development of universal credit management systems to enable the collation of the number of domestic violence easements.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278516","278516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139816","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with the permanent secretary of the Department of Communities in Northern Ireland on the extension of the review of the universal credit six month rule on terminal illness to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278405","278405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139817","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to (a) increase transparency of the amount of apprenticeship levy spent on different types of apprenticeship and (b) help ensure the availability of data on the socioeconomic background of apprentices by apprenticeship level.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278402","278402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139818","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the target set out in the NHS long term plan that 50 per cent of teenagers and young adults with cancer will be able to take part in clinical trials by 2025.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278391","278391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139819","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he had made of the number of new models of boilers introduced since October 2017 that have been tested for compliance with the new boiler plus regulations.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278341","278341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139820","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with (a) his Iraqi counterpart and (b) his counterpart in the Kurdistan Regional Government on security and reconstruction in Batnaya.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278548","278548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139821","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Iraqi counterpart on the safety and security of internally displaced people returning to Bartella.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278549","278549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139822","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of employment opportunities for internally displaced people returning to towns on the Nineveh Plains; and what support his Department is providing to those people.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278550","278550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139823","2019-07-22","Cabinet Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had with Microsoft on support for Windows 7 operating systems used by the public sector; and whether he has requested an extension of that support.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278600","278600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139824","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the proportion of companies that need economic operator and registration identification numbers have them.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278591","278591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139825","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) procurement and (b) life-cycle costs are for a Royal Navy Astute Class submarine.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278417","278417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139826","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which ministers he has  appointed to the taskforce to find a new buyer for the Novartis site in Great Grimsby.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278551","278551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139827","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many rough sleepers there are in Havering; and how many have been deported by his Department's Rough Sleeper Support Service in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278422","278422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139828","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the planned in-service date is for the cortisone IT programme for the Defence Medical Services; and what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the funding for that programme.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278418","278418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139829","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether restrictions have been imposed on the type of stores that are carried by the A400M as a result of vibration problems with that aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278419","278419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139830","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK nationals are suspected of leaving the UK in order to support the activities of Boko Haram and their splinter group Islamic State West Africa Province (ISWAP) in West Africa in the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278423","278423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139831","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce aircraft noise over South East England.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278424","278424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139832","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will place in the Library a copy of the algorithms citizen matching layer and business logic.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278477","278477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139833","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse is of the programme of work being undertaken by Airbus to increase the (a) serviceability and (b) reliability of the RAF's A400m aircraft fleet.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278420","278420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139834","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will include data on administrative reviews in his Department’s monthly statistics report on applications made to the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278478","278478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139835","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many full-time equivalent staff, including Revenue and Customs Digital Technology Services Ltd employees, does HMRC have.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278592","278592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139836","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to increase the armed forces presence in Gibraltar.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278425","278425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139837","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when (a) HMS Dauntless and (b) HMS Daring will next be put to sea.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278426","278426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139838","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made in the resurfacing of the runway on Ascension Island.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278427","278427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139839","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to increase the armed forces presence in the Falkland Islands.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278428","278428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139840","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of whether misogynistic crimes targeted at women should be treated as hate crimes by the police.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278479","278479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139841","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent engagements he has had with representatives of Norfolk Island.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278429","278429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139842","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the assessment process for eligibility for NHS continuing healthcare; and whether he has any plans to review that process.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278480","278480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139843","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to improve diplomatic relations with the British Virgin Islands.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278430","278430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139844","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with representatives from the Pitcairn Islands.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278431","278431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139845","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which radar system will be attached to the Type 31a frigate.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278406","278406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139846","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing the rate of the carer’s allowance to match the rate of jobseeker’s allowance.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278481","278481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139847","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of increasing carer's allowance to the same level as jobseeker’s allowance.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278482","278482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139849","2019-07-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what additional support will be allocated to Gibraltar in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278433","278433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139850","2019-07-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans the Government has to provide additional support to the Falkland Islands in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278434","278434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139851","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps he has taken to support the British Overseas Territories tackle environment threats.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278435","278435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139852","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether her Department has plans to modify the missile systems of P-8 aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278407","278407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139853","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to protect homes from the risk of unacceptably high levels of carbon monoxide.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278436","278436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139854","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of plastic straws on trends in levels of the ocean plastic pollution.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278437","278437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139855","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of uprating the financial thresholds for legal aid eligibility.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278403","278403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139856","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many contracts of a value of equal to or more than £1 billion have had the provisions of Chapter 6 Section 10 of the Green Book applied to them since the publication of the Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278408","278408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139857","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many contracts of a value of equal to or more than £100 million have had the provisions of Chapter 6 Section 10 of the Green Book applied to them since the publication of the Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278409","278409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139858","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 275643 on Railways: Surveys, what the (a) start and (b) end time was the gathering of information to prepare the National Rail Travel Survey December 2010.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278330","278330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139859","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many contracts of a value of equal to or more than £10 million have had the provisions of Chapter 6 Section 10 of the Green Book applied to them since the publication of the Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278410","278410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139860","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many GPs per 1000 of population there were in Bristol West in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278546","278546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139861","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it remains her Department's policy to take the Sting Ray lightweight torpedo out of service between 2026-2030; and what plans her Department has for the replacement that torpedo.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278411","278411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139862","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans the  Government has to encourage development of traditionalist villages similar to the Poundbury Estate near Dorchester.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278438","278438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139863","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to help local communities tackle anti-social behaviour.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278439","278439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139864","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to improve building (a) standards and (b) quality throughout the country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278440","278440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139865","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, (a) what the national average spend by local authorities on translation services was and (b) how much Havering Council spent on those services in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278441","278441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139866","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve the integration and cooperation of bus and train services.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278508","278508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139867","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timescale is for bringing forward proposals to make acts of deliberate trespass a criminal rather than a civil offence.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278421","278421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139868","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's policy is on participation of military surgeons in overseas training exercises involving animals that have been shot or otherwise injured with offensive weapons for the purpose of that exercise.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278578","278578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139869","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the 3,865 animals used in scientific procedures at DSTL Porton Down in 2017 were experimented upon under a multiple generic licence.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278579","278579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139870","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the 1,941 animals used in scientific procedures at DSTL Porton Down in 2018 were experimented upon under a multiple generic licence.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278580","278580"
