"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983320","2018-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with Exmoor National Park Authority on expanding the boundaries of the National Park to include the Quantocks and other areas.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176016","176016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983321","2018-10-10","Treasury","2018-10-08","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has received representations from Exmoor National Park for additional funding to expand the National Park beyond it present boundaries.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176017","176017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983322","2018-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his department has a policy on the protection of horses during racing.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176174","176174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983323","2018-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union on food safety regulations after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176175","176175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983324","2018-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's strategy is on reducing the amount of plastic going to landfill.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176176","176176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983325","2018-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people serving in the armed forces are from Northern Ireland.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176177","176177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983326","2018-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he last visited soldiers in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176178","176178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983327","2018-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what guidance his Department provides to departing military personnel on how to adapt to civilian life.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176179","176179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983328","2018-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many school visits were carried out by military personnel promoting a career in the armed forces in the academic year 2017-18.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176180","176180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983329","2018-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department provides counselling for ex-military personnel who have suffered PTSD as a result of their time in service.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176181","176181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983330","2018-10-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to increase funding allocated to schemes to support children with mental health problems.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176182","176182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983331","2018-10-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to enable the provision of additional services in general practice clinics to reduce the workload in accident and emergency departments.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176183","176183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983332","2018-10-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent research his Department has commissioned on irritable bowel syndrome; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176184","176184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983333","2018-10-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department spent on advertising in 2017.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176185","176185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983334","2018-10-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to increase the number of staff who assist people with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176186","176186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983335","2018-10-10","Treasury","2018-10-08","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on consumers of the increase in company car tax since 2013.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 175973","175973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983336","2018-10-10","Department for Transport","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that electric vehicles are affordable to (a) fleet operators and (b) consumers.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 175974","175974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983337","2018-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent equalities impact assessment her Department has conducted on its plans for the managed migration to universal credit.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176565","176565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983338","2018-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of recent trends in the average levels of household debt for people in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176566","176566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983339","2018-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of people expected to require additional support to make a universal credit claim during the managed migration process.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176567","176567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983340","2018-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will exempt people diagnosed with cancer from the three month wait to receive personal independence payments.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176246","176246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983341","2018-10-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that health, adult social care and children’s social care services work together to identify young carers.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176222","176222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983342","2018-10-10","Home Office","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he undertook an impact assessment of his decision not to carry over excess validity from previous passports; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176381","176381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983343","2018-10-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the reasons for (a) the NHS and (b) individual NHS trusts not meeting the target of 85 per cent of patients starting treatment for cancer within 62 days of an urgent GP referral for suspected cancer.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176194","176194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983344","2018-10-11","Treasury","2018-10-08","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the potential loss of revenue to the public purse of deferred payment of capital gains tax for trusts ceasing to be UK resident or non-UK resident individuals who trade through a UK branch or agency as proposed in Clause 36 of the draft Finance Bill.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176648","176648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983345","2018-10-11","Treasury","2018-10-08","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the level of revenue accrued to the public purse as a result of  the implementation of Article 5 of the EU Anti Tax Avoidance Directive (Directive (EU) 2016/1164 of the European Parliament.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176649","176649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983346","2018-10-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many vacancies there are for (a) nurses, (b) junior doctors at each grade and (c) consultants at (i) Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (ii) Nottingham University Hospitals Trust.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176195","176195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983347","2018-10-11","Home Office","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many civilian staff were employed by Nottinghamshire Police in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176196","176196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983348","2018-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many audits on health assessments have been undertaken for (a) employment support allowance and (b) personal independence payments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176388","176388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983349","2018-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the independence of audits carried out on health (a) assessments and (b) reports undertaken on claimants of (i) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payments.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176389","176389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983350","2018-10-11","Department for Education","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department has spent from the public purse on (a) advertising and (b) marketing the 30 hours of free childcare in (a) autumn 2017, (b) spring 2018, (c) summer 2018 and (d) autumn 2018.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176513","176513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983351","2018-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which organisations are responsible for the independent audits on health (a) assessments and (b) reports on claimants of employment support allowance and personal independence payments.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176390","176390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983352","2018-10-10","Home Office","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that charities suspected of extremist activities are not able to register with the Charities Commission.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 175965","175965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983353","2018-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Government of Thailand on free and fair elections in that country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176043","176043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983354","2018-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Government of Thailand on the freedom of assembly and association in that country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176044","176044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983355","2018-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in the Government of Thailand on reports of arbitrary arrests in that country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176045","176045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983356","2018-10-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of whether their is a causal link between the increased use of portable electronic devices and the (a) incidence and (b) prevalence of head lice in (i) primary and (ii) secondary school aged children; and what support his Department provides to schools to help (A) prevent and (B) treat head lice infestations.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 175966","175966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983357","2018-10-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of medicines stockpiling on (a) industry costs, (b) medicines pricing and (c) patient access to medicines.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176277","176277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983358","2018-10-10","Home Office","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of reasons for the recent rise in recorded hate crimes; and whether the Government has plans to identify crimes committed against people from alternative sub-cultures as hate crimes.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 175967","175967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983359","2018-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personnel from (a) Cumbria Constabulary, (b) Lancashire Constabulary and (c) Merseyside Constabulary her Department has (i) sign posted and (ii) recorded as made use of a local food bank in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 175968","175968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983360","2018-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 5 July 2018 to Question 159621 Universal Credit: Housing, how many and what proportion of universal credit claimants with a rent liability received their first payment of housing costs within two months of their date of claim for each month since March 2018.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176321","176321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983361","2018-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the evidential basis was for the introduction of the 20-metre rule as a criterion for mobility in the personal independence payment assessment procedure.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176485","176485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983362","2018-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of shale gas extraction on the UK’s ability to meet its climate change targets.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 175969","175969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983363","2018-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of the introduction of the 20-metre rule on the level of people's eligibility for personal independence payment compared with previous levels of eligibility for disability living allowance.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176486","176486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983364","2018-10-11","Home Office","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer on 6 September 2018 to Question 169147 on Animal Experiments, if the Government will introduce legislative proposals to bring regulations for the testing on animals of ingredients used in household products into line with those on ingredients used in cosmetics.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176053","176053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983365","2018-10-11","Home Office","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to publish his Department's response to the consultation on the review of Section 24 of the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986, published in 2014.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176054","176054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983366","2018-10-11","Department for International Trade","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on ending unnecessary ad hoc cosmetics testing on animals by Chinese authorities on shipments of cosmetic products imported into China.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176055","176055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983367","2018-10-11","Home Office","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance his Department has issued to universities engaged animal testing on the implementation of the principles of the 3Rs, Replacement, Reduction and Refinement.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176056","176056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983368","2018-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Bahrain to ensure that Hassan Mushaima (a) receives adequate medical care in line with the UN's Nelson Mandela Rules, (b) is granted family visitation rights, (c) is granted access to reading materials.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176581","176581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983369","2018-10-10","Department for Education","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, will he will make it his policy to extend the provisions of the pupil premium to disadvantaged students moving from secondary to further education.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176247","176247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983370","2018-10-10","Department for Education","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on funding for (a) post-16 education (b) skills training and (c) the further education sector after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176248","176248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983371","2018-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, for what reason the Government has encouraged multiple full fibre infrastructure providers to build competing networks in the same areas.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 175997","175997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983372","2018-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the building of multiple open access full fibre networks in the same locations on the Government’s target of nationwide full fibre by 2033.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 175998","175998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983373","2018-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Future Telecoms Infrastructure Review, published in July 2018, whether he has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to ensure transparency in the proposals for full fibre network build plans.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 175999","175999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983374","2018-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of multiple providers investing in full-fibre networks in the same areas on digital services in (a) suburban areas and (b) towns.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176000","176000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983375","2018-10-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to MIND's report entitled Brick by Brick: A Review of Mental Health and Housing, published in November 2017, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that the social housing system supports people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176363","176363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983376","2018-10-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has issued to Clinical Commissioning Groups on the provision of flu vaccinations for people over the age of 70.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176148","176148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983377","2018-10-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the announcement, Government announces new generation of council housing, published on 3 October 2018, what steps he is taking to encourage local authorities to build adequate numbers of social housing.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176304","176304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983378","2018-10-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the answer of 6 September 2018 to Question 169830 on Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme, what progress he has made on an outline deal for the next Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176660","176660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983379","2018-10-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library any correspondence in the last year between his Department and local authorities on the collection and reporting of local rough sleeping data.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 175938","175938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983380","2018-10-10","Department for Education","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of children eligible for free school meals reached a Good Level of Development at age five in Stockton South constituency in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176668","176668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983381","2018-10-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the announcement made by the Chief Executive of NHS England at the International Practitioner Health Summit 2018, if he has plans to extend the Practitioner Health Programme to (a) nurses, (b) midwives, (c) other NHS practitioners and (d) professionals treating NHS patients.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Sir Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 175777","175777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/984367","2018-10-15","Treasury","2018-10-08","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to use vehicle tax to help achieve the objectives set out in the 25 Year Environment Plan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 177165","177165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000291","2018-11-12","Cabinet Office","2018-10-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Advisory Military Sub-Committee of the Committee on the Grant of Honours, Decorations and Medals is considering the issue of a full medal for Bomber Command veterans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187386","187386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/980100","2018-10-11","Department for Transport","2018-10-02","What steps he is taking to improve the condition of local roads.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906933","906933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973917","2018-10-11","Department for Transport","2018-09-14","Whether he plans to approve a southern rail link to Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906922","906922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972261","2018-09-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of workplace support provided to pregnant women and new mothers.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906879","906879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973018","2018-09-13","Department for International Trade","2018-09-13","What recent discussions he has had on trade and investment with African governments.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906897","906897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973019","2018-09-13","Department for International Trade","2018-09-13","What recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on trade with Israel of the UK leaving the EU-Israel Association Agreement.","Biography information for Victoria Prentis","Victoria Prentis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906898","906898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973020","2018-09-13","Department for International Trade","2018-09-13","What progress the Board of Trade has made on its work programme.","Biography information for Mary Robinson","Mary Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906899","906899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973021","2018-09-13","Department for International Trade","2018-09-13","What his priorities are for the G20 Trade and Investment Ministerial Meeting on 14 September 2018.","Biography information for Vicky Ford","Vicky Ford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906900","906900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973022","2018-09-13","Department for International Trade","2018-09-13","What steps he is taking to secure a free trade agreement with the US.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906901","906901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973023","2018-09-13","Department for International Trade","2018-09-13","Whether his Department takes into account information from the Joint Incident Assessment Team when determining an application for a licence to export to Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906903","906903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973024","2018-09-13","Women and Equalities","2018-09-13","When she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to end the practice of gay conversion therapy.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906878","906878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973162","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his French counterpart on the recent Iran Freedom gathering in Paris.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174718","174718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973163","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Norwegian Refugee Council on Israel and the Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174719","174719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973164","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve safety for cyclists on roads in Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174617","174617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973165","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the number of road accidents involving telegraph poles or road signs in Coventry since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174618","174618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973166","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the numbers of pupils completing the English Baccalaureate in (a) Coventry South constituency, (b) Coventry, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174619","174619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973167","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of pregnant women who are homeless in (a) Coventry and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174620","174620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973168","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the number of cyclists who have died due to potholes on roads in (a) Coventry and (b) England in each year for which information is available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174621","174621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973169","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the (a) effect on and (b) additional costs incurred by (i) local planning authorities and (ii) qualifying bodies producing a Neighbourhood Development Plan of undertaking assessments of the implications for European Sites of those plans.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174705","174705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973170","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the requirements relating to Habitats Regulations Assessments and European Sites on the ability of qualifying bodies to produce a Neighbourhood Development Plan.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174706","174706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973171","2018-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on with whom responsibility will lie for Tourism Ireland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174720","174720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973172","2018-10-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on releasing the £150 million allocated to improve rural broadband in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174721","174721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973173","2018-10-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the lowering of stakes on fixed-odds betting terminals in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174722","174722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973174","2018-10-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to provide funding for regional youth programmes on historical and cultural topics relevant to Ulster Scots.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174723","174723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973175","2018-10-09","Attorney General","2018-09-13","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2018 to Question 129098, how many reports of hare coursing were received in each year since 2014; and how many (a) prosecutions and (b) convictions there have been relating to hare coursing in 2018 to date.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174788","174788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973176","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government's revised childhood obesity plan will make tackling noncommunicable diseases a priority.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174785","174785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973177","2018-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Child Maintenance Service deduction from earnings requests are complied with; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174786","174786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973178","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Written Statement of 25 April 2018 on Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse (IICSA) – Interim Report, HCWS645, what representations he has received on scheduling a debate in the House in Government time on that report.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174708","174708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973179","2018-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current status of the future IT system for the Defence Medical Services is; and what the (a) product name, (b) estimated cost, (c) estimated date for the initial operational capability of the programme is; and what the position of that programme within the MOD equipment plan is.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174645","174645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973180","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has held with his international counterparts on securing the release of Druze hostages in Syria.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174695","174695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973181","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that leaseholders in privately-owned blocks do not have to fund the replacement of cladding and remedial fire safety measures following the Grenfell Tower tragedy; and if he will he make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174629","174629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973182","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the 2018-19 Main Estimates, how much funding her Department has allocated to prepare for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174772","174772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973183","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the 2018-19 Main Estimates, how much funding his Department has allocated to prepare for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174773","174773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973184","2018-10-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the 2018-19 Main Estimates, how much funding his Department has allocated to prepare for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174774","174774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973185","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the 2018-19 Main Estimates, how much funding his Department has allocated to prepare for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174775","174775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973186","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the 2018-19 Main Estimates, how much funding her Department has allocated to prepare for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174776","174776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973187","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 63 of document entitled Statement of funding policy: funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly, published by his Department in November 2015, for what reason the London & Continental Railways Corp budget line in Table C.16: Department for Transport is classed as non-Barnett applicable to Scotland but High Speed Two is 100 per cent Barnett applicable to Scotland.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174777","174777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973188","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2018 to Question 165671 on China: Detainees, what recent estimate he has made of the level of internment of members of the Uighur minority in political re-education camps in the Xinjiang Uyghur Autonomous Region of China.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174652","174652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973189","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of reports that humanitarian access to conflict areas of the Kachin region has been systematically blocked by (a) the armed forces and (b) the Government of Myanmar.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174653","174653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973190","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much (a) revenue and (b) operating income Visas and Immigration derived from chargeable calls to its contact centres from outside the UK in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174654","174654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973192","2018-10-09","Cabinet Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the number of people turned away from polling booths during the Voter ID pilot at the Local Elections was in comparison to the number of people charged with voter ID fraud over the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174750","174750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973193","2018-10-09","Cabinet Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total cost to the public purse was of the Boundary Commission Review.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174751","174751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973194","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of arrests made by the police in the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174752","174752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973195","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of trends in the proportion of reported crimes that lead to a caution or a charge in the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174753","174753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973196","2018-10-09","Cabinet Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many criminal incidents which included the use of a bladed weapon were reported to the police in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174754","174754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973197","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what research his Department has (a) commissioned and (b) conducted on the health effects of PM (i) 2.5; (ii) 1 and (iii) 0.1.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174601","174601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973198","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent research he has consulted to formulate policy related to the effects on health of PM (a) 2.5 (b) 1 and (c) 0.1.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174602","174602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973199","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what method his Department uses to assess the effects on health of emissions of PM (a) 2.5 (b) 1 and (c) 0.1 from waste incinerator sites.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174603","174603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973200","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of waste collection authorities that charge money in addition to council tax for the collection of garden or food waste.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174604","174604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973201","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the draft Universal Credit (Transitional Provisions) (Managed Migration) Regulations 2018, what estimate she has made of the number and proportion of claimants in receipt of (a) severe disability premium and (b) enhanced disability premium under employment support allowance who will see a reduction in social security support as a result of moving to universal credit.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174727","174727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973202","2018-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to introduce an enhanced effective pension age of 60 years for Ministry of Defence police officers.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174770","174770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973203","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he had with his Emirati counterpart in London last week on the conflict in Yemen; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174596","174596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973204","2018-10-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what negotiations have taken place for the selection of training facilities for urban sports ahead of the 2020 Tokyo Olympics.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174728","174728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973205","2018-10-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the timetable is for the announcement of the preferred training facilities for Team GB ahead of the 2020 Tokyo Olympics.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174729","174729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973206","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 September 2018 to Question 168118 on Prisons: Construction, what analysis his Department has conducted on the potential financial savings to the public purse from not allowing HM Prison and Probation Service to submit a bid to run the new prison at Wellingborough.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174799","174799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973207","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 September 2018 to Question 168118 on Prisons: Construction, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure (a) transparency and (b) public confidence in the comparison process between the public sector benchmark and bids from private sector operators.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174800","174800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973208","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 September 2018 to Question 168118 on Prisons: Construction, what processes his Department plans to put in place to assess the robustness of the public-sector benchmark against which private-sector bids will be compared.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174801","174801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973209","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of additional GPs that will be needed in (a) Merseyside and (b) Wirral by 2020.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174630","174630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973210","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the number of GP's has been in (a) the North West, (b) Merseyside, (c) Wirral and (d) Wallasey constituency in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174631","174631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973211","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2018 to Question 171296 on Merseyside Fire and Rescue Service, how much core spending power Merseyside Fire and Rescue Authority has received in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174632","174632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973212","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) all pupils and (b) pupils from disadvantaged backgrounds in (i) The North West (ii) Merseyside and (iii) Wallasey Constituency entered university in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174633","174633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973213","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2018 to Question 171297 on Cervical Cancer: Screening, what steps he is taking to increase take-up of cervical screening in the North West.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174634","174634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973214","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the level of Government funding for the Citizens Advice Service in (a) Wirral and (b) Merseyside was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174635","174635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973215","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what comparative estimate he has made of the number of mental health staff employed in the NHS in Wirral (a) 2010 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174636","174636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973216","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of foster carers in (a) Merseyside and (b) Wirral in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174637","174637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973217","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase the number of foster carers in Merseyside.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174638","174638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973218","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support micro-enterprises in Wallasey constituency.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174639","174639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973219","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support small business growth in (a) Merseyside and (b) Wirral.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174640","174640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973220","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from self-employed people on the potential extension of IR35 off-payroll tax to the private sector; and what proportion of those representations have been critical of that potential change.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174787","174787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973221","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate has been made of the potential annual savings that will accrue to Network Rail after the sale of its property portfolio to Telereal Trillium and Blackstone Property Partners.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174778","174778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973222","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an assessment of the effectiveness of section 6 of the Health and Safety at Work Act 1974 as it applies to medical devices containing computers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174600","174600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973223","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason his call for evidence on last-mile deliveries excludes HGVs.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174779","174779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973224","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the introduction of range-extended, dual-fuelled HGVs to reduce last-mile emissions in urban environments.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174780","174780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973225","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish his Department’s response to the consultation, Strengthening consumer redress in housing, which closed on 16 April 2018.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174769","174769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973226","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households occupied by at least one person over 75 were in receipt of a free television licence by constituency in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174647","174647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973227","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport,  what steps the Government is taking to encourage traffic enforcement teams to check with the DVLA vehicle enquiry service before issuing penalty notices in order to avoid problems caused by potential vehicle license plate cloning.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174783","174783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973228","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will outline the scope of the consultation exercise to be undertaken in preparation for the forthcoming alcohol strategy.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174683","174683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973229","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required to work at the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency to cover work related to the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174684","174684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973230","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the additional staff required to issue and check International Driver Permits for drivers entering the UK from the EU member states after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174685","174685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973231","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government plans to introduce a combined form to enable people to notify the DVLA of a change of address for both driving licence and registered vehicle keeper.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174784","174784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973232","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many International Driver Permits have been issued to EU drivers and haulage companies in preparation for the UK leaving the EU to date.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174686","174686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973233","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September to Question 169517, how much his Department has spent on contracted security personnel to assist with the processing of tribunal cases in Scotland in the last five years.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174771","174771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973234","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of International Driver Permit checks that will be required for drivers who do not hold UK driving licenses who enter the UK from the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174687","174687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973235","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether drivers of goods vehicles who hold UK driving licenses will be required to purchase an International Driving Permit to travel to EU member states after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174688","174688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973236","2018-10-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the announcement, Government invests £5m to increase places for disadvantaged children in youth organisations, published on 10 September 2018, to which areas he plans to distribute that funding; and whether he has plans to allocate funding from that fund to Wakefield.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174651","174651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973237","2018-10-09","Department for International Trade","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to strengthen the collaboration between UK and Israeli companies in the medical sector.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174724","174724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973238","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on which dates in 2018 (a) Ministers and (b) officials met with Irish counterparts to discuss the Voisinage Agreement.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174646","174646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973239","2018-10-09","Department for International Trade","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussion he has had with his Chinese counterpart on the export of goods and services from Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174725","174725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973240","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many meetings of the NHS Property Board (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have attended in 2018 to date.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174755","174755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973241","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the (a) agendas and (b) attendance records of the NHS Property Board.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174756","174756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973242","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the NHS Property Board will be making a submission to the development of the long-term plan for the NHS.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174757","174757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973243","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174822","174822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973244","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS Property Services will be making a submission to the development of the long term plan for the NHS.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174758","174758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973245","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether Community Health Partnerships will be making a submission to the development of the long-term plan for the NHS.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174759","174759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973246","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174823","174823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973247","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many wholly-owned companies formed by (a) NHS Trusts and (b) NHS Foundation Trusts pay staff below the Living Wage.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174760","174760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973248","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many wholly-owned companies formed by (a) NHS Trusts and (b) NHS Foundation Trusts operate (i) bonus schemes and (ii) other financial incentives schemes for their senior staff.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174761","174761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973249","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the approval criteria for applications for NHS bodies to form wholly-owned companies will be applied retrospectively.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174762","174762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973250","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what consultation his Department is planning ahead of making a decision on the distribution of dividends from NHS LIFT Companies.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174763","174763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973251","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to respond to the July 2018 report of the National Infrastructure Commission’s entitled National Infrastructure Assessment.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174781","174781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973252","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has issued on how dividends from NHS LIFT Companies should be spent.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174764","174764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973253","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174824","174824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973254","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made on aligning the staff, roles and responsibilities of NHS Property Services and Community Health Partnerships into a regional structure alongside NHS England and NHS Improvement.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174765","174765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973255","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how may staff (a) are employed directly by, (b) are seconded to and (c) work under contract to her Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174825","174825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973256","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many Strategic Transformation Partnerships have developed and agreed a local strategic estates strategy.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174766","174766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973257","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff in her Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174826","174826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973258","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many Strategic Transformation Partnerships' local estates strategies have been published.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174767","174767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973259","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff in her Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174827","174827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973260","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in her Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174828","174828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973261","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how may staff (a) are employed directly by (b) are seconded to and (c) work under contract to her Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174829","174829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973262","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of the roll-out of universal credit on women on maternity leave.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174726","174726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973263","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has provided on the requirement for consultation on the development of Strategic Transformation Partnerships' local estate strategies.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174768","174768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973264","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Government plans to complete its evidence gathering on the issue of pavement parking including how it is addressed in legislation.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174649","174649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973265","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of addressing period poverty on achieving Sustainable Development Goal number four on inclusive and equitable quality education and lifelong learning opportunities for all.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174833","174833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973266","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the annual rental income was in each financial year since 2010-11 for the Network Rail properties due to be sold to Telereal Trillium and Blackstone Property Partners.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174782","174782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973267","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 March 2018 to Question 133707 on parking: pedestrian areas, when his Department will publish its conclusions from its work on pavement parking including how it is addressed in current regulation.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174650","174650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973268","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the Crossrail 2 independent affordability review.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174657","174657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973270","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the supply of Choline C-11 injection to meet the demand for PET scans for people with prostate cancer.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174834","174834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973271","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will extend the Govia Thameslink Railway additional industry compensation scheme to cover all part-time workers who travel on a regular basis; for what reasons that scheme covers only part-time workers who commute three days a week; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174673","174673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973272","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many practising GPs there were in (a) Jarrow constituency and (b) South Tyneside in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174641","174641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973273","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people in (a) Jarrow constituency and (b) South Tyneside have access to an adequate number of GP surgeries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174642","174642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973274","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time to see a GP in (a) Jarrow constituency, and (b) South Tyneside, (c) Tyne and Wear, (d) the North East and (e) England was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174643","174643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973275","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to Question 167956 asked on 24 July 2018, when his Department plans to answer that Question; and for what reasons that Question has not yet been answered.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174674","174674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973276","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons pavement parking is permitted outside London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174717","174717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973277","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many staff in his department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174802","174802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973278","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174803","174803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973279","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174804","174804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973280","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174805","174805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973281","2018-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174806","174806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973282","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174807","174807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973283","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174808","174808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973284","2018-10-09","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many staff in her Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174809","174809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973285","2018-10-09","Scotland Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174810","174810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973286","2018-10-09","Wales Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174811","174811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973287","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174812","174812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973288","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174813","174813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973289","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174814","174814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973290","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174815","174815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973291","2018-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174816","174816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973292","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174817","174817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973293","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174818","174818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973294","2018-10-09","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in her Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174819","174819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973295","2018-10-09","Scotland Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174820","174820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973296","2018-10-09","Wales Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174821","174821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973297","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Government's Drugs Taskforce on improving the safety and healthcare of prisoners.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174648","174648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973298","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 135248 on Nurses: Training, what the planned publication date is of that update.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174675","174675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973299","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 May 2018 to Question 139598, what steps he has taken to improve the availability of safe, secure and appropriate parking facilities for heavy goods vehicles in terms of (a) planning, (b) the role of Highways England (c) setting standards for lorry parking facilities and (d) tackling illegal parking.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174835","174835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973300","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 135422, when his Department plans to publish the information commissioned from UCAS on the number of applicants for university nursing courses in the 2018 undergraduate cycle by (a) by field of nursing and (b) English region.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174676","174676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973301","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his Department's policy is on business improvement districts using local authorities as debt enforcers to collect levies from council-owned services.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174789","174789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973302","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the (a) cost to and (b) liabilities on the public purse of developing a UK alternative to the Galileo satellite navigation system.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174709","174709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973303","2018-10-09","Cabinet Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2017 to Question 106493 on Cybercrime: USA, whether the National Cyber Security Centre plans to publish the outcome of its pilot; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174710","174710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973304","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to develop algorithms to assist in police investigations.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174711","174711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973305","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions his Department has had with the EU on the EU classification of sanitary items for VAT purposes.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174836","174836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973306","2018-10-09","Department for International Trade","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a human trafficking-risk index to support a sustainable trade policy that removes modern-day slavery practices from global supply chains; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174712","174712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973307","2018-10-09","Department for International Trade","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the level of trade with and procurement from Commonwealth nations of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174713","174713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973308","2018-10-09","Department for International Trade","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to promote trade relations between the UK and Liberia.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174714","174714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973309","2018-10-09","Department for International Trade","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many trade delegations there have been to Liberia in the last five years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174715","174715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973310","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the oversight of business improvement districts; and what recourse is available to individuals who wish to object to debt enforcement conducted by business improvement districts.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174790","174790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973311","2018-10-09","Department for International Trade","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many and what proportion of international trade delegations to the UK have visited the North East in the last year.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174716","174716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973312","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the guidance, Upholding environmental standards if there’s no Brexit deal, published on 13 September 2018, when he plans to publish the interim measures that may be necessary in a no deal scenario.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174677","174677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973313","2018-10-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on the classification of sanitary items for VAT purposes within the context of the EU withdrawal negotiations.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174837","174837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973314","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2018 to Question 145529 on affordable housing: construction, what estimate he has made of how many fewer homes will be delivered in the short-term; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174678","174678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973315","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) guarantees and (b) protections have been put in place to ensure that the Woodchester Badger Project is not adversely affected by the further roll-out of badger culling in Gloucestershire.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174605","174605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973316","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to provide hon. Members with (a) the location of and (b) information and guidance on proposed badger culls in their constituencies.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174606","174606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973317","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 165490 on Eating Disorders, if he will make it his policy to introduce waiting time targets for adults with eating disorders.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174679","174679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973318","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on incidences of companies sending unsold clothes to (a) landfill and (b) incineration.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174607","174607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973319","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to respond to the research report, Evaluation of the first year of the national roll-out of 30 hours free childcare, commissioned by his Department and published on 11 September 2018.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174791","174791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973320","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will direct the Environment Agency undertake an investigation of compliance with the Waste Hierarchy in relation to companies sending (a) unsold clothes and (b) other non-perishable goods to (i) landfill and (ii) incineration; and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174608","174608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973321","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the resources allocated to the Environment Agency to enforce (a) the Waste Hierarchy and (b) Part 5 and Regulation 25 of the Waste (England and Wales) Regulations 2011.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174609","174609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973322","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the release of dioxins by waste incineration sites on people's health.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174610","174610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973323","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effect of emissions of oxides of nitrogen from waste incineration sites on the health of people living within (a) half a kilometre, (b) one kilometre and (c) two and a half kilometres of such sites.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174611","174611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973324","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of services on the London Overground Barking-Gospel Oak line.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174597","174597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973325","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the availability of new trains on the London Overground Barking-Gospel Oak line, if he will direct Angel Trains to defer the transfer to West Midlands Trains of seven diesel trains currently subleased to Arriva Rail London.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174598","174598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973326","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, he will direct Angel Trains to return to Arriva Rail London the diesel train previously sub-leased to that company for use on the Barking to Gospel Oak line until new electric trains are brought into service on that line.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174599","174599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973327","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department's policy is on the safe limit for public health of inhalation of (a) PM 0.1, (b) PM1 and (c) PM2.5.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174612","174612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973328","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the wind speed required to disperse (a) PM 0.1, (b) PM 1 and (c) PM2.5 particles.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174613","174613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973329","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many horses were slaughtered in abattoirs in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017; and how many of those horses carried passports issued by Weatherbys.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174614","174614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973330","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many times officials in (a) his Department and (b) other Government Departments have met with the British Horseracing Authority in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018 to date to discuss horse deaths on racecourses.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174615","174615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973331","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has requested from the British Horseracing Authority (a) information on racehorse deaths, (b) reviews by that authority of racecourses with unusually high mortality rates and (c) information relating to the number of racehorses killed in training.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174616","174616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973332","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of bringing the new Royal Liverpool hospital into public ownership.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174838","174838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973333","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working in (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the (A) national and (B) London living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174680","174680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973334","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether it is his policy to commence section 43 of the Deregulation Act 2015.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174592","174592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973335","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether local authorities are legally empowered to set higher energy efficiency standards than those required by building regulations.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174593","174593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973336","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 25 March 2015 on Planning Update, HCWS488, whether it is his Department's policy that local authorities will continue to be able to set and apply policies in their local plans which require compliance with energy performance standards that exceed the energy requirements of Building Regulations.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174594","174594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973337","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether local authorities can set energy efficiency standards higher than Level 4 of the former Code for Sustainable Homes.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174595","174595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973338","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) doctors and (b) dentists have died by suicide in each of the last five years; what the average age of such doctors and dentists was when they died; and whether he has plans to create a national service to help health professionals suffering from mental illnesses.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Sir Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174590","174590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973339","2018-10-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the financial liabilities the UK would have to accept in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Sir Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174591","174591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973340","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many (a) businesses have used the Small Business Commissioner's website to resolve late payment disputes, (b) late payment cases have been resolved and (c) large companies have changed their payment practices as a result of the intervention of the Commissioner.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174700","174700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973341","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress his Department has made on strengthening the Prompt Payment Code; and whether he plans to include in the Code a (a) formal accreditation and (b) revalidation process.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174701","174701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973342","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many complaints his Department has received from suppliers dissatisfied with the late payment practices of companies that have signed up to the Prompt Payment Code.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174702","174702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973343","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to encourage businesses to become signatories to the Prompt Payment Code.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174703","174703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973344","2018-10-09","Cabinet Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Minister of the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure that all Government suppliers are signatories of the Prompt Payment Code.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174704","174704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973345","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many forfeitures of residential leaseholds have taken place following the serving of a section 146 notice of the Law and Property Act 1925 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174792","174792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973346","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many of the seven contracts for Genomics Laboratory Hubs with Additional Specialised Services have been awarded; and how many of the seven hubs will be fully operational on the scheduled date of 1 October 2018.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174730","174730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973347","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the efficacy of the Independent Case Examiner  in investigating complaints from women affected by state pension age equalisation measures.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174839","174839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973348","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the 70 individuals on board the charter flight bound for Nigeria and Ghana on 28 March 2017 which was prevented by protesters from leaving Stansted airport (a) have been referred under the National Referral Mechanism for the identification of victims of trafficking, (b) have since been granted leave to remain in the UK and (c) were a member of the Windrush generation.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174681","174681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973349","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 July 2018 to Question 159639 on Help to Buy Scheme, what the total amount of money loaned was in relation to the 3,905 equity loans taken out on leasehold properties.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174731","174731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973350","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the Independent Case Examiner's progress in dealing with complaints made by women affected by the state pension age equalisation measures.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174840","174840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973351","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total value is of refunds paid in each category of Stamp Duty in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174732","174732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973352","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of her Department's programmes in the Democratic Republic of Congo in the last three years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174733","174733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973353","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which organisations her Department allocates funding to for programmes in the Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174734","174734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973354","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which three programmes in the Democratic Republic of Congo receive the largest amount of funding from her Department.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174735","174735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973355","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps has she taken to assess the value for money of aid spending in the Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174736","174736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973356","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of granting all survivors of modern slavery rights to education through the National Referral Mechanism.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174830","174830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973357","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2018 to Question 162093 on Individual Savings Accounts, whether the data for the first quarter of 2018-19 is available for publication.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174737","174737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973358","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his answer of 16 July 2018 to Question 162084 Retail Trade: Ellesmere Port and Neston, how much of that £201.1 million is planned to be spent in Ellesmere Port & Neston Constituency.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174738","174738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973359","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his Answer of 18 July 2018 to Question 163133 on Work Experience: Pay, what the timetable is for the public guidance to be updated.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174739","174739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973360","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his answer of 18 July 2018 to Question 163805 on Industrial Disputes: Ballots, when that meeting is planned to take place; and who the invitees will be.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174740","174740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973361","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who pay both the employer and employee auto-enrolment pension contribution.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174741","174741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973362","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people who pay both the employer and employee National Insurance contribution.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174742","174742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973363","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the average tenure is of a cyber specialist working at (a) GCHQ and (b) the National Cyber Security Centre.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174841","174841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973364","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's guidance entitled Teacher appraisal and capability: A model policy, published on 22 May 2012, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that teachers' appraisals are carried out in accordance with the criteria set down in that guidance.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174707","174707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973365","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an estimate of the number of people employed by umbrella companies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174743","174743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973366","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the number of self-employment among workers aged 65 and above.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174744","174744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973367","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the number of self-employed people (a) with and (b) without employees.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174745","174745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973368","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential value to the UK economy of achieving a better gender balance on company boards.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174746","174746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973369","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions his Department has had with trade unions on reducing staff turnover.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174747","174747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973370","2018-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations he has received from the East of England Ambulance Service on the potential use of military personnel to cover staff shortages in winter 2018-19.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174748","174748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973371","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has received from the East of England Ambulance Service on the potential use of military personnel to cover staff shortages in winter 2018-19.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174749","174749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973372","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's publication entitled 30 hours free childcare: evaluation of the national rollout, published on 11 September 2018, support his Department plans to provide the 39 per cent of childcare providers who took part in the evaluation and reported a reduction in their profit or surplus due to the extended hours.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174793","174793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973373","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what provisions will be made to safeguard the rights of victims undergoing cross-examination as part of the Government's Victim's Strategy, published in September 2018, Cm. 9700 .","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174658","174658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973374","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what provisions will be made under the Government's Victim's strategy, published in September 2018, Cm. 9700 to support the mental health of victims.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174659","174659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973375","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Government plans to establish an Independent Violence Advocate as part of the Victim's Strategy, published in September 2018, Cm. 9700.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174660","174660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973376","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to publish full details of the Government's review into the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174661","174661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973377","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Care Quality Commission's report, Sexual safety on mental health wards, published in September 2018, what plans he has to make additional funding available for Mental Health Trusts to train the workforce in safeguarding patients from sexual incidents in the ward setting.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174696","174696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973378","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's publication, Evaluation of the first year of the national rollout of 30 hours free childcare, published in September 2018, whether he plans to provide additional funding to ensure that childcare providers do not suffer a loss in profit or report that they are only breaking even as a result of offering extended hours of childcare.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174794","174794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973379","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timescale is for the Government's review into the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174662","174662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973380","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Care Quality Commission's report, Sexual safety on mental health wards, published in September 2018, whether he plans to make additional funding available for Mental Health Trusts to promote joint-working between providers and other agencies such as the police.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174697","174697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973381","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans his Department has to grant local authorities more (a) flexibility and (b) powers in overseeing how and where asylum seekers are housed in their areas.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174682","174682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973382","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking in response to the Independent Monitoring Board report on HMP Parc.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174698","174698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973383","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timetable is for the consultation on the victims' law.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174663","174663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973384","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for how long the consultation on the victims' law will be open.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174664","174664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973385","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on the conclusions on mental health funding of the Independent Monitoring Board on HMP Parc.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174699","174699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973386","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timetable for the consultation process on establishing an independent public advocate is.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174665","174665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973387","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that 30 hours free childcare is (a) flexible and (b) free of additional charges for those who are eligible.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174795","174795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973388","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the £8 million spending increase for sexual assault referral centres set out in the Victims' Strategy, published in September 2018, Cm. 9700, will come from existing budgets.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174666","174666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973389","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the additional £8 million set out in the Victims Strategy, published in September 2018, Cm. 9700, allocated to support children who witness domestic abuse will come from existing budgets.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174667","174667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973390","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Government plans to publish its response to its consultation on domestic abuse.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174668","174668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973391","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the proposed average payments to community pharmacies were in Hampstead and Kilburn constituency under the Pharmacy Access Scheme in (a) 2015-16 (b)2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174796","174796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973392","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 23 of the Victims Strategy, published in September 2018, Cm. 9700, whether the spending commitment of £18.8m on domestic abuse accommodation services will come from existing budgets.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174669","174669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973393","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the overall cost is of spending commitments pledged in the Government's Victim's Strategy, published in September 2018, Cm. 9700.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174670","174670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973394","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the spending commitments pledged in the Government's Victim's Strategy, published in September 2018, Cm. 9700 will come from existing budgets.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174671","174671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973395","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2018 to Question 169126 on A14: road works, what estimate he has made of the delay to work on that road as a result of the archaeological work; and what estimate he has made of the cost of that delay.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Djanogly","Mr Jonathan Djanogly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174644","174644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973396","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the balance between sustainability and productivity in UK farming.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174831","174831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973397","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many former Carillion apprentices have been made redundant in (a) Barnsley and (b) South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174832","174832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973398","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the NHS budget has been spent on prevention of ill health in (a) 2009-10 (b) 2014-2015 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174797","174797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973399","2018-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces recruitment centres there were in the North East of England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174689","174689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973400","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children and young people have been admitted to accident and emergency in hospitals in London because of mental illness in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174798","174798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973401","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants there are in the Garston and Halewood constituency.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174622","174622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973402","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will estimate the number of households in Garston and Halewood constituency that will be migrated from legacy benefits to universal credit after its introduction at the end of 2018.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174623","174623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973403","2018-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of people from the North East of England who have enlisted in the (a) Army, (b) Royal Air Force and (c) Royal Navy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174690","174690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973404","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the amount given in budgetary advances to claimants awaiting their first universal credit payment is calculated.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174624","174624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973405","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how exceptional circumstances is defined when determining whether a universal credit claimant in receipt of a budgetary advance is eligible for the three month discretionary period after the first universal credit payment before repayments of the advance begin.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174625","174625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973406","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of (a) legacy benefits, (b) personal independence payments and (c) universal credit in the Garston and Halewood constituency have been given a budgetary advance to cover a delay in payment of their benefit in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174626","174626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973407","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure claimants of universal credit who receive a salary advance in December to cover the costs of Christmas do not have their eligibility for universal credit reduced as a result.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174627","174627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973408","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals in response to the tackling unfair lease practices in the leasehold market consultation.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174628","174628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973409","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the (a) Iraqi Government and (b) Kurdistan Regional Government on the effect of territorial disputes on reconstruction efforts in the Nineveh Plains.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174691","174691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973410","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the safety and security of internally displaced persons returning from the Kurdistan Region of Iraq to the Nineveh Plains.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174692","174692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973411","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance the UK is providing to livelihood creation for (a) internally displaced persons in the Kurdistan Region of Iraq and (b) Internally Displaced Persons returning from the Kurdistan Region of Iraq to the Nineveh Plains.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174693","174693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973412","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the use of funds allocated for mental health treatment by NHS Trusts and Clinical Commissioning Groups; and what steps his Department takes to ensure that such Trusts and Groups use such funds efficiently and effectively.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174694","174694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973413","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of increasing the number of registered intermediaries as set out in the Victims Strategy, published in September 2018, Cm. 9700.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174672","174672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972270","2018-09-12","Cabinet Office","2018-09-12","What steps the Government is taking to review the effectiveness of the civil service.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906839","906839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972271","2018-09-12","Cabinet Office","2018-09-12","What estimate he has made of the proportion of public procurement spending on digital and technology services placed with small and medium-sized enterprises in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Caroline Johnson","Dr Caroline Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906840","906840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972272","2018-09-12","Cabinet Office","2018-09-12","What recent estimate he has made of the number of eligible voters not on the electoral register.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906841","906841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972289","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to make available on the NHS the drug BAN2401 for the prevention of Alzheimers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174056","174056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972290","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of local authorities that have overspent on funding for community resource centres.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173952","173952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972291","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on the potential effect of legalising cannabis-oil medicines on the availability of cannabis as a gateway drug for social use.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173953","173953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972292","2018-10-09","House of Commons Commission","2018-09-12","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, whether the Commission has had discussions with the Minister for Women and Equalities on increasing the proportion of women employed as parliamentary researchers by hon. Members.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173954","173954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972293","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education,  how many pupils enrolled in the GCSE Citizenship course in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England in 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173955","173955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972294","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on funding for the protection on green spaces in Coventry from damage caused by grass fires during the the summer of 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173956","173956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972295","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to review the licensing of glyphosate herbicides.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173950","173950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972296","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Article 2 of Directive 2006/126/EC10, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on EU recognition of UK driving licences of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173935","173935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972297","2018-10-09","Cabinet Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the potential cost to the public purse of removing the 15-year time limit on the right of British citizens living overseas to vote in UK parliamentary elections.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173936","173936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972298","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government plans to maintain the current level of funding for the UN Relief and Works Agency in the next departmental spending review for her Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173937","173937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972299","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the US Government on its decision to withdraw funding from the UN Relief and Works Agency.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173938","173938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972300","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the letters sent to British pensioners residing in France by Caisse Nationale de l'Assurance Maladie informing them that their access to French healthcare system ends on 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173939","173939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972301","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to seek to ensure the continuity of British citizens’ entitlement to health care in EU Member States via form S1 in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173940","173940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972302","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to ensure that UK citizens residing in the EU continue to receive healthcare coverage in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173941","173941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972303","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government plans to cover the cost of health insurance for UK citizens living in the EU in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173942","173942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972304","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Border Force takes steps to seize bladed articles imported to the UK for delivery to a person under 18; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173944","173944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972305","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his US counterpart on that country's recent announcements on the International Criminal Court.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174138","174138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972306","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the increase in the attainment gap between white boys eligible for free school meals and white boys not eligible for free school meals from 31 to 33 percentage points between 2015 and 2017; which schools have countered that trend; and what steps are being taken to disseminate their practice.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173986","173986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972307","2018-10-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff who transferred into his Department were promoted to a higher grade upon their transfer; and how many have since transferred out of his Department at that higher grade.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173943","173943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972308","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 4 September 2018 on Pensions Update, HCWS933, what role industry will have in the delivery of the pensions dashboard; whether the Government plans to fund that dashboard; and how the Government plans to facilitate the delivery of that dashboard.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173951","173951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972309","2018-10-09","Cabinet Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Census (Amendment) Bill before the Scottish Parliament, whether he has plans to include in the 2021 Census White Paper, proposals to include questions on (a) sexual orientation and (b) transgender status for England and Wales.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174064","174064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972310","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff are employed in the office of (a) Ministers of his Department and (b) the Permanent Secretary.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174065","174065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972311","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy schools were waiting to be re-brokered at 1 September 2018.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174066","174066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972312","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the efficacy of the financial management of Bright Tribe Academy Trust.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174163","174163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972313","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 September 2018 to Question 170788 on Schools: Fees and Charges, what information his Department holds on the use of the pupil premium by schools to support children from low-income families.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174029","174029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972314","2018-10-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2018 to Question 167995 on Football: Females, how much and what proportion of that funding was allocated to programmes in Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174030","174030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972315","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to section 3.8, page 28 of Oil and Gas UK’s Economic Report 2018, published on 11 September 2018, what steps he is taking to encourage an increase in drilling activity on the UK Continental Shelf for oil and gas reserves that are more expensive to extract.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174031","174031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972316","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many (a) subsea and (b) platform wells were decommissioned on the UK Continental Shelf in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174032","174032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972317","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS Digital General and Personal Medical Services workforce data,  for what reason the number of patients per FTE GP has increased in Easington constituency since March 2016.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174033","174033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972318","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Growth Hubs in supporting women in the East Midlands who want to (a) start and (b) grow a business.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174150","174150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972319","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to increase public awareness of the symptoms of (a) lung cancer and (b) respiratory conditions.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174151","174151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972320","2018-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department and its agencies have taken to support the National Pollinator Strategy on Ministry of Defence-owned land.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174152","174152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972321","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate she has made of the number of children living in workless households in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174153","174153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972322","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support his Department provides to adults without a level 2 qualification in (a) English and (b) maths to allow them to undertake further study.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174154","174154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972323","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department has allocated from the Youth Opportunities Fund to projects in Nottinghamshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174155","174155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972324","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions there have been for motor vehicle theft in the Nottinghamshire area in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174156","174156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972325","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding from the Flexible Learning Fund has been allocated to projects in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174157","174157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972326","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the lease on the office block accommodating the Hamilton Job Centre expires; and whether her Department plans to renew that lease.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174075","174075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972327","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost of deploying detached duty public sector staff at HMP Birmingham in the next six months; and who will be responsible for paying that cost.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174052","174052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972328","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff from each prison establishment he plans to require to be deployed on detached duty at HMP Birmingham in each of the next six months.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174053","174053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972329","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff of each grade were employed at HMP Birmingham on 31 March 2010; and how many equivalent staff of each grade were employed at that prison on 20 August 2018.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174054","174054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972330","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the prison population of HMP Birmingham has been in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174055","174055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972331","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 10 September 2018 to Question 170891, what steps she plans to take to  assess whether the measures announced by the Prime Minister to increase the impact and effectiveness of UK aid across Africa deliver against expectations in the short and medium-term.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174132","174132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972332","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 10 September 2018 to Question 169665 on development aid, how much of the £3,736 million is spent in each broad sector.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174133","174133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972333","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 10 September 2018 to Question 169664 on developing countries: overseas trade, what assessment her Department has made of how many and which countries have the right resources.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174134","174134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972334","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the study by the International Finance Corporation and the UN Refugee Agency on Kakuma Refugee Camp, Kenya, published on 4 May 2018, what assessment her Department has made of the economic gains to host communities if refugees are able to work.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174135","174135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972335","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support long-term internally displaced people.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174136","174136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972336","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of vacancies in the West Midlands for (a) permanent and (b) temporary positions.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174137","174137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972337","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many days (a) Northern and (b) Transpennine Express have achieved their performance targets since the start of its franchise in April 2016.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174046","174046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972338","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of Universities UK on the UK’s post-study work system for international students have completed their study at a UK university.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173987","173987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972339","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to publish the review into the Emergency Services Network.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174139","174139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972340","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans for the Emergency Services Network to be fully operational.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174140","174140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972341","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to prevent young people from committing anti-social behaviour.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174015","174015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972342","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for the roll-out individual of components of the Emergency Services Network to police forces.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174141","174141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972343","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people charged with burglary in each of the last three years have been (a) convicted and (b) given a jail sentence.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174016","174016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972344","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers have taken more than two weeks of sick leave as a result of injuries that occurred at work.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174017","174017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972345","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) male and (b) female police officers were employed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174018","174018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972346","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police stations have closed in each of the last four years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174019","174019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972347","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many social houses have been purchased by the tenants of those homes in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174020","174020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972348","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many people are on the waiting list for social housing; and what steps he is taking to reduce the waiting time for social housing.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174021","174021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972349","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department has allocated for the building of new social housing.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174022","174022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972350","2018-10-09","Cabinet Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the commitments made by the UK at the Anti-Corruption Summit 2016, when the Crown Commercial Service plans to introduce a new check to prevent corrupt bidders winning public contracts.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174038","174038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972351","2018-10-09","Cabinet Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the commitments made by the UK Government at the Anti-Corruption Summit 2016, how an additional conviction check at the Crown Commercial Service will complement existing checks on convictions.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174039","174039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972352","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has a policy on helping students with children to study at university while providing childcare support.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174023","174023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972353","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on ensuring that UK students have opportunities to attend universities abroad for a year through (a) the Erasmas Programme and (b) other programmes once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174024","174024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972354","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the front-line policing review will consider (a) pay and (b) police officer numbers.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174078","174078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972355","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been allocated for new school builds and extensions in the next two years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174025","174025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972356","2018-10-09","Cabinet Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to require bidders to declare (a) convictions under Section 7 of the Bribery Act 2010 and (b) similar additional information in pre-contract questionnaires.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174040","174040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972357","2018-10-09","Cabinet Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the UK has excluded a company from public procurement for reasons of corruption.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174041","174041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972358","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timescale is for the introduction of student bus passes in the academic year 2018-19.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174026","174026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972359","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the (a) adequacy of supply and (b) demand for bleeding control packs in designated public places.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174079","174079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972360","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the resources provided to police forces over the last three years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174080","174080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972361","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the resources available to the police.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174081","174081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972362","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has held discussions with (a) the NPCC, (b) the National Police Co-ordination Centre and (c) other senior police leaders on the additional resources that will be required by those organisations to prepare for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174082","174082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972363","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to improve support for people who sleep rough who are non-UK nationals.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174047","174047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972364","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of affordable homes that are built in the UK.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174048","174048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972365","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of Support for Mortgage Interest before April 2018 continue to receive that benefit.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174049","174049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972366","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time is for a Support for Mortgage Interest payment to be transferred to a loan.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174050","174050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972367","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the proportion of his Department's appeals against immigration rulings which are refused; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174051","174051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972368","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many meetings of the Serious Violence Taskforce he has chaired between 30 April 2018 and 12 September 2018.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174083","174083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972369","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average processing time is for DS1500 forms for new claims for (a) universal credit, (b) personal independence payments, (c) disability living allowance, (d) employment and support allowance and (e) attendance allowance in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174071","174071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972370","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to host an International Violent Crime Symposium.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174084","174084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972371","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average processing time is for DS1500 forms for existing claims for (a) universal credit, (b) personal independence payments, (c) disability living allowance, (d) employment and support allowance and (e) attendance allowance in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174072","174072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972372","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many DS1500 forms have been processed within targets set for (a) universal credit, (b) personal independence payments, (c) disability living allowance, (d) employment and support allowance and (e) attendance allowance in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174073","174073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972373","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department will assess the potential merits of allowing personal independence payment claimants claiming under terminal illness rules to continue receiving their claim following a stay of longer than 28 days in hospital as is the case for stays of longer than 28 days in hospices.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174074","174074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972374","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many meetings he had with the Chief Constable of the Police Service Northern Ireland between 30 April 2018 and 12 September 2018 to discuss the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174085","174085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972375","2018-10-09","Attorney General","2018-09-12","To ask the Attorney General, whether the CPS plans to establish a central database of regulatory and enforcement actions taken against companies.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174042","174042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972376","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients under the age of (a) 25 and (b) 16 have been referred out of the area for mental health treatment in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174148","174148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972377","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time is for a mental health bed in Yorkshire and the Humber in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174149","174149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972378","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many child maintenance claimants her Department has supported to provide non-geographic bank account details to the paying parent in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174076","174076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972379","2018-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 24 July 2018, Ministry of Defence - Update, HCWS 909, when his Department was first aware that military personnel would be unable to receive their 0.9 per cent non-consolidated one-off payment as a result of issues with the online payroll system.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173998","173998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972380","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS Improvement, Performance of the NHS provider sector for the quarter ended 30 June 2018, what the underlying gross deficit was reported by trusts for the provider sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174063","174063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972381","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Government of Israel following the Israel Supreme Court’s decision to reject an appeal on the demolition of the village of Khan al-Ahmar.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174145","174145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972382","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the number of people who are (a) killed and (b) injured by motorists who are over the legal limit of alcohol.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174057","174057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972383","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 19 January 2018 on Welfare, HCWS414, how many of the 1.6 million personal independence payment cases have been reviewed by her Department to date.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174060","174060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972384","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2018 to Question 125505 on Personal Independence Payment: Mental Health, what recent assessment she has made of the administrative costs to her Department of reviewing the 1.6 million personal independence payment claims.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174061","174061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972385","2018-10-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many new starter homes have been built in (a) Wallasey and (b) Merseyside in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173988","173988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972386","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the pupil to teacher ratio was in primary schools in Wallasey constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173989","173989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972387","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the pupil to teacher ratio was in secondary schools in (a) Wallasey constituency and (b) East Hampshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173990","173990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972388","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students have studied at least two arts subjects at GCSE level in (a) Wallasey  and (b) East Hampshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173991","173991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972389","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many GCSE entries for arts subjects there were from students in Wallasey in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173992","173992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972390","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174112","174112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972391","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174113","174113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972392","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174114","174114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972393","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total number of staff (a) employed directly by (b) seconded to and (c) working under contract to his Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174115","174115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972394","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174116","174116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972395","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174117","174117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972396","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174118","174118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972397","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff (a) are employed directly by (b) are seconded to and (c) work under contract to his Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174119","174119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972398","2018-10-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174120","174120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972399","2018-10-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below  the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174121","174121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972400","2018-10-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174122","174122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972401","2018-10-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff (a) are employed directly by (b) are seconded to and (c) work under contract to his Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174123","174123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972402","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Iranian Government in relation to the recent missile attack on an Iranian Kurdish camp in Koya in the Kurdistan region in Iraq; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174034","174034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972403","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff in her Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174124","174124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972404","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff in her Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below  the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174125","174125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972405","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in her Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174126","174126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972406","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Secretary of State for Defence was consulted on the use of Manston Airport as part of the planning process under the Town and Country Planning (Operation Stack) Special Development Order 2015 and its subsequent amendments in 2016 and 2017; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the use of Manston Airport as a lorry park on its high resolution direction finding facility.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173928","173928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972407","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which body had responsibility for the investigation of military deaths in Scotland before the introduction of the Fatal Accident and Sudden Deaths (Scotland) Act 2016.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174142","174142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972408","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Government of Bahrain on the refusal by Jau prison authorities to allow political prisoner Hassan Mushaima access to (a) a diabetes specialist, (b) regular family visits and (c) books and personal notes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174027","174027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972409","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether officials of his Department have met Ali Mushaima to discuss making representations to the Government of Bahrain on the refusal by Jau prison authorities to allow political prisoner Hassan Mushaima access to (a) a diabetes specialist, (b) family visits and (c) books and personal notes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174028","174028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972410","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff (a) are employed directly by (b) are seconded to and (c) work under contract to his Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174127","174127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972411","2018-10-09","Department for International Trade","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174128","174128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972412","2018-10-09","Department for International Trade","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff in his Department that work (a) inside and (b) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174129","174129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972413","2018-10-09","Department for International Trade","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174130","174130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972414","2018-10-09","Department for International Trade","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff (a) are employed directly by (b) are seconded to and (c) work under contract to his Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174131","174131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972415","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the (a) overall amount and (b) proportion of tax revenue raised from the contributions of businesses with a turnover of £1 million or less in terms of (i) employer national insurance contributions, (ii) corporation tax, (iii) value added tax and (iv) business rates.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Sir Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173981","173981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972416","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 September 2018 to Question 168118, if he will publish the Estates and Transformation Team report.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174091","174091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972417","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference the announcement of £200 million of funding for the Women’s Integrated Sexual Health (WISH) programme, how much of that funding will be spent on abortion provision and related activities; which countries that spending will be targeted at; and what estimate she has made of how much will be spent in each such country.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173966","173966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972418","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that loans made to foreign governments under UK law by UK-based financial institutions are publicly disclosed when they are made.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174088","174088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972419","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the announcement of £200 million funding for the Women’s Integrated Sexual Health (WISH) programme, how many abortion procedures are projected to be funded by that project (a) in total and (b) in each country.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173967","173967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972420","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the announcement of £200 million funding for the Women’s Integrated Sexual Health (WISH) programme, which providers will deliver that project; and how much funding each of those providers will receive.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173968","173968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972421","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the announcement of £36 million of funding for family planning in Kenya, how much of that funding will be spent on abortion provision and related activities; and how many abortion procedures are estimated to be funded by that project.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173969","173969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972422","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2018 to Question 167122, what information her Department holds on the number of people who have been underpaid employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173971","173971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972423","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timescale is for resolving cases of underpayment of employment support allowance.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173972","173972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972424","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the Government plans to implement the Law Commission's recommendations with regard to Deprivation of Liberty Safeguards (DoLS) under the Mental Capacity Act 2005; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173948","173948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972425","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the representations in the East of England APPG Submission to Autumn Budget 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174068","174068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972426","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to respond to the Joint Committee on Human Rights' inquiry into Deprivation of Liberty Safeguards; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173949","173949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972427","2018-10-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he is taking to steps to increase the powers that Ofcom and the Phone-paid Services Authority have to prevent intermediaries charging people to use freephone Government services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174158","174158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972428","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his oral statement of 19 July 2018, Official Report, column 615 on Relationships and Sex Education, to which case law he was referring when he said that a right for parents to withdraw their child up to 18 years of age is no longer compatible with English case law or the European convention on human rights.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173970","173970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972429","2018-10-09","Department for International Development","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2018 to Question 167103 on Palestinians: ICT, what plans she has to promote the development of Palestinian IT firms and strengthen their capability to work with British businesses after the Palestinian Market Development Programme ceases in October 2019.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173929","173929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972430","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the (a) effectiveness of local authority health scrutiny committees and (b) ability of those committees to identify decisions and practices in the local health sector which have subsequently been changed.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174164","174164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972431","2018-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the conservation of the Spreading Bellflower.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174000","174000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972432","2018-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2018 to Question 158760 on Tornado aircraft: accidents, whether the GQ 5000 parachute was fitted as part of modification 2198 in 2007 and not 2010 as indicated in that answer.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174067","174067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972433","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how the risks of mobile applications are assessed by NHS Digital for inclusion in the NHS Apps Library.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174159","174159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972434","2018-10-09","Department for Transport","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to respond to the letters of 17 May 2018 and 3 July 2018 from the hon. Member for Clacton regarding infrastructure improvements in Essex.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174160","174160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972435","2018-10-09","Department for International Trade","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions he has had on trade and investment with the Government of China.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174161","174161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972436","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an assessment of the effectiveness of Growth Hubs in supporting women who want to start and grow a business; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174162","174162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972437","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff in his Department are classified as contingent labour.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173973","173973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972438","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many staff in his Department are classified as contingent labour.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173974","173974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972439","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff in his Department are classified as contingent labour.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173975","173975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972440","2018-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff in his Department are classified as contingent labour.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173976","173976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972441","2018-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many staff in his Department are classified as contingent labour.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173977","173977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972442","2018-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff in his Department are classified as contingent labour.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173978","173978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972443","2018-10-09","Cabinet Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff in his Department are classified as contingent labour.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173979","173979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972444","2018-10-09","Department for Education","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff in his Department are classified as contingent labour.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173980","173980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972445","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has published new guidance on the 10 yearly light touch review for  personal independence payment claimants with severe conditions.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174062","174062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972446","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the proportion of revenue to the Exchequer raised from businesses with (a) 0-9 employees, (b) 0-49 employees and (c) a turnover of £1 million or less.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Sir Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173982","173982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972447","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which (a) chief constables and (b) senior officers he met to discuss knife crime and serious violence between taking up his position and 12 September 2018.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174086","174086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972448","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of medication errors made each year in the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174058","174058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972449","2018-10-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the use of automated medicine cabinets on the level of deaths as a result of medication errors in the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174059","174059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972450","2018-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 24 July 2018 on Ministry of Defence -Update, HCWS909, when (a) his Department's online payroll system will process and (b) service personnel will receive the 0.9 per cent non-consolidated one-off payment.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173999","173999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972451","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) male and (b) female prisoners were recorded as having been a victim of domestic violence on the last date for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174009","174009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972452","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of (a) men and (b) women in prison were recorded as having been a perpetrator of domestic violence on the latest date for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174010","174010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972453","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offences were committed by offenders serving a community order in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174011","174011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972454","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2018 to Question 158711 on Prisoners' Release, which offence was committed in each of the cases of violence against the person and the case of sexual assault.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174012","174012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972455","2018-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders who breached their post-sentence supervision subsequently appeared before a court in the latest year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174013","174013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972456","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many recorded crimes relating to forced marriage there have been since 16 June 2014.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174014","174014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972457","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Figure 3 of the report, Financial sustainability of police forces 2018 published by the National Audit Office on 11 September 2018, if he will publish the reduction in real terms in £m for each police force.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174087","174087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972458","2018-10-09","Treasury","2018-09-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the contribution of the Prime Minister on 12 September 2018 during Prime Minister's Questions, when he plans to bring forward proposals on the funding for the increase in teachers' pay in Wales.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174143","174143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972460","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an estimate of the number of households in Greenwich and Woolwich constituency that will be migrated from legacy benefits to universal credit.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174089","174089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972461","2018-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when her Department undertook the most recent equality impact assessment of universal credit.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174090","174090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972462","2018-10-09","Home Office","2018-09-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the letter of 23 June 2018 from the hon. Member for Glasgow Central on the matter of a constituent, Habib Riaz.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174069","174069"
