"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61740","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the findings of Mental Health Foundation research into the impact of mindfulness-based interventions on the reduction in patient visits to the GP.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200425","200425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61741","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 10 June 2014, Official Report, column 896W, on hospitals, what progress his Department has made at Medway NHS Trust since it was placed in special measures in 2013.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200426","200426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61742","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answers given to the Rt hon. Member for Chelmsford of 4 March 2014, Official Report, columns 768-9W, on cancer: drugs, and to the hon. Member for Wells of 19 March 2014, Official Report, column 614W, on National Institute for Health Research, if he will place in the Library the data used to calculate those Answers.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200432","200432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61743","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training is provided to staff working within alcohol and drugs treatment in identifying and treating the problem of gambling addiction.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200541","200541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61744","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many financial bonuses of what amount have been paid to employees of Public Health England since April 2013; and on what criteria such bonuses were awarded.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200546","200546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61745","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Department is taking to improve healthcare outcomes by improving the awareness of gambling addiction on the part of healthcare professionals; and what guidance NHS England provides to local health authorities on the commissioning of services for gambling addiction.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200542","200542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61746","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the prevalence and effect of unlicensed performance enhancing drugs (a) online and (b) in shops.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200547","200547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61747","2014-06-17","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will carry out and publish a written risk assessment of the care.data programme; for what reason no such written risk assessment has been published; and which Minister in his Department took the decision not to publish such an assessment.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200563","200563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61748","2014-06-17","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adult cystic fibrosis patients were being cared for by specialist centres in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200612","200612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61749","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2014, Official Report, column 101W, on the human papillomavirus, when the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation will publish its conclusions into whether the human papillomavirus should be offered to males.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200577","200577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61750","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many parliamentary questions tabled to his Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200592","200592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61751","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with (a) NHS England and (b) Public Health England on improving treatment for gambling addicts.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200558","200558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61752","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of reports that scientists at the University of Wisconsin-Madison have created a life-threatening virus that closely resembles the 1918 Spanish flu strain; whether he has made an assessment of the potential threat to the UK population arising from that experiment; and whether the Government has made any representations to the US administration on this matter.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200589","200589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61753","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 8 May 2014, Official Report, column 288W, on Parkinson's Disease, over what timeframe NHS England will improve its collection of data concerning individual funding requests for treatments of progressive conditions.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200509","200509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61754","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential benefit of introducing a compulsory retirement programme for animals used in laboratories and scientific experiments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200559","200559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61755","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many parliamentary questions tabled to her Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200593","200593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61756","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) dogs, (b) cats and (c) horses were released from laboratories, returned and re-homed under the European Directive 2010/63/EU in the UK in each of the last three years; and if she will make a statement on its success.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200560","200560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61757","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the prevalence and effect of the sale of so-called legal highs (a) online and (b) in shops.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200545","200545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61758","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 11 November 2013, Official Report, columns 419-20W, on animals: experiments, when the Animals in Science Committee will publish its review of the Home Office inspectorate's report and Imperial College's independent report on the investigation into animal experiments at Imperial College, London; and when this report will be placed in the Library.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200535","200535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61759","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what revenue has been received by the Passport Office for (a) standard passport applications, (b) fast-track applications and (c) premium service applications in (i) 1 January 2012 to 31 May 2012, (ii) 1 January 2013 to 31 May 2013 and (iii) 1 January 2014 to 31 May 2014.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200525","200525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61760","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of fast-track passport applications made in the last six months have been processed within seven days.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200526","200526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61761","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much overtime has been paid to passport office staff at the Newport Passport Office since 2011.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200527","200527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61762","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) standard passport applications, (b) fast-track applications and (c) premium service applications were processed in (i) 1 January 2012 to 31 May 2012, (ii) 1 January 2013 to 31 May 2013 and (iii) 1 January 2014 o 31 May 2014.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200528","200528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61763","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much has been spent on courier services for passports outside the DX contract since 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200529","200529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61764","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost of redundancy payments for special advisers in her Department has been since May 2010.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200472","200472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61765","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what visits each of the Ministers in her Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200488","200488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61766","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 2 May 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mrs Amila Dar.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200503","200503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61767","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 2 May 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr RO Estemogbo.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200504","200504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61768","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 6 May 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mrs Bernioe Cssai Ogunribido.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200505","200505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61769","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much has been paid in overtime and other costs incurred in the last three weeks due to changes in HM Passport Office.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200523","200523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61770","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will revise her Department's guidelines to the Metropolitan Police on whether domestic violence cases should be referred to the Crown Prosecution Service before prosecutions can be initiated by the police; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200521","200521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61771","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, If she will ensure that all asylum interviews are routinely audio and video recorded.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200379","200379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61772","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that convictions are brought for possession of large quantities of illegal drugs.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200346","200346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61773","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of (a) new passport applications and (b) passport renewal applications were received by HM Passport Office in each week since 6 January 2014; and what proportion of those applications (i) were completed in three weeks, (ii) were completed in four weeks and (iii) remain outstanding for each of these weeks.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200466","200466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61774","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the policy is of the Passport Office on the passing of information on the status of a delayed passport application when dealing with correspondence from an hon. Member acting on behalf of a constituent.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200423","200423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61775","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what compensation the Passport Office provides to British passport holders who have faced increases on the cost of their flights because they have had to wait an extended period for a completed passport application.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200403","200403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61776","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were employed by HM Passport Office on 1 January (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200368","200368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61777","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people employed by HM Passport Office were specifically tasked with processing passport applications on 1 January, (a) 2011, (b) 2012, (c) 2013 and (d) 2014.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200369","200369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61778","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people employed by  HM Passport Office were specifically tasked with processing passport applications on (a) 1 January, (b) 1 February, (c) 1 March, (d) 1 April, (e) 1 May and (f) 1 June 2014.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200370","200370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61779","2014-06-17","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were employed by HM Passport Office on (a) 1 January, (b) 1 February, (c) 1 March, (d) 1 April, (e) 1 May and (f) 1 June 2014.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200371","200371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61780","2014-06-18","House of Commons Commission","2014-06-12","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, who was responsible for the appointment of Saxton Bampfylde for the search for a successor to the Clerk of the House and Chief Executive; and who will monitor its progress.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200393","200393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61781","2014-06-18","House of Commons Commission","2014-06-12","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, how much Saxton Bampfylde will be paid for its work on a successor to the Clerk of the House and Chief Executive; and if he will publish their terms of reference.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200391","200391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61782","2014-06-18","House of Commons Commission","2014-06-12","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, when Saxton Bampfylde was appointed for the search for a successor to the Clerk of the House and Chief Executive.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200392","200392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61783","2014-06-18","House of Commons Commission","2014-06-12","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, who will be responsible for the appointment of the next Clerk of the House and Chief Executive.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200394","200394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61784","2014-06-16","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many parliamentary questions tabled to her Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200447","200447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61785","2014-06-16","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what research her Department has undertaken into the humanitarian effects of the occupation of the West Bank and the blockade of Gaza.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200411","200411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61786","2014-06-16","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Syria.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200347","200347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61787","2014-06-16","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many meetings she has had with world leaders to discuss the humanitarian situation in Yemen since 1 January 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200357","200357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61788","2014-06-16","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of the £70 million which her Department offered to Yemen in 2013 for emergency food assistance, shelter, clean water and help for people recovering from conflict was provided to that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200355","200355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61789","2014-06-18","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she plans to increase the UK's humanitarian contribution to Iraq.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200571","200571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61790","2014-06-16","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what visits each of the Ministers in her Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200489","200489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61791","2014-06-16","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the budgeted spend is for humanitarian aid for Yemen for the next two years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200427","200427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61792","2014-06-16","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many parliamentary questions tabled to her Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200594","200594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61793","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200490","200490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61794","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many parliamentary questions tabled to his Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200448","200448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61795","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many racially aggravated attacks were recorded in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200511","200511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61796","2014-06-16","Leader of the House","2014-06-12","To ask the Leader of the House, what visits each of the Ministers in his Office have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200491","200491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61797","2014-06-16","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what visits each of the Ministers in her Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200492","200492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61798","2014-06-16","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many parliamentary questions tabled to her Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200595","200595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61799","2014-06-17","Prime Minister","2014-06-12","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will discuss climate change with his Chinese counterpart during his visit to the UK.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200468","200468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61800","2014-06-17","Prime Minister","2014-06-12","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions he has had on the Government's Action Plan on Business and Human Rights in advance of the visit by his Chinese counterpart to the UK.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200469","200469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61801","2014-06-17","Prime Minister","2014-06-12","To ask the Prime Minister, what his objectives are for discussions on human rights with the Chinese Premier, Li Keqiang during his visit to the UK this month.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200462","200462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61802","2014-06-16","Cabinet Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the level of unemployment in Kettering constituency  was (a) in May 2010 and (b) is at present; and how many net new jobs have been created in the Kettering economy since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200351","200351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61803","2014-06-16","Scotland Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200493","200493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61804","2014-06-16","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-12","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, in which 100 wards in which constituency in the UK turnout for voting at the polling station was lowest at the 2010 general election.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200435","200435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61805","2014-06-16","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-12","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, in which local authority wards in which constituency postal ballot turnout was greater than 90 per cent at the 2010 general election.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200436","200436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61806","2014-06-16","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the terms and conditions of the agreement reached between the Welsh and UK Governments in 2012 on the funding of the electrification of (a) the Great Western mainline from Cardiff to Swansea and (b) the Valleys lines.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200429","200429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61807","2014-06-16","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200494","200494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61808","2014-06-16","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he intends to respond to the Law Commission's final report and draft Bill on Taxis and Private Hire Services, published on 23 May 2014.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200506","200506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61809","2014-06-17","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will direct Network Rail to inform officially the hon. Member for Walsall North when the work on the bridge at Broad Lane, Bloxwich, Walsall arising from electrification of the railway line will be finally completed.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200522","200522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61810","2014-06-16","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many parliamentary questions tabled to his Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200596","200596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61811","2014-06-16","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the merits of including alcohol awareness training in the driving test assessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200561","200561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61812","2014-06-17","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the (a) availability and (b) effectiveness of scrubber technology on maritime vessels.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200613","200613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61813","2014-06-17","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policy of the report commissioned by the UK Chamber of Shipping on Impact on Jobs and the Economy of Meeting the Requirements of MARPOL annex VI, published in March 2013.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200614","200614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61814","2014-06-17","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consideration he has given to providing mitigation and transition support to maritime businesses during the introduction of maritime fuel sulphur regulations in January 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200615","200615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61815","2014-06-17","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will review the effect of the maritime fuel sulphur regulations earlier than 2019.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200616","200616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61816","2014-06-17","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with maritime industry stakeholders on the implications of maritime fuel sulphur regulations for freight traffic moving from water freight to road freight.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200617","200617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61817","2014-06-16","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proposals he has to further devolve responsibility for railways to the Scottish and Welsh governments and the English regions.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200609","200609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61818","2014-06-16","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with train operating companies on changes in staffing for revenue protection functions.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200610","200610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61819","2014-06-17","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the sufficiency of the transport links in the Streatham area; what plans he has to improve transport in that area; what research his Department has done on projects that might improve transport within the Streatham area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200375","200375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61820","2014-06-17","Department for Transport","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the availability of passenger information data on board trains.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200376","200376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61821","2014-06-16","Wales Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many parliamentary questions tabled to his Department in the last parliamentary Session did not receive a substantive answer by the time of the 2014 prorogation; and when each such question was first tabled.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200597","200597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61822","2014-06-16","Wales Office","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200496","200496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61823","2014-06-16","Women and Equalities","2014-06-12","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what visits each of the Ministers in the Government Equalities Office have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200486","200486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61824","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200497","200497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61825","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people in Birmingham, Selly Oak constituency are eligible for disabled students allowance (DSA); and how many such people will be negatively affected by proposed changes to DSA.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200507","200507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61826","2014-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department taks to investigate allegations from a whistleblower of impropriety in a Work Choice contract.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200520","200520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61827","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many parents are in arrears to the Child Support Agency in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200570","200570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61828","2014-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department takes to investigate whistleblowers' allegations of impropriety relating to employment support contracts.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200519","200519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61829","2014-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of jobseeker's allowance claims processed within (a) 10, (b) 20, (c) 30, (d) 40, (e) 60 and (f) more than 60 working days.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200530","200530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61830","2014-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of housing benefit claims processed within (a) 10, (b) 20, (c) 30, (d) 40, (e) 60 and (f) more than 60 working days.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200531","200531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61831","2014-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of employment and support allowance claims processed within (a) 10, (b) 20, (c) 30, (d) 40, (e) 60 and (f) more than 60 working days.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200532","200532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61832","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will create an independent panel to review and assess the effectiveness of the employment and support allowance and work capability assessment tests.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200534","200534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61833","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to collect data on work capability assessment outcomes for people diagnosed with fibromyalgia; and if he will estimate the cost of collecting such data.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200544","200544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61834","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to ensure that jobseekers whose jobseeker's allowance claim is cancelled are informed with greater clarity that their housing benefit will also be cancelled as a result.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200548","200548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61835","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance he gives to jobcentre staff on informing jobseekers of cancellation of their jobseeker's allowance claim.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200551","200551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61836","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will provide additional support to jobseekers whose jobseeker's allowance is sanctioned because they experience a series of short illnesses.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200550","200550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61837","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on whether jobseekers whose jobseeker's allowance claim is cancelled because they experience three periods of illness in one year must be informed of this by jobcentre staff.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200549","200549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61838","2014-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit sanctions for (a) not actively seeking employment, (b) refusal of employment, (c) failure to attend a mandatory interview, (d) failure to participate in work-related activity, (e) non-compliance with a Jobseeker's Direction were received by claimants in Wythenshawe and Sale East constituency between (i) April 2011 and March 2012 and (ii) April 2013 and March 2014.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200418","200418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61839","2014-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the extension of the shared accommodation rate to people under the age of 35 years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200363","200363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61840","2014-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit claims made in pilot areas have been based on independent self-assessment.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200464","200464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61841","2014-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the waiting period will be before an individual qualifies for support through universal credit; and how long he expects it will take to calculate entitlement and process new claims for universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200465","200465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61842","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training is available on autism for jobcentre plus advisers.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200380","200380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61843","2014-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have fallen below the auto enrolment threshold in each year since that policy was introduced.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200362","200362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61844","2014-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he proposes that his planned charge cap on workplace pensions from April 2015 will apply to new collective defined contribution schemes.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200361","200361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61845","2014-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are below the earnings threshold for auto enrolment into a workplace pension in each (a) region, (b) constituent part of the UK and (c) parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200360","200360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61846","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of adverse sanction decisions taken against jobseeker's allowance claimants in 2013 were repeat decisions.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200512","200512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61847","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he intends to respond to the recommendations made by the Social Security Advisory Committee in Occasional Paper 12 published in April 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200513","200513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61848","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what response he has given to the letter to him of 21 March 2014 from the Welfare Reform Committee of the Scottish Parliament on the recommendations of its review of work capability assessments.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200621","200621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61849","2014-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what response he has given to the recommendation of the Welfare Reform Committee of the Scottish Parliament that (a) those living with long-term progressive conditions should not be subject to reassessments and (b) changes should be made to the work capability assessment criteria to better recognise the impact of hidden symptoms and fluctuating conditions including multiple sclerosis.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200620","200620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62460","2014-06-18","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what programmes her Department operates to improve the criminal justice system of countries in receipt of overseas development assistance.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904303","904303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62461","2014-06-18","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to ensure that the funding of infrastructure projects in the Jordan Valley is not dependent on approval from the Israeli government.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904300","904300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62462","2014-06-18","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what programmes and activity her Department undertakes in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904305","904305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62463","2014-06-18","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to ensure that the funding of infrastructure projects in the Jordan Valley is not dependent on approval from the Israeli government.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904302","904302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62464","2014-06-18","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her health priorities are in discussions on the post-2015 development framework.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904304","904304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62465","2014-06-18","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the scale of the threat of rape faced by women in South Sudan; and what steps her Department plans to take to reduce such threats.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904306","904306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62466","2014-06-18","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in South Sudan.","Biography information for David Rutley","David Rutley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904301","904301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62467","2014-06-18","Department for International Development","2014-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effect of illegal settlements on the economic development of Palestine.","Biography information for Jim McGovern","Jim McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904307","904307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61297","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Written Statement of 11 June 2014, Official Report, column 47WS, on UK Green Investment Bank, whether the UK Green Investment Bank will be able to invest in green projects overseas.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200331","200331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61298","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Written Statement of 11 June 2014, Official Report, column 47WS, on UK Green Investment Bank, when he expects the assessment and feasibility stage to be finished; and when he expects to make a further statement on the Bank.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200332","200332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61299","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Written Statement of 11 June 2014, Official Report, column 47WS, on UK Green Investment Bank, whether funds additional to the £3.87 billion allocated to the UK International Climate Fund will be provided to the (a) Bank and (b) Fund.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200333","200333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61300","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Written Statement of 11 June 2014, Official Report, column 47WS, on UK Green Investment Bank, what additional funds will be provided to help assess the feasibility of the Green Investment Bank managing UK International Climate Fund projects.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200329","200329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61301","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Written Statement of 11 June 2014, Official Report, column 47WS, on UK Green Investment Bank, what estimate he has made of the staff resource the additional responsibilities on the Green Investment Bank will require.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200330","200330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61302","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which GP practices have been identified by NHS England as potentially losing more than £3 per patient in 2014-15 following the withdrawal of the Minimum Practice Income Guarantee.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200213","200213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61303","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of being able to access a GP appointment within 48 hours on levels of patient satisfaction.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200214","200214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61304","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of children were in (a) relative and (b) absolute poverty in each region and constituent part of the UK in each of the last 20 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200179","200179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61305","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of children in (a) relative and (b) absolute poverty in each region of the UK in the next three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200180","200180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61306","2014-06-16","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-11","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the postal vote turnout was as a proportion of all votes cast in each UK parliamentary constituency at the 2010 General Election.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200220","200220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61307","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households in each constituency in Northern Ireland were in receipt of child benefit during 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200194","200194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61308","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a statutory definition of a personal service company to enable HM Revenue and Customs to make a better informed assessment of those using such devices to artificially reduce income tax.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200196","200196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61309","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people applied to the UK Embassy in Dublin for British Passports between 2011 and 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200198","200198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61310","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will urgently increase the number of personnel working in the Belfast Passport Office.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200195","200195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61311","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress is being made in ensuring that all eligible employees have been offered automatic enrolment into a workplace pension scheme with minimum employer contributions.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200197","200197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61312","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the statement in Vodafone's 2013-14 Sustainability Report, that Section 19 of the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 prohibits disclosing the existence of any requirement to provide assistance in relation to a warrant, whether her Department issued guidance to that effect.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200249","200249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61313","2014-06-16","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-11","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what support his Department makes available to encourage electoral registration for those who are not able to register online.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200185","200185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61314","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review prescription charges for adults with cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200281","200281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61316","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the meaning is of the phrase responder hub as used in a communication from her Department to the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton; and if she will instruct her staff to use clearer and more comprehensible English in their communications with hon. Members and the public.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200201","200201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61317","2014-06-16","Department for International Development","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of the emergency response fund for the Central African Republic has so far been dispersed; and which international agencies have received such funding.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200313","200313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61318","2014-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish details of alternative proposals for fire fighter pensions which have been considered by his Department.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200312","200312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61319","2014-06-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance he has given local authorities on ensuring that road safety is not compromised by street lighting being switched off; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200251","200251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61320","2014-06-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on air quality of the escape of methane and other gases from disused mine workings in Derbyshire and Nottinghamshire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200250","200250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61321","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cats have been used in experiments in Britain in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200318","200318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61322","2014-06-18","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason scientific experiments on cats are permitted.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200319","200319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61323","2014-06-18","Department for Transport","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects work on the electrification of the railway line between Hull and Selby to begin.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200317","200317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61324","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much NHS trusts have spent (a) on agency and contract staff and (b) on all staff in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200211","200211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61325","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much NHS trusts (a) planned to spend and (b) spent on agency and contract staff in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200212","200212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61326","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on the extension of the lease for Diego Garcia Airbase.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200200","200200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61327","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what economic assessment he has made on the effect on tourism jobs in seaside areas and seaside economies of deregulating school holidays.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200272","200272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61328","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assistance his Department makes available to schools to survey for and remove asbestos.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200229","200229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61329","2014-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of primary pupils of each ethnic background and in total have engaged with (a) theatre activities, (b) music activities, (c) dance and (d) other arts in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200181","200181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61330","2014-06-16","Scotland Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what information he holds on the proportion of companies in (a) Glasgow North West, (b) Glasgow and (c) Scotland are ultimately owned by companies based in (i) Scotland, (ii) other parts of the UK, (iii) other countries in the EU and (iv) outside the EU.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200202","200202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61331","2014-06-16","Scotland Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will estimate the revenue generated in Scotland by companies that have their headquarters (a) in Scotland and (b) outside of Scotland.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200203","200203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61332","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in which single or multiple technology appraisals for pharmacological treatments for cancer the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (NICE) has considered the sequential use of the appraised technology with another available treatment; and whether in each such appraisal this resulted in a recommendation on sequential use in each year since NICE was established.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200238","200238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61333","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) pharmacological treatments and (b) associated indications the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence has recommended only for patients who have not been treated with a previously appraised drug.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200234","200234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61334","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) pharmacological treatments and (b) associated indications the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (NICE) has recommended for (i) prostate cancer, (ii) lung cancer, (iii) bowel cancer, (iv) breast cancer and (v) kidney cancer through either single or multiple technology appraisals and under the end of life criteria in each year since NICE was established.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200233","200233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61335","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have not received homecare medicines and products on time for treatment of (a) cystic fibrosis, (b) HIV and (c) rheumatoid arthritis in the last year.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200204","200204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61336","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many HSA4 certificates his Department has returned to terminating doctors pending completion in the last five years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200273","200273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61337","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the HS4A abortion notification form to require registered medical practitioners to indicate whether they have examined the presenting patient and/or discussed with her the grounds for abortion prior to forming their opinion in good faith that the provisions of the Abortion Act 1967 were met.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200274","200274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61338","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to speed up claims by asylum seekers.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200219","200219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61339","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the approach of the new Palestinian government to the peace process with Israel.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200310","200310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61340","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children began treatment for Type 1 diabetes in (a) Cannock Chase constituency and (b) Staffordshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200241","200241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61341","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeships commenced in each sector in (a) Cannock Chase constituency and (b) Staffordshire in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200236","200236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61342","2014-06-16","Cabinet Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of women in Cannock Chase constituency were in work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200237","200237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61343","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support his Department is giving to local authorities to implement changes to apprenticeship funding.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200172","200172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61344","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with training providers on changes to apprenticeship funding.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200173","200173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61345","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reason the option of maintaining the current provider-funded model was dropped in his Department's second consultation on funding reform for apprenticeships.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200174","200174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61346","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects HM Revenue and Customs to respond to Mapeley Estates, agents for the Custom House site, on the development of the new parking facilities at Dover Priory Railway Station.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200178","200178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61347","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the profitability and financial position of Mapeley Steps Contractor Limited in its role of managing the HM Revenue and Customs' estate.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200193","200193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61348","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses (a) applied for and (b) were granted authorisation as insurers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200244","200244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61349","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer to the hon. Member for Suffolk Coastal of 8 January 2014, Official Report, column 265W, on general practitioners: Suffolk, how much his Department spent funding each general practice in England in 2012-13; and what spending type and GP Practice code applies in each case.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200278","200278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61350","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 17 March 2014, Official Report, column 364W, on entry clearances, what options the policy and operational teams in her Department are considering to best accommodate a clearance programme once the appeal against the judgment of Mr Justice Blake on 5 July 2013 on the Government's visa income threshold is published.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200282","200282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61351","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the ability of Thames Water to service the costs of building the proposed Thames Tideway Tunnel.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200297","200297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61352","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which infrastructure projects have accessed the UK Guarantees scheme; and how much funding was issued in each such case.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200328","200328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61353","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what financial risk assessment he has carried out in respect of offering guarantees for the proposed Thames Tideway Tunnel.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200335","200335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61354","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what new buildings his Department plans to provide for the use of the private sector partner taking over the Defence Support Group; and what the potential cost to the public purse is of such provision.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200326","200326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61355","2014-06-17","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the contribution to economic growth of payment protection insurance repayments.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200336","200336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61356","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department saved for the Exchequer by closing the Passport Office in Newport.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200286","200286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61357","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much the recently employed additional staff in passport offices are estimated to cost.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200287","200287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61358","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the acceptable body mass index requirement is for an applicant to the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200275","200275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61359","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether applicants to the Royal Navy who meet an initial body mass index requirement of 28 face a different check at any other stage of the process.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200285","200285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61360","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people in Birmingham Northfield constituency qualify for the disabled students' allowance (DSA); and how many such people will be negatively affected by proposed changes to DSA.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200253","200253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61361","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many assaults on prison officers were committed by inmates in UK prisons in the last five years; and how many working days were lost as a result of such assaults.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200252","200252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61362","2014-06-16","Department for Transport","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects his Department's review of unpublished datasets to be completed.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200191","200191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61363","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) mean and (b) median age was of people who were registered as self-employed in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200314","200314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61364","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people were registered with HM Revenue and Customs as self-employed in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013; and how many of them reported net income (i) of zero and (ii) below the threshold for National Insurance in each year.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200315","200315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61365","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have received the New Enterprise Allowance since its commencement; and how many such people have subsequently (a) returned to jobseeker's allowance and (b) registered with HM Revenue and Customs as self-employed.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200334","200334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61366","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the policy of NHS England on the number of cycles of IVF it provides to armed forces personnel is to provide fewer than the number recommended by National Institute for Health and Care Excellence.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200338","200338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61367","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the forthcoming National Institute for Health and Care Excellence quality standard on fertility will be considered for a CCG Outcome Indicator.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200339","200339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61368","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the (a) prevalence and (b) effect of the sale of the unlicensed drug Melanotan (i) online and (ii) in shops.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200340","200340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61369","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of companies who have signed up to one or more pledges set out in the Responsibility Deal; and what estimate he has made of the proportion of those companies which are meeting all of the pledges they have signed up to.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200341","200341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61370","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the National Clinical Director for Cancer on the performance of the NHS against the waiting time targets for cancer treatment.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200342","200342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61371","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2014 Official Report, column 74W, on Members: Correspondence, when he expects to send a substantive reply to the letter of 30 April 2014 from the hon. Member for Walsall North about admissions to Walsall Academy which was separate from the letter sent to the Chief Executive of the Education Funding Agency; and for what reason that Answer does not mention that there was separate correspondence on the subject.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200309","200309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61373","2014-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much the Arts Council has spent per head of population in Ashfield constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200247","200247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61374","2014-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many businesses in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) Nottinghamshire have qualified for the full £1,000 business rates discount to date.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200189","200189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61375","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) Nottinghamshire paid the top rate of income tax in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200187","200187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61376","2014-06-16","Cabinet Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average salary was for a (a) man and (b) woman of (i) white ethnic origin and (ii) black and minority ethnic origin and who was (A) disabled and (B) not disabled in Ashfield constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200186","200186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61377","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much (a) public and (b) private funding has been provided to each sector skills council (i) on average and (ii) in the East Midlands in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200188","200188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61378","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason his Department did not provide an ICT hosting environment for Capita on time for the Recruiting Partnering Project.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200298","200298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61379","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information and communications technology projects his Department has implemented (a) to the original deadline and on budget and (b) after the original deadline and over budget in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200296","200296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61380","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what military or civilian personnel in his Department of what rank or grade have been reprimanded for failing to deliver an ICT hosting environment for Capita as part of the Recruiting Partnering Project.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200299","200299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61381","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate (a) the savings generated by each branch of the armed forces having separate recruiting programmes and (b) the annual cost of each such programme.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200295","200295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61382","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse to date is of the Recruiting and Partnering Project.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200320","200320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61383","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason the initial estimate of the additional costs of reverting to the fallback position of a hosting solution provided by Capita for the Recruiting Partnering Project increased from £47.7 million to £70 million; and who was responsible for these estimates.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200300","200300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61384","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of Scottish independence on businesses in the North East and Cumbria.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200254","200254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61385","2014-06-16","Cabinet Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what adjusted change there has been in average gross weekly earnings of (a) full-time workers, (b) men working full-time and (c) women working full-time since January 2010.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200227","200227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61386","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his Written Statement of 7 April 2014, Official Report, column 1WS on higher education, what public consultation he has undertaken on the proposed changes to disabled students' allowance.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200271","200271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61387","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the quality of provision of primary care in Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200222","200222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61388","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will meet the hon. Member for Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland to discuss the proposed closure of (a) minor injuries units at Guisborough and East Cleveland Hospitals, (b) Skelton Medical Centre, (c) Park End Clinic and (d) Skelton NHS Walk-in-Centre.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200221","200221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61389","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the extent to which there is a gender imbalance in the composition of Local Enterprise Partnership boards.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200232","200232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61390","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to devolve Air Passenger Duty to Scotland.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200267","200267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61391","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have waited longer than the advised waiting times for (a) new passport applications and (b) passport renewals in the last year.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200255","200255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61392","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent reports she has received of changes in the backlog for processing (a) new passport applications and (b) passport renewals.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200256","200256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61393","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department issues to police forces on marking cases as requiring No Further Action.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200257","200257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61394","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the average waiting time for (a) new passport applications and (b) passport renewals in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200258","200258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61395","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number and proportion of cases that police have marked as requiring No Further Action in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200259","200259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61396","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints her Department has received regarding delays to the issuing of a passport in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200216","200216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61397","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for (a) new passports and (b) passport renewals there have been in the last year; and what the annual change in such figures has been.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200217","200217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61398","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 13 May 2014, Official Report, column 462W, on private investigation, on what date she expects the new statutory licensing requirement to come into force.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200171","200171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61399","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average annual cost of training an apprentice aged 16 to 18 is; and what proportion of such costs is borne by (a) the public purse, (b) individuals and (c) employers.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200239","200239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61400","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average unit cost per year to train an apprentice aged 19 to 24 is; and what proportion of such costs is borne by (a) the public purse, (b) apprentices and (c) employers.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200240","200240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61401","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent estimate he has made of the cash value of the student loan book in each year to 2050 (a) before and (b) after sales of student loans.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200265","200265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61402","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what annual budget has been allocated to Unionlearn in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200266","200266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61403","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many disabled students allowance recipients there are in (a) Birmingham, Hodge Hill constituency, (b) Birmingham and (c) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200291","200291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61404","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent estimate his Department has made of the RAB charge for student loans issued after 2012.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200292","200292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61405","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish all forecasts held by his Department of the annual budget to be allocated to Unionlearn.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200268","200268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61406","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average unit cost per year to train an apprentice aged 24 is; and what proportion of such costs is borne by (a) the public purse, (b) apprentices and (c) employers.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200293","200293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61407","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish the externally audited copies of the last three years' accounts supplied by alternative learning providers who sought specific course designation under his Department's financial sustainability, management and governance checks.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200269","200269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61408","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what individual student number controls his Department has set for each provider which has been granted specific course designation under his Department's financial sustainability, management and governance checks.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200270","200270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61409","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what projections his Department has made of the future (a) face value and (b) carrying value of the student loan book.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200294","200294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61410","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answer of 14 May 2013, Official Report, column 130W, on minimum wage, if he will take steps to provide (a) clear and comprehensive guidance on the national minimum wage on gov.uk and (b) sector-specific guidance and case studies on the national minimum wage for the entertainment sector.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200284","200284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61411","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he plans to take to enable vulnerable witnesses to be able to give evidence remotely.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200321","200321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61412","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sites for giving remote evidence are operational in England and Wales.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200182","200182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61413","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) children and (b) vulnerable adult witnesses gave evidence remotely in 2013.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200183","200183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61414","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the payment of £97,000 made by his Department to the Third Millennium Education Trust on 29 November 2012 was a grant secured through the Sponsor Capacity Fund.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200280","200280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61415","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which organisations have received grants through the Sponsor Capacity Fund to date; when any such grant was awarded; how much was so awarded; and whether each organisation subsequently sponsored any academies.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200230","200230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61416","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department takes to (a) monitor how the grants awarded through the Sponsor Capacity Fund are used and (b) recoup grants from the Sponsor Capacity Fund  where the recipients do not go on to sponsor any academies or use the money in an inappropriate way.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200228","200228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61417","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to secure the future of coal mining at Thoresby Colliery in Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200311","200311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61418","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many custodial sentences have been passed for convictions for fraud in the last five years for which figures are available; what the average length of those sentences was in each such years; and what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals to increase the maximum sentence for fraud.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200327","200327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61419","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs there were in England per 100,000 population in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200231","200231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61420","2014-06-17","Cabinet Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average weekly gross earnings of (a) men, (b) women and (c) people in full time employment in Peterborough was (i) in cash terms and (ii) at constant prices in each year since 2006-07.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200316","200316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61421","2014-06-16","Cabinet Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many businesses there were in Peterborough in each year since 2001.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200263","200263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61422","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils in Peterborough constituency achieved (a) Level 1 and (b) Level 2 skills in English in each year since 2005; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200264","200264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61423","2014-06-17","Department for Education","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to support children with special educational needs in (a) Peterborough and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200288","200288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61424","2014-06-17","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many families whose head of household was (a) a Polish, (b) a Lithuanian, (c) a Latvian, (d) a Czech, (e) a Slovak, (f) a Portuguese and (g) an Estonian national resident in the Peterborough city council area were in receipt of child benefit in each year since 2005; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200289","200289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61425","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what details parents will be required to provide for the quarterly reconfirmation process for tax-free childcare; what measures will be in place to ensure that parents are reminded about the deadline for quarterly reconfirmation; and what provisions he will put in place in the event that parents fail to provide the necessary details for (a) one quarter and (b) more than one quarter.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200215","200215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61426","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the revised plans for the roll-out of universal credit announced on 5 December 2013, what estimate he has made of the number of families which will be eligible for support for childcare through universal credit in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, (c) 2017-18 and (d) 2018-19.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200190","200190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61427","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the average annual cost of childcare in the UK for a child aged (a) two and under, (b) three to four and (c) five and over; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200175","200175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61428","2014-06-16","Department for Transport","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2014, Official Report, column 6W, on cycling, if he will publish the (a) membership and (b) agendas, minutes and attendees of all previous meetings of the Cycling Stakeholder Forum.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200279","200279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61429","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the position of (a) the Christian community and (b) other religious minorities in Mosul, Iraq; what reports he has received of Christians fleeing their homes in Mosul; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200192","200192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61430","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average ambulance response times in (a) Doncaster, (b) Barnsley, (c) Rotherham and (d) Sheffield was in each year since May 2010; and what the national average response time was in each of those years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200245","200245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61431","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of how long is needed to bring the Army Reserves to full strength as set out in Army 2020.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200246","200246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61432","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have received on the use of constraint in secure colleges.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200242","200242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61433","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what equality impact assessments his Department has carried out on the proposed introduction of a secure college.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200243","200243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61434","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which company designed and what the cost to the public purse was of production in 2009 of the plans for a young offender institute at Glen Parva.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200248","200248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61435","2014-06-16","Attorney General","2014-06-11","To ask the Attorney General, whether officials of the Crown Prosecution Service have (a) met the Attorney General of Nigeria since January 2012, (b) had any conversations about the sale of the OPL 245 oil concession in Nigeria involving Shell and ENI with (i) the Attorney General of Nigeria and (ii) any other senior official of the Nigerian government and (c) received any requests for mutual legal assistance regarding the OPL 245 case.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200209","200209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61436","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether Ministers or officials of his Department have (a) met the Attorney General of Nigeria since January 2012 and (b) had any conversations about the sale of the OPL 245 oil concession in Nigeria involving Shell and ENI with (i) the Attorney General of Nigeria and (ii) any other senior official of the Nigerian government.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200207","200207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61437","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his Department's press release of 1 November 2013 entitled Government considering new powers to tackle non-payment of tribunal awards, what progress he has made in considering the various policy options for improving enforcement of unpaid employment tribunal awards.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200177","200177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61438","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many of the employers issued with a notice of underpayment of the minimum wage by HM Revenue and Customs since 1 October 2013 have been considered for naming and shaming by his Department; how many of those employers have successfully appealed against being named and shamed; how many employers have been named and shamed; and how many cases remain under consideration.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200277","200277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61439","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many of the financial penalties for non-compliance with the minimum wage issued by HM Revenue and Customs in 2013-14 were for the then maximum sum of £5,000.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200170","200170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61440","2014-06-16","Cabinet Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether Ministers or officials of his Department have (a) met the Attorney General of Nigeria since January 2012 and (b) had any conversations about the sale of the OPL 245 oil concession in Nigeria involving Shell and ENI with (i) the Attorney General of Nigeria and (ii) any other senior official of the Nigerian government.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200208","200208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61441","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Ministers or officials of his Department have (a) met the Attorney General of Nigeria since January 2012 and (b) had any conversations about the sale of the OPL 245 oil concession in Nigeria involving Shell and ENI with (i) the Attorney General of Nigeria and (ii) any other senior official of the Nigerian government.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200205","200205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61442","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether Ministers or officials of his Department have (a) met the Attorney General of Nigeria since January 2012 and (b) had any conversations about the sale of the OPL 245 oil concession in Nigeria involving Shell and ENI with (i) the Attorney General of Nigeria and (ii) any other senior official of the Nigerian government.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200206","200206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61443","2014-06-16","Prime Minister","2014-06-11","To ask the Prime Minister, for what reasons the G7 Summit Declaration does not mention Iraq; what discussions took place at that summit on (a) the rise of Al Qaeda-linked organisations in western and northern Iraq and (b) other issues relating to Iraq; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200283","200283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61444","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether officials of her Department have (a) met the Attorney General of Nigeria since January 2012, (b) had any conversations about the sale of the OPL 245 oil concession in Nigeria involving Shell and ENI with (i) the Attorney General of Nigeria and (ii) any other senior official of the Nigerian government and (c) received any requests for mutual legal assistance regarding the OPL 245 case.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200210","200210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61445","2014-06-18","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cancer patients aged between 13 and 24 have (a) accessed treatments through the already approved Cancer Drugs Fund (CDF) list, (b) applied for individual CDF requests, (c) had individual CDF requests put forward for consideration by the CDF panel, (d) had individual CDF requests approved by the CDF panel and (e) had individual CDF requests refused by the CDF panel in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200176","200176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61446","2014-06-18","HM Treasury","2014-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of whether Atos is an appropriate body to conduct (a) the delivery of tax-free childcare and (b) other outsourced work on behalf of National Savings and Investments.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200290","200290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61447","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that the Green Investment Bank does not provide support to (a) the proposed Helius Bioenergy Plant at Avonmouth and (b) other biofuel projects.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200184","200184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61448","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the contribution by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs of 13 May 2014, Official Report, columns 200-3WH, what representations he has made to the government of the Democratic Republic of Congo on the recent acquittal of 14 officers of the armed forces of that country on charges of mass rape and murder.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200235","200235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61449","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department will reply to the report by the All Party Parliamentary Group on Skin into sunbed regulation in England.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200218","200218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61450","2014-06-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of how many properties at risk of flooding in (a) Windsor constituency and (b) the Thames Valley that will not be covered by the new Flood Re scheme.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200307","200307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61451","2014-06-16","Cabinet Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he for the future of the UK Census; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200302","200302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61452","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the UK Space Agency in promoting the UK space industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200304","200304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61453","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disabled entrepreneurs have been able to access additional support funding through the Access to Work programme.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200306","200306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61454","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the return on public investment in the UK Space Agency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200305","200305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61455","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent progress she has made in introducing universal exit checks; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200301","200301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61456","2014-06-16","Cabinet Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of the International Passenger Survey for estimating migration flows; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200303","200303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61457","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of those held in open prisons in each month in 2010 to 2013 had previously (a) absconded, (b) attempted to abscond, (c) escaped and (d) attempted to escape.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200226","200226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61458","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many life sentence prisoners were released on temporary licence in each month between 2010 and 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200225","200225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61459","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on which occasions Ministers in his Department have taken decisions on (a) moving prisoners into open conditions and (b) releasing prisoners on temporary licence since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200224","200224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61460","2014-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many unfilled vacancies there were on 1 June 2014 in (a) each community rehabilitation company and (b) the National Probation Service.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200223","200223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61461","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the cost to the public purse of litigation associated with the declaration of the Marine Protected Area on 1 April 2010 are to date.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200337","200337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61462","2014-06-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether agreement has been reached to extend to 2020 the reduction to household water bills for South West Water customers.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200276","200276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61463","2014-06-16","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-11","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what checks are in place to ensure that multiple property owners do not vote twice in European or general elections on the same date as local or council elections; how many people have been charged with attempting to vote twice in the last three such elections; and how many fines have been issued as a result of those charges.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200308","200308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61464","2014-06-16","Department for Transport","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the value of London Midland's rolling stock maintenance contract with Siemens after the direct award of the franchise for the period September 2015 to June 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200325","200325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61465","2014-06-16","Department for Transport","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the value of London Midland's rolling stock contract with Angel Trains after the direct award of the franchise for the period September 2015 to June 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200324","200324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61466","2014-06-16","Department for Transport","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to monitor London Midland's (a) budgeting and (b) contractual relationship with Siemens for maintenance work on the Desiro EMU fleet.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200322","200322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61467","2014-06-16","Department for Transport","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of London Midland's current rolling stock is within the scope of the company's fleet maintenance contract with Siemens.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200323","200323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61468","2014-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with B&K Universal Ltd, Yorkshire Evergreen or their associates about their planning application for a facility at Grimston, Yorkshire for the breeding of dogs and other animals for laboratory use in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200261","200261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61469","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions his Department has had with B&K Universal Ltd, Yorkshire Evergreen or their associates relating to their planning application for a facility at Grimston, Yorkshire for the breeding of dogs and other animals for laboratory use in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200262","200262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61470","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with B&K Universal Ltd, Yorkshire Evergreen or their associates about their planning application for a facility at Grimston, Yorkshire for the breeding of dogs and other animals for laboratory use in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200260","200260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61471","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) new passport applications and (b) passport renewal applications have been received by HM Passport Office since the beginning of the current financial year; and what proportion of such applications were completed and dispatched within (i) three and (ii) four weeks.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200199","200199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62176","2014-06-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what role his Department is playing in the Government's review of the Muslim Brotherhood announced in April 2014.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904265","904265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62177","2014-06-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effects on the Middle East Peace Process of the new unity Palestinian government.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904258","904258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62178","2014-06-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote peace and reconciliation in the African Great Lakes region.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904266","904266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/62179","2014-06-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which powers he is seeking to repatriate from the EU.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904264","904264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60872","2014-06-12","Attorney General","2014-06-10","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of staff within the Law Officers' Departments who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199897","199897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60873","2014-06-12","Attorney General","2014-06-10","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of staff within the Law Officers' Departments who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199876","199876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60874","2014-06-12","Attorney General","2014-06-10","To ask the Attorney General, what targets the Law Officers' Departments have for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199919","199919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60875","2014-06-12","Attorney General","2014-06-10","To ask the Attorney General, what consideration the Law Officers' Departments' give to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199940","199940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60876","2014-06-12","HM Treasury","2014-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employers registered in (a) Washington and Sunderland West constituency, (b) the Sunderland local authority area and (c) the North East region have been the subject of enforcement action for paying employees less than the National Minimum Wage in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200000","200000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60877","2014-06-12","HM Treasury","2014-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints have been made against employers registered in (a) Washington and Sunderland West constituency, (b) the Sunderland local authority area and (c) the North East region for paying employees less than the National Minimum Wage in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200001","200001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60878","2014-06-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of those (a) starting and (b) completing an apprenticeship in England since May 2010 were (i) female, (ii) registered disabled and (iii) from an ethnic minority background.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199999","199999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60879","2014-06-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the ethnic breakdown of workers earning between the National Minimum Wage and the Living Wage.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199996","199996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60880","2014-06-12","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the ethnic breakdown of workers on zero hour contracts.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199997","199997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60881","2014-06-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to increase the number of black and minority ethnic professors teaching in public universities.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199998","199998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60882","2014-06-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what consideration his Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199939","199939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60883","2014-06-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what targets his Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199918","199918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60884","2014-06-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199875","199875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60885","2014-06-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199896","199896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60886","2014-06-12","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish a new diversity strategy for the Civil Service.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199873","199873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60887","2014-06-12","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199898","199898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60888","2014-06-12","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what consideration his Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199941","199941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60889","2014-06-12","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what targets his Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199920","199920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60890","2014-06-12","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199877","199877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60891","2014-06-12","HM Treasury","2014-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199916","199916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60892","2014-06-12","HM Treasury","2014-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199894","199894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60893","2014-06-12","HM Treasury","2014-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what targets his Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199937","199937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60894","2014-06-12","HM Treasury","2014-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what consideration his Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199958","199958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60895","2014-06-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199899","199899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60896","2014-06-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what consideration his Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199942","199942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60897","2014-06-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199878","199878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60898","2014-06-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what targets his Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199921","199921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60899","2014-06-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what targets his Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199922","199922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60900","2014-06-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199879","199879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60901","2014-06-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what consideration his Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199943","199943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60902","2014-06-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199900","199900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60903","2014-06-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199901","199901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60904","2014-06-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what consideration his Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199944","199944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60905","2014-06-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199880","199880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60906","2014-06-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what targets his Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199923","199923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60907","2014-06-12","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-10","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what proportion of staff within his Office who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199881","199881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60908","2014-06-12","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what targets the Cabinet Office has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199924","199924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60909","2014-06-12","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-10","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what consideration his Office gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199945","199945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60910","2014-06-12","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-10","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what proportion of staff within his Office who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199902","199902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60911","2014-06-12","Department for Education","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199903","199903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60912","2014-06-12","Department for Education","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in (a) Washington and Sunderland West constituency, (b) the Sunderland local authority area and (c) the North East region are receiving less overall funding in 2013-14 than they did in 2010-11.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199864","199864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60913","2014-06-12","Department for Education","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much capacity funding for universal infant free school meals has been (a) requested by and (b) disbursed to schools in (i) Washington and Sunderland West constituency, (ii) the Sunderland local authority area and (iii) the North East region.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199863","199863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60914","2014-06-12","Department for Education","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consideration his Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199946","199946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60915","2014-06-12","Department for Education","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what targets his Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199925","199925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60916","2014-06-12","Department for Education","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199882","199882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60917","2014-06-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199883","199883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60918","2014-06-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what targets his Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199926","199926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60919","2014-06-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what consideration his Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199947","199947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60920","2014-06-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199904","199904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60921","2014-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199905","199905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60922","2014-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what consideration his Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199948","199948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60923","2014-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what targets his Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199927","199927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60924","2014-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199884","199884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60925","2014-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199885","199885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60926","2014-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what targets his Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199928","199928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60927","2014-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what consideration his Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199949","199949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60928","2014-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199906","199906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60929","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199908","199908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60930","2014-06-12","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many births, broken down by the week of pregnancy in which the birth occurred, there were in England in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199856","199856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60931","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199887","199887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60932","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what targets his Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199930","199930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60933","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children spent (a) up to two weeks, (b) two to four weeks, (c) four to six weeks and (d) more than six weeks in hospital immediately after being born in England in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200003","200003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60934","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of changes in average waiting times for GP appointments in Sunderland since May 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200002","200002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60935","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consideration his Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199951","199951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60936","2014-06-12","Home Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what consideration her Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199952","199952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60937","2014-06-12","Home Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what targets her Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199931","199931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60938","2014-06-12","Home Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of staff within her Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199888","199888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60939","2014-06-12","Home Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of staff within her Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199909","199909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60940","2014-06-12","House of Commons Commission","2014-06-10","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what proportion of staff within the House of Commons Commission who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199910","199910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60941","2014-06-12","Department for International Development","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of staff within her Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years were white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199911","199911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60942","2014-06-12","Department for International Development","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of staff within her Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199889","199889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60943","2014-06-12","Department for International Development","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what targets her Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199932","199932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60944","2014-06-12","Department for International Development","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what consideration her Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199953","199953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60945","2014-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what consideration his Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199954","199954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60946","2014-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what targets his Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199933","199933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60947","2014-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199890","199890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60948","2014-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199912","199912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60949","2014-06-12","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of staff within her Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199913","199913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60950","2014-06-12","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what targets her Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199934","199934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60951","2014-06-12","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of staff within her Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199891","199891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60952","2014-06-12","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what consideration her Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199955","199955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60953","2014-06-12","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what consideration No. 10 Downing Street gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199956","199956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60954","2014-06-12","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what targets No. 10 Downing Street has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199935","199935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60955","2014-06-12","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of staff within No. 10 Downing Street who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199892","199892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60956","2014-06-12","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of staff within No. 10 Downing Street who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199914","199914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60957","2014-06-12","Department for Transport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199915","199915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60958","2014-06-12","Department for Transport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199893","199893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60959","2014-06-12","Department for Transport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what targets his Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199936","199936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60960","2014-06-12","Department for Transport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consideration his Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199957","199957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60961","2014-06-12","Women and Equalities","2014-06-10","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what consideration the Government Equalities Office gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199950","199950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60962","2014-06-12","Women and Equalities","2014-06-10","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what targets the Government Equalities Office has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199929","199929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60963","2014-06-12","Women and Equalities","2014-06-10","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what proportion of staff within the Government Equalities Office who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199886","199886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60964","2014-06-12","Women and Equalities","2014-06-10","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what proportion of staff within the Government Equalities Office who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199907","199907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60965","2014-06-12","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times the Social Justice Cabinet Committee has met since 5 May 2010; what issues were on the agenda for each such meeting; and which Ministers attended each such meeting.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199874","199874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60966","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in (a) Washington and Sunderland West constituency, (b) the Sunderland local authority area and (c) the North East region are paying the under-occupancy penalty; and how many of those households contain someone registered as disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199861","199861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60967","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average annual amount of under-occupancy penalty is paid by households in (a) Washington and Sunderland West constituency, (b) the Sunderland local authority area and (c) the North East region.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199862","199862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60968","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of personal independence payments claims not made under the special rules for terminally ill people, by claimants resident in (a) Washington and Sunderland West constituency, (b) the Sunderland local authority area and (c) the North East region were successful in each month for which records are available.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199855","199855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60969","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payments claims, not under the special rules for terminally ill people, have been made by residents of (a) Washington and Sunderland West constituency, (b) the Sunderland local authority area and (c) the North East region in each month for which records are available.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199857","199857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60970","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people resident in (a) Washington and Sunderland West constituency, (b) the Sunderland local authority area and (c) the North East region have been referred to the work programme to date; and how many of those have achieved sustained job outcomes.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199858","199858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60971","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time between an assessment appointment for personal independence payment and a decision being made has been for residents of (a) Washington and Sunderland West constituency, (b) the Sunderland local authority area and (c) the North East region since the beginning of the scheme.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199860","199860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60972","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time between applying for a personal independence payment and an assessment appointment has been for residents of (a) Washington and Sunderland West constituency, (b) the Sunderland local authority area and (c) the North East region since the beginning of the scheme.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199859","199859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60973","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been dismissed following formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199917","199917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60974","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of staff within his Department who have been subject to formal disciplinary proceedings in each of the last five financial years classed themselves as white British.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199895","199895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60975","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what targets his Department has for increasing diversity; and what progress has been made on meeting those targets in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199938","199938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60976","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what consideration his Department gives to the diversity policies and records of businesses or other organisations when considering their bid for commercial contracts or grants.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199959","199959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60977","2014-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many fines have been (a) paid, (b) collected and (c) reduced for alcohol-related motoring offences in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199838","199838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60978","2014-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many fines have been (a) paid, (b) collected and (c) reduced for motoring speeding offences in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199839","199839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60979","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who is responsible for the intellectual property policy of the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200098","200098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60980","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what evaluation was made of NHS innovation hubs by the Innovation, Health and Wealth sunset review.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200097","200097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60981","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many commercial agreements were completed for the exploitation of NHS intellectual property by NHS organisations in each year from 2004 to 2010; and what total revenues to each such organisation was in each year from 2004 to 2010.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200096","200096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60982","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the Commissioning for Quality and Innovation initiative on the commercialisation of intellectual property by NHS providers; and what metrics are used to monitor the commercialisation of such intellectual property.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200094","200094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60983","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what Commissioning for Quality and Innovation payments have been made as a result of NHS providers complying with the commercialisation of intellectual property pre-qualification to date.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200095","200095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60984","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many commercial deals were completed to exploit NHS intellectual property in each NHS organisation in each year from 2010 to date; and what revenue accrued to each NHS organisation from such deals in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200104","200104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60985","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to monitor the implementation of clinical commissioning groups' legal duty to promote innovation, adoption and diffusion of new techniques.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200105","200105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60986","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Innovation, Health and Wealth Sunset Review will be published.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200106","200106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60987","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many innovations of each type have been identified and recorded in each year following the implementation of the Cquin pre-qualification of the commercialisation of intellectual property.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200107","200107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60988","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who is responsible for auditing the compliance of clinical commissioning groups with their duty since the introduction of self-certification to provide innovation across all three stages of innovation.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200102","200102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60989","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who is responsible for monitoring NHS England compliance with its duty to promote innovation across all three stages of innovation.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200099","200099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60990","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what metrics have been used to monitor NHS England's compliance with its duty to promote innovation across all three stages of innovation.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200100","200100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60991","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) forecast and (b) actual figures of (i) absolute and (ii) relative child poverty were in each year since the Child Poverty Act 2010 came into force.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200109","200109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60992","2014-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the state of health of the UK tree population following the recent Ash Dieback epidemic.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200115","200115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60993","2014-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether he has had any discussions with his counterpart in the United States Department of Energy as to any change in the estimated levels of recoverable shale gas reserves which has occurred in the US since fracking began; what effect, if any, this might have on potential fracking in the UK; and how the emerging lessons of shale gas extraction in the US and elsewhere are applied in calculating and updating estimates of recoverable reserves in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200161","200161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60994","2014-06-12","Home Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance she has issued to police forces on ensuring constituency and flexibility in policing of parades and demonstrations ensuring the smooth flow of traffic and safety of participants, motorists and pedestrians.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200114","200114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60995","2014-06-12","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many directors of national charities were in receipt of annual salaries, pensions and other payments in excess of £150,000 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200118","200118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60996","2014-06-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people have begun learning British Sign Language in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200117","200117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60997","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made in licensing drugs to deal with Duchenne muscular dystrophy.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200116","200116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60998","2014-06-16","Attorney General","2014-06-10","To ask the Attorney General, how many cases of unduly lenient sentences were (a) referred to his Department, (b) taken up by him and (c) upheld in court since 2010 where the offender whose sentence was the subject of the appeal could have been released prior to the conclusion of the case if there had been a delay in the commencement of proceedings by (i) 14 days, (ii) 28 days, (iii) 42 days and (iv) 62 days; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200137","200137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60999","2014-06-16","Attorney General","2014-06-10","To ask the Attorney General, how many times an appeal made against an unduly lenient sentence in the last five years has led to someone being returned to prison who had already been released.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200138","200138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61000","2014-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many risk assessments on prisoners were carried out by (a) fully-qualified forensic psychologists and (b) trainee psychologists in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200108","200108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61001","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) India and (b) Pakistan on sexual violence against women in those countries.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200040","200040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61002","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the recent presidential elections in Ukraine on the political situation in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200037","200037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61003","2014-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political situation in Egypt; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200041","200041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61004","2014-06-16","Department for International Development","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Syria.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200038","200038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61005","2014-06-16","Department for International Development","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to tackle female genital mutilation overseas; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200039","200039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61006","2014-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on human rights abuses in Western Sahara.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199872","199872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61007","2014-06-12","Department for International Development","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Western Sahara.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199871","199871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61008","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that pregnant women living in England but registered with GPs in Wales have the option of a nuchal translucency scan as part of their antenatal care.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199843","199843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61009","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that people living in England but registered with GPs in Wales have full access to services provided by NHS England.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199847","199847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61010","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the capacity of English, Welsh and Northern Ireland shipyards to build surface warships following the closure of the BAE shipyard in Portsmouth.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199842","199842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61011","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the BAE shipyard in Portsmouth is planned to close.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199841","199841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61012","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to ensure that specialised manufacturing and engineering equipment located at the BAE shipyard, Portsmouth, will be made available to potential new users of the shipyard.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199846","199846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61013","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the availability of training in manufacturing and engineering skills in Hampshire subsequent to the closure of the BAE shipyard in Portsmouth.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199844","199844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61014","2014-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of proposals to utilise the current BAE shipyard in Portsmouth subsequent to its planned closure.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199845","199845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61015","2014-06-12","Department for Transport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of delays to East Coast Main Line rail services in 2013-14 were due to (a) overhead wire failures, (b) signalling failures, (c) other infrastructure failures, (d) flooding or other weather events, (e) vehicles, persons, or animals on the line, (f) train failures, (g) unavailability of staff and (h) other causes.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200030","200030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61016","2014-06-12","HM Treasury","2014-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) on extending the FCA's powers to include regulatory powers over tailored business loans.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200088","200088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61017","2014-06-12","HM Treasury","2014-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance his Department has given to the Financial Conduct Authority on its remit in relation to tailored business loans.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200092","200092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61018","2014-06-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Welsh Assembly Government on the broadband rollout programme in Wales.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200020","200020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61019","2014-06-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the Green Deal Home Improvement Fund on people who live in rural areas and rely on oil fired central heating.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200086","200086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61020","2014-06-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he has taken to incentivise off-gas homes to install modern condensing boilers.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200087","200087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61021","2014-06-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of a potential link between wind farms and tidal patterns in North Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200019","200019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61022","2014-06-12","Wales Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent assessment he has made of the success of UK Trade & Investment in relation to Welsh exports; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200091","200091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61023","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many local authorities in (a) Wales and (b) the UK returned unused discretionary housing payment to his Department in 2013-14.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200090","200090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61024","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much each local authority in (a) Wales and (b) the UK returned to his Department in unused discretionary housing payment funding in 2013-14.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200089","200089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61025","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many companies (a) expressed an interest in and (b) tendered for the Help to Work scheme in Wales.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200022","200022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61026","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many local authorities in Wales applied for additional financial assistance to cover discretionary housing payments in 2013-14; and what assistance such local authorities received.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200023","200023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61027","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to expand the PAYE reporting in real time to Child Support Agency claims.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200021","200021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61028","2014-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the availability of telephones and computers for jobseekers to use in Jobcentre Plus offices; and what plans he has to improve the provision of such equipment.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199830","199830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61029","2014-06-12","Department for Education","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional funding his Department makes available to schools to commission extra-curricular activities and projects.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199837","199837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61030","2014-06-12","Home Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what advice her Department gives to parents travelling with a child who has a different surname on ensuring they do  not encounter delays at UK border control.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199836","199836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61031","2014-06-16","Department for Education","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many GCSE entries there were in (a) music, (b) drama and (c) art and design in England in (i) 2009-10 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200043","200043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61032","2014-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent meetings he has had with the Secretary of State for Education to discuss arts, music and culture in schools.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200042","200042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61033","2014-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent meetings he has had with educational organisations to discuss arts, music and culture in schools.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200036","200036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61034","2014-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to ensure that community rehabilitation companies operated by external providers are considered public bodies for the purposes of the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199825","199825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61035","2014-06-12","Department for Transport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the annual amount of carcinogens that are released by biofuels activity in the UK.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200012","200012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61036","2014-06-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of investment by the Green Investment Bank has been given to biofuels to date.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200013","200013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61037","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the health dangers of wood dust.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200011","200011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61038","2014-06-16","HM Treasury","2014-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total value was of tax credits paid to claimants who were (a) out of work, (b) self-employed and (c) employed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199850","199850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61039","2014-06-16","Cabinet Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect of the exclusion of universal credit claimants on the overall claimant count for data published in (a) February, (b) March, (c) April and (d) May 2014.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199848","199848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61040","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the current total remuneration package is for the Chief Executive of HM Passport Office.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199849","199849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61041","2014-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of antibiotics used in the UK are given to farm animals.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199824","199824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61042","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which Minister in his Department leads on anti-microbial resistance in the UK.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199981","199981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61043","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the uptake rate was of each (a) childhood vaccination, (b) vaccination for people aged 65 and over and (c) vaccination for people who fall into risk groups recommended by his Department as a proportion of the total eligible population for the vaccination, in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199984","199984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61044","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the availability of pneumococcal vaccine to (a) children, (b) adults under the age of 65 in at-risk groups and (c) adults over the age of 65; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199986","199986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61045","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans (a) NHS England and (b) Public Health England have to fund awareness campaigns to increase vaccination uptake rates.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199989","199989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61046","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England plans to commission immunisation services through the any qualified provider procurement model.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199990","199990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61047","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken following his Department's consultation on a review of the procurement of seasonal infuenza vaccine in May 2011.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199991","199991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61048","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in which areas NHS England pays for NHS services through (a) block grants, (b) activity payment mechanisms and (c) outcomes-based approaches.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199992","199992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61049","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment (a) he and (b) NHS England have made of the consistency of NHS England's commissioning of immunisation services in different areas of the country; what plans NHS England has to conduct such an assessment in the future; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199987","199987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61050","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the Statement of Financial Entitlements for the pneumococcal vaccination Directed Enhanced Service for aged 65 years and over and for at-risk groups does not include a national payment scheme.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199985","199985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61051","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish detailed expenditure by NHS England on vaccination and immunisation services in 2013-14.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199988","199988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61052","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps NHS England is taking to reduce inequalities in access to immunisation programmes.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199993","199993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61053","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment NHS England has made of the effectiveness of the delivery of vaccines to recommend at-risk groups of people under 65 in need of (a) influenza, (b) pneumococcal and (c) pertussis vaccines.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199994","199994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61054","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what target vaccination rates are set for each public-funded vaccination programme; what changes have been made to those rates in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199995","199995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61055","2014-06-12","Department for Transport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the planned direct rail service from Shrewsbury to London submitted by Network Rail and Virgin trains to the Office of Rail Regulation.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200025","200025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61056","2014-06-12","Department for Transport","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to create a link between the M54, the M6 northbound and the M6 toll road.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200024","200024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61057","2014-06-16","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what provision is made for the use of non-NHS facilities for MRI scans where the patient's weight precludes the use of an NHS-standard scanner.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200163","200163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61058","2014-06-12","Department of Health","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will meet Ms Diane Belshaw.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200026","200026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61059","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of passport applications have been processed under the expedited service in each month since June 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199970","199970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61060","2014-06-16","Home Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of passport applications have been received in each month since June 2010 from (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199971","199971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61061","2014-06-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 8 April 2014 to the hon. Member for Bradford East, Official Report, columns 222-3W, on private rented housing, when he intends to publish a new model tenancy agreement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 200027","200027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61062","2014-06-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department has provided directly to the public to help understand the threat from extremism and to promote integration; and whether such information has been made available in languages other than English.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199829","199829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61063","2014-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has (a) budgeted and (b) spent on work with Muslim organisations to further integration and community cohesion in (i) the current financial year and (ii) each of the last three years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199833","199833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61064","2014-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what grants his Department has made to Muslim organisations to support integration and community cohesion, by organisation, in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199834","199834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61065","2014-06-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made on developing a model for rent review clauses which are index-linked to inflation.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199822","199822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61066","2014-06-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which organisations involved in reporting hate crime his Department has funded in each financial year since May 2010.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199823","199823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61067","2014-06-12","Home Office","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance his Department has provided to local authorities (a) to help the understand the threat from extremism and (b) relating to statutory powers available to them to challenge extremist speakers.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199827","199827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61068","2014-06-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what research his Department has (a) commissioned and (b) published since May 2010 on citizenship and public attitudes towards extremism.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199828","199828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61069","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training (a) Atos staff and (b) staff of his Department are given in mental health for the purposes of assessing whether claimants are fit for work.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199817","199817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61070","2014-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have currently been waiting (a) up to one month, (b) one to two months, (c) two to three months, (d) three to four months, (e) four to five months and (f) more than six months for their appeal against their being deemed fit for work to be determined.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199818","199818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61071","2014-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the current average waiting time is for personal independence payment assessments to be completed and a decision made in (a) England and (b) Leeds.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199819","199819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61072","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether a Minister will be responsible for preparing the Department's response to the Belgian government's request for information regarding the Typhoon as a successor to their F-16 fleet.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199960","199960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61073","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he intends next to discuss the possibility of Typhoon sales to Belgium with his counterpart in that country.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199961","199961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61074","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when (a) he and (b) other Ministers in his Department last met representatives of BAE to discuss Typhoon exports.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199962","199962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61075","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many officials in his Department he expects to be involved in preparing the Department's response to the Belgian government's request for information regarding the Typhoon as a successor to their F-16 fleet.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199963","199963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61076","2014-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he intends to ask the Foreign and Commonwealth Office and the Ministry of Defence for assistance in pursuing export sales of Typhoon to Belgium.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199964","199964"
