"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446790","2016-01-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to ensure that pet rescue centres scan the microchip of dogs in their care and contact their owners.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23690","23690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446791","2016-01-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received on the refusal of the Kurdistan Regional Government to pay tuition fees and living expenses to Kurd students studying in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23681","23681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446792","2016-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received on the case of the Hares Boys; what discussions he has had with the Israeli authorities on that case; and what information he holds on the current situation.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23710","23710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446793","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will request the government of Burma to release former monk U Gambira from custody.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23626","23626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446794","2016-01-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of progress in electoral registration in Somaliland; and what support the UK is providing for that process.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23619","23619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446795","2016-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information the Government holds on whether blueprints of (a) UK Magnox reactor designs and (b) URENCO uranium enrichment plant designs have been used by North Korea to manufacture plutonium and highly enriched uranium as fissile materials for use in its nuclear warhead programme.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23642","23642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446796","2016-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Question 22275, what assessment his Department made of the risk that items might be used in the commission of a serious violation of international humanitarian law as defined in the Export Control Act 2002 and the EU Common position when making the decision to grant licences for the sale of arms to Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23647","23647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446797","2016-01-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2016 to Question 19992, what the reason was for the time taken to answer that Question.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23634","23634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446798","2016-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials of his Department and at which grades are classified speakers of foreign languages for each such language spoken.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23665","23665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446799","2016-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has formulated plans to assist a mass humanitarian emergency response if instability were to occur in North Korea.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23510","23510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446800","2016-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will increase funding for human rights projects in North Korea.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23511","23511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446801","2016-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK has identified any people or ministries responsible for human rights violations in the Democratic People's Republic of Korea.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23512","23512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446802","2016-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much funding from UK sources is estimated to become available to Iran following the signing of the nuclear deal and sanctions relief.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23560","23560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446803","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures and regulations are in place to ensure that clinical drug tests are low-risk and safe.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23562","23562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446804","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to support Cervical Cancer Awareness Week on 24 to 30 January 2016.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23536","23536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446805","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take in response to recommendation 15 of the Independent Cancer Taskforce report, Achieving world-class cancer outcomes; a strategy for England 2015-2020, published in July 2015, on the use of awareness campaigns to improve uptake of screening programmes for cervical and other cancers.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23554","23554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446806","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with urinary incontinence in each of the last five years; and what the cost to the NHS was of treating that condition in each such year.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23555","23555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446807","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to address falling cervical cancer screening rates among women in age groups (a) 25 to 29 and (b) 60 to 64.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23537","23537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446808","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with urinary incontinence in each clinical commissioning group area in each of the last five years; and what the cost was of treating that condition in each such area in each such year.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23556","23556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446809","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were admitted to hospital for falls and fractures associated with urinary incontinence in each of the last five years; and what the cost to the NHS was of treating people so admitted in each such year.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23557","23557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446810","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were admitted to hospital for urinary tract infections in each of the last five years; and what the cost to the NHS was of treating people so admitted in each such year.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23558","23558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446811","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress is being made on conducting antenatal mental health assessments.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23608","23608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446812","2016-01-26","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on treatment for drug and alcohol addiction in (a) each year since 2010 and (b) each month of 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23579","23579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446813","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were admitted to hospital for catheter-associated urinary tract infections in each of the last five years; and what the cost was of treating those people.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23516","23516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446814","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that pharmacists are trained to understand autism.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23692","23692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446815","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues on safeguards in hospitals for patients who are heavily medicated while they eat.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23650","23650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446816","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people who receive a diagnosis of autism can access appropriate post-diagnostic interventions.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23696","23696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446817","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that health visitors are trained to recognise autism and make appropriate referrals.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23697","23697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446818","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to address the mental health needs of people with autism.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23693","23693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446819","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all GPs are trained in awareness of the diagnostic pathway for people seeking a diagnosis of autism.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23694","23694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446820","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to help prevent bleach and other ineffective treatments advertised as miracle cures being used to treat autism.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23695","23695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446821","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to improve access to food hygiene score information in England.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23652","23652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446822","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to specialist care for people with muscular dystrophy.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23653","23653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446823","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the (a) cost to the economy and (b) number of deaths attributable to antimicrobial resistance in the last 12 months for which figures are available; whether he has made such estimates for future years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23658","23658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446824","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the age at which the death of people with learning disabilities is classified as premature has been set at 60 in the draft NHS Outcomes Framework.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23638","23638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446825","2016-01-26","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS bodies which carry out surgery to repair work performed by outsourcing companies are able to claim back the costs of carrying out that work.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23636","23636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446826","2016-01-26","Cabinet Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prime Minister's speech of 11 January 2016, on life chances, what the sources of the £60 million of social investment for drug and alcohol treatment are expected to be.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23621","23621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446827","2016-01-26","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much compensation the NHS has paid to patients who were injured by healthcare carried out by private contractors in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23616","23616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446828","2016-01-26","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether there is any requirement for NHS bodies which outsource health services to ensure that companies with which they contract are fully insured.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23614","23614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446829","2016-01-26","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether private outsourcing companies which take on NHS contracts and obtain insurance by paying into the NHS insurance scheme are required to contribute (a) full or (b) a partial cost of that cover.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23615","23615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446830","2016-01-26","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to promote awareness across NHS trusts in England of preventative measures to reduce the risk of atrial fibrillation-related strokes.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23717","23717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446831","2016-01-26","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of additional perinatal specialist mental health practitioners that will be needed to meet the additional requirements set out in the Prime Minister's speech on life chances of 11 January 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23676","23676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446832","2016-01-26","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the funding for health measures and services referred to by the Prime Minister in his speech of 11 January 2016, on life chances, will be derived from invest to save measures.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23682","23682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446833","2016-01-26","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2016 to Question 22946, what action he will take to deal with clinical commissioning groups found not to have arrangements in place to offer mental health patients a choice of provider.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23677","23677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446834","2016-01-26","Department of Health","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the NHS of (a) fixing eye operations contracted out by Musgrove Park Hospital which had a high failure rate and (b) paying compensation for eye injuries sustained as a result of operations outsourced by Musgrove Park Hospital.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23680","23680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446835","2016-01-26","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 22087, when she plans to give a substantive answer to that Question.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23674","23674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446836","2016-01-26","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) longest, (b) shortest and (c) average time serving police borough commanders have been in post in London boroughs.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23718","23718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446837","2016-01-26","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police borough commanders there have been in post in each London borough since 2008.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23719","23719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446838","2016-01-26","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provision is made for victims of crimes committed by foreign prisoners to access information about the progress of their deportation.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23716","23716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446839","2016-01-25","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average waiting time for a decision on an asylum application was in each of the last 10 years; and what steps her Department is taking to reduce the waiting time for such decisions.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23654","23654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446840","2016-01-26","Department for Education","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on how many occasions (a) knives, (b) guns and (c) other offensive weapons were found in schools and colleges in each London borough in (i) 2010 and (ii) the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23705","23705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446841","2016-01-25","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many skilled migrant visas were issued in respect of each category of industry in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) 2015.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23669","23669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446842","2016-01-26","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase border security at ferry ports.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23707","23707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446843","2016-01-26","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Government will hold a formal public consultation on proposed extremism disruption orders which makes reference to issues of free speech before bringing such proposals to the House.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23521","23521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446844","2016-01-26","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to ensure that registration on the Worker Registration Scheme between 2009 and 2011 has no bearing on any subsequent application to naturalise as a British citizen.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23522","23522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446845","2016-01-25","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to consult farmers and the agricultural sector on its firearms policy.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23604","23604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446846","2016-01-26","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the number of Syrian refugees brought to the UK under the Private Sponsorship Scheme will be in addition to the Government's commitment to take 50,000 refugees over the next five years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23577","23577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446847","2016-01-26","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Private Sponsorship Scheme for Syrian refugees; and what estimate she has made of the number of people likely to participate in that scheme.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23578","23578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446848","2016-01-26","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost was to the public purse of the public inquiry into the death of Alexander Litvinenko; and what the average cost was to the public purse of inquiries into suspicious deaths undertaken by coroners over the last three years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23589","23589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446849","2016-01-26","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average cost was to the public purse of police investigations into suspicious deaths over the last three years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23590","23590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446850","2016-01-26","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has (a) guidelines issued and (b) imposed rules on police forces relating to the specific information required to be provided to the Disclosure and Barring Service to appear on an individual's record; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23547","23547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446851","2016-01-26","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if police forces will be required to provide information to the Disclosure and Barring Service where a person has been arrested and bailed pending an investigation into their alleged offences.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23543","23543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446852","2016-01-25","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers in (a) Burnley, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West are trained to use tasers.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23565","23565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446853","2016-01-26","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that refugees admitted to the UK from Syria are provided with the necessary support to enable them to integrate into British society.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23576","23576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446854","2016-01-25","Department for International Development","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2015 to Question 16005, what steps her Department is taking to promote water and sanitation within the (a) agriculture, (b) social protection and (c) education programme areas to tackle malnutrition.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23572","23572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446855","2016-01-25","Department for International Development","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2015 to Question 17479, what recent steps her Department has taken to work with the government of Sierra Leone to deliver high-quality programmes that will increase access to clean water.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23574","23574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446856","2016-01-25","Department for International Development","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that adequate clean water is provided in refugee camps near the Syrian border.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23593","23593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446857","2016-01-25","Department for International Development","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the three most common causes of global child mortality were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23598","23598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446858","2016-01-25","Department for International Development","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that all children and young people affected by the Syrian conflict are in school and learning by the 2016-17 school year.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23509","23509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446859","2016-01-25","Department for International Development","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with the UN Relief and Work Agency of the potential effect of financial shortfalls in (a) 2015-16 and (b) future on the provision of aid to the Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23651","23651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446860","2016-01-25","Department for International Development","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what information her Department holds on the number of child mortalities attributable to infections caused by (a) lack of access to safe water and (b) unclean environments of each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23599","23599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446861","2016-01-25","Department for International Development","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what research her Department has conducted or commissioned on the link between poor sanitation and associated hygiene practices and maternal and newborn health and survival.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23629","23629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446862","2016-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offences were committed by (a) escaped or (b) absconded prisoners in each year since 2010; and what those offences were.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23624","23624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446863","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons the National Offender Management Service decided not to impose financial penalties on private prisons on each occasion when such penalties were applicable in the last five years; and what the value of those fines so foregone was.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23627","23627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446864","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Question 22284, how many members of (a) the National Tactical Response Group and (b) Tornado Teams have been injured during a callout at HM Prison Oakwood in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23628","23628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446865","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much (a) the Legal Aid Agency and (b) HM Courts and Tribunal Service spent on intermediaries in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23667","23667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446866","2016-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what process there is for updating victims on the progress of a prisoner's appeal.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23706","23706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446867","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of prisoners who have converted to Islam in prisons in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23661","23661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446868","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of intermediaries were used for (a) witnesses, (b) victims and (c) defendants in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23666","23666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446869","2016-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Question 22284, how many members of (a) the National Tactical Response Group and (b) Tornado Teams have been injured during a call out at HM Prison Oakwood in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23678","23678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446870","2016-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison staff from which prisons were dismissed for conducting inappropriate relationships with prisoners in (a) 2010, (b) 2013, (c) 2014 and (d) 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23523","23523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446871","2016-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the five items most commonly recorded by the Incident Report System are; and how many of each such item were recorded in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23524","23524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446872","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers who have received severance or redundancy packages since May 2010 have subsequently been re-employed (a) as a prison officer or (b) in another capacity by his Department.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23513","23513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446873","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison staff have been dismissed in each year since 2010; what the reasons were for each such dismissal; and how many prison staff have received custodial sentences for crimes committed while working in prisons since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23517","23517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446874","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent representations he has received from charities and families on the effectiveness of the operation of the Fatal Accidents Act 1976.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23526","23526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446875","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the trends in the prison population for (a) white and (b) non-white prisoners over the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23609","23609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446876","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of (a) white and (b) non-white people convicted of a crime were sentenced to immediate custody for each category of offence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23610","23610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446877","2016-01-26","Attorney General","2016-01-21","To ask the Attorney General, what his policy is on use of the charge of treason; and what is his Department's guidance on sentencing those charged and convicted of that offence.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23591","23591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446878","2016-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times police cells were used to hold prisoners overnight in each month in 2014 and 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23552","23552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446879","2016-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners escaped from prison vans in each year since 2010; how many such prisoners remain on the run; of what offences each such prisoner was convicted; and what length of custodial sentence each such prisoner was given.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23553","23553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446880","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward proposals to require the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority to compensate families of victims of criminal offences.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23528","23528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446881","2016-01-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much of the £50 million fund established for First World War commemorations has been allocated to or spent in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23700","23700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446882","2016-01-26","Scotland Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on (a) the nature of the Government's consultation on the proposed Bill of Rights and associated measures and (b) ensuring that that timing does not overlap with the period of the purdah of the Scottish Government or the dissolution of the Scottish Parliament.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23583","23583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446883","2016-01-25","Department for Transport","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what tests a person convicted of death by careless or dangerous driving is required to undertake being allowed to drive again.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23525","23525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446884","2016-01-26","Department for Transport","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the proposed timescales are for the completion of the business case work for the electrification of the Southport to Salford Crescent and Kirkby to Salford Crescent railway lines set out in the March 2015 report of the North of England Electrification Task Force.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23544","23544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446885","2016-01-25","Department for Transport","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward proposals to require the DVLA immediately to (a) suspend the driving licences of people suspected to have drug-related seizures and (b) require such people to undergo medical tests before their suspension can be lifted.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23527","23527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446886","2016-01-26","Department for Transport","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2015 to Question 19163, what assessment his Department has made of reasons for changes in the level of prosecutions for tachograph violations.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23715","23715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446887","2016-01-26","Department for Transport","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Question 22573, what equipment and buildings of any kind situated along the side of the Bexleyheath rail line were damaged in the landslides which blocked the line during the week beginning 11 January 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23673","23673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446888","2016-01-26","Department for Transport","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Question 22575, whether failure to inspect equipment or buildings situated adjacent to Bexleyheath rail line contributed to the line being blocked during the week beginning 11 January 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23671","23671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446889","2016-01-26","Department for Transport","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Question 22574, for what reasons, during the closure of the Bexleyheath rail line during the week beginning 11 January 2016, (a) Southeastern services on adjacent lines were cancelled, (b) there was a lack of information about alternative services and (c) staff had no information to pass onto customers about alternative services or when replacement bus services would arrive; what systems were put in place to communicate regular updates of information to staff so customers could be given accurate advice; what advice was given to staff regarding assistance for people with disabilities; what steps he is taking to determine whether the responses to the situation from Network Rail and Southeastern were adequate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23672","23672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446890","2016-01-25","Department for Transport","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the (a) Egyptian Ambassador and (b) Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs on resuming flights to Sharm El Sheikh.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23664","23664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446891","2016-01-25","Wales Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Welsh Government on Tata Steel's recent announcement on job losses.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23646","23646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446892","2016-01-25","Wales Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Secretaries of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, Work and Pensions and Energy and Climate Change and with the Chancellor of the Exchequer since the announcement of job losses this week by Tata Steel.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23649","23649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446893","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what monitoring his Department is undertaking to ensure that the level of service to the public is not negatively affected by the transfer of responsibilities from the Child Support Agency to the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23656","23656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446894","2016-01-25","HM Treasury","2016-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average time taken was to resolve enquiries from hon. Members about tax credit cases; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce that time.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23655","23655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446895","2016-01-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of whether paragraph 20 of Schedule 9 of the Income Support (General) Regulations 1987 accurately reflects the real costs borne by a claimant who takes a boarder into their home.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23708","23708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446896","2016-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons different criteria apply in the assessment of risk of self-harm or suicide to men and women in his Department's guidance on work capability assessments.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23709","23709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446897","2016-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2016 to Question 22115, why information on the number and value of cold weather payments has not been (a) collected and (b) made available for each constituency in each year since their introduction.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23675","23675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446898","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women in Airdrie and Shotts constituency will be affected by changes in the State Pension Age introduced under the (a) Pensions Act 1995 and (b) Pensions 2011 Act.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23699","23699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446899","2016-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department is developing alternative online identity authentication for people unable to use the Verify system developed by the Cabinet Office.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23539","23539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446900","2016-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many calls to his Department's helpline in 2015 related to universal credit; and what proportion such calls were of the total number of calls.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23538","23538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446901","2016-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of the new technology required to deliver universal credit has been completed to date.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23542","23542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446902","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants with (a) Parkinson's disease, (b) rheumatoid arthritis, (c) motor neurone disease, (d) multiple sclerosis and (e)  cystic fibrosis have been (i) placed in support groups, (ii) placed in the work-related activity group and (iii) found fit for work since 2008; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23529","23529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446903","2016-01-25","HM Treasury","2016-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that parents who are the sole carer for disabled children aged over 18 will not lose out on vital income as a result of the reforms of tax credits.","Biography information for Joanna Cherry","Joanna  Cherry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23530","23530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446904","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to enable special circumstances to be taken into account when making the decision to withhold pension credit to people who are away from their homes for a period of more than four weeks.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23518","23518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446905","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of implementing a scheme based on the actuarial pension model to increase the speed at which women born in the 1950s qualify for state pension.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23514","23514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446906","2016-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to enable claimants to identify themselves online if they are unable to use the Verify system developed by the Cabinet Office.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23540","23540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446907","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on working families of his proposed reductions to the work allowance of universal credit.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23567","23567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446908","2016-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the reasons are for the delay in transferring his Department's Transactional Bulk Print Services contract to Williams Lea from the current provider, Hewlett Packard, originally scheduled for February 2015; what the revised timetable is for that transfer; what assessment he has made of potential risks to service delivery arising from loss of key staff as a result of that delay; and what contingency plans his Department has prepared to mitigate such risks.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23548","23548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446909","2016-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the monetary value was of each type of benefits withdrawn in (a) Dundee and (b) Scotland as a result of benefit sanctions in each month from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23549","23549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446910","2016-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Energy and Climate Change on sharing data on households in receipt of welfare benefits; and what privacy safeguards apply to sharing individuals' data with other Departments.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23581","23581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446911","2016-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claimants of personal independence payments at the time of the introduction of the Centre for Health and Disability Assessments system have been subsequently taken off those payments; and what estimate he has made of the proportion of current claimants of that payment who will be taken off over the next six months.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23586","23586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446912","2016-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what use is made of correspondence from GPs in undertaking personal independence payments assessments.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23587","23587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446913","2016-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether targets have been set for Centre for Health and Disability Assessment staff on the number of people to take off personal independence payments.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23588","23588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447035","2016-01-27","Home Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle extremism in British young people.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903298","903298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447317","2016-01-27","Cabinet Office","2016-01-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much Government funding has been allocated to help increase the number of young people on the electoral register.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903293","903293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446189","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations the Government has received from the Welsh Government on the steel industry in the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23244","23244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446190","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of employers withholding wages from employees; and what steps he is taking to prevent that practice.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23246","23246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446191","2016-01-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the implications are for the Government's policy of bringing into force provisions of the Easter Act 1928 to fix a date for Easter of recent comments by the Archbishop of Canterbury; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23267","23267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446192","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students from the London Borough of Southwark are in receipt of student maintenance grants.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23259","23259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446193","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department plans to include an undertaking to retain the staff of the Green Investment Bank as a condition when privatising that body.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23262","23262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446194","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that the privatisation of the Green Investment Bank represents value for money to the public purse.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23263","23263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446195","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether all companies in the steel industry which are entitled to state aid for renewables obligation and feed-in tariffs are receiving that compensation.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23288","23288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446196","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on the potential effect of China obtaining market economy status on steel dumping across the EU.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23291","23291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446197","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government has requested be taken at EU level to respond to the effects of over-production of Chinese steel.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23292","23292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446198","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on the granting of market economy status to China.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23293","23293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446199","2016-01-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of whether there have been market failures in green and low carbon investment over the last five years; and if she will make an assessment of the most important potential threats to such investment.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23294","23294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446200","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans his Department has to ensure that a privatised Green Investment Bank would be able to maximise the deployment of equity and debt from the European Fund for Structural Investment and other EU sources.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23295","23295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446201","2016-01-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the amount of (a) public and (b) private sector investment needed to fulfil Government targets for low-carbon infrastructure and supply chain investment in each year to 2025.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23296","23296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446202","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the level of security of supply of rare earth metals required by industry.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23377","23377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446203","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students from Warrington North constituency are in receipt of maintenance grants while pursuing a course in higher education.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23376","23376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446204","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his letter of 15 December 2015 setting out Skills Funding Agency priorities and funding for 2016-17, whether it is his policy that an area can only have its adult education budget devolved once it has fully implemented the recommendations of its area review.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23420","23420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446205","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect that China's potential Market Economy Status will have on the UK steel industry; and when he last met the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs to discuss that matter.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23407","23407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446206","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding the Green Investment Bank has invested in fracking projects in the UK.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23436","23436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446207","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the potential costs to (a) consumers and (b) the public purse of the privatisation of the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23437","23437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446208","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether any trade missions to Iran are planned involving businesses from the UK in 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23456","23456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446209","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses were compensated for the indirect costs of the (a) EU Emissions Trading System and (b) carbon price floor; what the average award per eligible business was; and what the total monetary value of such compensation was in (i) 2013-14, (ii) 2014-15 and (iii) 2015-16 to date.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23405","23405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446210","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2015 to Question 657, what tangible progress towards the EU-US Free Trade Agreement had been made by the end of 2015; and whether any agreement in principle had been reached on that matter by that date.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23460","23460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446211","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on how many occasions in each of the last two calendar years his Department has been notified by outside consultants or other third parties of breaches by employees or subcontractors of those consultants of document retention or security policies relating to confidential or secure materials.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23350","23350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446212","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's policy is on providing direct web links to information requested in written parliamentary questions in the Answers to those questions.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23446","23446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446213","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding the Green Investment Bank has invested in fracking projects in the UK.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23448","23448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446214","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the proportion of (a) public and (b) private investment was in each project in which the Green Investment Bank has invested.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23449","23449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446215","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the timescale is for privatisation of the Green Investment Bank; and whether he has made contingency plans to extend that timescale in the event of adverse market conditions.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23450","23450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446216","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions officials in his Department have had with officials of the Department for Work and Pensions on JobCentre Plus involvement in the Find An Apprentice Service.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23454","23454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446217","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many full-time equivalent staff there were in the Skills Funding Agency in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23452","23452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446218","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the National Apprenticeship Service will continue to be (a) administered and (b) funded through the Skills Funding Agency in 2016-17.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23453","23453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446219","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to launch his Department's consultation for target numbers of apprenticeships in the public sector.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23507","23507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446220","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what value of freight was imported by sea into the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23495","23495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446221","2016-01-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what additional checks on standards and quality his Department and the National Apprenticeship Service plan to introduce in response to the targets listed in his Department's publication, English Apprenticeships: Our 2020 Vision, published on 7 December 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23508","23508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446222","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to reduce export costs for businesses to encourage small and medium-sized enterprises to increase their levels of exports.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23498","23498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446223","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department has made an assessment of the impact of its policies on the automotive sector on the competitiveness of that sector.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23499","23499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446224","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to encourage larger companies to make payments to small and medium-sized enterprises on time.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23500","23500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446225","2016-01-22","Cabinet Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young people participated in the National Citizen Service in 2015.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23330","23330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446226","2016-01-22","Cabinet Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what forecast he has made of the number of young people that will participate in the National Citizen Service in each year from 2015 to 2020.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23331","23331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446227","2016-01-25","Cabinet Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has (a) guidelines and (b) a template contract for the leasing of government property to mobile telephone operators for the purposes of erecting masts.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23300","23300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446228","2016-01-22","Cabinet Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate the annual cost of providing places on the National Citizen Service for all children aged 16 and 17.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23302","23302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446229","2016-01-25","HM Treasury","2016-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has had on the number of complaints to the Financial Ombudsman in relation to the misselling of packaged bank accounts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23255","23255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446230","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans the Government has to review the amount of compensation for losses paid to Equitable Life policy holders over the course of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23265","23265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446231","2016-01-25","HM Treasury","2016-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what he assesses to be the major risks to the UK economy.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23378","23378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446232","2016-01-25","HM Treasury","2016-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Question 22263, what procedures, budgets and facilities are in place to compensate tax credit claimants for the cost and inconvenience of losing supporting documents confirming identity and finances lost by the Tax Credit Office.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23398","23398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446233","2016-01-25","HM Treasury","2016-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposed removal of third party contributions from the Landfill Communities Fund on (a) the future availability of funding for community and biodiversity projects and (b) environmental bodies.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23479","23479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446234","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to increase the compensation available to Equitable Life pensioners.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23468","23468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446235","2016-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Question 22026, what proportion of the £47 million paid to local authorities under the Communities and Business Recovery Scheme was subsequently paid by local authorities to households which were not entitled to flood compensation payments.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23341","23341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446236","2016-01-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to ensure that borough councils in two-tier authority areas provide sandbags to all residents to protect their properties during incidents of flooding.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23402","23402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446237","2016-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions in each of the last two calendar years his Department has been notified by outside consultants or other third parties of breaches by employees or subcontractors of those consultants of document retention or security policies relating to confidential or secure materials.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23349","23349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446238","2016-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to require six-monthly inspections of all licensed houses in multiple occupation and bed and breakfasts catering for homeless people.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23439","23439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446239","2016-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2015 to Question 16318, what recent progress he has made on discussions with stakeholders on proposals to exempt certain groups from the removal of automatic entitlement to housing support for 18 to 21 years olds on universal credit; and when he plans to publish proposals resulting from those discussions.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23440","23440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446240","2016-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward plans to (a) require all local authorities to measure the level of single non-priority homelessness in their areas and (b) collate that data in a national database.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23444","23444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446241","2016-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of non-priority single homeless people in the UK in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23445","23445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446242","2016-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what housing support is provided to ex-offenders on leaving prison; and if he will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a statutory requirement to provide settled accommodation for ex-offenders.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23462","23462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446243","2016-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that vulnerable people are prioritised in the provision of settled accommodation.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23326","23326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446244","2016-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of ex-offenders leaving prison who were provided (i) settled and (ii) temporary accommodation in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23419","23419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446245","2016-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues to local authorities on ensuring that consent is granted before a person undertakes work on a neighbour's tree.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23247","23247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446246","2016-01-25","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will assess the potential merits of enabling or compelling local authorities to use housing and council tax benefit data to (a) identify children who are eligible for free school meals and the pupil premium and (b) enable parents and guardians of those children to claim free school meals for their children.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23261","23261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446247","2016-01-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to receive a reply to his letter of 9 December 2015 on behalf of a social housing provider in his constituency.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23258","23258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446248","2016-01-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding streams his Department has for the promotion of tourism to UK regions; and what proportion of those funds was spent on each region in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23251","23251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446249","2016-01-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will discuss with mobile telephone companies steps to reduce and standardise the time between a provider unlocking a phone and the owner of that phone being able to use it with another provider.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23249","23249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446250","2016-01-28","HM Treasury","2016-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the Government's tax reliefs on (a) the film and (b) other creative industries.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23413","23413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446251","2016-01-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the maximum level of engagement by children and young people with the commemoration of the First World War.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23393","23393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446252","2016-01-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2015 to Question 227069, whether his Department has yet considered the recommendations of the Use of Dormant Betting Accounts Report, relating to the use of money from dormant betting accounts and unclaimed winnings held by betting operators for investment in good causes.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23340","23340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446253","2016-01-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with betting operators to ascertain how much is held in dormant betting accounts and unclaimed winnings.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23344","23344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446254","2016-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any person or body has sought disclosure of documents relevant to the decision to target Reyaad Khan by drone strike in Syria on 21 August 2015 for purposes related to the Inquiry by the Intelligence and Security Committee into that matter.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23432","23432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446255","2016-01-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assistance British service personnel are providing to Saudi Arabian forces in Yemen.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23505","23505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446256","2016-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timescale is for the extension of the provisions of the Armed Forces Bill to the Channel Islands.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23501","23501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446257","2016-01-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how the movement of nuclear materials on roads in Scotland by his Department is supervised and regulated.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23386","23386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446258","2016-01-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many movements of nuclear material there have been on roads in Scotland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23374","23374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446259","2016-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implications of the Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015 for the Royal Navy's global reach.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23411","23411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446260","2016-01-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what advisory notices of movements of nuclear material by road in Scotland his Department gives to (a) the Scottish Government and (b) Scottish local authorities in advance of any such movements.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23383","23383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446261","2016-01-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what safety and contingency measures his Department puts in place before nuclear materials are transported on roads in Scotland.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23384","23384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446262","2016-01-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what road routes have been used for the movement of nuclear materials in Scotland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23385","23385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446263","2016-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he last met his Pakistani counterpart.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23338","23338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446264","2016-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department keeps a record of former employees of the Ministry of Defence who are now serving in foreign militaries.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23339","23339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446265","2016-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what analysis his Department has commissioned of the potential effect of a British withdrawal from the EU on Anglo-French defence projects.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23361","23361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446266","2016-01-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference his oral evidence to the Joint Committee on Human Rights of 16 December 2015, Question 20, HC 574, whether his Department's position was that the UK was in an armed conflict (a) before, (b) on the date of or (c) as a result of the drone strike that killed Reyaad Khan of 21 August 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23435","23435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446267","2016-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions his Department has been notified by external consultants or other third parties of breaches by employees or subcontractors of those consultants of document retention or security policies relating to confidential or secure materials.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23346","23346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446268","2016-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the relative distribution of engineering workload across naval bases; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23270","23270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446269","2016-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy that the House be given an opportunity to debate in advance any decision to deploy UK Reaper aircraft outside Syria and Iraq.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23290","23290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446270","2016-01-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answers of 10 November 2015, 4 December 2015 and 12 December 2015 to Questions 17693, 18405 and 18552, when he plans to place in the Library the documents referred to in those Answers.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23301","23301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446271","2016-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any vessels of the Royal Navy or the Royal Fleet Auxiliary have exercised or sought to exercise freedom of navigation or passage rights in disputed areas of the South China Sea claimed by the government of the People's Republic of China since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23284","23284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446272","2016-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any aircraft of the Royal Air Force have exercised or sought to exercise freedom of navigation or passage rights over disputed areas of the South China Sea claimed by the government of the People's Republic of China since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23285","23285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446273","2016-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the comments made by a spokesperson of his Department in an article published in The Herald newspaper on 10 January 2016, and pursuant to his oral contribution of 18 January 2016, Official Report, column 1118, if he will issue guidance to independent monitoring groups on how to contact his Department on, and how to submit evidence relating to, possible civilian casualties from air strikes in Syria and Iraq; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23253","23253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446274","2016-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what working definition of imminence his Department uses in the application of article 51 of the UN Charter.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23242","23242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446275","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is a requirement for schools built through the Priority School Buildings programme to be tested for compliance with acoustic regulations before they open.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23323","23323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446276","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) secondary and (b) primary schools are academies.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23279","23279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446277","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to promote character education in schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23280","23280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446278","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to publish A-Level data for each type of special educational need.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23318","23318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446279","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average point score for deaf A-level students was in 2015 was.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23319","23319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446280","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many deaf students had not achieved a level 2 qualification in English by the age of 19 in 2015.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23320","23320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446281","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many local authorities her Department has identified as being non-compliant with the statutory requirements relating to the content of the Local Offer since September 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23321","23321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446282","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether an evaluation has been undertaken of the Ofsted pilot inspections of local area provision for children with special educational needs and disability; and if she will publish that evaluation.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23314","23314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446283","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many local authorities have been identified by her Department as being non-compliant with the statutory requirements relating to the content of Education, Health and Care plans since September 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23322","23322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446284","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of the Ofsted budget has been allocated for the purpose of carrying out local area inspections of provision for children with special educational needs and disability for each of the next three years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23316","23316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446285","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to improve collection of data on the outcomes achieved by children who have a disability but not a special educational need.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23324","23324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446286","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how she plans to determine whether the Children and Families Act 2014 has successfully improved outcomes for children who have a disability but not a special educational need.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23325","23325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446287","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what amount of additional funding her Department has allocated to Ofsted to carry out local area inspections of provisions for children with special educational needs and disability; and if so, what amount has been allocated for each of the next three years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23313","23313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446288","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding her Department plans to allocate to support the Holocaust Educational Trust's Lessons from Auschwitz Project.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23266","23266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446289","2016-01-25","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to allocate two unique reference numbers to schools which have designated provision within the school for the purpose of differentiating results for that provision and the whole school.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23260","23260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446290","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that demand for school places in Solihull is met.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23347","23347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446291","2016-01-25","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the affordability of childcare in (a) Lambeth, (b) Southwark and (c) London.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23399","23399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446292","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data her Department publishes on the education achievements of children and young people with special educational needs, for each type of special educational need.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23317","23317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446293","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many deaf students achieved three A* to A grades or better in their A-levels in 2015.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23315","23315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446294","2016-01-25","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received from business organisations on the quality of careers information advice and guidance in (a) Lambeth and (b) Southwark; and how she has responded to those representations.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23373","23373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446295","2016-01-25","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with education providers in (a) Lambeth and (b) Southwark on FE area reviews.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23372","23372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446296","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will meet representatives of High Arcal Academy in Dudley to discuss its Condition Improvement Fund bid for a new sports hall.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23334","23334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446298","2016-01-25","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answers of 6 July 2015 to Questions 5048, 5049 and 5050, whether bat removal licences have been granted; and whether it is expected that the new premises for Parkfield School at Hurn will be ready for occupation by September 2016.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23506","23506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446299","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on how many occasions in each of the last two calendar years her Department has been notified by outside consultants or other third parties of breaches by employees or subcontractors of those consultants of document retention or security policies relating to confidential or secure materials.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23345","23345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446300","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans the Government has to improve employment and careers advice.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23469","23469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446301","2016-01-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the effect of the removal of eligibility for Renewables Obligations Certificates on businesses seeking to develop onshore wind farms.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23470","23470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446302","2016-01-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the cost per household of implementing measures agreed at the Paris Climate Conference.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23491","23491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446303","2016-01-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government is taking to improve the process of switching suppliers for customers with prepayment meters.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23416","23416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446304","2016-01-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she plans to provide funding for carbon capture and storage projects in the next Contracts for Difference allocation round.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23417","23417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446305","2016-01-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on how many occasions in each of the last two calendar years her Department has been notified by outside consultants or other third parties of breaches by employees or subcontractors of those consultants of document retention or security policies relating to confidential or secure materials.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23348","23348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446306","2016-01-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the 450 million euros of funding from the EU allocated to carbon capture and storage projects in Yorkshire and the Humber will be spent in the UK following the decision to reduce spending on carbon capture and storage announced in the Comprehensive Spending Review.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23271","23271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446307","2016-01-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether all fines issued in June 2015 by the Environment Agency to aircraft operators for failure to surrender allowances under the EU Emissions Trading System were paid by the deadline.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23303","23303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446308","2016-01-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what representations her Department has received from the Welsh Government on energy costs for the steel industry in the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23243","23243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446309","2016-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on who took the decision to request the use of a helicopter to winch passengers off the bus in Dailley, Ayrshire, during the floods of December 2015.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23256","23256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446310","2016-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on who took the decision not to use a professional heavy vehicle recovery operator to recover the bus which was trapped in floodwater in Dailley, Ayrshire, in December 2015.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23257","23257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446311","2016-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what aspects of policy on (a) farming and (b) other issues within her remit are under discussion in the UK's negotiations with other EU member states on the terms of UK membership of the EU; and what her role has been in those negotiations.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23252","23252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446312","2016-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which Ministers and staff of her Department will be attending the Hanoi Conference on the Illegal Wildlife Trade in November 2016; and what the projected cost of that attendance will be in (a) staff salaries, (b) travel and (c) other costs.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23306","23306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446313","2016-01-22","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to co-ordinate steps to enhance public transport and accelerate the transition to ultra-low emission vehicles.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23277","23277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446314","2016-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has  made of the level of milk prices paid to farmers in comparison to their costs of production.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23397","23397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446315","2016-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether it is her policy to make funding available for woodland planting to help with water retention during times of flooding.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23364","23364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446316","2016-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2015 to Question 11026, whether the Inter-Ministerial Group on International Animal Welfare has met; when that group's next meeting will be; and who will be chairing that group.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23463","23463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446317","2016-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many farmers who were on the Higher Level Scheme and Entry Level Scheme have joined the Countryside Stewardship Scheme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23337","23337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446318","2016-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to increase the amount of British meat sold in supermarkets.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23354","23354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446319","2016-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of measures to stimulate demand for recycled material; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23375","23375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446320","2016-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much compensation has been paid to farmers for loss of cattle in badger cull areas (a) in each of the three years before that cull started and (b) since that cull started.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23327","23327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446321","2016-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the proportion of farmers who will have received their payments under the Basic Payments Scheme by the end of January 2016.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23371","23371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446322","2016-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the trends in the level of farm borrowing.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23369","23369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446323","2016-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to introduce interim payments under the Basic Payments Scheme for farmers who have not received their payments by the end of January 2016.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23370","23370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446324","2016-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the European Commission's Circular Economy Action Plan proposals, published in December 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23430","23430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446325","2016-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will make funds available to help clear up debris from the flooding of farmers' fields in cases in which those farmers have allowed that land to flood to help avoid flooding elsewhere.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23328","23328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446326","2016-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what government funding is available to pay farmers to allow parts of their land to flood to avoid flooding elsewhere.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23442","23442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446327","2016-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy that there will be no further emergency authorisations of the use of neonicotinoid pesticides.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23360","23360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446328","2016-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the merits of refunding money lost by farmers under the modulation scheme to farmers who are taking part in the trial badger cull scheme.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23443","23443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446329","2016-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 11 January 2016 to Question 21375 and of 18 January 2016 to Question 22215 on flood control: per capita costs, what steps she took to ensure that the geographical boundaries of Environment Agency areas and census regions matched for the purposes of those calculations.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23408","23408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446330","2016-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Bourne Report on the incidence of bovine TB in badger cull areas been updated since 2014.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23465","23465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446331","2016-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many partridge (a) eggs for hatching, (b) chicks and (c) poults were imported into England from each EU country in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23489","23489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446332","2016-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many pheasant (a) eggs for hatching, (b) chicks and (c) poults were imported into England from each EU country in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23488","23488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446333","2016-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will disclose a summary of his Department's legal advice to the (a) Joint Committee on Human Rights and (b) Intelligence and Security Committee relevant to the drone strike that killed Reyaad Khan on 21 August 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23431","23431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446334","2016-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the UK Embassy in Israel has taken to monitor attacks on Christian places of worship.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23464","23464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446335","2016-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proposal the Government plans to put to the second UN open-ended working group on nuclear disarmament.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23329","23329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446336","2016-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether the Shia in Bahrain accept the Al Khalifa government as the legitimate government of that country.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23382","23382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446337","2016-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the number of political prisoners in Bahrain; and if he will make representations to the government of Bahrain calling for the release of such prisoners.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23381","23381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446338","2016-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on how many occasions his Department has been notified by external consultants or other third parties of breaches by employees or subcontractors of those consultants of document retention or security policies relating to confidential or secure materials in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23481","23481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446339","2016-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which Ministers and staff of his Department will be attending the Hanoi Conference on the Illegal Wildlife Trade in November 2016; and what the projected cost of that attendance will be in (a) staff salaries, (b) travel and (c) other costs.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23305","23305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446340","2016-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made a formal request for the Government of the People's Republic of China to state the legal basis for its territorial claims in the South China Sea.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23312","23312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446341","2016-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to protect Christians in Syria from persecution by Daesh.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23250","23250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446342","2016-01-22","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has conducted or commissioned on the effectiveness of pre-exposure prophylaxis in preventing HIV infection in men who have sex with men.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23245","23245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446343","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Prime Minister's speech of 11 January 2016, on life chances, how the £400 million funding for community and home mental health teams will be allocated.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23473","23473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446344","2016-01-25","Cabinet Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prime Minister's speech of 11 January 2016, on life chances, what period the £30 million social investment outcomes fund will cover; when that funding will become available; and to which bodies that funding will be made available.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23474","23474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446345","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Prime Minister's speech of 11 January 2016, on life chances, how the waiting time target for patients with psychosis will be monitored; and when the first results of that monitoring will be published.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23475","23475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446346","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in which regions the NHS provides funding for IVF treatment.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23477","23477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446347","2016-01-22","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions his Department has been notified by external consultants or other third parties of breaches by employees or subcontractors of those consultants of document retention or security policies relating to confidential or secure materials in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23482","23482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446348","2016-01-22","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many admissions there were to accident and emergency departments of children requiring tooth extraction in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23363","23363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446349","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many incidents of medication errors involving hospital patients with Parkinson's disease resulting in (a) no, (b) low, (c) moderate and (d) severe harm were reported to the National Reporting and Learning System in the last quarter of 2014 and in each quarter of 2015; and which reporting organisation reported each such incident.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23406","23406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446350","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department paid to charities in 2014-15; and what criteria were used to make decisions about those payments.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23458","23458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446351","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times the Sexual Health Forum has met in each of the last five years; what the dates were of each such meeting; and who attended each such meeting.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23396","23396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446352","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurse training places were available in England in each year from 2009 to 2015.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23380","23380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446353","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the removal of bursaries for nurse training on the diversity of the workforce; and if he will place in the Library a copy of the evidence used in making that assessment.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23379","23379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446354","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many da Vinci surgical systems for use in the treatment of prostate cancer are in operation in the NHS in England.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23429","23429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446355","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve recruitment and retention of embryologists in the NHS in (a) England and (b) the North East.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23390","23390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446356","2016-01-25","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of difficulties in recruiting embryologists in (a) England and (b) the North East.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23391","23391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446357","2016-01-22","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that the men who have sex with men population is aware of the availability of the HPV vaccination at sexual health clinics.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23466","23466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446358","2016-01-22","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when HPV vaccinations are planned to be available at sexual health clinics to men who have sex with men.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23467","23467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446359","2016-01-22","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve end of life care and the account taken of the needs of patients with regard to (a) hydration and (b) respect and dignity.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23492","23492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446360","2016-01-22","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to reduce levels of obesity.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23490","23490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446361","2016-01-22","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with Bell's Palsy in each of the last five years; and how many such people were (a) women and (b) men aged (i) under 18, (ii) between 18 and 45, (iii) between 45 and 65 and (iv) over 65.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23502","23502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446362","2016-01-22","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal College of Nursing on whether there may be a connection between passive smoking and the menopause.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23503","23503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446363","2016-01-22","Department of Health","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential link between social media and self-harm among young people.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23494","23494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446364","2016-01-22","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of women murdered as a result of domestic violence.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23493","23493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446365","2016-01-22","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure that asylum seekers are not housed in properties that make their status as asylum seekers easily identifiable.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23358","23358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446366","2016-01-22","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what requirement there is for a person to reveal their identity when requested to do so by a police officer.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23441","23441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446367","2016-01-22","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when (a) her Department and (b) the contractor G4S became aware of concerns that asylum seekers were being housed in properties with doors that are all uniform or nearly uniform in colour.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23356","23356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446368","2016-01-22","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects the inquiry announced by her Department on 20 January 2016 into the housing of asylum seekers in the north-east of England to report its findings.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23357","23357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446369","2016-01-22","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to increase the number of psychological and psychiatric specialist services available for Syrian refugees and asylum seekers in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23333","23333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446370","2016-01-22","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Syrian refugees and asylum seekers were informed of mental health provisions they could expect in Northern Ireland before they agreed to settle there.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23332","23332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446371","2016-01-25","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Question 21728, how many applications for a Tier 2 (General) restricted Certificate of Sponsorship have been rejected on the grounds that the job is in an establishment which provides a take-away service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23423","23423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446372","2016-01-25","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of people who were interviewed under caution (a) for all offences and (b) for sexual offences were subsequently charged in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23368","23368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446373","2016-01-25","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20287, when she plans to give a substantive answer to that question.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23422","23422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446374","2016-01-25","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department provides to police forces on how to deal with a situation in which an emergency 999 call is erroneously directed to the wrong police force; and what procedures police forces have put in place to deal with such a situation.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23400","23400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446375","2016-01-25","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether (a) Ministers and (b) officials in her Department have met (i) mobile telephone operators and (ii) BT to discuss the transfer of emergency calls made from mobile telephones to the wrong police force.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23401","23401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446376","2016-01-25","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that people using mobile telephones to call 999 are put in touch with the correct police force; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23404","23404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446377","2016-01-25","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued to police forces on their emergency response to incidents reporting breaking and entering, burglary and vandalism to vehicles, and other criminal activity when the criminal act is reported as being in progress.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23403","23403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446378","2016-01-22","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions her Department has been notified by external consultants or other third parties of breaches by employees or subcontractors of those consultants of document retention or security policies relating to confidential or secure materials in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23483","23483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446379","2016-01-22","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether contractors have housed asylum seekers in properties with doors that are all uniform or nearly uniform in colour in regions other than the North East.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23355","23355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446380","2016-01-25","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Questions 22594 and 22595, whether it is her Department's policy that an applicant for international protection who enters the UK from France clandestinely but had not made an application for international protection in France should be returned to France in accordance with the Dublin Regulation.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23455","23455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446381","2016-01-22","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Ministers and staff of her Department will be attending the Hanoi Conference on the Illegal Wildlife Trade in November 2016; and what the projected cost of that attendance will be in (a) staff salaries, (b) travel and (c) other costs.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23304","23304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446382","2016-01-22","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the rationale is for people on spousal visas resident in the UK being required to pay a health surcharge as part of their visa.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23278","23278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446383","2016-01-25","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of illegal immigrants in residence in each constituent region and nation of the UK in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23254","23254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446385","2016-01-22","Department for International Development","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, on how many occasions her Department has been notified by external consultants or other third parties of breaches by employees or subcontractors of those consultants of document retention or security policies relating to confidential or secure materials in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23484","23484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446386","2016-01-22","Department for International Development","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2016 to Question 20675, how much of the £300 million provided to eradicate polio was spent in each of the last three years; and how much will be spent in each of the next four years.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23362","23362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446387","2016-01-22","Department for International Development","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to InsuResilience, the G7 Initiative on Climate Risk Insurance, if she will make it her policy to (a) allocate additional funding of £100 million to that programme, (b) scale up by at least £50 million weather-indexed microinsurance that provides direct coverage for smallholder farmers pastoralists and other vulnerable groups and (c) increase her Department's grant funding for the African Risk Capacity to £20 million in order to improve the capacity of that programme to meet its targets.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23366","23366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446388","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff working in (a) young offender institutions, (b) secure training centres and (c) secure children's homes have been (i) suspended following a child protection allegation (ii) disciplined following a child protection allegation, (iii) dismissed following a child protection allegation and (iv) convicted of sexual or violent offences against children in the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23395","23395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446389","2016-01-25","Home Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the change was in the number of people convicted of murder between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23459","23459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446390","2016-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions his Department has been notified by external consultants or other third parties of breaches by employees or subcontractors of those consultants of document retention or security policies relating to confidential or secure materials in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23485","23485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446391","2016-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much G4S was paid for (a) bedding, (b) children's birthdays, (c) Christmas allowances, (d) children's sports and PE costs, (e) educational materials, (f) electricity, (g) staff uniforms, (h) staff training materials and (i) stationery at Medway Secure Training Centre for Young People in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23353","23353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446392","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national offenders are in prison in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23472","23472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446393","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of offender-on-offender violence there have been in (a) secure children's homes, (b) secure training centres, (c) youth offender institutions and (d) young offenders institutions in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23478","23478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446394","2016-01-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many enforcements under the Housing Health and Safety Rating System have been made as a result of category 1 hazards relating to (a) gas safety and (b) electrical safety in each local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23392","23392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446395","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many grievances have been lodged by Prison Service staff in each prison in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23394","23394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446396","2016-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Question 22665, which ministers visited Medway Secure Training Centre on which dates.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23286","23286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446397","2016-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what special measures exist for survivors of domestic abuse in the family courts in child contact proceedings.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23268","23268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446398","2016-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that judges and other decision-makers have appropriate knowledge and training on issues relating to child arrangements orders made in the family court in cases in which there is a history of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23269","23269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446399","2016-01-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what is the maximum amount of time his Department has determined as a reasonable time for court users to have to travel to their nearest court by public transport when making decisions on court closures.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23272","23272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446400","2016-01-22","Leader of the House","2016-01-20","To ask the Leader of the House, what events have taken place in the Leader's Parliamentary Office in 2016; and what the cost to the public purse has been of each such event.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23287","23287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446401","2016-01-22","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, on how many occasions her Department has been notified by external consultants or other third parties of breaches by employees or subcontractors of those consultants of document retention or security policies relating to confidential or secure materials in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23486","23486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446402","2016-01-22","Prime Minister","2016-01-20","To ask the Prime Minister, whether any person or body has sought disclosure of his Department's legal advice on the drone strike that killed Reyaad Khan for purposes related to the Inquiry by the Intelligence and Security Committee into that matter.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23433","23433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446403","2016-01-25","Prime Minister","2016-01-20","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he plans to issue a new Memorandum of Understanding under section 2(2) of the Justice and Security Act on the remit of the Intelligence and Security Committee in the current Parliament.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23447","23447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446404","2016-01-22","Prime Minister","2016-01-20","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will disclose a summary of the government advice on the legality of the drone strike that killed Reyaad Khan in the manner set out in Part 6 of the Cabinet Manual.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23438","23438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446405","2016-01-25","Scotland Office","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with Ministers in the Department for Transport on the closure of the West Coast Main Line between Glasgow and Carlisle.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23410","23410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446406","2016-01-25","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2016-01-20","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, how many P11D forms for 2014-15 were incorrectly issued by IPSA.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23273","23273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446407","2016-01-25","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2016-01-20","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, what discussions the Committee has had with IPSA on the reissuing of the P11D forms for hon. Members for 2014-15.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23274","23274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446408","2016-01-25","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2016-01-20","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, what discussions the Committee has had with HM Revenue and Customs on the reissuing of P11D forms for hon. Members for 2014-15.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23275","23275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446409","2016-01-25","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2016-01-20","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, what information the Committee holds on steps being taken by IPSA to prevent errors in P11D forms for hon. Members occurring in future financial years.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23276","23276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446410","2016-01-22","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2015 to Question 11881, if he will discuss with the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency the reasons for that agency not approving the pilot scheme for bike racks on the front of buses in Bath in 2015.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23248","23248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446411","2016-01-25","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to bring into force the provisions in the Deregulation Act 2015 to allow for special permits to be issued for on-road racing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23264","23264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446412","2016-01-22","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department is aware of any occasion since 2010 on which the government of the People's Republic of China has sought to limit or exclude civilian aircraft registered in the UK from exercising freedom of navigation or passage rights over disputed areas of the South China Sea by that government.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23283","23283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446413","2016-01-25","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the cost to business of the closure of the West Coast Main Line between Glasgow and Carlisle.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23409","23409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446414","2016-01-25","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will assess the implications for his policies of the Oxford Research Group's recent report entitled, The Hostile use of Drones by Non-State Actors against British Targets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23388","23388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446415","2016-01-25","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which (a) ministers attended and (b) departments are represented on the Government's working group on drones; when that group was formed; and what its schedule of meetings is.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23389","23389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446416","2016-01-22","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to section 3.3 of his recently published British Road Safety Statement, how the incentive element of local roads maintenance funding will operate.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23359","23359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446417","2016-01-25","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that London is accessible by rail to people who cannot afford peak-time prices and are on lower incomes, when they are travelling to London for meetings during working hours.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23424","23424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446418","2016-01-25","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will hold discussions with train operators on making the process of purchasing railway tickets from ticket machines simpler in respect of (a) indicating peak and off-peak times, (b) where peak and off-peak times differs between train operators and (c) in other ways.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23425","23425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446419","2016-01-22","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 20950, which routes would offer greater benefits from the additional paths referred to in that answer than the proposal from Arriva Trains Wales.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23415","23415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446420","2016-01-22","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 20950, how many other rail franchises his Department has commented on to the Office of Rail and Road in relation to track access when new additional paths are created.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23414","23414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446421","2016-01-22","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what schemes are available to commercial drivers under the plug-in van grant scheme to purchase a home charge and charge point at work.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23365","23365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446422","2016-01-22","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many more modern, safer pedestrian crossings he expects to be introduced as a consequence of the revision in 2014 of the Traffic Signs Regulations and General Directions.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23352","23352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446423","2016-01-22","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the Birmingham to Bristol rail line to be electrified.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23351","23351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446424","2016-01-22","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions his Department has been notified by external consultants or other third parties of breaches by employees or subcontractors of those consultants of document retention or security policies relating to confidential or secure materials in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23487","23487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446425","2016-01-25","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's statistical table BUS0840, on discretionary concessionary travel enhancements, which Travel Concessionary Authorities that reported that they funded enhancements in 2010-11 did not report funding those enhancements in 2015-16 in the category of (a) companions to disabled people, (b) young people, (c) extensions to travel times pre 0930, (d) extensions beyond 2300 during weekdays and (e) national rail services within geographic area.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23476","23476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446426","2016-01-22","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps he has taken to promote safety among older drivers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23343","23343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446427","2016-01-22","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's British Road Safety Statement, published in December 2015, Cm 9175, when he plans to consult on legislative changes to improve urban cycle safety by ensuring that sideguards and rear under-run devices are not removed from HGVs but remain permanently fitted.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23471","23471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446428","2016-01-22","Department for Transport","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he had made of the progress in introducing graduated licensing for drivers in Northern Ireland; and what representations he has received on that matter.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23342","23342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446429","2016-01-25","Women and Equalities","2016-01-20","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what progress she is making on raising the profile of International Women's Day.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23367","23367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446430","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many completed repeat work capability assessments there have been of people with (a) cystic fibrosis, (b) rheumatoid arthritis, (c) motor neurone disease, (d) multiple sclerosis and (e) Parkinson's disease in each year since the introduction of employment and support allowance in 2008.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23299","23299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446431","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the average change in income for an individual as of the result of the delay in qualifying for pension credit resulting from the introduction of the revised state pension age timetable in the Pensions Act 2011.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23298","23298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446432","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the cost of reinstating the qualifying age for pension credit to its 1995 timetable.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23297","23297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446433","2016-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many reimbursement claims his Department has received from UK citizens for health treatment in other European countries for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23281","23281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446434","2016-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2016 to Question 22645, what estimate he has made of the potential cost of answering that question for each of the resources that would be so required.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23282","23282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446435","2016-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the UK's arrangements with French authorities for processing reimbursement claims from UK citizens for state-funded health treatment received in France.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23307","23307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446436","2016-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for which countries that the UK has reimbursement arrangements with under the European Health Insurance Card regulations his Department has identified as not having staff with relevant language skills.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23308","23308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446437","2016-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what arrangements are in place to enable UK citizens to submit reimbursement claims under the European Health Insurance Card regulations; and what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of those arrangements.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23309","23309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446438","2016-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what languages his Department's overseas health team is trained to speak.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23311","23311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446439","2016-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with cancer who were awarded the daily living component of personal independence payment scored all of their points due to aid and appliances.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23289","23289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446440","2016-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidelines are in place on the amount of time that should be taken to process reimbursement claims from UK citizens for health treatment in other European countries; and what data his Department holds on the average amount of time taken to process such claims.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23310","23310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446441","2016-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the likely average change in the amount received by workless 18 to 21 year olds as a result of the removal of housing allowance from such people in April 2017.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23336","23336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446442","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many motability vehicles were held by people in (a) Wrexham, (b) Wales and (c) the UK in receipt of the enhanced mobility component of personal independence payments in each of the last six months for which records are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23451","23451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446443","2016-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the removal of housing allowance for 18 to 21 year-olds who receive universal credit in the number of (a) homeless people and (b) claimants living on temporary accommodation.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23434","23434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446444","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to assist people with restricted visibility pursuing careers and training opportunities.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23457","23457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446445","2016-01-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the gross working premium of insurers which was required to fund the Diffuse Mesothelioma Payments Scheme in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23412","23412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446446","2016-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will take into account the effect on blind and partially sighted people when deciding whether to change eligibility for recipients of the personal independence payment daily living component who qualify because of their use of aids and appliances.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23418","23418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446447","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2016 to Question 22115, whether information on the number and value of cold weather payments is kept by local authority area; what data his Department keeps on cold weather payments; and what steps his Department has taken to keep Parliament updated about cold weather payments.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23421","23421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446448","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease have had at least one repeat assessment, by year of initial assessment, since the introduction of employment and support allowance in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23426","23426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446449","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many completed repeat assessments there have been of people with Parkinson's disease by year of repeat assessment, since the introduction of employment and support allowance in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23427","23427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446450","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with motor neurone disease who have been awarded the daily living component of personal independence payment scored all of their points due to aid and appliances","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23387","23387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446451","2016-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of workless 18 to 21-year olds who will be enrolled on universal credit in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19 and (d) 2019-20.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23335","23335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446452","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease have been placed in (a) the support group and (b) the work-related activity group with a prognosis statement of (i) three, (ii) six, (iii) 12, (iv) 18 months, (v) two years and (vi) in the longer term since the introduction of employment and support allowance in 2008.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23428","23428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446453","2016-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with (a) cystic fibrosis, (b) rheumatoid arthritis, (c) motor neurone disease, (d) multiple sclerosis and (e) Parkinson's disease have had at least one repeat work capability assessment by year of initial assessment since the introduction of employment support allowance in 2008.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23480","23480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446730","2016-01-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with his Cabinet colleagues on cases in which workers do not receive compensation awarded by an employment tribunal because the companies which were paying them less than the national minimum wage have moved into voluntary liquidation.","Biography information for Pat Glass","Pat Glass","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903245","903245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447576","2016-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will discuss with the Secretary of State for Defence ways by which vexatious claims against soldiers who have served on operations overseas can be minimised; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903257","903257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447577","2016-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans the Government has to seek legislative consent from the Scottish Parliament for the proposed repeal of the Human Rights Act 1998.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903254","903254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447578","2016-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Government plans to publish the findings of its review of employment tribunal fees.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903255","903255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447579","2016-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans the Government has to seek legislative consent from the Scottish Parliament for the proposed repeal of the Human Rights Act 1998.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903258","903258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445835","2016-01-21","Attorney General","2016-01-19","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions have been brought under the Fraud Act 2006 in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23175","23175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445836","2016-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many meetings Ministers have had with representatives of Keep me Posted since May 2015.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23120","23120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445837","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received on the proposed privatisation of the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23237","23237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445838","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Office for National Statistics on the issuing of special shares in the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23238","23238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445839","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the privatisation of the Green Investment Bank on the level of investment it will make in the UK green economy.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23239","23239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445840","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2015 to Question 14108, whether the Government has imposed binding conditions in previous privatisations.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23240","23240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445841","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that UK citizens can take up apprenticeships in other EU states.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23206","23206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445842","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that best practice is shared with each of the devolved institutions on development among employers of agri-tech and skills strategies.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23207","23207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445843","2016-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps the Government has taken to improve toy safety.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23052","23052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445844","2016-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what regulations govern the manufacture, import and sale of laser pens in the UK.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23018","23018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445845","2016-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an estimate of the collective cost to small and medium-sized enterprises to recover overdue payments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23007","23007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445846","2016-01-21","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to improve the monitoring of late payments by insurance companies to claims made by small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23008","23008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445847","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the cost and benefits of using (a) Green ISAs and Citizen Finance, (b) UK Pension Funds, (c) the European Investment Bank and (d) co-funding with devolved administrations as a means of increasing its capital base.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23094","23094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445848","2016-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2015 to Question 18005, how many of the students in Burnley qualified for maintenance grants in academic year 2013-14.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23065","23065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445849","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what options were considered during the decision-making process of privatisation of the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23222","23222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445850","2016-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the proposed sale of the Green Investment Bank will include all assets of the bank.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23223","23223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445851","2016-01-21","Cabinet Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of per capita GDP in each of the nations of the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23166","23166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445852","2016-01-22","Cabinet Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to ensure a reduction in the use of paper in departments.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23076","23076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445853","2016-01-22","Cabinet Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of people removed from the electoral register since December 2015 are (a) men and (b) women.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23086","23086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445854","2016-01-22","Cabinet Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people who voted in the 2015 General Election are not on the latest electoral register.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23087","23087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445855","2016-01-22","Cabinet Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total cost is of the transfer to Individual Electoral Registration; and what proportion of such costs have been borne by local government.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23088","23088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445856","2016-01-22","Cabinet Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of ministerial letters have been signed on behalf of Ministers in their absence in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23025","23025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445857","2016-01-22","Cabinet Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will commission an assessment of the potential economic impact on Oldham of the reduction in Oldham's public estate.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23030","23030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445858","2016-01-21","Cabinet Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will ensure that charity commissions across the UK collaborate to ensure that extremist groups are unable to obtain charitable status.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23180","23180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445859","2016-01-21","Cabinet Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect of civil service redundancies in the last 12 months on the effectiveness of departments' work.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23139","23139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445860","2016-01-21","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to provide assistance to people who have purchased homes under the Help to Buy scheme in the event that interest rates subsequently rise.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23182","23182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445861","2016-01-21","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is his policy to change the rate of fuel duty applied to certain isolated and rural areas in response to changes in oil price.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23181","23181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445862","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with waste operators on the effect of planned changes to the Landfill Communities Fund.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23195","23195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445863","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on waste operators of planned changes to the Landfill Communities Fund.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23196","23196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445864","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how he plans to assess the effectiveness of the implementation in the UK of the EU Anti-Money Laundering Directive.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23205","23205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445865","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the new electronic system of quarterly income tax reporting will allow small businesses to align their reporting with VAT returns.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23214","23214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445866","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) employees and (b) employers have taken advantage of savings to National Insurance contributions from salary sacrifice schemes for occupational pensions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23085","23085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445867","2016-01-21","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the number of people in the UK who own property worth over £1 million.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23056","23056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445868","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what Government capital projects (a) have been carried out in the last and (b) are planned over the next five years in Greater Manchester; and what the (i) cost and (ii) location was and will be for each such project.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23029","23029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445869","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the likely change in the number of projects being funded through the Landfill Communities Fund if the Contributory Third Party element is removed.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23152","23152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445870","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will publish the results of its consultation into the Reform of the Landfill Communities Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23157","23157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445871","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether (a) all and (b) part of the funding for universal technology schools count as public sector borrowing for the purposes of calculating the national debt.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23159","23159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445872","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of how much has been lost to the National Insurance Fund from salary sacrifice schemes for occupational pensions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23083","23083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445873","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to (a) make provision for non-EU furnished holiday let owners to benefit from the ability to offset finance costs, but not the additional reliefs that are available to EU furnished holiday let owners, or to extend the definition of a furnished holiday let to be include non-EU properties and enable access to all reliefs.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23099","23099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445874","2016-01-21","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether preliminary impact assessments were carried out on the effect of the current HM Revenue and Customs Location Strategy on local tax compliance, across all heads of duty, the Scottish economy, equal opportunities in Scotland, the environment, and the individual staff whose offices are to be closed and what those assessments have indicated.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23041","23041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445875","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has conducted research on the total cost to the public purse of tax credits paid to private hire vehicle drivers in London in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23013","23013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445876","2016-01-22","HM Treasury","2016-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number and value of projects funded by the Landfill Communities Fund in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23224","23224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445877","2016-01-21","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to the public purse was of the purchase of the Kingsland Fire Station site for use by the Hackney New Primary School; and how much accrued to the public purse from the sale of that site.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23068","23068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445878","2016-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the overall effect of changes to housing legislation and housing-related benefits which have come into force since 2010.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23149","23149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445879","2016-01-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of housing association residents have access to the internet at home.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23146","23146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445880","2016-01-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of local authority social housing residents have access to the internet at home.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23147","23147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445881","2016-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many disabled social housing residents have moved out of their property in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23148","23148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445882","2016-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities offer a council tax (a) exemption and (b) discount to foster carers within their area.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23145","23145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445883","2016-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of changes in the level of services provided by housing associations to tenants since 2013.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23150","23150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445884","2016-01-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many disabled housing association residents moved out of their property in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23121","23121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445885","2016-01-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment (a) his Department and (b) Ofcom have made of the effectiveness of the gaining provider-led notification of transfer process for broadband since its introduction.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23179","23179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445886","2016-01-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if the Government will set out for broadcasters the level of progress it expects to see on the provision of subtitles and audio-descriptions for on-demand content before it reviews the legislation in that area.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23040","23040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445887","2016-01-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the role of the Code for America programme and its applicability to the UK.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23160","23160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445889","2016-01-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of spaces available for disabled people in music venues; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John McNally","John Mc Nally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23066","23066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445890","2016-01-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of relocation of Ofcom departments from London to other areas of the country on Ofcom's ability to maintain its service standards.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23000","23000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445891","2016-01-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, on what basis Broadband Delivery UK (BDUK) provides forecasts for the rollout of BDUK-funded broadband infrastructure in local areas.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23015","23015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445892","2016-01-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what responsibilities Ofcom has for (a) data protection, (b) consumer rights relating to data and (c) data markets; and what plans he has to review those responsibilities.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23016","23016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445893","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the effect equipment gifted to the Lebanese armed forces between 2012 and 2015 on that country's ability to secure its border with Syria against (a) the spread of the Syrian conflict, (b) the movement of Hezbollah fighters supporting the Assad Regime and (c) the movement of Daesh fighters.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23071","23071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445894","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many veterans in (a) Pendle, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West have been helped by Veterans UK since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23072","23072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445895","2016-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much of the (a) conflict pool and (b) conflict security stability fund has been allocated to other states fighting Daesh since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23069","23069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445896","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much Veterans UK has spent on providing support to veterans in (a) Pendle, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23070","23070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445897","2016-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times unsanctioned Russian military aircraft have been detected entering UK airspace in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23095","23095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445898","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to ensure that harbours can accommodate any new vessels built for use by the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23047","23047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445899","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the importance of the (a) Merchant Navy and (b) Royal Fleet Auxiliary to the security of the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23045","23045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445900","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what training his Department provides for women to enable them to serve in combat on the front line.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23046","23046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445901","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assistance the Government has given to the Libyan government for training Libyan army personnel.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23048","23048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445902","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent representations he has received in favour of Government involvement in any part of the running of departments or divisions of Rolls Royce connected to that company's production of the Nuclear Reactor Component of the Successor Programme.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23128","23128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445903","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of whether Rolls Royce will complete the Nuclear Reactor Component of the Successor Programme on schedule; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23127","23127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445904","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in how many countries UK Reapers are currently operational.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23171","23171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445905","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether UK Reapers have been deployed to Libya.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23172","23172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445906","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much is spent daily on food on each serving solider.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23130","23130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445907","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the quality and nutritional value of food served to the Armed Forces.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23131","23131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445908","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many inspections have been carried out into the quality of the food served to UK Armed Forces in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23132","23132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445909","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on whether there has been an application to the Criminal Cases Review Commission in respect of the case of Sergeant Blackman.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23100","23100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445910","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what guidance his Department has issued on the standard, quality and nutritional content of food served to UK armed forces.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23136","23136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445911","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions his Department held with its French counterpart on the potential effect on Anglo-French defence contracts of a British exit from the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23129","23129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445912","2016-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Caroline principles are applied to any further targeted killing carried out in self-defence of the UK.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23236","23236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445913","2016-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any personnel from UK Reaper Squadrons have been deployed to (a) Libya, (b) Kenya and (c) Somalia in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23227","23227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445914","2016-01-21","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the financial savings to schools in (a) Pendle, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West as a result of its memorandum of understanding with Microsoft announced on 13 January 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23167","23167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445915","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of teaching vacancies at the start of September 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23198","23198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445916","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many higher education institutions have had their funding allocated by the National College of Teaching and Leadership reduced as a consequence of training more teachers than places allocated in each academic year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23197","23197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445917","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what records her Department keeps of the number of unfilled teaching positions at secondary schools (a) nationally and (b) in each local authority area.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23199","23199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445918","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many places were available on teacher training courses at higher education institutions in each academic year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23200","23200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445919","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will discuss with the Secretary of State for Defence how the best examples of literacy and numeracy education carried out in initial basic training in HM Armed Forces can be introduced to assist underachieving pupils in attaining GCSE grade C in English and mathematics.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23241","23241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445920","2016-01-21","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase secondary school places in London.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23125","23125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445921","2016-01-21","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has been deducted from funding allocated by the National College of Teaching and Leadership to higher education institutions who have trained more teachers than places allocated in each academic year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23169","23169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445922","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of qualified teachers.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23232","23232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445923","2016-01-21","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to support the academic and socio-emotional needs of children diagnosed with attention deficit hyperactivity disorder.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23111","23111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445924","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations she has received on changing the way school performance data is published so that data on children in designation provision is disaggregated from data on children in mainstream schooling; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23155","23155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445925","2016-01-22","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve teacher recruitment in local education authority areas with poor educational attainment; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23090","23090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445926","2016-01-21","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on school budgets of the National Living Wage.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23067","23067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445927","2016-01-21","Department for Education","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to (a) include understanding of the signs for attention deficit hyperactivity disorder in teacher training and (b) encourage earlier identification, assessment and positive intervention in relation to that disorder.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22999","22999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445928","2016-01-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what level of domestic content her Department expects to be used in the construction of the Hinkley Point C nuclear power plant.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23001","23001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445929","2016-01-22","Cabinet Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times the inter-ministerial group on clean growth has met since 7 May 2015.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23081","23081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445930","2016-01-22","Cabinet Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the terms of reference are for the inter-ministerial group on clean growth.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23082","23082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445931","2016-01-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to ensure that Carbon Capture and Storage is rolled out in the UK energy generation market.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23170","23170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445932","2016-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of vehicles transporting livestock through UK ports were inspected by the Animal Health and Veterinary Laboratories Agency in each of the last three years; and in what proportion of such inspections animal ear tags were physically inspected.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23123","23123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445933","2016-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2016 to Question 21765, on birds: census, when she plans to publish her Department's internal allocations.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23026","23026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445934","2016-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the environmental effects of the use of imported fox urine for the purposes of trail hunting.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23004","23004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445935","2016-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance her Department issues on the import and use of fox urine for the purpose of trail hunting.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23005","23005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445936","2016-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what guidance his Department has provided to Europe Direct on the information it provides to people in the UK in the period before the referendum on the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22993","22993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445937","2016-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the transfer of protected persons from the West Bank to prisons inside Israel.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23077","23077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445938","2016-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Law Enforcement Adviser, Larry Covington, declared any interests relevant to his employment by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22995","22995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445939","2016-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what further representations his Department plans to make to the Iranian government on securing the release of Kamal Foroughi from imprisonment.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23102","23102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445940","2016-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Turkish government on the arrest of academics (a) in general and (b) at the Kocaeli University in north-western Turkey.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23103","23103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445941","2016-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the cost to the public purse was of the promotion of democracy and human rights through the Arab Partnership Fund in 2014-15.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 23104","23104"
