"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905450","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the quality of transitions for children in need into adulthood.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144977","144977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905451","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether private clinics will be used to carry out additional mammograms following the failure to invite women aged 68 to 71 to breast screening appointments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144992","144992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905452","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is still a principle of the Government that an individual should spend on average up to one third of their adult life above state pension age.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144951","144951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905453","2018-05-21","Attorney General","2018-05-16","To ask the Attorney General, if he will provide an update on the status of the case of the Serious Fraud Office investigation into allegations concerning GPT and the conduct of its business in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144950","144950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905454","2018-05-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a recognised governing body for white collar boxing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144978","144978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905455","2018-05-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the regulatory and statutory framework relating to white collar boxing events.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144979","144979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905456","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether data will be collected by her Department from claimants using the Find a Job website.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144817","144817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905457","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance and training is provided to staff determining sanctions for (a) jobseekers allowance and (b) universal credit to help them understand mental health problems which may legitimately account for claimants missing appointments with little or no notice.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144818","144818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905458","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of new NHS consultant posts dedicated to neuro-oncology.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144897","144897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905459","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary for Transport of 14 May 2018, Official Report, column 99, if he will make an assessment of the compatibility of the 1968 Vienna Convention on Road Traffic with the (a) testing and (b) use of fully autonomous vehicles.","Biography information for Alex Burghart","Alex Burghart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144969","144969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905460","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 20 March 2018 on Access to Work, HCWS563, how many people will be affected by the increased funding cap.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144997","144997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905461","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what date was the requirement for disabled people to contribute towards the cost of their wheelchairs as part of the access to work scheme introduced; how many disabled people have had to contribute towards the cost of their wheelchair since the introduction of that policy; and whether an equality impact assessment was undertaken before the introduction of that policy.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144998","144998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905462","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's announcement of 30 April 2018 on early language skills, what best practice his Department has identified for the effective use of children’s centres to improve outcomes.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144985","144985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905463","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's announcement on 30 April 2018 on early language skills, how much of the £8.5 million Early Years Social Mobility Peer Review Programme he expects to be spent on the development of effective strategies to improve outcomes through the effective use of children’s centres.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144986","144986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905464","2018-05-21","House of Commons Commission","2018-05-16","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many kilogrammes of food the House of Commons has disposed of as waste in each of the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144987","144987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905465","2018-05-21","House of Commons Commission","2018-05-16","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission,  how many kilogrammes of food the House of Commons has disposed of as waste  in (a) April 2013, (b) April 2014, (c) April 2015, (d) April 2016 and (e) April 2017.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144988","144988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905466","2018-05-21","Department for International Development","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department provides to internally displaced Christians who wish to return to the Nineveh Plains area of Iraq.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144840","144840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905467","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to his oral contribution of 15 May 2018, Official Report, column 116, if he will place in the Library a copy of the transcript of his appearance on the US TV programme Fox and Friends on 7 May 2018.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144946","144946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905468","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to have a role in monitoring the forthcoming general election in Mexico.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144981","144981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905469","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives of the Mexican Government on ensuring free and fair elections in that country.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144982","144982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905470","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made representations to the Government of Mexico on the potential effect of its Internal Security Law passed in December 2017 on freedom of expression and the ability to hold free and fair elections in Mexico.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144983","144983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905471","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans the Government has to establish UK electoral observation missions to monitor elections in other countries after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144984","144984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905472","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy to increase the maximum age for magistrates.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144898","144898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905473","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to allow courts in England and Wales to hear cases (a) in the evening and (b) at weekends.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144899","144899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905474","2018-05-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking following the action taken by the Advertising Standards Authority against misleading presentation of pricing information on the websites of secondary ticket operators.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144968","144968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905475","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) all children and (b) children eligible for free school meals reached a good level of development at the age of five in Colne Valley constituency in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144980","144980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905476","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the compatibility of the work of the Office of Religious Affairs in the Cuban Communist Party with the right to freedom of religion or belief in Cuba.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144859","144859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905477","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on freedom of religion or belief of registration requirements for religious groups in Cuba; and if he will take steps to encourage the establishment of a clear framework for religious groups to operate legally in that country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144860","144860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905478","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the role that religious leaders play as human rights defenders in Mexico; and what representations he has made to the Government of Mexico on its complying with the recommendations it accepted in the last UN Universal Period Review cycle on ensuring the protection of religious leaders in that country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144861","144861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905479","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Mexico on the culture of impunity in that country towards repeat perpetrators of violations of religious freedom.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144862","144862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905480","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has plans to raise issues relating to freedom of religion or belief in Mexico at that country's Universal Periodic Review in November 2018.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144863","144863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905481","2018-05-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much government research funding was provided to each higher education institution in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144791","144791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905482","2018-05-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the science and technology sectors in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144792","144792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905483","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reports of immigration crime his Department received from hon. Members in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144781","144781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905484","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reports of immigration crime his Department received from the Department for Work and Pensions in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144782","144782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905485","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many communications his Department received from hon. Members and their offices on immigration enforcement hotlines during 2017.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144783","144783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905486","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reports of immigration crime his Department received from members of the public in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144784","144784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905487","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reports of immigration crime his Department received from HMRC in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144785","144785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905488","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much money from the public purse was spent on housing in (a) Coventry South constituency, (b) Coventry, (c) the West Midlands and (d) the UK in each year since 1998.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144793","144793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905489","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support his Department makes available to ensure that newly arrived asylum seekers placed in initial accommodation have immediate access to the education system.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144794","144794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905490","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to improve the processes for identifying children with rights to family reunion in the UK throughout refugee camps in Europe.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144795","144795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905491","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many requests for financial assistance to undertake fire safety work from local councils and housing associations has his Department refused since the Grenfell Tower fire; and of each such request what the sum of money applied for was.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144961","144961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905492","2018-05-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle the challenges faced by honeybees in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144796","144796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905493","2018-05-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Department is taking to increase the availability of gluten-free food to consumers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144797","144797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905494","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the (a) availability and (b) efficiency of (i) wi-fi and (ii) telephone signals on the Midland main line route.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144798","144798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905495","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the member of British diplomatic staff with prime responsibility for the safety of UK fans at the 2018 World Cup has been expelled from Russia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144962","144962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905496","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff from his Department or seconded from other Ministerial Departments have been assigned to roles in the (a) British Embassy, Pristina, (b) United Nations Mission in Kosovo, (c) NATO Kosovo Force, (d) European Union Rule of Law Mission in Kosovo and (e) other international organisations' missions in Kosovo in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144843","144843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905497","2018-05-21","Department for International Development","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff from her Department have been assigned to roles in the (a) British Embassy, Pristina, (b) United Nations Mission in Kosovo, (c) NATO Kosovo Force, (d) European Union Rule of Law Mission in Kosovo and (e) other international organisations' missions in Kosovo in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144844","144844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905498","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) staff from his Department and (b) officers from UK police forces have been assigned to roles in the (i) British Embassy, Pristina, (ii) United Nations Mission in Kosovo, (iii) NATO Kosovo Force, (iv) European Union Rule of Law Mission in Kosovo, and (v) other international organisations' missions in Kosovo in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144845","144845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905499","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) civilian staff from his Department, (b) military officers and (c) other ranks have been assigned to roles in the (i) British Embassy, Pristina, (ii) United Nations Mission in Kosovo, (iii) NATO Kosovo Force, (iv) European Union Rule of Law Mission in Kosovo and (v) other international organisations' missions in Kosovo in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144846","144846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905500","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of turnover of the membership of personal independence payment appeal tribunals.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144829","144829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905501","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the UK's financial contribution to the budgets of the (a) United Nations Interim Administration Mission in Kosovo, (b) European Union Rule of Law Mission in Kosovo, (c) NATO Kosovo Force and (d) other international organisations' missions in Kosovo has been in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144847","144847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905502","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of whether the benefits system is providing adequate financial support for young cancer patients and their families.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144819","144819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905503","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people between 16 and 24 years old were in part-time employment in (a) 2012 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144841","144841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905504","2018-05-21","Department for International Trade","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what diplomatic steps the Government has taken to support UK industry in its pursuit of Turkish TF-X fighter aircraft contracts.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144848","144848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905505","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who contacted his Department's Taskforce for Windrush subsequently experienced (a) immigrant enforcement and (b) police action.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144786","144786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905506","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to support Taiwan's participation in the World Health Assembly; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144882","144882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905507","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the World Health Organisation to facilitate Taiwan's attendance as an observer in the 2018 World Health Assembly.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144883","144883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905508","2018-05-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for sites to be informed whether they have been successful in securing a grant towards development as a spaceport.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144941","144941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905509","2018-05-21","Prime Minister","2018-05-16","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions she has had with President Erdogan of Turkey on the violence at the Gaza Border of 14 May 2018.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144974","144974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905510","2018-05-21","Department for International Development","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure the (a) adequacy and (b) reliability of funding provided by her Department to (i) regional and (ii) global civil society network programmes to respond to the HIV epidemic.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144931","144931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905511","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to Question 141675 on Prisoners: Caribbean asked by the hon. Member for Tottenham on 8 May 2018.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144787","144787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905512","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Oral Statement of 23 November 2017 on universal credit, Official Report, column 1200, what steps her Department has taken to ensure (a)  that all new claimants in need are able to access an advance payment and (b) greater collaboration between Citizens Advice and her Department.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144932","144932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905513","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 135706, on Flexible Support Fund, what assessment her Department has made of trends in (a) claimant needs and (b) volumes between 2013-14 and 2016-17.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144900","144900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905514","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to Autumn Budget 2017, what progress her Department has made on the review of the taper rate for universal credit.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144933","144933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905515","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the Middle East peace process continues in a fair and legitimate manner.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144975","144975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905516","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, in how many medical negligence claims against the NHS which were settled in the last five years legal proceedings were issued; and in how many such claims (a) damages payments were made, (b) the issue of proceedings has been required in order to obtain court approval of the settlement and (c) damages payments were not made.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144836","144836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905517","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department plans to publish the Defence in the UK Prosperity Review by the hon. Member for Ludlow.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144864","144864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905518","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 135706, on Flexible Support Fund, what estimate he has made of the average funding received per person from the Flexible Support Fund in each of the last five financial years for which data is available.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144901","144901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905519","2018-05-21","Department for International Development","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to deliver (a) drugs and (b) medical equipment to Gaza.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144778","144778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905520","2018-05-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the value of seasonal migrant labour to the UK's hospitality and tourism industry.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144947","144947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905521","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trains have been cancelled in each month of the last five years for services which come under the terms of the east coast main line franchise.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144799","144799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905522","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he is making to the Government of Israel on their use of ordnance in Gaza.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144779","144779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905523","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that British businesses can continue to recruit temporary workers from the European Economic Area to meet seasonal demand for the hospitality and tourism industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144948","144948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905524","2018-05-21","Women and Equalities","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much funding her Department has allocated for legal proceedings in relation to the case brought in the Supreme Court on 14 May 2018 by Keidon & Steinfold on civil partnerships.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144774","144774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905525","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to tackle cable theft on railway infrastructure in (a) Tyne and Wear, (b) North East England and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144821","144821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905526","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to tackle metal theft in (a) Tyne and Wear, (b) North East England and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144822","144822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905527","2018-05-21","Women and Equalities","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the command paper, Future operation of Civil Partnerships, Cm. 9606, published in May 2018, what additional information is being sought by her Department in its latest consultation on extending civil partnerships.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144775","144775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905528","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent progress has been made on the negotiations between NHS England and Vertex pharmaceuticals on making the drug Orkambi available on the NHS for people diagnosed with cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144823","144823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905530","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for a decision to be made on the proposed changes to acute services at South Tyneside District Hospital; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144824","144824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905531","2018-05-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government plans to amend its policy on safe standing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144825","144825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905533","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will make an assessment of the effect of changes to the state pension age on women born in the 1950s in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside and (c) the North East.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144826","144826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905534","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the reasons why unemployment is higher in the North East than in other regions of the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144827","144827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905536","2018-05-21","Women and Equalities","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she plans to make a decision on the future of the Access to Elected Office Fund; what assessment she has been made of the potential merits of reinstating this fund; and what information the Government holds on the (a) number of disabled candidates who have stood for office in each of the past five years and (b) the proportion of candidates who have stood for office in each of the last five years who have disabilities.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144789","144789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905537","2018-05-21","Women and Equalities","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the command paper, Future operation of Civil Partnerships, Cm. 9606, published in May 2018, for what reasons the public consultation will not start before 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144776","144776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905539","2018-05-21","Women and Equalities","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent representations she has received on extending civil partnerships to opposite sex couples.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144777","144777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905541","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the names of (a) the 41 local authorities that have contacted his Department regarding fire safety works and (b) the 14 local authorities which his Department have classed as carrying out essential fire safety works.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144976","144976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905542","2018-05-21","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to answer Question 136059 asked by the hon. Member for Ashton-under-Lyne on 16 April 2018, on Cabinet Office: Apprentices.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144923","144923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905544","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the firm number of planned solid support ships for the Royal Fleet Auxiliary is which is required by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144849","144849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905545","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what wage rate is paid to apprentice nurses by NHS employers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144924","144924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905547","2018-05-21","Treasury","2018-05-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2018 to Question 141345 on Instalment Credit, whether (a) he, (b) Ministers of his Department and (c) officials of his Department have discussed the feasibility of introducing a total cap on the cost of rent-to-own goods with the Financial Conduct Authority.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144880","144880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905549","2018-05-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the evidential basis is for his decision to curtail development of renewable energy.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144814","144814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905550","2018-05-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the evidential basis is for his proposal to ban new onshore wind farms.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144815","144815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905552","2018-05-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much the Government plans to invest in renewable energy in 2018-2019; and whether this figure is an increase from the previous year.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144816","144816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905553","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cold weather payments have been issued in 2018 for people in postcode area SR8; and what the timetable is for recipients to receive their payments.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144886","144886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905555","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the Health Service Investigation Branch plans to being its investigation into avoidable baby deaths.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144994","144994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905556","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what additional (a) funding and (b) resources have been allocated to the Health Service Investigation Branch for its investigation into avoidable baby deaths; and what the timeframe is for that funding.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144995","144995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905557","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether hospitals are compelled to accept and act on Health Service Investigation Branch recommendations that result from the investigation of avoidable baby deaths.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144996","144996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905559","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse of the refit of HMS Ocean was; and what revenue was generated for his Department's budget from the sale of that vessel.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144865","144865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905560","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 24 April, 23 April, 28 March, 26 February, 29 January, 24 January, 22 January, 18 January, 8 January 2018 and 6 December 2017 to Questions 136807, 136288, 134056, 127728,  123767, 123012, 122413, 122522, 120771 and 116150 and with reference to the Answer of 12 February 2018 to Question HL5304, what the timetable is for the Task and Finish Group on Taxi and Private Hire Vehicles licensing to (a) submit and (b) publish its report; and what the reasons are for the time taken for that group to submit and publish its report.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144959","144959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905562","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many victims detailed in domestic homicide Reviews were classified as  (a) migrant to the UK and (b) no recourse to public funds in the last three years.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144939","144939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905564","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what role the planned Royal Fleet Auxiliary Fleet solid support ships are planned to play in enabling future UK carrier strike capability.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144850","144850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905565","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what active weapon systems arm each vessel within the Royal Fleet Auxiliary.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144851","144851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905567","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what weapon systems are planned to arm each of the planned Royal Fleet Auxiliary solid support ships.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144852","144852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905568","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Goliath crane located in Rosyth has been sold.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144853","144853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905569","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which parts of the F-35 Autonomic Logistics Information System are planned to be integrated into the planned Royal Fleet Auxiliary Fleet solid support ships.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144854","144854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905570","2018-05-21","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants there have been in the Commercial Profession in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144806","144806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905571","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many decommissioned nuclear ballistic missile submarines are laid up at Rosyth dockyard.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144855","144855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905572","2018-05-21","Treasury","2018-05-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 15 May 2018 to Question 142837 on Royal Bank of Scotland: Small Businesses, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the compensation scheme for SME customers of the Royal Bank of Scotland.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144893","144893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905573","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department plans to take to increase support for teenagers with ADHD in schools.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144967","144967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905574","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what projects have been supported by the 2016-18 budget of the Pharmacy Integration Fund.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144944","144944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905575","2018-05-21","Department for International Development","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development,  what steps her Department is taking to ensure that money supplied to the Gaza region is used only for humanitarian purposes.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144842","144842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905576","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the role and remit of local plan inspectors.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144878","144878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905577","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, under what circumstances a local plan inspector is able to recommend the alteration of a local plan; and what the remit for a local authority, group or individual to appeal an inspector’s recommendation which will increase housing is.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144879","144879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905578","2018-05-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the value to the UK economy of the outbound tourism industry.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144830","144830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905579","2018-05-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the annual spend in the UK’s domestic tourism sector in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144831","144831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905580","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect on health outcomes of a reduction in the NHS Continuing Healthcare budget.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144945","144945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905581","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the back-pay liability for social care providers on trends in the number of care workers.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144889","144889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905582","2018-05-21","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of people in (i) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency, (ii) the Liverpool City Region and (ii) England who are paid less than the Living Wage Foundation's living wage.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144890","144890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905583","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will assess the merits of a UK-based consortium block-build bid for planned Royal Fleet Auxiliary solid support ships.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144856","144856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905584","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost of replacing all cladding materials on high rise buildings with (a) cladding materials which are not of limited combustibility and (b) materials that are of limited combustibility.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144800","144800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905585","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, where liability lies for costs incurred as a result of changes to building regulations and applied retrospectively.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144801","144801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905586","2018-05-21","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's publication entitled Expenditure over £25,000 - March 2018, published on 2 May 2018, for what work for the digital and technology team the payments to Team Consulting International UK were made.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144807","144807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905587","2018-05-21","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's publication entitled Expenditure over £25,000 - March 2018, published on 2 May 2018, for what work on Fast Stream learning and development the payments to CSL KPMG LLP were made.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144808","144808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905588","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of high rise buildings with cladding materials which are not of limited combustibility; and what materials are being used instead on each of those buildings.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144802","144802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905589","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to seek to obtain date-verifiable material of Tibet's missing Panchen Lama from the Chinese authorities.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144942","144942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905590","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress has been made on testing cladding systems other than ACM cladding on high rise buildings.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144803","144803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905591","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the safety of ZCM cladding systems on high rise buildings.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144804","144804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905592","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what powers he has to compel the owners of non-publicly owned buildings to have the cladding systems on those properties tested.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144805","144805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905593","2018-05-21","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's publication entitled Expenditure over £25,000 - March 2018, published on 2 May 2018, for what parts of SME contract management the payments to NTT Data UK Ltd were made.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144809","144809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905594","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how his Department ensures diplomatic reciprocity in its relations with other states.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144943","144943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905595","2018-05-21","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's publication entitled Expenditure over £25,000 - March 2018, published on 2 May 2018, for what parts of the NSDR team the payments to PA Consulting Services Ltd were made.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144810","144810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905596","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in England and Wales were the subject of a (a) probation supervision order and (b) community service order in each of the last five years; and how many of those people had previously served in the Armed Forces.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144960","144960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905597","2018-05-21","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's publication entitled Expenditure over £25,000 - March 2018, published on 2 May 2018, for what work on Hub Memphis the payments to BNP Paribas were made.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144811","144811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905598","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of recorded assaults on prison staff resulted in a prosecution in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144866","144866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905599","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what offences against the person were committed by serving prisoners on prison staff in the last year for which information is available; and what the sentencing outcome was in each of those cases.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144867","144867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905600","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the largest number of offences committed by a person has been prior to being sent to prison for the first time in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144868","144868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905601","2018-05-21","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's publication entitled Expenditure over £25,000 - March 2018, published on 2 May 2018, for what parts of the Next Gen Shared Services project the payments to Deliotte LLP were made.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144812","144812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905602","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of pre-sentence reports presented to magistrates’ courts contained a sentence recommendation of (a) immediate custody; (b) suspended custody and (c) a community order in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144869","144869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905603","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times magistrates have handed down a 12 month sentence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144870","144870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905604","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sentences magistrates handed down in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144871","144871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905605","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in prison are not being held in relation to a criminal case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144872","144872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905607","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many successful matches there were between DNA profiles taken from crime scenes and profiles stored on the national DNA database in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144873","144873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905609","2018-05-21","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's publication entitled Expenditure over £25,000 - March 2018, published on 2 May 2018, for what parts of the Infrastructure and Projects Authority GMPP operations the payments to Price Waterhouse Coopers were made.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144813","144813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905610","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many DNA profiles were (a) held on the national DNA database and (b) added to the national DNA database in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144874","144874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905612","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it remains the Government's policy to roll-out the 26-30 year railcard scheme throughout the UK.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144971","144971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905613","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been released from prison on Home Detention Curfew in each month in the last two years; and what offence each person released on curfew had committed.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144875","144875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905614","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many community resolutions there have been by offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144876","144876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905615","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many doctors currently working in the NHS have been convicted of (a) manslaughter, (b) clinical medical negligence and (c) culpable homicide.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144877","144877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905616","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to ensure that relationships and sex education is (a) impartial and (b) LGBT-inclusive in all types of schools.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144972","144972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905617","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that faith schools are compliant with the Equality Act 2010 when teaching relationships and sex education.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144973","144973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905618","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a temporary Blue Badge scheme for people with temporary but debilitating and incapacitating injuries and conditions.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144952","144952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905619","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of whether UK arms were used at the Gaza border against protesters.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144790","144790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905620","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the contribution of undernutrition to the number of falls by elderly people.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144857","144857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905621","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timetable is for opening the next round of bidding for the Strategic Schools Improvement Fund.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144820","144820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905622","2018-05-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what dates and with whom he has had discussions on a rural development programme for Unilever's manufacturing operations in Norwich and its associated supply chain.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144894","144894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905623","2018-05-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to respond to the letter of 2 May 2018 from Eamon O'Hearn on Unilever Norwich job losses.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144895","144895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905624","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the east coast main line change in ownership will affect the new train services to Lincoln scheduled to begin in 2019.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144993","144993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905626","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many clinical endoscopists have been recruited to date as part of Health Education England’s target to recruit and train an additional 400 clinical endoscopists; and what type of endoscopy procedures those recruited will be trained to carry out.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144989","144989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905627","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of how the additional 400 clinical endoscopists recruited as part of Health Education England’s targets will free up more consultant Gastroenterologist time for more complex cases.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144990","144990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905629","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to Health Education England’s target to train 400 clinical endoscopists by 2021, whether his Department is making additional funding available to support hospitals with the backfill and supervision costs required to enable trainees to receive the release time required to participate in the training programme.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144991","144991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905631","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities his Department assesses to be a financial risk.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144887","144887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905632","2018-05-21","Treasury","2018-05-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many parents using the tax free childcare online application system have submitted compensation claims after not receiving a top-up from HMRC; what the average amount of those claims is; what the average response time for such claims has been; and how much compensation has been paid (a) to each such claimant and (b) in total.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144949","144949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905634","2018-05-21","Department for International Trade","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many international investment agreements to which the UK is a signatory include protections against expropriations without compensation.","Biography information for Robert Courts","Robert Courts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144966","144966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905635","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of child and adolescent mental health psychiatrists who have been hired in the (a) London Borough of Lewisham and (b) UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144953","144953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905637","2018-05-21","Prime Minister","2018-05-16","To ask the Prime Minister, when she plans to respond to the letter of 4 April 2018 from the hon. Member for Sefton Central on Hillsborough Law.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144896","144896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905639","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his Department's policy is on funding from Apprenticeship Levy digital vouchers that businesses did not spend within the two-year time limit.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144908","144908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905640","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending (a) the number of SMEs to which unspent apprenticeship levy digital vouchers can be transferred to by larger firms and (b) the proportion of unspent digital vouchers that can be transferred.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144909","144909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905642","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many companies that are headquartered in England were unable to spend all their apprenticeship levy digital vouchers as a result of their apprenticeship programmes being based elsewhere in the UK.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144910","144910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905644","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 May 2018 to Question 142874 on Disabled Students' Allowances, whether he has assessed the potential merits of providing additional student loans to fund the £200 contribution made by students in receipt of Disabled Students’ Allowances for the purchase of computer hardware.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144925","144925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905645","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons his Department plans to introduce a single provider model for each T-level; and what contingency measures his Department is putting in place in the event of the failure of a T-level awarding organisation.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144911","144911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905647","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Competition and Markets Authority has provided an analysis of the single provider proposals for T-levels; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144912","144912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905649","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 May 2018 to Question 137063, what data was collected on the educational backgrounds of applicants to be Chair of the Social Mobility and Child Poverty Commission.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144926","144926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905650","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many learning disability nurses have been employed by the NHS in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144934","144934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905652","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many learning disability nursing students there have been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144935","144935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905653","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will publish the submissions made to the joint Department for Communities and Local Government and Department for Work and Pensions funding for supported housing consultation which closed on 13 February 2017.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144936","144936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905654","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many nursing associates had begun apprenticeship courses by the end of April 2018.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144927","144927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905656","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the Government plans to publish its response to the Report on Child Migration Programmes published by the Independence Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse on 1 March 2018.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144837","144837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905657","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of local authorities on the directing funding for supported housing by local government.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144937","144937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905659","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what representations she he has received from local authorities on her Department’s proposed model of funding for supported housing.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144938","144938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905661","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May 2018 to Question 136300, what steps his Department is taking to obtain the information of the number of Windrush citizens who have been (a) denied and (b) charged for NHS treatment.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144891","144891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905662","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children are being looked after as a result of their parents or guardians being deemed homeless.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144920","144920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905664","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on how many occasions children subject to special guardianship orders and adoption orders have been placed into local authority care under section 20 of the Children Act 1989 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144921","144921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905665","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) adoptions and (b) special guardian placements have broken down in the each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144922","144922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905667","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Oral Answer of the Minister for Universities, Science, Research and Innovation to the hon. Member for Battersea of 14 May 2018, Official Report, column 15, what the evidential basis is for his statement that students spend on average £250 on computers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144928","144928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905669","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the reasons are for his Department's decision to purchase F-35A aircraft for the Royal Air Force.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144838","144838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905670","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Oral Answer of the Minister for Universities, Science, Research and Innovation to the hon. Member for Battersea of 14 May 2018, Official Report, column 15, when he plans to complete the evaluation of the impact of the £200 charge for computer equipment for students in receipt of Disabled Students' Allowances.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144929","144929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905672","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Oral Answer of the Minister for Universities, Science, Research and Innovation to the hon. Member for Battersea of 14 May 2018, Official Report, column 15, what costs Disabled Students' Allowances are planned to cover.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144930","144930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905673","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, further to the oral evidence of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Education on Evidence-based early-years intervention inquiry on 1 May 2018, Q 384 and Q 457, HC 506, which outcome measures have been identified as improving in (a) Staffordshire and (b) Newcastle since children’s centre provision was reorganised.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144963","144963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905675","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the oral evidence given by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State to the Science and Technology Select Committee on 1 May 2018, 384, what the evidential basis is for the statement that the number of children’s centres that are open in the most disadvantaged areas has stayed constant.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144964","144964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905677","2018-05-21","House of Commons Commission","2018-05-16","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what estimate the Commission has made of the number of weekly non-passholders who are admitted to the Parliamentary estate without being accompanied or sponsored by a Member.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144832","144832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905678","2018-05-21","House of Commons Commission","2018-05-16","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, whether the Commission has made an assessment of the adequacy of security in the Palace of Westminster as a result of the number of unaccompanied non-passholders accessing the Parliamentary estate in order to use refreshment facilities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144833","144833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905680","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding was allocated from the public purse to dementia research in 2016-17.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144915","144915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905682","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding from the public purse the Government plans to allocate to dementia research in the 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144916","144916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905683","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, (a) on which motorways and (b) at which locations on those motorways automatic number plate recognition cameras are in use; and what offences such cameras are being used to detect.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144834","144834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905684","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to avoid criminalising rough sleeping when tackling anti-social behaviour.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144917","144917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905685","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 17 of the Early Years Workforce Strategy, published in March 2017, when his Department plans to undertake a consultation on amending the regulations for Early Years Teacher Status.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144965","144965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905686","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of integrating Stingray torpedoes onto the new Boeing P-8As.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144839","144839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905687","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to bring forward the ban on sales of new petrol and diesel vehicles from 2040 to 2030.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144881","144881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905688","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have had their personal independence payments changed from weekly to four-weekly payments.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144918","144918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905689","2018-05-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the economic value of tourism to (a) the UK and (b) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144835","144835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905690","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number of 13-25 year olds in prison in (a) 1997, (b) 2007, (c) 2010 and (d) 2017.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144954","144954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905691","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people received weekly disability living allowance payments in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144919","144919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905692","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of money spent from the public purse on Sure Start in (a) 1997, (b) 2007, (c) 2010 and (d) 2017.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144955","144955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905693","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of money spent from the public purse on education in (a) 1997, (b) 2007, (c) 2010 and (d) 2017.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144956","144956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905694","2018-05-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of money spent from the public purse on youth services in (a) 1997, (b) 2007, (c) 2010 and (d) 2017.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144957","144957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905695","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of money spent from the public purse on policing in (a) 1997, (b) 2007, (c) 2010 and (d) 2017.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144958","144958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905696","2018-05-21","Department for International Development","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of (a) recent trends in the capacity of the health services in Yemen to treat (i) cholera and (ii) diphtheria cases and (b) the effect of those trends on the rate of cases of each disease.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144788","144788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905697","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2018 to Question 132470 on Engineering: Vocational Guidance, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the programme to raise the profile of engineering during the Year of Engineering will result in a long-term increase in the awareness of engineering careers in schools.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144902","144902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905698","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2018 to Question 133046 on adult education: finance, whether those organisations eligible for support have different national funding arrangements from other specialist designated institutions.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144903","144903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905699","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the answer of 19 March 2018 to Question 1324703 on Engineering: Vocational Guidance, whether his Department plans to allocate additional funding to schools for the provision of career strategies.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144904","144904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905701","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2018 to Question 132470 on Engineering: Vocational Guidance, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Insight into Industry initiative for teachers; and whether he plans to expand the scheme.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144905","144905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905702","2018-05-21","Treasury","2018-05-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he is taking steps to ensure that the liquidity introduced into long-term credit markets by Bank of England quantitative easing is disbursed to the real economy.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144906","144906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905704","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2018 to Question 133046 on adult education: finance, what assessment the Government has made of the funding requirements of the specialist providers affected by the devolution of the adult education budget.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144907","144907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904574","2018-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","What recent assessment he has made of the UK’s diplomatic relations with the US.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905297","905297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904575","2018-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","What recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on foreign policy co-operation after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Matt Rodda","Matt Rodda","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905299","905299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904576","2018-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","What recent assessment he has made of the UK's diplomatic relations with India.","Biography information for Mr Philip Dunne","Mr Philip Dunne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905300","905300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904577","2018-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","What recent assessment he has made of trends in the size of Hezbollah’s weapons arsenal.","Biography information for Chris Davies","Chris Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905304","905304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904625","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has watched any part of series three of the BBC Two television programme Hospital, episodes first broadcast on 26 March 2018, 3 April 2018, 10 April 2018, 17 April 2018, 24 April 2018 and 1 May 2018.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144258","144258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904626","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish correspondence by Ministers with external bodies from the period between January 2018 and 2 May 2018 relating to the breast cancer screening failure.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144281","144281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904627","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish updated information on the number of women since 2010 who have failed to receive breast cancer screening as a result of the recent breast cancer screening failure.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144282","144282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904628","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate his Department has made of the adequacy of the size of the cancer nursing workforce.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144283","144283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904629","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure a consistent increase in the uptake of cancer screening throughout all parts of the country.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144284","144284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904630","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to fully fund the proposed pay award for Agenda For Change NHS Staff for all affected organisations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144305","144305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904631","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that clinical commissioning groups implement the NICE DG27 guidance, Molecular testing strategies for Lynch syndrome in people with colorectal cancer.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144152","144152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904632","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average distance was that a patient travelled from their home to an A&E in each region of England in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144285","144285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904633","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, over what dates the most recent deep clean of each NHS hospital took place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144286","144286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904634","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the level of (a) access to and (b) uptake of diabetes prevention (i) methods and (ii) programmes in each clinical commissioning group area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144306","144306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904635","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of geographic variations in the level of access to prevention education on diabetes potentially becoming a disease of deprivation.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144307","144307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904636","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the uptake of new diagnostic devices of the lack of mandatory requirement for clinical commissioning groups to provide funding for such devices following approval by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144308","144308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904637","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions (a) he, (b) Ministers of his Department and (c) officials of his Department have had with the Department of Health and Social Care on driving and new technology for blood glucose monitoring of drivers with diabetes.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144309","144309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904638","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has requested updated advice from the Medical Advisory Panel on Driving and Visual Disorders on whether or not to allow glucose monitors that measure interstitial fluid rather than blood; and whether his Department has received advice on a minimum accuracy standard for such monitors.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144310","144310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904639","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of Nigeria on reports of the armed forces' participation in acts of ethnic cleansing in the riverine states of that country undertaken by the Fulani militia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144272","144272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904640","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the requirement for government and public bodies to reflect the federal character of the county under its constitution, what reports he has received on the ethnic and religious diversity in the (a) leadership and (b) general personnel of the security forces of Nigeria.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144273","144273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904641","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2018 to Question 121787, whether the Government has made an assessment of the potential merits of issuing guidance or bringing forward proposals on banning or restricting the sale of high caffeine energy drinks in supermarkets.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144274","144274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904642","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Government of Venezuela on safeguards to ensure that the forthcoming elections in that country are free, fair and transparent.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144275","144275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904643","2018-05-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the removal of sea weed from beaches on the eco-diversity of the beach habitat.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144276","144276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904644","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what change has been recorded in rates of childhood obesity in each year from 2011 to 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144216","144216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904645","2018-05-21","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what implications there are for his policy of the report Care workers, challenges of the tax and benefits system, published on 2 May 2018 by the Low Incomes Tax Reform Group; and whether his Department has made an assessment of potential risks of care workers being paid less than the minimum wage.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144269","144269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904646","2018-05-21","Department for International Trade","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions his Department has had with HM Treasury on staff changes for his Department.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144270","144270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904647","2018-05-21","Department for International Trade","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of any decrease in its staffing on its ability to carry out its remit.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144271","144271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904648","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of (a) armed forces and (b) his Department's personnel work for the Joint Cyber Unit in (i) Corsham and (ii) Cheltenham.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144362","144362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904649","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the structural integrity of the UK rail infrastructure’s (a) track and (b) signalling in (i) Control Period 6, (ii) Control Period 7 and (iii) Control Period 8.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144299","144299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904650","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what contingency plans he has in place in the event of a rail freight operator entering insolvency.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144300","144300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904651","2018-05-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to A Green Future: Our 25 Year Plan to Improve the Environment, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of the proposed Bradley open-cast coal mine in Pont Valley, County Durham on the Government’s commitment to restore the natural environment.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144251","144251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904652","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timetable is for the publication of the next statistical set on early years provision for children under five years in the local-authority-maintained, private, voluntary and independent sectors in England.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144291","144291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904653","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons Northern Lincolnshire and Goole NHS trust has not met the target for 95 percent of patients entering A&E to be treated or admitted in 4 hours since September 2015; how many discussions he has had with that trust to understand why they have not achieved that target for 30 continuous months; what steps he has taken over the past 12 months to support A&E services within that trust in meeting that target; and what steps he plans to take to support that trust in meeting that target.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144259","144259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904654","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons Northern Lincolnshire and Goole NHS trust has had a 6 per cent reduction over the past 12 months away from the target for 85 per cent of patients to begin treatment within 62 days of urgent GP referral; how many discussions he has had with Northern Lincolnshire and Goole NHS trust to understand for what reasons they have not achieved that target for 18 continuous months; what steps he has taken over the past 12 months to support cancer services within Northern Lincolnshire and Goole NHS trust; and what steps he plans to take to support that trust in meeting that target.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144260","144260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904655","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons Northern Lincolnshire and Goole NHS trust has had a 13.2 per cent reduction over the past 12 months away from the target of ensuring that 92 per cent of patients are waiting less than 18 weeks for planned operations and care; how many discussions he has had with Northern Lincolnshire and Goole NHS trust to understand for what reasons they (a) rank 127th out of 127 NHS trusts for that target and (b) have not achieved that target for 27 continuous months; what steps he has taken over the past 12 months to support such planned treatments within Northern Lincolnshire and Goole NHS trust; and what steps he plans to take to support that trust in meeting that target.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144261","144261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904656","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money from the public purse was spent on tax-free childcare in 2017-18.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144292","144292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904657","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has spent on tax-free childcare in the financial year 2018-19 to date.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144293","144293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904658","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, (a) how much his Department has allocated to spend on and (b) what recent estimate his Department has made of its total spending on tax-free childcare for the financial year 2018-19.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144294","144294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904659","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average duration of mandatory reconsideration is for people who following an initial decision on their employment and support allowance claim (a) do and (b) do not set up a new claim for universal credit while awaiting the outcome of that reconsideration.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144198","144198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904660","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether guidance is provided to departmental staff and contractors on communicating to claimants how they can establish a source of income during the mandatory reconsideration of their benefit claim; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144199","144199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904661","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to collect data on the number of pupils in England who are eligible for free school meals on the ground of household income but are not registered for such meals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144200","144200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904662","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria were applied when deciding which schools within the University of Chester Academies Trust should be rebrokered.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144317","144317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904663","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the accuracy of the Real Time Information system in calculating the universal credit that is awarded to low-paid workers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144201","144201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904664","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) complaints and (b) inquiries that her Department has received from or on behalf of universal credit claimants in employment have been prompted by inaccurate earnings data from the Real Time Information system.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144202","144202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904665","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when Ofsted plans to publish its final report of its 21 and 22 March 2018 inspection of The John Roan secondary school in the Royal Borough of Greenwich.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144366","144366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904666","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what transitional protections are in place to ensure that claimants of employment and support allowance retain their severe disability premium when they move on to universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144203","144203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904667","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many requests for very senior manager salaries above £142,500 have been (a) made by NHS trusts and (b) approved in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144318","144318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904668","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many households that lived in (a) Grenfell Tower and (b) Grenfell Walk have accepted offers of (i) temporary and (ii) permanent accommodation since the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144228","144228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904669","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many households that lived in (a) Grenfell Tower and (b) Grenfell Walk have moved out of (i) temporary and (ii) permanent accommodation into permanent accommodation since the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144229","144229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904670","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many of the 41 local authorities that have contacted his Department regarding fire safety in buildings since the Grenfell Tower fire have been provided financial support by his Department.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144230","144230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904671","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of prisoners with a history of opioid misuse were provided with Naloxone when released from prison in the latest year for which information is available; and from which prisons those prisoners were released.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144253","144253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904672","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make the supply of the opioid-overdose antidote Naloxone to all at-risk prisoners upon their release a mandatory requirement for prisons.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144254","144254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904673","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the DVSA is taking to monitor the (a) safety during the driving test and (b) effectiveness of the new sat nav element of the driving test.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144255","144255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904674","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of patients who were left waiting in ambulances for at least 30 minutes before being admitted to hospital in (a) Scunthorpe County Constituency, (b) North Lincolnshire and (c) England and Wales in each year from 2008 to 2017.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144262","144262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904675","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has plans to extend the Learning Disability Mortality Review programme beyond 2019.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144248","144248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904676","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to make mandatory the reporting of all early deaths of people with learning disabilities.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144249","144249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904677","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received from (a) the Local Government Association and (b) local authorities on the allocation of additional funding from central government to tackle potholes.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144363","144363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904678","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department has allocated to the London Borough of Redbridge to tackle potholes in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144364","144364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904679","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussion he has had with his Swedish counterpart on future defence and security cooperation in the Baltic region.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144379","144379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904680","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to encourage closer cooperation between Sweden and NATO; and whether he has held discussions with his Swedish counterpart on that county's potential membership of NATO.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144380","144380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904681","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the recommendations made in the report Crumbling Futures, published by Children’s Society in March 2018.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144403","144403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904682","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of (a) educational and (b) career outcomes for children in need.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144404","144404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904683","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to improve the (a) educational and (b) career outcomes for children in need.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144405","144405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904684","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of support provided to children in need in the transition from childhood to adulthood.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144406","144406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904685","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing transitional support for children in need as they reach adulthood.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144407","144407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904686","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what is Department's policy is on the instigation of a UN-led investigation into the recent deaths of Palestinian protesters.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144367","144367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904687","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make it mandatory for health professions to adhere to (a) NICE Clinical Guideline on nutritional support in adults, CG32 and (b) NICE Quality Standard QS24.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144342","144342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904688","2018-05-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what support his Department makes available for new community energy co-operatives.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144374","144374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904689","2018-05-21","Cabinet Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many polling stations were operational in elections for each relevant year since 2010.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144375","144375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904690","2018-05-17","Cabinet Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many electors were registered for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144376","144376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904691","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to sell the Help to Buy loan book to outside financial organisations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144206","144206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904692","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to sell the Help to Buy loan book; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144207","144207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904693","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS Trusts in England offered (a) one (b) two (c) three and (d) more than three courses of IVF treatment as a routine service to eligible women in each of the years between 2010 and 2018.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144263","144263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904694","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information he holds on the number of NHS Trusts which implemented in full NICE guidelines for the provision of IVF treatment in each year between 2010 and 2018 to date.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144264","144264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904695","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of approving the home as a place for pregnant women to take misoprostol.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144257","144257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904696","2018-05-21","Department for International Development","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department is providing to agencies in Palestine to help with medical aid.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144156","144156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904697","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) his Israeli counterpart and (b) his Palestinian counterpart on the recent violence in Gaza.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144368","144368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904698","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the international community to work together to speed up the process of peace between Palestine and Israel and develop a two state solution.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144157","144157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904699","2018-05-21","Department for International Development","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to Rohingya refugees; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144158","144158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904700","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on that country's commitment to the Oslo Peace accords.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144369","144369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904701","2018-05-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government is permitted to provide additional funding to the match-funding contribution of the European Maritime and Fisheries Fund projects.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144265","144265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904702","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of children designated as in need achieved (a) five A* to C grades at GCSE including English and mathematics and (b) no A* to C grades at GCSE excluding equivalents in (i) Coventry and (ii) the West Midlands from 2008 to the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144159","144159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904703","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support the Government provides to help children with disabilities get to and from school.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144160","144160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904704","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information the Government holds on whether Hamas has encouraged Palestinian protesters to use violence against Israeli military forces along the border of Gaza.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144370","144370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904705","2018-05-17","Department for International Development","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of medical provision in Gaza as a result of the casualties among Palestinian protesters.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144371","144371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904706","2018-05-17","Department for International Development","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to allocate addition funding for medical services in Gaza.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144372","144372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904707","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education,  how many (a) modern languages and (b) art teachers have left the teaching profession (i) through retirement and (ii) for other reasons in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144161","144161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904708","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what policies her Department has in place to ensure that refugees do not face (a) language and (b) other barriers to entering the education system.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144162","144162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904709","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress his Department has made on its review into the Panama Papers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144163","144163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904710","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to legislate to prevent unreasonable increases in ground rents on existing leasehold properties.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144171","144171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904711","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 14 May 2018 to Question 141024, on Young Offender Institutions, if he will publish that same information (a) per young person and (b) by age.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144301","144301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904712","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to review the value and safety of the regulations under the 1967 Abortion Act relating to the home use of misoprostol for women who are having an early medical abortion.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144401","144401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904713","2018-05-17","Department for International Development","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the merits of using drones to drop emergency aid into Syria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144164","144164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904714","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the causes of the changes in the number of claimants aged between 18 and 24 in Great Grimsby constituency between April 2017 and April 2018.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144339","144339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904715","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the causes of the changes in the number of claimants aged between 16 and 64 in Great Grimsby constituency between April 2017 and April 2018.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144340","144340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904716","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS England is legally required to ring fence any part of its allocation to Clinical Commissioning Groups to ensure it is used for Better Care Fund schemes which are classified as social care.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144287","144287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904717","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to ensure NHS England achieves the objectives set out in the Mandate for 2018-19.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144288","144288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904718","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what (a) sanctions and (b) penalties his Department can be apply to NHS England in the event that it fails to meet the objectives established in its mandate for 2018-19.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144289","144289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904719","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the effect is of the non-renewal of the annual mandate under section 13A of the National Health Service Act 2006 on the requirement for compliance by the Board of NHS England with its responsibilities and delegated authorities as set out in the Framework Agreement between the Department of Health and NHS England and Managing Public Money.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144290","144290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904720","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the value of (a) average backdated benefits and (b) total backdated benefits for PIP claimants who won PIP appeal tribunals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144208","144208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904721","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of waiting times for PIP appeal tribunal dates on (a) the physical health and (b) the mental health of claimants.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144209","144209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904722","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the proportion of UK domestic lending by banks to UK businesses.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144165","144165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904723","2018-05-21","Cabinet Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2018 to Question 137479 on UK Membership of EU: Referendums, and with reference to the oral evidence of the Chief Executive of the Electoral Commission to the Committee for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport on Fake News on 15 May 2018, Q 2618 and Q2619, HC 363, what recent discussions he has had with the Electoral Commission on the merits of increasing the level at which the Electoral Commission's can levy fines.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144210","144210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904724","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his oral contribution of 2 May 2018, Official Report, column 325, when he plans to provide a detailed answer to the question from the hon. Member for Halton.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144172","144172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904725","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to conduct a review of the effect of air passenger duty on tourism in (a) England, (b) Scotland and (c) Wales.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144337","144337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904726","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will write to women affected by changes to the state pension age to alert them to the effects of those changes.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144153","144153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904727","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2017 to Question 6370 on Incinerators: Health Hazards, what conclusions Public Health England has drawn from its review of evidence on the health effects of waste incinerators published in peer review journals; and what the timetable is for the papers from the study on emissions from waste incinerators commissioned by Public Health England to be published.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144226","144226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904728","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing transition support for children in need.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144402","144402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904729","2018-05-17","Wales Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the Welsh Government on the decision by Virgin Media to consult on the closure of its Swansea site.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144311","144311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904730","2018-05-17","Wales Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with Virgin Media on the decision to consult on the closure of its Swansea site.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144312","144312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904731","2018-05-17","Wales Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps he is taking to help ensure Virgin Media operations in Swansea remain open.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144313","144313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904732","2018-05-17","Wales Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps he is taking to support the workforce affected by the decision by Virgin Media to consult on the closure of its Swansea site.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144314","144314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904733","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the viability of enabling men to contribute to the pension of their spouse on the same basis as the contribution that they make to their own and with the same tax advantages.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144341","144341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904734","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether emergency funding has been provided by the Education and Skills Funding Agency to the University of Chester Academies Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144173","144173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904735","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the management performance of the University of Chester Academies Trust as a result of its reporting a financial deficit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144174","144174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904736","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his officials have raised concerns over potentially wrongful deportation of highly skilled migrants under section 322(5) of the Immigration Act in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144295","144295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904737","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department first became aware that some highly skilled migrants could potentially face wrongful deportation under section 322(5) of the Immigration Act.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144296","144296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904738","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his ministerial team were made aware of concerns over wrongful deportation of highly skilled migrants under section 322(5) of the Immigration Act on appointment.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144297","144297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904739","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he is taking steps to ensure that University Academy Warrington is effectively managed as a result of reports of its financial problems from the University of Chester Academies Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144175","144175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904740","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will issue guidance to providers of social housing on how they should deal with and respond to enquiries from hon. Members.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144176","144176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904741","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has received from Amnesty International and other NGOs on reports of actions taken by the Iranian authorities to destroy the mass graves of people who were massacred in 1998.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144250","144250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904742","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of new-build properties purchased by (a) owner-occupiers and (b) buy-to-let landlords in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Caroline Johnson","Dr Caroline Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144378","144378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904743","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 22 March 2018 to Question 133149, how much funding his Department allocated on the preparation for piloting digital capabilities in each of the other sites listed in that question.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144343","144343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904744","2018-05-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has plans to raise the minimum legal safety requirements for for (a) fridges and (b) freezers.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144214","144214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904745","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Independent Monitoring Board (a) members and (b) vacancies there have been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144344","144344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904746","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether any Independent Monitoring Boards have fewer than three members as of 1 May 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144345","144345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904747","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the public purse has been of expenses for his Department's staff by grade in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144346","144346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904748","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time spent on remand pending trial was for people facing summary offences in the last twelve months for which data is available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144347","144347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904749","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time spent on remand pending trial by people facing triable either way offences was in the last twelve months for which data is available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144348","144348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904750","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time spent on remand pending trial by people facing indictable-only offences was in the last twelve months for which data is available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144349","144349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904751","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of people who were remanded on their first appearance appeared in court from police custody in the last twelve months for which data is available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144350","144350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904752","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information the Government holds on the effect of remand decisions in cases where the defendant appears on video either from the police station or from prison.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144351","144351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904753","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the proportion of remanded prisoners who receive support from bail information services.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144352","144352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904754","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what monitoring his Department carries out on the extent and quality of bail information services in prison.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144353","144353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904755","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans his Department has put in place to ensure that members of the public and journalists are able to access information about cases to at least the same extent that they can at present after the planned extension of digital court hearings.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144354","144354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904756","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the business case for the planned digital courts reform programme redacted as necessary.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144355","144355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904757","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what research his Department has undertaken or commissioned on the views of victims of crime in respect of the planned digital courts reform programme.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144356","144356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904758","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what research his Department has undertaken or commissioned on the views of witnesses in respect of the planned digital courts reform programme.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144357","144357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904759","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 May 2018 to Question 139567, on prison officers redundancy pay, what estimate his Department made of the cost to the public purse of answering that question.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144358","144358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904760","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost was to the public purse of severance packages paid to prison officers who took voluntary early departure in 2011 and were subsequently re-recruited.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144359","144359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904761","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost was to the public purse of severance packages paid to prison officers who took voluntary early departure in 2012 and were subsequently re-recruited.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144360","144360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904762","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost was to the public purse of severance packages paid to prison officers who took voluntary early departure in 2013 and were subsequently re-recruited.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144361","144361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904763","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much his Department has paid in compensation for (a) wrongful detentions and (b) wrongful deportations in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144298","144298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904764","2018-05-21","Department for International Development","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much Government overseas development assistance expenditure has been spent (a) directly and (b) indirectly on low-fee for profit private schools since 2015; and which countries are the top ten recipients of such assistance.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144381","144381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904765","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on which UK organisations are in receipt of funding from the EU Rights Equality and Citizenship Programme.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144302","144302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904766","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has received representations from local authorities on their capacity to implement the Homelessness Reduction Act 2017.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144204","144204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904767","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 May 2018 to Question 137063, what other diversity monitoring data was collected from applicants for the position of Chair of the Social Mobility Commission.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144382","144382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904768","2018-05-17","Department for International Development","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans the Government has made to provide humanitarian support for a potential increase in Palestinian refugees across the Middle East as a result of the recent violence in Gaza.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144394","144394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904769","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 5.5 on page 47 of Budget 2017, what proportion of funding allocated for (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 201920 is allocated for (i) funding care packages for more people, (ii) supporting social care providers and (iii) relieving pressure on the NHS locally by local authority and NUTS 1 region.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144231","144231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904770","2018-05-17","Home Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has to support Palestinian refugees seeking to enter the UK as a result of recent violence in Gaza.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144395","144395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904771","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2017 to Question 902945, how much of the share of the £2 billion allocated to the social care sector in 2017-18 has been spent on attracting and retaining talented staff; and how many local authorities receiving that funding saw staff numbers (i) increase and (ii) decrease in 2017-18.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144232","144232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904772","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure an independent inquiry into recent civilian deaths on the Gaza border.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144396","144396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904773","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2018 to Question 128062, how much of the share of the £2 billion funding for (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20 the Government estimates will be used to fund meeting National Minimum Wage requirements for sleep-in shifts.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144233","144233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904774","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether use of the new Find a Job website will be compulsory for claimants of (a) jobseekers allowance and (b) universal credit.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144177","144177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904775","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2018 to Question 125600, what proportion of (a) the additional £9.25 billion social care funding and (b) all other social care funding in (i) 2017-18, (ii) 2018-19 and (iii) 2019-20 is ring-fenced.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144234","144234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904776","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the announcement in Budget 2017 of an additional £2 billion of funding for social care, whether all of that allocated funding is ring-fenced exclusively for providing social care support and reducing pressure on the NHS; and whether such a ring-fencing requirement is set out as a condition for the grant to local authorities.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144235","144235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904777","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to ensure NHS England provides funding for Ibrutinib for chronic lymphocytic leukemia patients.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144154","144154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904778","2018-05-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has plans to improve the safety of white collar boxing events; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144408","144408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904779","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to Figure 2 on page 7 of NHS Digital’s report, Adult Social Care Activity and Finance: England 2016-17, published on 25 October 2017, what those figures are in real terms; and whether social care funding rose in real terms in every NUTS 1 region in 2016-17 compared to 2015-16.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144236","144236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904780","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what provision his Department has made available for claimants to share their feedback on the new Find a Job website.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144178","144178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904781","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the announcement in Budget 2017 of an additional £2 billion of funding for social care, how many and which local authorities have had their share of the funding in (a) 2017-18 and (b) 2018-19 withheld due to a failure to meet grant conditions.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144237","144237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904782","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the announcement in Budget 2017 of an additional £2 billion of funding for social care, how many and which (a) health and wellbeing boards, (b) local authorities and (c) clinical commissioning groups have yet to sign off plans for the use of their respective local authorities' share of the funding for (i) 2018-19 and (ii) 2019-2020.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144238","144238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904783","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Prime Minister has had with the Turkish President on that country's involvement in the humanitarian crisis in Kurdish Northern Syria.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144397","144397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904784","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the announcement in Budget 2017 of an additional £2 billion of funding for social care, how long it took on average for (a) health and wellbeing boards, (b) local authorities and (c) clinical commissioning groups to sign-off plans for the use of their respective local authorities' share of the funding for 2017-18.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144239","144239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904785","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the success rate for appeals against decisions on employment and support allowance entitlement has been in Barnsley in the most recent 12-month period for which data is available.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144383","144383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904786","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the success rate for appeals against decisions on personal independence payment entitlement has been in Barnsley in the most recent 12-month period for which data is available.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144384","144384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904787","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of allegations that the Kurdish population in Northern Syria are being displaced from their homes by forces loyal to the Turkish Government.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144398","144398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904788","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  what the hourly rate of pay was which local authorities set for care providers in (a) residential care and (b) community-based care (i) as a national average and (ii) for each local authority.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144240","144240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904789","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time for an employment support allowance appeal hearing was in (a) Barnsley and (b) nationally in (i) each of the last 12 months and (ii) the last 12 months overall in the most recent period for which data is available.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144385","144385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904790","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to social care providers nationally of (a) paying the National Living Wage and (b) meeting historical and future National Minimum Wage requirements for sleep-in shifts in (i) 2017-18, (ii) 2018-19 and (iii) 2019-20.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144241","144241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904791","2018-05-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent progress the Government has made on implementation of the recommendations Julie Deane MBE's Self Employment Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anna Soubry","Anna Soubry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144252","144252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904792","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the announcement in Budget 2017 of an additional £2 billion of funding for social care, whether any of the additional funding (a) for 2017-18 has been used and (b) for 2018-19 or 2019-20 is planned to be used to meet social care providers' (i) historical back-dated costs or (ii) ongoing costs of complying with the tribunal ruling on sleep-in payments and the National Minimum Wage.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144242","144242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904793","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Find a Job website will clearly display whether an advertised position is full time, part time, flexible hours or a zero-hours contract.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144179","144179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904794","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many agency workers were employed in the care home sector in each year since 2009-10; and what the cost to the public purse was of that employment in each of those years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144243","144243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904795","2018-05-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to groups (a) 871, (b) 872, (c) 873 and (d) 874, Division 87 (Residential Care Activities), (e) 881, Division 88 (Social Work Activities Without Accommodation), Section Q, Table A1c of the Insolvency Service dataset Insolvency statistics January to March 2018 industry breakdown, published on 27 April 2018, what this date is by NUTS 1 region.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144244","144244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904796","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time for personal independence payment appeal hearing was in (a) Barnsley and (b) nationally in (a) Barnsley and (b) nationally in (i) each of the last 12 months and (ii) the last 12 months overall in the most recent period for which data is available.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144386","144386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904797","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of advertised consultant posts in hospitals (a) nationally, (b) in South Yorkshire and (c) in Barnsley were not appointed to.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144387","144387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904798","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of consultants currently working in hospitals in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) nationally are expected to reach the planned average age of retirement over the next decade.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144388","144388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904799","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to maintain the level of the consultant workforce over the next decade.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144389","144389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904800","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the Government has to support doctors who want to continue working after reaching retirement age.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144390","144390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904801","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the Government has to ensure dementia training is provided to all health and social care professionals.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144391","144391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904802","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications for 30 hours of free childcare have been processed in Barnsley in each of the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144392","144392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904803","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the most recent average point score per entry was for students of (a) A-levels and (b) equivalent qualifications in (i) Barnsley East constituency, (ii) Barnsley and (iii) England who were (A) eligible and (B) not eligible for free school meals when they were 15 years of age.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144393","144393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904804","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 21 February 2018 to Question 128965 on Sri Lanka: Diplomatic Service, what discussions he has had with his Sri Lankan counterpart since the return of the that country's Defence Attaché to Colombo.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144215","144215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904805","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish an evaluation of the Total Transport pilot schemes.","Biography information for Matt Rodda","Matt Rodda","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144409","144409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904806","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the out-of-service dates are for each of the Royal Navy's active weapons systems.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144219","144219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904807","2018-05-21","Department for International Development","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what mental health care programmes her Department is funding for Rohingya refugees in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144227","144227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904808","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has plans to replenish Royal Navy stocks of Tomahawk Land Attack Missiles.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144220","144220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904809","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether (a) the roll-out of broadband fibre to (i) households and (ii) other buildings, (b) electric vehicle charging points and (c) major housebuilding programmes will be exempt from lane rental scheme charges.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144411","144411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904810","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria his Department uses to  approve a local authority’s application for a lane rental scheme.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144412","144412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904811","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether there is a cap on lane rental scheme charges for major works to (a) install and (b) replace apparatus.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144413","144413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904812","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) discounts and (c) fee waivers from lane rental schemes are available for joint works; and what definition his Department uses for joint works.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144414","144414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904813","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether lane rental scheme charges will apply to street works undertaken by the Highways Agency.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144415","144415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904814","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much Northern has been fined for cancellations and partial cancellations since Arriva took over that franchise.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144180","144180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904815","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much Network Rail has paid out to Northern in compensation for cancellations since Arriva took over that franchise.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144181","144181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904816","2018-05-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of rules of origin under the proposed maximum facilitation model on the manufacturing sector.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144365","144365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904817","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings he has had with trades union representatives in respect of the ongoing Northern industrial dispute.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144182","144182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904818","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to investigate allegations of Israel’s contravention of UK national arms licensing criteria.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144212","144212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904819","2018-05-21","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate has been of made the cost to the public purse of the (a) total and (b) additional staffing costs of the Windrush compensation programme.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144377","144377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904820","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will make an assessment of the financial effect of the three-month waiting period for personal independence payment on people who have received a cancer diagnosis.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144155","144155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904821","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on the use of live ammunition against Palestinian protesters.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144213","144213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904822","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Lancashire Director of Children's Services on early intervention, resourcing and identified or non-funding pressures.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144277","144277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904823","2018-05-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual in-year costs for operating the UK Military Flying Training System have been in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144221","144221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904824","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Northern services have been cancelled due to staffing issues in each month since Arriva took over that franchise.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144183","144183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904825","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress her Department has made on rolling out a  programme of placing an officer of her Department into local food banks to assist with benefits (a) access and (b) problems as first piloted in Morecambe.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144278","144278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904826","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on what date the study on incinerators by the Small Area Health Statistics Unit is planned to be published.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144246","144246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904827","2018-05-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many RAF Sentinel R1 aircraft were serviceable on the first day of each month of 2017.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144222","144222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904828","2018-05-21","Cabinet Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of exports to (a) the USA and (b) the EU since 2011.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144247","144247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904829","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps his Department has taken to (a) publicise and (b) support debt advice services.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144184","144184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904830","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps his Department has taken to improve and promote access to credit unions.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144185","144185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904831","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department overpaid in tax credit claims in the last financial year; and what the estimated cost is of recovering those overpayments.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144186","144186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904832","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the amount of money spent by local authorities in the North West on sports and leisure in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144187","144187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904833","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what reports of concern have been submitted to the Lancashire Children's Safeguarding Board on (a) Morecambe Bay Primary School and (b) West End Primary School in the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144279","144279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904834","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of unclaimed entitlement to tax credits in the last financial year.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144188","144188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904835","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the rules governing people with (a) indefinite leave to remain and (b) refugee status to (i) leave and then return to Northern Ireland and (ii) to travel to the Republic of Ireland are.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144338","144338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904836","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans the Government has to improve access to financial education.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144189","144189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904837","2018-05-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the UK maintains the ability to build combat aircraft and that such capability is not outsourced to foreign powers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144223","144223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904838","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Chilean counterpart on Martin Pickett, a constituent of the Rt hon Member for Sevenoaks, to help him re-establish contact with his children who are living in Chile.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144146","144146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904839","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the reasons why Morecambe Bay Primary School failed to meet the threshold to retain the support of a social worker team to reduce the number of children on child protection plans to zero.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144280","144280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904840","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government has made an assessment of the export potential of operational RAF-manned ISTAR aircraft manufactured in part or entirely in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144224","144224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904841","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many sanctions have been imposed on (a) jobseekers allowance and (b) universal credit claimants who are experiencing mental health problems in the most recent 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144190","144190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904842","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of self-employed claimants on universal credit full service who have remained self-employed once the Minimum Income Floor is applied at the end of their first 12 months of trading.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144410","144410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904843","2018-05-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department’s procurement policy takes account of the use of secondary materials in the purchasing of new products; and if he will he make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144166","144166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904844","2018-05-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to promote sustainable procurement throughout government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144167","144167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904845","2018-05-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to review the potential merits of alternatives to weight based recycling targets as part of his Department’s future resources and waste strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144168","144168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904846","2018-05-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his policy is on adopting the future EU circular economy package; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144169","144169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904847","2018-05-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has discussed with Cabinet colleagues the waste and energy requirements for new housing developments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144170","144170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904848","2018-05-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with animal welfare organisations since the closure of the consultation on the Draft Animal Welfare Bill.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144225","144225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904849","2018-05-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the gross value added to the (a) UK and (b) East Midlands economy of (i) international and (ii) county-level cricket in the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144315","144315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904850","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent on incarcerating the perpetrators of (a) acid attacks, (b) knife attacks and (c) violent crimes; in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144147","144147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904851","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department has spent on the treatment of (a) acid attack victims, (b) knife attack victims and (c) victims of violent crime in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144148","144148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904852","2018-05-17","Cabinet Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length was of that leave.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144319","144319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904853","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144320","144320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904854","2018-05-17","Home Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144321","144321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904855","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144322","144322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904856","2018-05-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144323","144323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904857","2018-05-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144324","144324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904858","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144325","144325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904859","2018-05-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what new models of financing the repair and maintenance of church buildings are being considered by the Government as part of the pilot scheme under the Taylor Review on the sustainability of English churches and cathedrals.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144316","144316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904860","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144326","144326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904861","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much has been spent by police forces on handling (a) acid attacks, (b) knife attacks and (c) violent crimes in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144149","144149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904862","2018-05-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144327","144327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904863","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144328","144328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904864","2018-05-17","Department for International Trade","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144329","144329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904865","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144330","144330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904866","2018-05-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144331","144331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904867","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144332","144332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904868","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many male staff of her Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144333","144333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904869","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the Health and Safety Executive earned through selling consultancy services in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144150","144150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904870","2018-05-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared paternal leave; and the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144334","144334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904871","2018-05-17","Department for International Development","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many male staff  in her Department have taken shared paternity leave in the last twelve months; and what the length of each such leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144335","144335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904872","2018-05-17","Scotland Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many male staff of his Department have taken shared parental leave; and what the average length of that leave was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144336","144336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904873","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for sixth-form colleges to provide careers advice.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144191","144191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904874","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for sixth-form colleges to provide mental health support.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144192","144192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904875","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for sixth-form colleges to provide extra-curricular activities to develop employability skills.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144193","144193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904876","2018-06-04","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his Oral Answer of 17 April 2018, Official Report, column 179, what progress HMRC is making on reaching an agreement with the Roadchef Employee Benefit Trust on the outstanding tax issues.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144245","144245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904877","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to accelerate the use of adaptive trials for brain tumour patients.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144266","144266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904878","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to improve internet connectivity for the personal use of serving UK military personnel in the Falkland Islands.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144256","144256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904879","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to increase public and health professionals' awareness of the signs and symptoms of brain tumours.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144267","144267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904880","2018-05-17","Home Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessments he has made of (a) the quality of big data which his Department collects and b) the effectiveness of big data in his Department's policy formulation processes.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144211","144211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904881","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the annual cost to the public purse is for a place in a (a) Young Offenders Institution, (b) Secure Treatment Centre and (c) Secure Children’s Home.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144303","144303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904882","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether there is a difference in the cost to the public purse of a child placed in a secure residential accommodation (a) on remand and (b) for other reasons.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144304","144304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904883","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on producing a formal response to the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse's report on Child Migration Programmes.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144268","144268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904884","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of a diagnosis of cancer automatically requiring an education, health and care plan.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144205","144205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904885","2018-05-17","Department for International Trade","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will rescind all export licences allowing the export of arms to Israel.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144399","144399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904886","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will seek urgently the establishment of a UN-led investigation in to the recent actions of the Israeli Government towards protesters in Palestine.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144400","144400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904887","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government plans to introduce significantly discounted bus and train travel for apprentices.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144194","144194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904888","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment has he made of the propensity of students living and studying in rural areas to take up T levels.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144195","144195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904889","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to inform further education providers on whether they will be delivering T-levels.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144196","144196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904890","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 May 2018 to Question 142744 on the Educational Testing Service, how many people whose results were marked as questionable were given the opportunity to (a) re-sit a test with another provider and (b) attend an interview; and of those people how many were subsequently refused immigration leave.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144151","144151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904891","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Oral Answer of the Minister for Apprenticeships and Skills of 14 May 2018, Official Report, column 6, on Sixth-Form Colleges: Funding, whether funding for 16 and 17 year olds will be included in the Government's post-18 review.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144197","144197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904892","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on whether any G4S staff at Brook House Immigration Removal Centre received charges for unacceptable use of force against detainees.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144373","144373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904893","2018-05-21","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the implications of the High Court judgment of 14 May 2018 on the Mallusk incinerator plant for her policies on ministerial decision-making; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144217","144217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904894","2018-05-21","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will confirm that she has no plans to seek a border poll in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144218","144218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905383","2018-05-21","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate his Department has made of the effect on the public purse of the Government’s plans to lower corporation tax to 17 per cent from 2020.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905448","905448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906284","2018-05-21","Treasury","2018-05-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to support families with the cost of living.","Biography information for Victoria Prentis","Victoria Prentis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905455","905455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903728","2018-05-14","Department for Education","2018-05-14","How many schools will not receive a cash terms increase in their budget per pupil in 2018-19.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905261","905261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903729","2018-05-14","Department for Education","2018-05-14","What steps his Department is taking to promote apprenticeships.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905263","905263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903730","2018-05-14","Department for Education","2018-05-14","What steps his Department is taking to support more pathways from education into employment for young people.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905264","905264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903731","2018-05-14","Department for Education","2018-05-14","What discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the effect of the public sector pay cap on the level of recruitment and retention of staff in schools.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905266","905266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903732","2018-05-14","Department for Education","2018-05-14","How many schools will not receive a cash terms increase in their budget per pupil in 2018-19.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905267","905267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903758","2018-05-14","Department for Education","2018-05-14","What steps he has taken to reduce teacher workload.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905269","905269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903897","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) people and (b) women detained without charge in (i) Darfur and (ii) Sudan.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143617","143617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903899","2018-05-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with his European counterparts on UK lawyers being able to practice in the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143880","143880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903900","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to review national guidance on the importance of sleep to babies and children to include (a) good sleep hygiene, (b) consistent bedtimes, (c) safe infant sleeping, (d) screen-based usage for parents; and provide initial training and CPD for Health Visitors and Early Years teachers.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143753","143753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903901","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the All-Party Parliamentary Group for Education report entitled How well do schools prepare children for their future published in May 2017, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of taking steps to encourage an increase in the number of qualified careers guidance counsellors and the number of institutions in which they work.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143754","143754"
