"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017257","2018-12-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the recent statement he agreed with the President of the European Commission and President of the European Council, that Gibraltar will not be included in the territorial scope of agreement to be concluded between the EU and the UK (a) replaces or (b) amends the provisions of Article 24 of the Article 50 guidelines which provided for the application to Gibraltar of agreement between the EU and the UK after the UK leaves the EU; and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197346","197346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017258","2018-12-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the statistical data set, Affordable housing starts and completions funded by Homes England and the GLA, published by his Department,  what steps he is taking to identify the units labelled as unknown tenure type.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197329","197329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017259","2018-12-03","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of the proposed EU withdrawal agreement on the economy of Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197467","197467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017260","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the withdrawal agreement for the UK leaving the EU on the transportation and sale of livestock from Northern Ireland to the rest of the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197396","197396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017261","2018-12-03","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect of growth deals on the economy of Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197468","197468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017262","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment the Government has made of the effect on low-income families of the roll-out of universal credit throughout Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197469","197469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017263","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to publish the Government's plans on funding for farmers who are currently in receipt of funding from the Common Agricultural Policy after 2021.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197397","197397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017264","2018-12-03","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the fishing industry in Northern Ireland on access to UK fishing waters after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197470","197470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017265","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans the Government has to ensure the UK has control over fisheries policy in UK waters after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197398","197398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017266","2018-12-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Mental Health and Inequalities of 27 November 2018, Official Report, Column 152, on what date his Department is planning to provide a formal response to the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse's report on Child Migrant Programmes, published on 1 March 2018.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197399","197399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017267","2018-12-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what funding his Department has allocated to arts and culture projects in Nottinghamshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197471","197471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017268","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Nottinghamshire who have diabetes.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197472","197472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017269","2018-12-04","Department for International Development","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government plans to provide additional funding to tackle climate change in developing countries beyond the £5.8 billion allocated between 2016 and 2021.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197473","197473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017270","2018-12-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans the Government has to provide additional funding to tackle climate change in next year’s comprehensive spending review.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197474","197474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017271","2018-12-04","Department for International Development","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations her Department plans to make on climate change at the UN COP24 Climate Change conference taking place in Katowice, 2-14 December 2018.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197475","197475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017272","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he will publish the legal advice on the effect of the proposed Withdrawal Agreement on the Belfast Good Friday Agreement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197357","197357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017274","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance his Department provides to Police and Crime Commissioners on the proportion of their budget that should be used for the running of their offices.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197476","197476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017275","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many staff are employed to provide (a) leadership and (b) strategic direction to the NHS as a result of the establishment of the NHS Property Board.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197401","197401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017276","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what accountability procedures have been established in relation to staff providing (a) leadership and (b) strategic direction to the NHS  as a result of the establishment of the NHS Property Board.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197402","197402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017277","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 174768, what steps his Department is taking in respect of Sustainability and Transformation Partnerships which have not produced an estates strategy.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197403","197403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017278","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 November 2018 to Question 174765 on NHS Property Services and Community Health Partnerships: staff, what steps he plans to take to align the 16 hub sites to the seven regions recognised by NHS England and NHS Improvement.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197404","197404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017279","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 174766, what steps his Department is taking to assess the quality of the 42 Sustainability and Transformation Partnership estate strategies.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197405","197405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017280","2018-12-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 174763, what proportion of the income from dividends and investments due to Community Health Partnerships in the 49 LIFT Companies has been reinvested in improving local health facilities.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197406","197406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017281","2018-12-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 174763 on NHS Local Improvement Finance Trust, what proportion of that income has been used in supporting Departmental initiatives.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197407","197407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017282","2018-12-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 174763 on NHS Local Improvement Finance Trust, what proportion of that income has been used to meet the costs of managing the 49 Lift Companies.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197408","197408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017283","2018-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of whether there are any financial links between extreme Islamist groups in the Middle East and North Africa and extreme Islamist groups in the United Kingdom.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197409","197409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017284","2018-12-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will hold discussions with the Chancellor on (a) extending the Community Housing Fund for the whole of the next five-year Spending Review period and (b) allowing unspent money from the current Fund to rollover; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197410","197410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017285","2018-12-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will make an assessment of the effect of anti-vaccination groups on vaccination take-up.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197411","197411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017286","2018-12-04","Department for Education","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether confirmation on funding availability for EU students accessing 16-19 provision for the 2019-20 academic year will be published prior to the publication of funding guidance in March 2019.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197412","197412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017287","2018-12-04","Home Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people (a) aged 18 and over and (b) aged under 18 successfully applied for asylum in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197413","197413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017288","2018-12-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to fully exempt Community Land Trusts and cohousing tenants from the Voluntary Right to Buy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197414","197414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017289","2018-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who drowned while attempting to reach Europe from the Middle East and North Africa in 2017.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197415","197415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017290","2018-12-03","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what criteria she will use in deciding to call a Northern Ireland Assembly election; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197358","197358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017291","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2018 to Question 121082, what recent progress his Department has made on securing the right of onward movement for UK nationals with status in an EU Member State.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197416","197416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017292","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, further to the Answer of 26 June 2017 to Question 162, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Withdrawal Agreement in achieving the Government's aim of a seamless and frictionless border between Northern Ireland and Ireland.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197417","197417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017293","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many full time equivalent staff are employed in his Department.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197418","197418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017294","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 28 June 2017 to Question 250, if he will publish the agreements which will require replacement as a result of the UK’s exit from the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197419","197419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017295","2018-12-03","Scotland Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 135627, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on land prices in rural areas throughout Scotland.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197420","197420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017296","2018-12-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 19 July 2018 on Grenfell Update, HCWS890, what progress he has made on (a) establishing a more effective regulatory regime for fire and building safety and (b) producing an implementation plan for that regime.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197421","197421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017297","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether (a) Ayrshire Earlies, (b) Forfar Bridies, (c) Ayrshire Dunlop, (d) Orkney Cheddar, (e) Stornoway black pudding, (f) Scottish wild salmon, (g) Scottish farmed salmon, (h) native Shetland wool, (i) Scottish lamb, (j) Scottish beef, (k) Arbroath smokies, (l) Teviotdale cheese, (m) Shetland lamb, (n) Orkney beef and (o) Orkney lamb will continue to be protected by either (i) Protected Designation of Origin, (ii) Protected Geographical Indication and (iii) Traditional Speciality Guaranteed provisions after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197422","197422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017298","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to prevent state-funded schools making inadequate provision for Religious Education.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197423","197423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017299","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consequential provisions are in place for the leaderships of state-funded schools which do not make statutory Religious Education available to all their pupils.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197424","197424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017300","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of current methods for securing the provision of Religious Education in state-funded schools.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197425","197425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017301","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what percentage of (a) religious education and (b) history lessons in state secondary schools are taught by teachers with no post A-level qualification in the subject.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197426","197426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017302","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the level of resources required for teachers, school leaders and other school staff to implement effectively the national protocol on reducing the unnecessary criminalisation of looked-after children and care leavers.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197427","197427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017303","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the resources required for the police effectively to implement the national protocol on reducing the unnecessary criminalisation of looked-after children and care leavers.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197428","197428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017304","2018-12-03","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will provide the evidential basis for her statement to the Northern Ireland Affairs Select Committee on 21 November 2018 that between 1 January 2017 and 31 October 2018 £8,504,716 was spent on salaries for Members of the Legislative Assembly of Northern Ireland in the absence of a functioning Assembly; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197429","197429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017305","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the additional resources required to enable effective implementation of the national protocol on reducing unnecessary criminalisation of looked-after children and care leavers by Youth Offending Teams, the Crown Prosecution Service, Her Majesty's Courts and Tribunals Service, and local Youth Panels.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197430","197430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017306","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received on the detention of Uighur Muslims in China; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197477","197477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017307","2018-12-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the resources required for local authority children's services, care services and care leaver services effectively to implement the national protocol on reducing the unnecessary criminalisation of looked-after children and care leavers.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197431","197431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017309","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to change the operation of the Border Force when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197433","197433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017310","2018-12-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS Foundation Trusts will be required to comply with the new NHS Improvement regulatory framework on wholly owned subsidiary companies.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197434","197434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017311","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to maintain compliance with the Aarhus convention on access to information, public participation in decision-making and access to justice in environmental matters after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197435","197435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017312","2018-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many adverse sanction decisions have been made against universal credit claimants since August 2015 in (a) Salford and Eccles constituency, (b) Salford local authority area, (c) Greater Manchester and (d) the North West.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197436","197436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017313","2018-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the resources used to calculate the market benchmarks for the new pay structure for Defence Equipment and Support employees that began in April 2017 were taken from the sum allocated for pay increases in 2017.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197437","197437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017314","2018-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the methodology used to calculate the market benchmarks to set pay increases for Defence Equipment and Support employees.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197438","197438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017315","2018-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 November 2018 to Question 189645 on Defence Equipment and Support: Staff, what the average salary increase was for each grade Defence Equipment and Support employee in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197439","197439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017316","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff his Department has recruited to conduct work related to the UK leaving the EU since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197440","197440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017318","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many countries his Department will be required to reach an agreement with on acceptance of UK versions of export health certificates to allow the export of animals and animal products; and how many such agreements have been concluded to date.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197441","197441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017319","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on changing the Export Health Certificate system from a manual system to an e-certification system.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197442","197442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017320","2018-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of people at risk of experiencing debt as a result of the six-week transitory wait from legacy benefits to universal credit.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197443","197443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017321","2018-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many posts there are at the Office for Product Safety and Standards; and whether all those posts have been filled.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197478","197478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017322","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to (a) commence and (b) allocate funding to schemes to reduce children's exposure to air pollution; and how much funding will be allocated to each project.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197319","197319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017323","2018-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made a recent assessment of the adequacy of the resources allocated to the Office for Product Safety and Standards; and whether he plans to make an up to date assessment of those resources.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197479","197479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017324","2018-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how the Office of Product Safety and Standards is held accountable by his Department.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197480","197480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017325","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of additional veterinary surgeons that will be required for Export Health Certificate checks after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197444","197444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017326","2018-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the Office for Product Safety and Standards plans to report on its progress against its objectives.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197481","197481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017327","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the at-sea and aerial capability that will be required for marine control and enforcement after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197445","197445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017328","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to strengthen the rules-based international order.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197482","197482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017329","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how long on average the (a) recruitment and (b) training of each marine enforcement officer has taken in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197446","197446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017330","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much it has cost on average to (a) recruit and (b) train each marine enforcement officer in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197447","197447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017331","2018-12-04","Department for Education","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers in (a) Salford, (b) Greater Manchester and (c) the North West Region are on the (a) upper, (b) leading practitioner and (c) leadership pay ranges.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197448","197448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017332","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department’s mandate to Health Education England will specify the need for a health and care workforce which can meet the end of life care choice commitment for babies, children and young people.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197449","197449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017333","2018-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the annual cost of the Administrative Arrangement that the Government plans to conclude with the European Defence Agency; and whether any such Arrangement would enable the UK to exert formal influence on decisions taken by that Agency, including future funding decisions.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197450","197450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017334","2018-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his EU counterpart on the UK's participation in European Union Permanent Structured Cooperation projects after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197451","197451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017335","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what advice was commissioned on the implications of the proposed EU Withdrawal agreement for the operation and powers of institutions established under the Belfast Agreement.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197350","197350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017336","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what goods are exempt from the provisions of Annex five of the EU Withdrawal Agreement.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197351","197351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017337","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support the monitoring of air quality in every primary school.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197341","197341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017338","2018-12-04","Home Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many veterans have been deported in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197452","197452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017339","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support the monitoring of air quality in every educational institution in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197342","197342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017340","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations have been made to the Government of Kuwait on respect for religious freedom in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197352","197352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017341","2018-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's Civilian Personnel Biannual Diversity Dashboard, for what reason the answers that respondents can provide to the question on religious representation are limited to Christian, Non-Christian and secular.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197453","197453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017342","2018-12-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to reply to the letter from Andy Street, Metro Mayor of the West Midlands, on proposed changes to the geography of the Greater Birmingham and Solihull local enterprise partnership; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197323","197323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017343","2018-12-04","House of Commons Commission","2018-11-29","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, the last occasion on which a fire evacuation drill was conducted in the Chamber of the House of Commons; and whether he plans to conduct such a drill in future.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197454","197454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017344","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to make a comparative assessment of air quality in (a) primary schools, (b) secondary schools, (c) universities and (d) other educational environments.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197343","197343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017345","2018-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Office for Product Safety and Standards has an annual report plan.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197483","197483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017346","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits for the tourism industry of a reduction in VAT on hotels and tourist attractions.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197455","197455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017347","2018-12-04","Home Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish guidance on registering under the EU Settlement Scheme for EU nationals who do not have identification or residency documentation due to being in the UK in a situation of trafficking and who have chosen not to enter the National Referral Mechanism and therefore do not have a positive conclusive grounds decision relating to their trafficked status.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197484","197484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017348","2018-12-04","Home Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2018 to Question 185054, what estimate he has made of the number of EU victims of modern slavery within the UK who have been found under section 45 of the Modern Slavery Act 2015 to have been forced to commit a criminal act by their traffickers; and what assessment he has made of the potential merits of exempting those victims from the EU public policy and security tests for deportation.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197485","197485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017349","2018-12-04","Home Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of EU victims of modern slavery in the UK with a (a) positive conclusive grounds decision or (b) reasonable grounds decision under the National Referral Mechanism; and what estimate he has made of the potential cost to the public purse of waiving the EU Settlement Scheme registration fee for people with those decisions.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197486","197486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017350","2018-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of self-employed parents who are evading payment of child maintenance by diverting their income to their partner or spouse.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197456","197456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017351","2018-12-04","Home Office","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times his Department has refused discretionary leave to remain where the child has not lived continuously in the UK for at least seven years but who has then reached that period after appeal in the last (a) 12 months, (b) three years and (c) five years.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197487","197487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017352","2018-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what sums his Department has paid to Leidos to operate the logistics, commodities and services transformation programme in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197457","197457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017353","2018-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the affordability gap in the Equipment Plan 2017-2027.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197458","197458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017354","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to publish the Tailored Review of the Criminal Cases Review Commission.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197344","197344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017355","2018-12-04","Church Commissioners","2018-11-29","To ask the Rt. Hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, with reference to her oral contribution of 29 November, Official Report, what status the suspension of the Dean of Christ Church, Oxford, from his role as Dean of the Anglican cathedral has as a result of the complaint being an internal matter for the college and neither the Church Commissioners nor the wider Church of England has any role in that process.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197459","197459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997124","2018-10-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to promote public awareness of the the effect on people's health of poor quality indoor environments.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 184965","184965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015370","2018-11-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of veterans who are homeless in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) Linlithgow and East Falkirk Constituency.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196216","196216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016120","2018-11-29","Church Commissioners","2018-11-28","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what recent steps the Church of England has taken at parish level to support the needs of local communities.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907925","907925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016125","2018-11-28","Scotland Office","2018-11-28","What recent assessment the Government has made of the effect on low-income families of the roll-out of universal credit throughout Scotland.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907841","907841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016126","2018-11-28","Scotland Office","2018-11-28","What assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of the proposed EU withdrawal agreement on the Scottish economy.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907842","907842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016127","2018-11-28","Scotland Office","2018-11-28","What recent assessment the Government has made of the effect on the Scottish economy of the devolution of powers to set the rates and bands of income tax payable by Scottish taxpayers.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907845","907845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016128","2018-11-28","Scotland Office","2018-11-28","What recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the effect on the Scottish economy of maintaining the current level of excise duty on spirits.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907847","907847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016218","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of spending on research into the causes and treatment of dementia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196678","196678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016220","2018-12-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, for what reasons Government Departments' and other public bodies were excluded from applying to the Cyber Skills Immediate Impact Fund.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196902","196902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016221","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many women are held in immigration detention in the UK.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196774","196774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016223","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of women in immigration detention.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196775","196775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016224","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to address the effects of missed appointments on primary care services.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196776","196776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016226","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the level of workplace skills of university students in the UK and other countries.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196710","196710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016228","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has been made of the relationship between women’s mental health and experience of violence and abuse.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196777","196777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016229","2018-12-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps he has taken to progress a tourism sector deal to support tourist resorts hosting major events.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196711","196711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016231","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has developed targets to ensure the numbers of Black, Asian and Minority Ethnic organ donors more accurately represent the proportion of those ethnic groups in wider society.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196712","196712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016233","2018-12-03","Department for International Trade","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many Departmental staff are working on trade policy; and what estimate he has made of the number of Departmental staff that will work on new international trade deals in 2019-20.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196713","196713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016234","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to provide additional funding to ensure the 2020 modern slavery victim care contract complies with the Human Trafficking Foundation's slavery and trafficking survivor care standards.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196679","196679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016235","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Home Office's national referral mechanism reform guidance published in October 2018 and the High Court judgement on AM & K versus SSHD, whether the plans to make the cuts proposed as part of the national referral mechanism reforms will still go ahead in February and March 2019.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196680","196680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016236","2018-12-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the average licensing costs for organisations with more than one society lottery licence.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196778","196778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016237","2018-12-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Gambling Commission’s Review of society lotteries advice, published in June 2018, (a) what assessment he has made of the conclusion that there was no statistically significant effect of society lotteries affecting National Lottery sales on his proposal to allow an increase in the amount that a large society lottery can raise per year and (b) if he will bring in legislation to reform society lottery sector to support fundraising for charitable causes.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196779","196779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016238","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with NICE on acceptance of the classification of myalgic encephalomyelitis as a neurological disease as defined by the World Health Organisation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196648","196648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016239","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure that the tobacco industry is excluded from funding or helping to provide stop smoking services at a local government level.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196780","196780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016240","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's press release New 'Social Value' contracts to revolutionise government procurement published on 19 November 2018, what steps is the Crown Commercial Service is taking to obtain from Interserve the key organisational information that he said could have smoothed the management of the liquidation of Carillion.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196714","196714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016241","2018-12-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what criteria appointees to the board of the Centre for Data Ethics and Innovation were assessed against when candidates were considered for that role.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196781","196781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016242","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will take steps to reduce the time taken for autistic children to receive a statement of special educational needs.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196715","196715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016243","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number children that have received the meningococcal conjugate vaccine injection in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196716","196716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016244","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to support refugees who have to travel long distances for appointments with immigration officials.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196717","196717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016245","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the appointment of Gina Haspel as director of the CIA, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the UK does not become complicit in facilitating or aiding the use of torture by any third party state cooperating in joint operations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196654","196654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016246","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government provides to search and rescue operations in the central Mediterranean provided by NGOs.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196718","196718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016247","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the provision of support for NGO search and rescue ships in the Mediterranean.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196719","196719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016248","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on maintaining safe and efficient air traffic management beyond 29th March 2019, in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196720","196720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016249","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have illegally entered the UK in the past three months by means of crossing the English Channel.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196721","196721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016250","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on the recruitment of (a) primary and (b) secondary school teaching staff.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196782","196782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016251","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his Department's most recent estimate is of the number of teaching support staff who are EEA nationals.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196783","196783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016252","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) EEA and (b) foreign nationals who have left the teaching profession in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196784","196784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016253","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent progress has been made on securing continued access to the Erasmus programme after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196785","196785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016254","2018-12-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on scientific and academic research in UK universities.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196786","196786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016256","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of care homes had direct access to clinical advice including appropriate on-site assessment at (a) March 2017 and (b) October 2017.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196787","196787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016257","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made on the planned roll-out of urgent treatment centres by Spring 2018.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196788","196788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016259","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress the Government has made on the implementation of the recommendations of the Ambulance Response Programme.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196789","196789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016260","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to enable the establishment of collective defined contribution pensions.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196655","196655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016262","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the (a) timeliness and (b) accuracy of RTI data used in the calculation of awards of universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196656","196656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016264","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) timeliness and (b) accuracy of PAYE Real Time Information data received from employers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196657","196657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016265","2018-12-03","Department for International Development","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department has allocated to programmes to improve the disaster resilience of local communities; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196662","196662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016266","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic steps his Department is taking to support (a) local and (b) national peacebuilding work in South Sudan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196663","196663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016267","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 46 of Autumn Budget 2017, how much and what proportion of the charging investment infrastructure fund has been invested in charging infrastructure.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196790","196790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016268","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer,with reference to page 46 of Autumn Budget 2017, how much and what proportion of the £200 million of private investment for the charging investment infrastructure fund has been raised.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196791","196791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016269","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on providing Julian Assange with safe passage to Ecuador.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196792","196792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016270","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the real terms change was in his Departmental Resource Budget, excluding income received in each year since 2010; and what estimate he has made of the real terms change in that budget in each year until 2022.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196793","196793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016271","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to publish his decision on the renewal of the police transformation fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196681","196681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016272","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied child refugees have been allowed into the UK under the vulnerable children resettlement scheme.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196682","196682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016273","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied refugee children have been relocated to the UK under section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196683","196683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016274","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of the closure of the Probate Service in Nottingham on access to probate services for the bereaved; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196684","196684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016275","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the impact of the increase in probate charges from April 2019 on the (a) personal finances of the bereaved and (b) potential changes in the level of use of probate services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196685","196685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016276","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2018 to Question 194760 on Treasury: Brexit and the Answer of 21 November 2018 to Question 190947 on Treasury: Brexit, for what reason his Department is unable to provide that information.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196903","196903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016277","2018-12-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2018 to Question 194759 on Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy: Brexit and the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 190945 on Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy: Brexit, for what reason his Department is unable to provide that information.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196904","196904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016278","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 191474 on Special Educational Needs: Finance, when he plans to publish data showing the amount of schools block funding local authorities have allocated in 2018-19 to date compared with the amount they received in order to provide an indication of funding directed to other areas such as high needs.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196905","196905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016280","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many enforcement undertakings for waste crime the Environment Agency has undertaken in each of the last three years; how many resulted in successful prosecution; and what fines were imposed in each case if the sums were greater than £10,000.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196686","196686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016281","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Life sentences for killer drivers, published on 15 October 2017, what the timescale is for bringing forward legislation on introducing life sentences for causing death by dangerous or careless driving.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196794","196794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016283","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to respond to the consultation on new cycling offences: causing death or serious injury when cycling, which closed on 5 November 2018.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196795","196795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016285","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made in developing the UK Shared Prosperity Fund (UKSPF); and what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on the publication of the planned public consultation on the UKSPF.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196796","196796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016286","2018-12-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress has been made in developing the UK Shared Prosperity Fund(UKSPF); and when he plans to publish the public consultation on the UKSPF.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196797","196797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016287","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will make an assessment of the effect of the closure of five walk-in centres and minor injury units in Eastham, Wallasey, Birkenhead, New Ferry and Moreton in Wirral on the capacity of the A&E department at Arrowe Park Hospital.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196722","196722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016288","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of step-down beds in NHS hospitals that are staffed by private healthcare companies.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196723","196723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016289","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the value is of his Department's contract with Four Seasons Health Care; and what steps his Department is taking to measure the value for money of that contract.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196724","196724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016290","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what measures his Department has in place to identify suppliers with precarious financial situations during the procurement process.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196725","196725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016291","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the financial health of companies that hold contracts with the NHS.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196726","196726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016292","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding has been provided by his Department for (a) domestic violence prevention programmes and (b) services for victims of domestic violence in (i) St Helens and (ii) Liverpool City Region.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196798","196798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016293","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the independence and sovereignty of Ukraine.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196687","196687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016294","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with his French counterpart on migrants illegally crossing the English Channel.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196688","196688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016295","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional financial support his Department makes available to (a) primary and (b) secondary schools with high numbers of SEND children.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196799","196799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016296","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce the amount of food wastage from supermarkets.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196689","196689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016297","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the staffing budget for schools has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196800","196800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016298","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the UK is able unilaterally to withdraw from the proposed EU withdrawal agreement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196727","196727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016299","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what financial support is available to schools from local authorities to support SEND children.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196801","196801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016300","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department has allocated to Southampton City Council to support children with SEND needs in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196802","196802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016301","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has in place to ensure the entry of (a) medical supplies and (b) medicines to the UK in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196728","196728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016302","2018-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in which countries British armed forces are deployed in operations to tackle the illegal drugs trade.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196690","196690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016303","2018-12-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what planning protections are in place to prevent inappropriate road developments in areas of outstanding natural beauty.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196729","196729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016304","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has issued to universities on study trips to foreign countries since the arrest and imprisonment of Matthew Hedges.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196691","196691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016305","2018-12-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what planning protections are in place to prevent inappropriate housing developments in areas of outstanding natural beauty.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196730","196730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016306","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to increase the level of the recruitment and retention of core and higher trainees in psychiatry in England; and if will he make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196803","196803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016307","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to increase the number of full-time equivalent GPs in England; and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196804","196804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016308","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress he has made on the plan to provide an additional 5,000 full-time equivalent GPs in England by 2020; and if will he make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196805","196805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016309","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many full-time equivalent doctors worked in paediatrics in England in each year since 2009; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196806","196806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016310","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2018 to Question 191268, on Pensions: Advisory Services, what steps he is taking to encourage those identified in the pension wise service evaluation report for 2016-17 who are not pre-disposed to taking actions that help them make informed decisions on their pensions.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196692","196692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016311","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people in receipt of legacy benefit payments had a deduction in the latest month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196807","196807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016312","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the High Court Judgment K & Anor, R (on the application of) v Secretary of State for the Home Department of 8 November 2018, whether plans set out in the NRM reforms, announced in October 2017 to align subsistence rates for victims of trafficking with asylum seekers will not be implemented through the statutory guidance on victim support, Section 49 of the Modern Slavery Act 2015.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196808","196808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016313","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit payments were subject to a deduction excluding sanctions in the latest month for which data is available.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196809","196809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016314","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much the Government plans to spend on preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal in each month until March 2019.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196731","196731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016315","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit claimants were subject to a level of deduction excluding sanctions from the standard allowance (a) at the 40 per cent cap, (b) above the 30 per cent level (c) above the 20 per cent level and (d) above the 10 per cent level in the latest month for which data is available.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196810","196810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016316","2018-12-03","Department for International Trade","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the UK will be able to agree free trade deals with third countries during the transitional period proposed in the withdrawal agreement with the EU.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196732","196732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016317","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people in (a) Bexley borough and b) the Bexleyheath and Crayford constituency are at risk of developing Type 2 diabetes.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196733","196733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016318","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) median and (b) mean times were for landlords to progress from a claim to possession of a property by a county court bailiff under the accelerated process for the most recent period for which figures are available (i) across England and (ii) by each court circuit.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196734","196734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016319","2018-12-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to end the practice of no-fault eviction under section 21 of the Housing Act 1998; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196735","196735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016320","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the transition period set out in the agreement on the withdrawal of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland from the European Union, whether the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency will retain its status as a competent authority; and whether existing CE marks assigned under that agency will be valid from 29 March 2019 until the end of that transition period.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196736","196736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016321","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to extend the zero rate of VAT to digital publications.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196811","196811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016322","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2018 to Question 191271 on Fires: Solar Power, whether there are processes in place to oblige local fire and rescue authorities to consider firefighter guidance recommendations made by relevant reports.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196693","196693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016323","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NICE’s highly specialised technology programme, if he will publish the (a) quality adjusted life year gains and (b) incremental cost effectiveness ratios according to (i) pharmaceutical company estimates, (ii) expert reference group estimates and (iii) NICE-agreed rates for (A) technologies with final guidance since 2015, (B) technologies with draft guidance since 2015 and (C) the comparators used for each assessment.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196812","196812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016324","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of NHS expenditure on medicines with an orphan designation in England in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196813","196813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016325","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what progress he has made in negotiations with the EU on the UK's participation in the Prum Convention on the exchange of fingerprint, DNA and vehicle registration data after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196737","196737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016326","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2018 to Question 189538 on Palliative Care: Children, what processes (a) NHS England and (b) his Department have in place to assess the level of collaboration between the relevant authorities and organisations.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196694","196694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016327","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment has been made of the effect on the operation of Tourism NI and Tourism Ireland of the proposed EU Withdrawal Agreement.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196738","196738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016328","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what progress he has made in negotiations with the EU on UK participation in European Reference Networks after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196739","196739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016329","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has (a) funded, (b) awarded contracts to and (c) procured the services of the Integrity Initiative in each financial year since 2015-16.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196814","196814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016330","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has (a) funded, (b) awarded contracts to and (c) procured the services of the Integrity Initiative in each financial year since 2015-16.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196815","196815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016331","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has (a) funded, (b) awarded contracts to and (c) procured the services of the Integrity Initiative in each financial year since 2015-16.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196816","196816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016332","2018-12-03","Department for International Trade","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department has (a) funded, (b) awarded contracts to and (c) procured the services of the Integrity Initiative in each financial year since 2015-16.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196817","196817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016333","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect on the UK's participation in the (a) Brussels and (b) Lugano Conventions on jurisdiction and the enforcement of judgments in civil and commercial matters of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196740","196740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016334","2018-12-03","Department for International Development","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has (a) funded, (b) awarded contracts to and (c) procured the services of the Integrity Initiative in each financial year since 2015-16.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196818","196818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016335","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure the maintenance of mutual recognition of judgements in the area of family law after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196741","196741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016336","2018-12-03","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the representatives of the Government of the Irish Republic on the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196742","196742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016337","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of using geotechnical baseline reports to assess the possible (a) settlement damage to and (b) strengthening required for buildings along the High Speed Two London tunnel route.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196819","196819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016338","2018-12-03","Leader of the House","2018-11-28","To ask the Leader of the House, with reference to the Government's loneliness strategy, published in October 2018, what steps the Early Years Ministerial Group on Family Support is taking to (a) improve family support and (b) ensure local services work together in a more cost efficient and integrated way.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196820","196820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016339","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November to Question 192869 on Buckingham Palace: Honours, which organisations are contracted to (a) create and (b) sell the items; and when each of the tendering processes took place for those contracts.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196743","196743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016340","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November to Question 192869 on Buckingham Palace: Honours, in which of the three categories of items listed in the Income section of the table on Page 53 of the Annual Report and Accounts of the Sovereign Grant 2017-18 is the income deriving from the contract to create and sell the items.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196744","196744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016341","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November to Question 192869, what other sources of income are included in the same category of items listed in the Income section of the table on Page 53 of the Annual Report and Accounts of the Sovereign Grant 2017-18 as the income deriving from the contract to create and sell the items mentioned in that answer; and where not constrained by commercial sensitivity, how much income was derived from each of those other sources in 2017-18.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196745","196745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016342","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many full-time equivalent staff (a) the Cabinet Office and (b) Number 10 Downing Street employ whose responsibilities include the (i) photography and filming of official events and (ii) production of official photographs and films.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196746","196746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016343","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the combined annual salaries of all full-time equivalent staff of (a) the Cabinet Office and (b) Number 10 Downing Street whose responsibilities include (i) the photography and filming of official events and (ii) the production of official photographs and films in 2017-18.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196747","196747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016344","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether (a) HS2 Ltd, (b) third party contractors or (c) his Department will be liable in the event that settlement damage to vulnerable and listed buildings occurs due to works along the High Speed Two London tunnel route.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196821","196821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016345","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations his Department has received on the risks to buildings along the High Speed Two London tunnel route in the last six months.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196822","196822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016346","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his latest estimate is of the total cost of High Speed Two; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196823","196823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016347","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department has taken to provide assurance to (a) users and (b) employers on the security of documents stored on cloud services in relation to the IT system for applying for settled status.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196664","196664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016348","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of Windrush people that were held in immigration detention centres.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196665","196665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016349","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of Windrush people that participated in voluntary removal.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196666","196666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016350","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the written evidence submitted by Interserve to the Public Accounts Committee on 6 June 2018,  Strategic Suppliers SSU0003, whether Crown Representatives are able to discuss issues relating to contracts not yet awarded with strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196748","196748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016351","2018-12-03","Department for International Development","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government has funded Radio Dabanga in Sudan since its creation in December 2008.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196749","196749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016352","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much money his Department has spent on each (a) consultant and (b) consultancy firm to support the HS2 project in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196824","196824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016353","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of Windrush people that worked in the NHS who were (a) held in immigration detention centres and (b) deported to other countries.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196667","196667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016354","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of Windrush people that were veterans of the armed forces who were (a) held in immigration detention centres and (b) deported to other countries.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196668","196668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016355","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the risk of conflicts of interest in relation to settlement deed surveys provided by companies contracted to work on the High Speed Two London Tunnel Route.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196825","196825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016356","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much HS2 Ltd has spent on compensation grouting in advance of construction work along the High Speed Two London tunnel route.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196826","196826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016357","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will amend universal credit regulations to allow for the housing cost element for renters to be calculated for a 53-week year in 2019-20; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196906","196906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016358","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many speech and language therapists are employed in (a) children and young people’s NHS mental health services and (b) adult NHS mental health services.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196658","196658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016359","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate he has made of the number of members of the Windrush generation who were (a) held in immigration detention centres and (b) deported to other countries who had (i) been teachers and (ii) held other educational positions in the UK.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196669","196669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016360","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate he has made of the number of members of the Windrush generation who were (a) held in immigration detention centres and (b) deported to other countries who had worked for public transport services in the UK.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196670","196670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016361","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report entitled Health at a Glance: Europe 2018, published by the OECD on 22 November 2018, whether he plans to respond to the findings on the estimated direct and indirect costs of mental health.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196659","196659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016362","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of members of the Windrush generation who were deported to other countries and who have since died.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196671","196671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016363","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of youth unemployment.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196660","196660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016364","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate he has made of the number of members of the Windrush generation who were deported to other countries who have since died; and what information he has on their former employment in the UK.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196672","196672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016365","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has had discussions with HS2 Ltd on the use of target cost contracts instead of geotechnical baseline reports; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the level of compensation arising from damage to vulnerable buildings along the High Speed Two construction route of excluding the use of those reports.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196827","196827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016366","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate he has made of the number of members of the Windrush generation who were deported to other countries and have family members who are entitled to be in the UK but have been refused entry.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196673","196673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016367","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate he has made of the number of members of the Windrush generation who were deported to other countries and have since been refused entry to the UK.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196674","196674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016368","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to EU Exit Long-term economic analysis published on 28 November, which of the four scenarios most accurately reflects the Prime Minister's proposed agreement on the withdrawal of the UK from the EU and Euratom.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196828","196828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016369","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate he has made of the number of members of the Windrush generation who were deported to other countries and have subsequently requested compensation.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196675","196675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016370","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate he has made of the number of members of the Windrush generation who were detained at an immigration centre and have subsequently requested compensation.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196676","196676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016371","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much money from the public purse was spent (a) producing and (b) promoting the Facebook advertisement entitled The Brexit Deal explained.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196829","196829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016372","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what other platforms the Facebook advertisement entitled The Brexit Deal explained was run.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196830","196830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016373","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what audience targeting filters were used for the Facebook advertisement entitled The Brexit Deal explained.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196831","196831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016374","2018-12-03","Scotland Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much money from the public purse was spent (a) producing and (b) promoting the Facebook advertisement entitled Closing the Gender Pay Gap.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196832","196832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016375","2018-12-03","Scotland Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland,  what audience targeting filters were used for the Facebook advertisement entitled Closing the Gender Pay Gap.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196833","196833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016376","2018-12-03","Scotland Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, for what reason the Facebook advertisement entitled Closing the Gender Pay Gap does not appear in Facebook Ad Library as a political advertisement.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196834","196834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016377","2018-12-03","Scotland Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, on what other platforms the Facebook advertisement entitled Closing the Gender Pay Gap was run.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196835","196835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016378","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reason the Facebook advertisement entitled The Brexit Deal explained does not appear in Facebook Ad Library as a political advertisement.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196836","196836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016379","2018-12-03","Scotland Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much money was spent from the public purse (a) producing and (b) promoting the Facebook advertisement entitled Scotland's public spending.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196837","196837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016380","2018-12-03","Scotland Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what audience targeting filters were used for the Facebook advertisement entitled Scotland's public spending.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196838","196838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016381","2018-12-03","Scotland Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, for what reason the Facebook advertisement entitled Scotland's public spending does not appear in Facebook Ad Library as a political advertisement.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196839","196839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016382","2018-12-03","Scotland Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, on what other platforms the Facebook advertisement entitled Scotland's public spending was run.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196840","196840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016383","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of people from the Windrush generation who have lost their job because they could not provide the evidence required to demonstrate their right to remain in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196677","196677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016384","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of people from the Windrush generation who have lost their home because they could not provide evidence to demonstrate their right to remain.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196695","196695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016385","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of people from the Windrush generation who could not obtain a mortgage because they could not provide the evidence to demonstrate their right to remain.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196696","196696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016386","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of members of the Windrush generation who were denied access to NHS treatment because they could not demonstrate their right to remain in the country.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196697","196697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016387","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate he has made of the number of members of the Windrush generation who were unable to obtain a driver’s licence because they could not provide evidence of their right to remain in the country.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196698","196698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016388","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the finding of the British Medical Journal's report, Temporal and geographic patterns of stab injuries in young people: a retrospective cohort study from a UK major trauma centre, published on 6 November 2018, that children under 16 are at the highest risk of being stabbed when going home from school, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of staggering school leaving times to reduce incidents of knife crime between children.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196841","196841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016389","2018-12-03","Department for International Trade","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will suspend arms sales to Saudi Arabia until an independent international inquiry can establish culpability for violations of international humanitarian law on all sides of the Yemeni conflict.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196649","196649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016390","2018-12-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that skilled workers in the offshore oil and gas sector can train to work in the offshore wind sector without incurring unreasonable extra cost or duplicate qualifications.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196842","196842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016391","2018-12-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to improve the enforcement of the national minimum wage for seafarers working on merchant ships operating between UK ports and offshore energy installations on the UK continental shelf.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196843","196843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016392","2018-12-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps HMRC has taken to ensure compliance with the national minimum wage for seafarers working on vessels working in the construction and maintenance phase of the offshore wind industry.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196844","196844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016393","2018-12-03","Prime Minister","2018-11-28","To ask the Prime Minister, on how many occasions the Prime Minister has attended the Royal Visits Committee in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196650","196650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016394","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the criteria are by which the Royal Visits Committee recommends a royal visit.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196651","196651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016395","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to promote awareness of food allergies in schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196699","196699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016396","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he or Ministers in his Department have met the hon. Member for Wells to discuss LGBT asylum cases.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196845","196845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016397","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 5.27 of Budget 2018, how much of the £160 million allocated in 2019-20 for counter-terrorism policing will be spent on counter-terrorism in Scotland.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196907","196907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016398","2018-12-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 188024 on Care Leavers: Rough Sleeping, if he will make it his policy to record statistics on whether or not people sleeping rough have spent time in foster care.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196750","196750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016399","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 188024 on Care Leavers: Rough Sleeping, whether his Department consulted with representatives of local authorities prior to their announcement of additional funding for local authority areas to employ specialist personal advisers.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196751","196751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016400","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions has he had with representatives of Lima Group countries on the political and economic situation in Venezuela.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196846","196846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016401","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle the effect of deprivation on epilepsy and reduce the number of deaths caused by that condition.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196700","196700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016402","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 188024 on Care Leavers: Rough Sleeping, how many specialist personal advisers his Department estimates will be provided as a result of the additional funding announced.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196752","196752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016403","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for biometric information have been processed in each post office in Glasgow Central constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196847","196847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016404","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for biometric information have been processed by post offices in each Parliamentary constituency in the each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196848","196848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016405","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2018 to Question 188021 on Places of Worship Security Funding Scheme, how many officials of his Department have been involved in visiting religious buildings.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196753","196753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016406","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has plans to up-rate the Christmas bonus paid to recipients of certain benefits.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196849","196849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016407","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to ensure that families receive appropriate advice and support when their relatives have died as a result of symptoms relating to epilepsy.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196701","196701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016408","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2018 to Question 188021 on Places of Worship Security Funding Scheme, whether officials of other Government departments have been involved in (a) visiting religious buildings and (b) attending faith-based roundtables.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196754","196754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016409","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for how many years the Christmas bonus for recipients of certain benefits has been set at the value of £10.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196850","196850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016410","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will estimate how many benefit recipients will receive the Christmas bonus for Christmas 2018.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196851","196851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016411","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2018 to Question 188021 on Places of Worship Security Funding Scheme, which (a) mosques, (b) gurdwaras, (c) churches, (d) temples and (e) faith-based roundtables officials of his Department attended.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196755","196755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016412","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2018 to Question 188021 on Places of Worship Security Funding Scheme, whether (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have attended (i) religious buildings and (ii) meetings with religious representatives to discuss the Places of Worship Security Funding Scheme in 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196756","196756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016413","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether seafarer recruitment and placement agencies registered in (a) Crown Dependencies and (b) British Overseas Territories operate in the territory of the UK for the purposes of compliance with (i) Regulation 1.4 and (ii) Standard A1.4 of the Maritime Labour Convention.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196852","196852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016414","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many seafarer (a) Ratings and (b) Officers working in the UK shipping industry are employed by recruitment and placement agencies registered outside the UK.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196853","196853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016415","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish a list of those maritime recruitment and placement agencies that provide crew to company groups which have qualified for the tonnage tax; and whether each of those agencies are regulated by the Maritime and Coastguard Agency for compliance with the Merchant Shipping (Maritime Labour Convention) (Recruitment and Placement) Regulations 2014.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196854","196854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016416","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many UK-resident seafarer (a) Ratings and (b) Officers are employed on tonnage tax qualifying vessels registered on (i) the UK flag, (ii) other Red Ensign Group flags and (iii) non-UK flags.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196855","196855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016417","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cases of non-compliance with the Merchant Shipping (Maritime Labour Convention) (Recruitment and Placement) Regulations 2014 have been recorded by Maritime and Coastguard Agency surveyors since those regulations came into force.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196856","196856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016418","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on (a) the country under which vessels fishing in UK waters are flagged and (b) the proportion of those vessels (i) under 24 metres and (ii) covered by The Code of Practice for the Safety of Small Fishing Vessels.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196857","196857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016419","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2018 to Question 180168 on Shipping: Training, which merchant vessel departments those 40 ratings were trained to work in.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196858","196858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016420","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many new ships were registered on the UK Ship Register in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196859","196859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016421","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2018 to Question 180168 on Shipping: Training, whether those 40 ratings are (a) employed in the UK shipping industry and (b) UK residents.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196860","196860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016422","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on public scrutiny of the International Maritime Organisation’s decision-making process.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196861","196861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016423","2018-12-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate his Department has made of the proportion of households living in a leasehold property.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196862","196862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016424","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Defence on the Royal Fleet Auxiliary contract for a new fleet of solid support vessels; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of that contract on the level of UK (a) commercial shipbuilding and (b) merchant seafarers.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196863","196863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016425","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate his Department has made of the proportion of school children who received at least six swimming lessons in the last academic year for which information is available.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196864","196864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016426","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of (a) prosecutions for firework offences and (b) firework-related attacks on emergency workers in the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196757","196757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016427","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of injuries caused to livestock by fireworks in the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196758","196758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016428","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of injuries to domestic pets caused by fireworks in the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196759","196759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016429","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that Sandy Lane Nursery and Forest School in Warrington receives adequate funding to ensure its future sustainability.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196760","196760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016430","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in the Warrington North constituency will receive a cash increase in their budget per pupil for 2019-20.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196761","196761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016431","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect on (a) access to justice and (b) waiting times for hearings of the removal of civil matters from Warrington courts.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196762","196762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016432","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the value is of his Department's contract with Four Seasons Healthcare in (a) Merseyside and (b) Wirral.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196763","196763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016433","2018-12-03","Department for International Development","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2018 to Question 190838, how much UK funding will be used to fund local observation of the upcoming general election in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196764","196764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016434","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to Answer of 24 July 2018 to Question 166215 and the review of the evidence base for the Bowland Fells SPA, on what basis that review was considered to be necessary; when that review was commissioned; what the scope was of that review; who carried out that review; when that review will be made available to his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196865","196865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016435","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools have been rated by Ofsted as inadequate for (a) two years, (b) three years, (c) four years, (d) five years and (e) more than six years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196866","196866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016436","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools have been rated by Ofsted as requires improvement for (a) two years, (b) three years, (c) four years, (d) five years and (e) more than six years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196867","196867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016437","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of (i) primary, (ii) secondary, (iii) special schools and (iv) alternative provision pupils attend schools judged (A) inadequate and (B) requires improvement at the (I) last inspection and (II) last inspection of their predecessor school.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196868","196868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016438","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2018 to question 193440 on Universal Credit: Easington, how many claimants of universal credit have been called for a work capability assessment since the Centre for Health and Disabilities Assessment started its contract in March 2015.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196869","196869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016439","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the gross value added to the economy was from the tonnage tax scheme in each year since 2003-04.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196870","196870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016440","2018-12-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made on the introduction of three-year tenancies for families in the private rented sector.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196765","196765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016441","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of academy schools that were rated (a) inadequate and (b) requires improvement before being granted academy status have not been subject to an inspection.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196871","196871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016442","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many local authority maintained schools that failed an Ofsted inspection with an inadequate judgement have been waiting (a) less than nine months, (b) between nine and 18 months, (c) two years, (d) three years and (e) over three years for an academy sponsor to be confirmed; and how many of those schools are in the process of being issued an academy order.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196872","196872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016443","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will publish the dates of the visits he has made to the port of Dover since May 2015.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196873","196873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016444","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that products containing palm oil that are sold in the UK use sustainably-produced palm oil.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196874","196874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016445","2018-12-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Office for Product Safety and Standards has plans to undertake an investigation into the safety of Whirlpool tumble dryers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196875","196875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016446","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what fiscal steps his Department has put in place to ensure the timely payment of universal credit for families with children born during the assessment period.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196876","196876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016447","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the provision of community mental health services for people with severe mental illness.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196877","196877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016448","2018-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Service Complaints Ombudsman is a member of the Service Justice Board; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196766","196766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016449","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many of the phase two recommendations of sites qualifying in relation to bittern are (a) existing Special Protection Areas (SPA) that require reclassifying to add bittern as a feature, (b) restored reedbed habitat outside of existing SPAs and (c) newly created reedbed habitat outside of existing SPAs.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196767","196767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016450","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, for what reasons the EU Withdrawal Agreement does not contain information on UK access to EU Science funding beyond December 2020.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196908","196908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016451","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the publications entitled, Political Declaration setting out the framework for the future relationship between the European Union and the United Kingdom and the Draft Agreement on the withdrawal of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland from the European Union and the European Atomic Energy Community, what future (a) legislation, (b) directives, (c) rules and (d) other instructions the EU plans to introduce which will have an effect on the UK from 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196878","196878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016452","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2018 to Question 195102, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport on supporting the Nigerian Government to reduce the spread of false information on social media.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196879","196879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016453","2018-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) staff were employed as investigation officers, (b) investigations were current and (c) investigations were awaiting allocation to an investigation officer in the office of the Service Complaints Ombudsman in each quarter since January 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196768","196768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016454","2018-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many successful applicants for the role of investigation officer were awaiting security vetting in each quarter since 2017; how long each such investigation officer was waiting for that vetting to be completed; how many people found other employment during the period of security vetting; who was responsible for that security vetting; how often the contractual standards for security vetting were not met in that time period; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196769","196769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016455","2018-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what budget is available each year to the office of the Armed Forces Ombudsman to access legal advice from (a) the Government's legal service, (b) his Department's legal services and (c) independent legal services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196770","196770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016456","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether contingency planning and expenditure by the Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency (MHRA) on any systems or processes, including software is being incurred on systems or processes which will be redundant in the event that an agreement is reached that includes continued full co-operation, based on regulatory alignment, with the European Medicines Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196702","196702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016457","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what other aspects of medicines regulation including regulation related to patient safety is postponed due to contingency planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196703","196703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016458","2018-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the last three inspections were carried out by the Independent Police Complaints Commission into any aspect of the military police service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196771","196771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016459","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the (a) legislative requirements and (b) timetable required to hold a second referendum on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196652","196652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016460","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 15 of the Political Declaration setting out the framework for the future relationship between the European Union and the United Kingdom and the provisions on the European Investment Bank contained within the Draft Agreement on the withdrawal of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland from the European Union and the European Atomic Energy Community; what plans he has for the future relationship with the European Investment Bank Group; the involvement that the UK would have in the decision-making; the cost of that activity; and the effect of that activity on the arrangements for the financial settlement with the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196880","196880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016461","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in each local authority are (i) academies and (ii) maintained schools.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196881","196881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016462","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in each local authority have an Ofsted rating of (i) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requires improvement and (d) inadequate.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196882","196882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016463","2018-12-03","Department for International Trade","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the effect of the provisions in the Political Declaration setting out the framework for the future relationship between the European Union and the United Kingdom and the Draft Agreement on the withdrawal of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland from the European Union and the European Atomic Energy Community on the ability of the UK to (a) agree and (b) implement international trade deals with countries outside of the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196883","196883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016464","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will establish a public inquiry (a) to examine matters relating to campaigning and foreign influence in the EU referendum campaign that are not currently being examined by the police, the National Crime Agency or the Information Commissioner; (b) to consider the consequences of potentially irregular and unlawful conduct during the EU referendum campaign; and (c) to make recommendations for appropriate action.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196772","196772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016466","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average number of attendances seen per day was in A&E Departments at NHS hospitals in England in 2018.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196885","196885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016467","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to classify diabetes as a clinical priority.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196653","196653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016468","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many A&E units in NHS hospitals in England attend to more than the national average number of patients per day.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196886","196886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016469","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of providing additional signalling staff to enable the earlier running of Sunday services between Derby and Crewe.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196887","196887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016470","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on how many occasions the Royal Visits Committee met in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196661","196661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016471","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Digital report, Mental Health of Children and Young People in England, 2017, published on 22 November 2018, when the data on children and young people’s mental health will next be updated and with what frequency that data will be updated.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196888","196888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016472","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the time taken between the publication of Mental health of children and young people in Great Britain, 2004 and Mental Health of Children and Young People in England, 2017 on the understanding of demand for children’s mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196889","196889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016473","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report entitled, Mental Health of Children and Young People in England, 2017, published by NHS Digital on 22 November 2018, if he will reissue the Government Green Paper, Transforming Children and Young People’s Mental Health on the demand for mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196890","196890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016474","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 23 of the Government response to the joint Education and Health Select Committee Report, the Government’s Green Paper on mental health: failing a generation, Cm 9627, what progress he has made on the keep-in-touch exercise with respondents to the NHS Digital report, Mental Health of Children and Young People in England, 2017.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196891","196891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016475","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to revise the mental health component of the NHS long-term plan to take account of the data contained in the NHS Digital Report, Mental Health of Children and Young People in England, 2017.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196892","196892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016476","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the publications entitled, Political Declaration setting out the framework for the future relationship between the European Union and the United Kingdom, and Draft Agreement on the withdrawal of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland from the European Union and the European Atomic Energy Community, on what matters the Court of Justice of the European Union will exercise (a) jurisdiction, (b) binding judgements and (c) judgements that influence the UK after 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196893","196893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016477","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the publications entitled, Political Declaration setting out the framework for the future relationship between the European Union and the United Kingdom and Draft Agreement on the withdrawal of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland from the European Union and the European Atomic Energy Community, what (a) primary and (b) secondary legislation will be required to facilitate the measures in relation to the jurisdiction of the Court of Justice of the European Union.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196894","196894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016478","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the publications entitled, Political Declaration setting out the framework for the future relationship between the European Union and the United Kingdom and Draft Agreement on the withdrawal of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland from the European Union and the European Atomic Energy Community, on what matters the Court of Justice of the European Union will exercise (a) jurisdiction, (b) binding judgements and (c) judgements that effect the UK after 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196895","196895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016479","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the publications entitled, Political Declaration setting out the framework for the future relationship between the European Union and the United Kingdom and Draft Agreement on the withdrawal of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland from the European Union and the European Atomic Energy Community, what (a) primary and (b) secondary legislation will be required to facilitate the measures contained in relation to the jurisdiction of the Court of Justice of the European Union.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196896","196896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016480","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 83 of the Political Declaration setting out the framework for the future relationship between the European Union and the United Kingdom, under which circumstances the Court of Justice of the European Union will (a) have jurisdiction, (b) make binding judgements and (c) make judgements that carry influence in the UK after 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196897","196897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016481","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 83 of the Political Declaration setting out the framework for the future relationship between the European Union and the United Kingdom, under which circumstances the Court of Justice of the European Union can make a judgement involving the interpretation of the EU Charter on Fundamental Rights which could affect the UK after 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196898","196898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016482","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the methodology used by HMRC to decide on the figure for top-slicing relief.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196899","196899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016483","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 54 of the Political Declaration setting out the framework for the future relationship between the European Union and the United Kingdom, how many non-UK EU nationals (a) currently living in the UK and (b) expected to be living in the UK over the next 15 years will qualify for social security support from the public purse; what benefits those people will be eligible for; and what estimate he has made of the cost of providing those benefits.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196900","196900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016484","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-UK EU nationals (a) are in receipt of universal credit and (b) will be in receipt of universal credit in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196901","196901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016485","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has plans to visit Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196704","196704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016486","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received from the Tamil community on the situation in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196705","196705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016487","2018-12-03","Department for International Development","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much Overseas Development Assistance has been allocated to Sri Lanka in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196706","196706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016488","2018-12-03","Department for International Trade","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent estimate he has made of the level of bi-lateral trade with Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196707","196707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016489","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic support he is providing to the Government of Sri Lanka during the current constitutional situation.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196708","196708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016490","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the Prime Minster has last held a conversation with the Prime Minister of Sri Lanka on the political situation in that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196709","196709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1016491","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the (a) level of harm caused to children and (b) amount of police time expended as a result of the absence of regulations governing over 16 year old children's homes; if he will (i) instruct Ofsted to undertake inspections of those homes and (ii) introduce a fit and proper person test for directors of those homes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196773","196773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015206","2018-11-28","Department for Education","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions the Prime Minister has had with the President of the Republic of Ireland on the undergraduates from England studying at Irish universities; and whether the current financial arrangements will be made available to (a) them and (b) EU citizens after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 195518","195518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015270","2018-11-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to protect green spaces in the South East.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907900","907900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015278","2018-11-29","Church Commissioners","2018-11-27","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England is taking to tackle problem gambling.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907931","907931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015347","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what factors are taken into consideration when decisions are taken on storing government data by contracted private sector cloud companies.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196203","196203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015348","2018-12-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many applications (a) submitted to and (b) approved by the Cyber Skills Immediate Impact Fund there were in each of the three award ranges set out in the application guidance.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196204","196204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015349","2018-12-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 November 2018 to Question 190517, Cybercrime: Small Businesses, whether Government funding is available to small and medium-sized businesses to help them achieve CyberEssentials certification.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196205","196205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015350","2018-12-03","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland,  what progress she has made in discussions with the Irish Government on the implementation of improvements to the management of Lough Foyle.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196108","196108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015351","2018-12-03","Treasury","2018-11-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what (a) financial and (b) other support the Government makes available to people diagnosed with cancer who have (i) banking and (ii) other financial problems.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196109","196109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015352","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) geographical area and (b) age range the National Careers Service covers.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196110","196110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015353","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people served a sentence of imprisonment for convictions under the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991 in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196140","196140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015354","2018-12-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the total cost to the public purse of the Cyber Accelerator scheme has been to date; and what criteria his Department is using to determine the scheme's success.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196206","196206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015355","2018-12-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Cyber Accelerator Scheme, what steps he has taken to ensure that the results of technological and cyber innovation funded by public investment are made available to the public.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196207","196207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015356","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of people that have had an application for asylum rejected who have no recourse to public funds in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196311","196311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015357","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the letter from the Minister of State for Policing and the Fire Service to the hon. Member for Birmingham, Ladywood, MIN/0014431/18, for what reason his Department is unable to obtain statistics from the Police National Computer on the number of person records relating to non-charge or conviction action by (a) force and (b) race.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196141","196141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015358","2018-11-29","Department for Education","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he has met the Chancellor of the Exchequer to discuss education funding in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196208","196208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015359","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much additional funding announced in Budget 2018 has been allocated to the prevention of Type 2 diabetes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196310","196310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015360","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the potential effect on the price of care purchased by self-funders of local authorities purchasing care packages from the same providers in bulk at a lower unit cost price.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196209","196209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015361","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to Sir Keith Pearson’s review entitled Taking revalidation forward: improving the process of relicensing for doctors, published in January 2017, what steps his Department have taken in response to identified weaknesses in the appraisal and revalidation processes for doctors working as locums; and if he will publish a timeline showing when such steps were (a) initiated and (b) completed.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196142","196142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015362","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will undertake a review of the General Medical Council's procedures for revalidating medical professionals as a result of the Zholia Alemi case.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196143","196143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015363","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will review the powers conferred by the Medical Profession (Responsible Officer) Regulations 2010 and 2013 that enable locum agencies to revalidate doctors.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196144","196144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015364","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations he has received from (a) the National Ballistics Intelligence Service, (b) the National Police Chiefs Council, (c) police forces and (d) the National Crime Agency on the prohibition of .50 calibre rifles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196210","196210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015365","2018-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel who were born overseas currently serve in the (a) Army, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Royal Air Force.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196211","196211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015366","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK citizens are imprisoned in the United States.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196212","196212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015367","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers were injured while on duty in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017 and (d) 2018.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196213","196213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015368","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what data-gathering methodologies his Department uses to count the number of people arriving in the UK from (a) the EU, (b) the EEA and (c) other countries.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196214","196214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015369","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful prosecutions were made under section 121 of the Anti-social Behaviour, Crime and Policing Act 2014 in each year since its commencement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196215","196215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015371","2018-12-03","Department for International Development","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding she has allocated to Feed the Hungry and where in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196081","196081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015372","2018-12-03","Department for International Development","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has plans to make an assessment of the effectiveness of the eligibility criteria in applications for funding to ensure that (a) small charities and (b) other small organisations are not disadvantaged; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196082","196082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015373","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2018 Question 193410 on Diplomatic Service: EU Countries, in which countries UK citizens do not have any direct national representation.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196145","196145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015374","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report entitled Unfinished business: An assessment of the national approach to improving cancer services in England 1995–2015, published by the Health Foundation in November 2018, whether he plans to take steps in response to the conclusions of that report; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196146","196146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015375","2018-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his Department's data Costs relating to State and Guest of Government visits, if he will update that data to include the July 2018 visit to the UK of US President Donald Trump for the costs relating to state and guests of Government visits.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196147","196147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015376","2018-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made a recent assessment of the ability of the United States to continue to be an honest broker in Israeli-Palestinian peace talks; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196083","196083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015377","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the Green Paper on adult social care.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196217","196217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015378","2018-11-29","Home Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passports sent out by his Department were reported as lost in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018 to date.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196084","196084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015379","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the regulations on political lobbying of members of the Government.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196085","196085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015380","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many adults with severe disabilities are in receipt of local authority-run social care services in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196086","196086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015381","2018-12-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many stroke beds there are (a) at University Hospitals Coventry and Warwickshire NHS Trust and (b) throughout (i) the West Midlands and (ii) England.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196087","196087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015382","2018-12-03","Department for International Trade","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on the viability of a UK-US trade agreement after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196088","196088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015383","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2018 to Question 194763 on Department of Education: Apprentices, how many of the 193 apprentices employed by his Department work in each of its executive agencies.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196218","196218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015384","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political and security situation in Zimbabwe.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196089","196089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015385","2018-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the total cost to the public purse is of processing and issuing a permit for the importation of a hunting trophy for species listed in Appendix I, II and III of the Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196219","196219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015386","2018-11-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the June 2018 Gambling Commission advice on society lotteries which noted that such lotteries have not affected National Lottery sales and both represent complementary streams of funding for the charity sector.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196220","196220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015387","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what funds his Department allocated to pay the private school fees of the children of staff in his Department at (a) schools in the UK and (b) schools overseas in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196148","196148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015388","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff in his Department who had the private school fees of their children paid by his Department were (a) based in posts in the United Kingdom and (b) based in posts overseas in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196149","196149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015389","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many children had their private school fees paid by his Department at (a) schools in the UK and (b) schools overseas in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196150","196150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015390","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much expenditure his Department allocated to pay the private school fees of the children of  Departmental staff at each of (a) Cheltenham Ladies College, (b) Roedean School, (c) Wycombe Abbey, (d) Benenden School, (e) Malvern St James, (f) Wellington College, (g) St Francis College, (h) Sevenoaks School, (i) Malvern College and (j) Hurtwood House in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196151","196151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015391","2018-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what funds his Department allocated to pay the private school fees of the children of staff in his Department at (a) Tonbridge school, (b) Harrow school, (c) Winchester college, (d) Charterhouse school, (e) Eton college, (f) Westminster school,  (g) Rugby school, (h) St Lawrence college, (i) Brentwood school and (j) Millfield school in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196152","196152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015392","2018-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the conviction rates were for (a) sexual offences and (b) rape in the 12 months to June (i) 2018 and (ii) in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196111","196111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015393","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many specialist multiple sclerosis nurses are employed in (a) NHS England and (b) Trafford.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196221","196221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015394","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people living with multiple sclerosis in Trafford who are eligible for a disease-modifying treatment are accessing one.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196222","196222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015395","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people in Trafford have been diagnosed with a progressive form of multiple sclerosis.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196223","196223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015396","2018-12-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will include the Association of Residential Managing Agents in his departmental working group on  the future of leasehold reform.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196224","196224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015397","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the number of people with primary progressive multiple sclerosis in (a) England and (b) Trafford who will be eligible for treatment using ocrelizumab in the event that that drug becomes available on the NHS.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196225","196225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015398","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time was for a first appointment following referral to the Gender Identity Development Service (a) in Leeds and (b) at the Tavistock Centre for children in each age group in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196226","196226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015399","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of transition arrangements for young people moving from the gender identity development service to adult services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196227","196227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015400","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance is provided to clinical commissioning groups on preserving the fertility of children and young people who undergo treatment for gender dysphoria.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196228","196228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015401","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions and meetings the Government has had with the (a) tobacco and (b) vaping industries on e-cigarette regulation and policy in the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196229","196229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015402","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the Government plans to publish its Command Paper in response to the Science and Technology Committee's Seventh Report of Session 2017-19 on E-cigarettes, HC 505; and whether it has taken steps to implement the report’s recommendations.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196230","196230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015403","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what training is provided for social work (a) students and (b) practitioners on gender dysphoria in children and young people.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196231","196231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015404","2018-12-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for International Development of Wednesday 21 November 2018, Official Report, column HL233, when the updated impact assessments on the effects of exiting the EU on regions and nations will be published.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196153","196153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015405","2018-11-29","Department for Education","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether departmental resources have been used to promote the Agreement on the withdrawal of the United Kingdom of the Great Britain and Northern Ireland from the European Union and the European Union and the European Atomic Energy Community.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196232","196232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015406","2018-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with international (a) counterparts and (b) partners on tackling the reduction in the global wildlife population.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196112","196112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015407","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of merits of providing physical documentation to holders of settled status as proof of their legal status.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196154","196154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015408","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what alternative proof of legal status the Government plans to be available to holders of settled status in the event that they lose access to their digital proof.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196155","196155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015409","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with which (a) other public and (b) private sector organisations in (i) the UK and (ii) overseas his Department plans to be able to share the biometric data provided by applicants to the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196233","196233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015410","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that biometric data provided by applicants to the EU Settlement Scheme will be securely protected.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196234","196234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015411","2018-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the levels of forced repatriation of Christian asylum seekers to Pakistan.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196113","196113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015412","2018-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken taken to promote (a) religious freedoms and (b) the ability to evangelise in China.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196114","196114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015413","2018-11-29","Department for Education","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the amount of his Department's time that has been used to promote the Government's agreement on the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196235","196235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015414","2018-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Turkish counterpart on the effect on non-Muslims of the rapid incorporation of Islam into that country's education system.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196115","196115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015415","2018-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of the Philippines on that country's promotion of respect for human rights and religious freedoms.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196116","196116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015416","2018-12-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has had discussions with the Office for Nuclear Regulation on (a) restarting Hunterston Nuclear Reactor and (b) reported cracks in that Reactor's graphite core; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196236","196236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015417","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has had discussions with the Treasury on the National Audit Office report on improving the Government's planning and spending framework; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196237","196237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015418","2018-11-29","Department for Education","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations he has received from trade union representatives on school funding.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196238","196238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015419","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his department has had with NHS England on improving the support available to unpaid carers in the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196239","196239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015420","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the NHS Long Term Plan is planned to include to ensure unpaid carers are (a) identified and (b) offered support.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196240","196240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015421","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the NHS Long Term Plan on the health outcomes for unpaid carers.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196241","196241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015422","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to extend the provision of support for NHS staff who have unpaid caring responsibilities outside work; and whether that provision will be a core part of the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196242","196242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015423","2018-11-29","Department for Education","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department last conducted a review of the cost of universal infant free school meals and; and what the timeframe is for his Department to conduct another review of that policy.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196243","196243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015424","2018-11-29","Department for Education","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much and what proportion of the £2.30 awarded for free school meals is spent on (a) food and (b) labour.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196244","196244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015425","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Crown Commercial Service has plans to issue guidance to public sector bodies on the financial risks associated with contracting with Interserve.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196092","196092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015426","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what date the strategic supplier Interserve was classified with a red risk rating.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196093","196093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015427","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if his Department will take steps to accelerate the creation of a living will to be delivered by Interserve.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196094","196094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015428","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the conclusion in the letter of the Chairs of the Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy and Work and Pensions Committees of 4 September 2018, on Carillion, that the current system of monitoring suppliers was not able to identify or prevent the precarious state of Carillion and its decline and collapse, what extraordinary steps his Department is taking to monitor the financial health of Interserve.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196095","196095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015429","2018-12-03","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department has taken since January 2018 to improve the efficiency and effectiveness of Crown Representatives.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196096","196096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015430","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Department for Housing, Communities and Local Government on restricting the number of fast food restaurants near schools.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196245","196245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015431","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Department of Education to improve healthy eating education.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196246","196246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015432","2018-12-03","Department for Transport","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 19 April 2018 to Question 136001 and 11 September to Question 169103, when he plans to announce the successful bidder for the new South Eastern rail franchise.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196117","196117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015433","2018-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate he has made of the proportion of offenders who are in paid work at the time of being sent to prison.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196156","196156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015434","2018-11-29","Home Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on the ethnicity of each offender and their victim in murder cases in each of the last three years in cases where the ethnicity of the perpetrator and the victim was recorded as being different.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196157","196157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015435","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Crown Commercial Service is taking to ensure that Interserve managers pass on relevant and accurate information to Crown Representatives.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196097","196097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015436","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment the Government has made of the economic effect on the UK food industry of proposed Public Health England measures to reduce the size of food products by 20 per cent.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196158","196158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015437","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on consumer health of reducing the size of food products by 20 per cent.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196159","196159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015438","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government plans to take in relation to food products that do not meet forthcoming Public Health England guidelines on calories.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196160","196160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015439","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prosperity Fund: Annual Report 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Treasury-delivered projects in tackling (a) persistent poverty, (b) high levels of inequality and (c) potential instability.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196247","196247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015440","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prosperity Fund: Annual Report 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of projects delivered by the Department for International Development in tackling (a) persistent poverty, (b) high levels of inequality and (c) potential instability.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196248","196248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015441","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prosperity Fund: Annual Report 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of projects delivered by the Foreign and Commonwealth Office in tackling (a) persistent poverty, (b) high levels of inequality and (c) potential instability.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196249","196249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015442","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prosperity Fund: Annual Report 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of projects delivered by the Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport in tackling (a) persistent poverty, (b) high levels of inequality and (c) potential instability.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196250","196250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015443","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prosperity Fund: Annual Report 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the fund's effectiveness in supporting inclusive growth in middle income countries.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196251","196251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015444","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect on the environment of the (a) official development assistance and (b) non-official development assistance (i) components and (ii) programmes of the Prosperity Fund .","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196252","196252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015445","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prosperity Fund: Annual Report 2017-18, what measures the Government uses to assess the contribution of that fund to the delivery of Sustainable Development Goals (a) 5, (b) 7, (c) 8 and (d) 9 in each country to which the fund is allocated.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196253","196253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015446","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prosperity Fund: Annual Report 2017-18, what steps he is taking to help Departments achieve a rating of good from the International Aid Transparency Initiative.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196254","196254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015447","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will establish a standard evaluation by which Departments publish their progress on the delivery of programmes funded by the Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196255","196255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015448","2018-11-29","Department for Education","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to establish a regulatory body for foster agencies.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196161","196161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015449","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to encourage people to discuss mental health issues.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196162","196162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015450","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives of surgical mesh implant groups on their experiences of such implants.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196163","196163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015451","2018-11-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help prevent young people from developing type 2 diabetes as a result of a bad diet.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196164","196164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015452","2018-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on the safety of British Christians resident in China to practice their religion in that country.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196165","196165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015453","2018-11-29","Department for International Trade","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on UK trade with the US after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196166","196166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015454","2018-11-29","Department for International Trade","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in other countries on the benefits of manufacturers operating in those countries basing their manufacturing operations in the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196167","196167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015455","2018-11-29","Department for Education","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils are listed in the school census as (a) receiving SEN support and (b) being subject to a statement of SEN or Education Health and Care Plan in each year from 2015 to 2018.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196256","196256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015456","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the (a) number of and (b) demand for independent sector welfare secure children's home placements (i) in England and (ii) in (A) unitary and (B) upper-tier local authority areas.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196257","196257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015457","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of children referred to secure welfare children's home placements outside their local authority area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196258","196258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015458","2018-11-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has displayed county flags to commemorate annual county days at its Marsham Street building in 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196168","196168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015459","2018-12-03","Department for Education","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of children's home placements available for children with a combination of autistic spectrum disorder, attention deficit hyperactivity disorder and emotional and behavioural difficulties.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196259","196259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015460","2018-11-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress his Department has made on developing its policy on imposing a ban on hunting trophy imports.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196260","196260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015461","2018-11-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether (a) Downing Street and (b) other government buildings in Whitehall display county flags to commemorate annual county days.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196169","196169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015462","2018-11-29","Department for Transport","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of Govia Thamelink Railway's preparations for the winter timetable update starting on 10 December 2018.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196261","196261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015463","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people with multiple sclerosis in Newcastle upon Tyne North constituency who received a reduced rate of mobility support as a result of the transition from disability living allowance to personal independence payments (PIP) (i) appealed that decision and (ii) were successful in their appeal in each year since PIP was introduced.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196262","196262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015464","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people employed by his Department work in the UK Financial Intelligence Unit.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196263","196263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015465","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total annual budget for the UK Financial Intelligence Unit is for the financial year 2018-19.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196264","196264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015466","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the 2018-19 budget is for the National Crime Agency's international corruption unit.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196265","196265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015467","2018-12-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2018 to Question 191454 on employment: Electronic Tagging, what the Government's policy is on employers microchipping their employees.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196266","196266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015468","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral evidence of the Executive Director, Prison Estate Transformation Programme, HM Prison and Probation Service of 13 November 2018 to the Justice Select Committee inquiry on Prison Population 2022: planning for the future, Question 495, HC 483, whether it is his Department's policy that running in-house bids for the operation of new-build prisons is divisive.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196267","196267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015469","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral evidence of Simon Boddis, Executive Director, Prison Estate Transformation Programme, HM Prison and Probation Service to the Justice Committee on Prison Population 2022, planning for the future on 13 November 2018, Question 495, HC 340, what assessment his Department has made of the accuracy of the statement that running in-house bids for the operation of new-build prisons is a waste of money.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196268","196268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015470","2018-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral evidence of Simon Boddis, Executive Director, Prison Estate Transformation Programme, HM Prison and Probation Service to the Justice Committee on Prison Population 2022, planning for the future on 13 November 2018, Question 495, HC 340, what estimate he has made of the cost of running in-house bids for the operation of new-build prisons.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196269","196269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015471","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when Interserve is planned to provide a living will for his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196098","196098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015472","2018-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has received representations from the the Crown Commercial Service on the financial health of the strategic supplier Interserve.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196099","196099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015473","2018-11-29","Home Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department is making contingency plans in the event that Interserve is unable to continue to provide traffic management services on behalf of the Metropolitan Police.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196100","196100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015474","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will direct the Crown Commercial Service to undertake a review of the ability of Interserve to deliver services guaranteed under its public sector contracts.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196101","196101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015475","2018-12-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent comparative assessment his Department has made of the level of fuel poverty in each region.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196270","196270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015476","2018-12-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the level of fuel poverty in (a) the North West and (b) Blackburn constituency.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196271","196271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015477","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the value is of all public sector (a) contracts and (b) joint contracts held by Interserve.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196118","196118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015478","2018-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make it her policy to undertake a review of the application process for personal independence payments.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196272","196272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015479","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has provided training or other instruction to the Crown Representatives intended to ensure learning from the collapse of Carillion.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196119","196119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015480","2018-11-29","Cabinet Office","2018-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings the Crown Commercial Service has had with representatives of Interserve to discuss significant material concerns relating to that company.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196120","196120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1015481","2018-11-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of people who have been evicted for not paying their rent due to a delay before their first payment of universal credit.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196273","196273"
