"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682335","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the new robotic silicone sleeve that can help damaged hearts pump will be made available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62547","62547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682336","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission an all-encompassing analysis of the overall health burden of infectious diseases in the UK.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62566","62566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682337","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to ensure that there will be no restriction on IVF availability.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62548","62548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682338","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reach the WHO target of at least 95 per cent of children at age two are vaccinated for MMR.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62567","62567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682339","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the Better Care Fund programme on the most vulnerable people in society.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62500","62500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682340","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to ensure all GPs are trained in suicide awareness.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62513","62513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682341","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which persons not employed by his Department and its agencies hold security passes entitling them to enter his Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62536","62536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682342","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many local authorities in England provide or commission an oral health improvement programme; and what estimate he has made of the funds committed to such programmes by local authorities in England in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62516","62516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682343","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NICE to conclude deliberations on (a) Crizotinib, (b) Pemetrexed, (c) Cetuximab, (d) Dasatinib, (e) Sornfenib, (f) Ibrutinib, (g) Cabazitaxel, (h) Brentuximab, (i) Radium 223 and (j) Trastuzumab Emtansine; what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of providing each of these drugs for a 12 month trial period; and what estimate he has made of the period; what estimate he has made of the number of people likely to be prescribed each of these drugs on the NHS in the 12 months following any approval by NICE.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62519","62519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682344","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 September 2016 to Question 45640, how many participants have received the HPV vaccine as part of the pilot to provide that vaccine to gay and bisexual men.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62520","62520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682345","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) children and (b) adults spent time in a police station as a place of safety due to a mental health condition in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62625","62625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682346","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to educate parents on child obesity.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62632","62632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682347","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adult inpatient psychiatric beds there were in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62621","62621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682348","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2017 to Question 61891, how much his Department has spent on the Healthy Start Scheme in each region in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62622","62622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682349","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2017 to Question 59889, on NHS: complaints, for what reasons data for the year 2015-16 was not included in the Answer.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62623","62623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682350","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department will publish the new Tobacco Control Plan.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62600","62600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682351","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2017 to Question 59052, what the reason was for the increase in funding on Official Development Assistance by his Department from £11 million in 2014 to £32 million in 2015; what such figures are for 2016; and what the (a) cost and (b) purpose is of each project in receipt of such funding in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62581","62581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682352","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to prevent suicides.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62582","62582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682353","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Capita improves its performance relating to the processing of dental performer list applications.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62580","62580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682354","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department is giving to middle-aged people diagnosed with eating disorders.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62555","62555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682355","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NICE to conclude their deliberations on the use of Bosutinib; what the cost is of providing Bosutinib for a 12 month period; and what estimate he has made of the number of people who could benefit from Bosutinib being approved by NICE.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62571","62571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682356","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking with NHS England to ensure that gay and bisexual men sign up to the HPV vaccination pilot.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62579","62579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682357","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what transcranial direct current stimulation will be made available on the NHS to treat bulimia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62554","62554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682358","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the rates of (a) gonorrhoea and (b) other sexual transmitted infections among deprived urban communities.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62568","62568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682359","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the rate of TB in the 10 per cent of the population living in the most deprived areas.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62569","62569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682360","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of people diagnosed with diabetes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62552","62552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682361","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NICE to conclude their deliberations on the use of Everolimus; what the cost is of providing Everolimus for a 12 month period; and what estimate he has made of the number of people who could benefit from Everolimus being approved by NICE.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62570","62570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682362","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many contracts (a) his Department and (b) its non-departmental public bodies and agencies have awarded to Louise Guss Consulting Ltd since 2013.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62460","62460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682363","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what systems his Department plans to put in place to support the recruitment of GPs from abroad.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62457","62457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682364","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress the Government has made on recruiting more GPs in (a) Devon and (b) Plymouth.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62458","62458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682365","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the comparative effects on health of (a) sugar and (b) artificial sweeteners in drinks.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62479","62479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682366","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) complaints, (b) Freedom on Information requests and (c) Parliamentary Questions concerning the group Action on Smoking and Health his Department has dealt with in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62473","62473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682367","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the capacity of the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency as a result of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62400","62400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682368","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the process is for NHS England to determine its funding annually for the prioritisation of specialised services.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62401","62401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682369","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will award nurses a pay rise of greater than one per cent of salary in the next available pay round.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62427","62427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682370","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) mothers and (b) fathers have been treated for peri-natal mental health conditions in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62440","62440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682371","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the criteria are for deciding which local bids will receive part of the additional £200 million funding announced by NHS England in December 2016 to improve local cancer services in England.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62432","62432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682372","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many babies have been stillborn in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62438","62438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682373","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish data on regional variations in stillbirths; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62439","62439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682374","2017-02-02","Home Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents involving off-road motorcycles have been recorded by police forces in (a) Liverpool, (b) Merseyside and (c) England.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62403","62403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682375","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what role her Department and its agencies play in the oversight of the operation by the Security Industry Authority of its complaints procedures; what regulatory role she plays in connection with that authority; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62413","62413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682376","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what duty the Security Industry Authority has to provide complainants with the details of any investigations, outcomes or actions relating to the complaints they have made.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62407","62407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682377","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Security Industry Authority is required to disclose details of actions taken as a result of an investigation into alleged criminality by licence holders.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62408","62408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682378","2017-02-02","Home Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to (a) ensure that the initial discussions on asylum applications are correct and (b) reduce the number of asylum decisions overturned at appeal.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62574","62574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682379","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the training module developed for asylum caseworkers has been fully implemented.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62611","62611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682380","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which persons not employed by her Department and its agencies hold security passes entitling them to enter her Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62601","62601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682381","2017-02-02","Home Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers in (a) the UK and (b) Scotland were housed in initial accommodation for longer than the 17 day target period, in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62575","62575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682382","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Home Office torture evidence assessments were judicially appealed by asylum seekers in 2016; and how many such appeals overturned a Home Office assessment on whether an asylum seeker had experienced torture.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62612","62612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682383","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the undertaking given by the then Attorney-General on 8 February 1977, that the five techniques of questioning used in Northern Ireland in 1971, have not in any circumstances been reintroduced since then as an aid to interrogation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62619","62619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682384","2017-02-02","Cabinet Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2017 to Question 60953, if he will place in the Library summary data on the incidence and prevalence of (a) cyber-enabled crime, (b) plastic payment card fraud and (c) other similar technology crimes in each year between 1999 and 2015.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62514","62514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682385","2017-02-02","Home Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for how many (a) Case Assurance and Audit Unit and (b) legacy cases her Department has records of people who reside in Cambridge.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62499","62499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682386","2017-02-02","House of Commons Commission","2017-01-31","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, which persons not employed by the House of Commons Commission hold security passes entitling them to enter the House of Commons Commission's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62537","62537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682387","2017-02-02","Department for International Development","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2017 to Question 59290, for what reasons other Departments have Official Development Assistance (ODA) budgets; and if she will review the effectiveness of the ODA budgets of other Departments to ensure value for money for the public purse.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62592","62592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682388","2017-02-02","Department for International Development","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2017 to Question 59290, what the value of other Departments' Official Development Assistance budgets was for each of the last six years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62593","62593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682389","2017-02-02","Department for International Development","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which persons not employed by her Department hold security passes entitling them to enter her Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62538","62538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682390","2017-02-02","Department for International Trade","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the role the European Convention of Human Rights in future trade deals the UK makes with other countries.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62404","62404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682391","2017-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which persons not employed by her Department and its agencies hold security passes entitling them to enter her Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62540","62540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682392","2017-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will place in the Library a list of public consultations, White Papers and other documents her Department plans to publish to assist the UK in making effective the Government's plans for the UK to leave the EU within the two year timetable from the triggering of Article 50 of the Lisbon Treaty.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62507","62507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682393","2017-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of suicides which took place in prisons were by people who were not on the Assessment, Care in Custody and Teamwork programme in each month of 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62624","62624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682394","2017-02-02","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what information his Department holds on whether the Republic of Ireland has introduced equal status legislation since 10 April 1998 as provided by paragraph 9 of the chapter on rights, safeguarding and equality of opportunity in the Belfast Agreement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62551","62551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682395","2017-02-02","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will place in the Library a list of public consultations, White Paper and other documents his Department plans to publish to assist the UK in making effective the Government's plans for the UK to leave the EU within the two year timetable from the triggering of Article 50 of the Lisbon Treaty.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62509","62509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682396","2017-02-02","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which persons not employed by his Department hold security passes entitling them to enter his Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62541","62541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682397","2017-02-03","Prime Minister","2017-01-31","To ask the Prime Minister, whether her Government had advance knowledge of the intention of the US Administration to issue an executive order to restrict immigration on 27 January 2017.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62414","62414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682398","2017-02-03","Prime Minister","2017-01-31","To ask the Prime Minister, whether, during her recent visit to the US, (a) the issue of the US Administration's intention to issue an executive order to restrict immigration and (b) any potential impact of that order on British citizens were discussed.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62415","62415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682399","2017-02-03","Prime Minister","2017-01-31","To ask the Prime Minister, who was present at the meeting with Myron Ebell at Number 10 Downing Street on 31 January 2017; what was discussed at that meeting; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62486","62486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682400","2017-02-02","Prime Minister","2017-01-31","To ask the Prime Minister, which persons not employed by 10 Downing Street hold security passes entitling them to enter 10 Downing Street premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62542","62542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682401","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 25 January 2017, column 295, what extra money the Government has put into reducing the changes in women's pensions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62618","62618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682402","2017-02-02","Scotland Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, which persons not employed by his Department hold security passes entitling them to enter his Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62543","62543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682403","2017-02-02","Scotland Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will place in the Library a list of public consultations, White Paper and other documents his Department plans to publish to assist the UK in making effective the Government's plans for the UK to leave the EU within the two year timetable from the triggering of Article 50 of the Lisbon Treaty.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62505","62505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682404","2017-02-02","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place in the Library a list of public consultations, White Paper and other documents his Department plans to publish to assist the UK in making effective the Government's plans for the UK to leave the EU within the two year timetable from the triggering of Article 50 of the Lisbon Treaty.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62506","62506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682405","2017-02-02","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the upcoming aviation strategy will outline how the UK will limit aviation emissions to at least below 2005 levels by 2050.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62503","62503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682406","2017-02-02","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his speech to Airlines UK on 25 January 2017, on what grounds he asserts that the doubling of the world's aircraft fleet over the next 20 years and the introduction of cleaner and more efficient aircraft will deliver a fall in global carbon emissions.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62511","62511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682407","2017-02-02","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which persons not employed by his Department hold security passes entitling them to enter his Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62544","62544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682408","2017-02-02","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's policy is on the provision of roadside toilets and other facilities for HGV drivers.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62578","62578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682409","2017-02-02","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether a publication date has been set for his Department's review of airspace modernisation and noise policies in the UK.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62577","62577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682410","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department is making through the European Aviation Safety Agency to update common drone regulations; and in what ways he intends his Department's consultation on the safe use of drones in the UK to support that process.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62613","62613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682411","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what remedies are available to him, in addition to removing the franchise from Govia Thameslink Railway, if that company is in default of its franchise agreement.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62409","62409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682412","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Govia Thameslink Railway will be in default of its franchise agreement if its applications for force majeure are not agreed by his Department.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62410","62410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682413","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which vehicles operated on the Thameslink, Southern and Great Northern Franchise are (a) compliant and (b) not compliant with the Rail Vehicle Accessibility (Non-Interoperable Rail System) Regulations 2010.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62411","62411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682414","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what exemptions have been given for vehicles operated on the Thameslink, Southern and Great Northern Franchise since that franchise began; and when those exemptions were granted.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62412","62412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682415","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the Aviation Strategy to be published.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62418","62418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682416","2017-02-02","HM Treasury","2017-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to vehicle excise duty from April 2017 on the rate of early scrappage of private cars.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62426","62426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682417","2017-02-02","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many agency staff his Department has employed in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62492","62492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682418","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of traffic incidents or accidents caused by lorries relying on satellite navigation devices designated for cars in the last 12 months; and if he will look at ways of discouraging HGV drivers from using such devices.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62526","62526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682419","2017-02-02","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with Airbus Helicopters on (a) Airbus' internal investigations into the accident at Turøy in April 2016 and (b) progress made in identifying with the Accident Investigation Board for Norway the causes of that accident.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62445","62445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682420","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which internationally registered vessels were detained by the Maritime and Coastguard Agency for infringement of the provisions of Annex VI of the International Convention for the Prevention of Pollution from Ships in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62467","62467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682421","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with (a) the Civil Aviation Authority and (b) external groups, regarding the Civil Aviation Authority's definition of a safe distance used for regulating drone activity; and how that definition compares with those used by other countries.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62466","62466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682422","2017-02-02","Wales Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will place in the Library a list of public consultations, White Paper and other documents his Department plans to publish to assist the UK in making effective the Government's plans for the UK to leave the EU within the two year timetable from the triggering of Article 50 of the Lisbon Treaty.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62508","62508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682423","2017-02-02","Home Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Home Office on the Government's proposal to continue direct grant funding to support independent domestic violence advisers and multi-agency risk assessment conference coordinators after March 2017.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62446","62446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682424","2017-02-02","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will amend the Equality Act 2010, or bring forward new legislation, to protect volunteers from encountering discrimination in the workplace.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62447","62447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682425","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when an Equality Impact Assessment will be published on the proposal to close Goldthorpe jobcentre.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62455","62455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682426","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will increase resources for the Independent Care Examiner to enable it to deal with Child Support Agency appeal cases in a timely manner.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62433","62433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682427","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment has been made of the effect on the local economy of proposed relocation of jobs from Goldthorpe jobcentre.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62451","62451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682428","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether compulsory redundancies will result from the closure of Goldthorpe jobcentre.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62450","62450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682429","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the criteria used were for the selection of Goldthorpe jobcentre for proposed closure.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62453","62453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682430","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what powers of enforcement are available to the Child Maintenance Service if parents are on a direct-pay scheme and the paying parent refuses to meet their obligation to pay.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62448","62448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682431","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is the Government's policy to encourage parents to use the Child Maintenance Services collect and pay service.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62449","62449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682432","2017-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment the Government has made of the (a) effectiveness of those relationship support services provided by Relate which are funded from the public purse and (b) effect of those services on family stability.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62490","62490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682433","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of the benefit freeze on trends in the level of child poverty.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62502","62502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682434","2017-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations he has received on Government funding of services by Relate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62491","62491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682435","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants are served by Goldthorpe jobcentre; and how many of those claimants are (a) disabled and (b) women.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62454","62454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682436","2017-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish the conclusions of the review carried out under section 141 of the Welfare Reform Act 2012 on the effect of child maintenance charges; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62417","62417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682437","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appeals against each type of benefit sanction have been (a) upheld and (b) overturned in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62510","62510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682438","2017-02-02","HM Treasury","2017-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on child poverty of restrictions on child benefit for third and subsequent children.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62517","62517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682439","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit sanctions have been applied to (a) employment and support allowance claimants, (b) jobseeker's allowance claimants, (c) universal credit claimants with children in each parliamentary constituency in the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62518","62518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682440","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many completed repeat assessments there have been of people with (a) Parkinson's disease, (b) multiple sclerosis, (c) motor neurone disease, (d) rheumatoid arthritis and (e) cystic fibrosis by year of repeat assessment, since the introduction of personal independence payments in 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62586","62586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682441","2017-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with other potential users of his Department's building on Llanelli on sharing the use of that space.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62607","62607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682442","2017-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost per square metre is of each office, excluding jobcentres, currently used by his Department.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62609","62609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682443","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the expected costs are of the proposal to relocate staff and resources from Goldthorpe Jobcentre.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62576","62576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682444","2017-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 January 2017 to Question 58293, what steps his Department is taking to end food poverty and reliance on food banks.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62617","62617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682445","2017-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of moving additional work from elsewhere to his Department's building in Llanelli to make that site more cost effective.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62608","62608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682446","2017-02-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding his Department has provided to start-up businesses in (a) St Helens, (b) Merseyside, (c) the North West and (d) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62616","62616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682447","2017-02-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect on the (a) Joint European Torus project and (b) Culham Centre for Fusion Energy of the UK's decision to withdraw from Euratom; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62627","62627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682448","2017-02-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the UK ceasing to be a member of Euratom on the Joint European Torus project's (a) funding, (b) staffing, (c) operational experiments and (d) collaboration with other EU scientist and member states.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62628","62628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682449","2017-02-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the recommendations in the Hendry Review on the proposed Swansea tidal lagoon and other similar projects; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62629","62629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682450","2017-02-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to meet with farming unions and industry groups who formally declined to submit evidence to the Groceries Code Adjudicator Review.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62614","62614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682451","2017-02-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which persons not employed by his Department and its agencies hold security passes entitling them to enter his Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62603","62603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682452","2017-02-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the commercial viability of the methods proposed by recent research and development on reducing the costs of carbon capture technology by up to two-thirds in the (a) UK and (b) rest of the world.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62425","62425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682453","2017-02-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential use of deep offshore saline aquifers in developing a viable business model for carbon capture and storage technology.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62416","62416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682454","2017-02-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to invite councils to volunteer to be part of the Radioactive Waste Management search for a geological disposal facility host community.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62478","62478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682455","2017-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the merits of encouraging the development of tidal lagoons to provide energy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62525","62525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682456","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish and promote a stronger set of guidelines to businesses and banks to ensure they respect international law and human rights in their dealings with Israeli businesses operating in occupied territory.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62461","62461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682457","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will support measures by the UN Human Rights Council to draw up a database of all UK firms involved in trade or financial dealings with illegal settlements in coordination with the EU and UN.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62462","62462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682458","2017-02-03","Department for International Trade","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on potential increases in the amount of Scotch whisky exported.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62487","62487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682459","2017-02-02","Department for International Trade","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to strengthen the mining trade between the UK and South Africa.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62630","62630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682460","2017-02-02","Department for International Trade","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what information he holds on receipts and revenue flows accruing to the regimes in Libya from oil exports in the most recent period for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62594","62594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682461","2017-02-02","Department for International Trade","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which persons not employed by his Department hold security passes entitling them to enter his Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62539","62539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682462","2017-02-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which persons not employed by his Department hold security passes entitling them to enter his Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62535","62535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682465","2017-02-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, at what hourly rate cleaners are paid by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62496","62496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682466","2017-02-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what systems are in place to monitor overtime worked by his Department's employees.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62497","62497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682467","2017-02-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many hours of recorded overtime have been worked by staff in his Department since its creation.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62495","62495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682468","2017-02-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2017 to Question 60441, approximately how many more staff he needs to recruit to his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62434","62434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685135","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support teachers in improving educational outcomes.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908608","908608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685136","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will provide support to people who incur debt owed to the Skills Funding Agency as a result of training providers ceasing to operate.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908603","908603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685137","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to improve the quality of maths teaching in primary schools.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908610","908610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685138","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to increase provision for adult skills and lifelong learning.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908600","908600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681146","2017-02-02","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when he plans to publish the total costs to the public purse of R (on the application of Miller and Dos Santos) v Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union in the (a) High Court and (b) Supreme Court.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62196","62196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681147","2017-02-01","Cabinet Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the hourly pay-rate is for his Department's cleaning staff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62261","62261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681148","2017-02-01","Cabinet Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether any cyber attacks have been carried out on the UK which had the potential to affect its democratic processes.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62244","62244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681149","2017-02-01","Cabinet Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking beyond those outlined in the Cyber Security Strategy of November 2016 to defend the UK from cyber attacks from abroad.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62245","62245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681150","2017-02-01","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will place in the Library a list of public consultations, White Papers and other documents his Department plans to publish to assist the UK in making effective the Government's plans for the UK to leave the EU within the two year timetable from the triggering of Article 50.","Biography information for Ms Gisela Stuart","Ms Gisela Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62280","62280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681151","2017-02-01","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the hourly pay-rate is for his Department's cleaning staff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62273","62273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681152","2017-02-01","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have received income tax exemption for junior individual savings account savings in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62208","62208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681153","2017-02-02","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax exemption for interest on National Savings Certificates including index-linked certificates in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62176","62176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681154","2017-02-02","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax exemption on the first £30,000 of payments on termination of employment in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62177","62177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681155","2017-02-02","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax relief for renting a room in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62178","62178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681156","2017-02-02","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax relief for Seafarers Earnings Deduction in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62179","62179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681157","2017-02-02","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax relief for employer-supported childcare including workplace nurseries in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62180","62180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681158","2017-02-01","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax relief for farming etc. averaging of profits in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62203","62203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681159","2017-02-01","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax relief for post-trading expenditure in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62204","62204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681160","2017-02-01","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax exemption for life insurance premiums for contracts made prior to 14 March 1984 in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62205","62205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681161","2017-02-01","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received blind person's allowance for income tax in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62202","62202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681162","2017-02-01","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax exemption for life annuities interest in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62206","62206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681163","2017-02-01","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax exemption for Child Trust Fund account savings in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62207","62207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681164","2017-02-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the need to record people as having been made intentionally homeless on their ability to find new homes.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62210","62210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681165","2017-02-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the hourly pay-rate is for his Department's cleaning staff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62262","62262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681166","2017-02-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library a list of public consultations, White Papers and other documents his Department plans to publish to assist the UK in making effective the Government's plans for the UK to leave the EU within the two year timetable from the triggering of Article 50.","Biography information for Ms Gisela Stuart","Ms Gisela Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62274","62274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681167","2017-02-01","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the hourly pay-rate is for her Department's cleaning staff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62263","62263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681168","2017-02-01","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will place in the Library a list of public consultations, White Papers and other documents her Department plans to publish to assist the UK in making effective the Government's plans for the UK to leave the EU within the two year timetable from the triggering of Article 50.","Biography information for Ms Gisela Stuart","Ms Gisela Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62275","62275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681169","2017-02-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding her Department has provided for the promotion and development of darts in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62189","62189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681170","2017-02-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, (a) how many times and (b) on which dates (i) Ministers and (ii) officials of her Department have met representatives of MG Alba in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62195","62195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681171","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many allegations of humanitarian law violations by the Saudi-led coalition in Yemen his Department is tracking; and if he will place in the Library the reports relating to each such allegation.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62165","62165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681172","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many offensive cyber attacks the Government has authorised since 2010.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62181","62181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681173","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Ministers in his Department are responsible for authorising offensive cyber attacks on other states or terrorist groups.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62182","62182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681174","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, (a) how many people and (b) in what roles work in the Royal Electrical and Mechanical Engineers at Hightown Barracks, Wrexham.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62174","62174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681175","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the establishment is of HQ Field Army by (a) rank and (b) responsibility.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62236","62236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681176","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a list of public consultations, White Papers and other documents his Department plans to publish to assist the UK in making effective the Government's plans for the UK to leave the EU within the two year timetable from the triggering of Article 50.","Biography information for Ms Gisela Stuart","Ms Gisela Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62276","62276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681177","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the hourly pay-rate is for his Department's cleaning staff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62264","62264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681178","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he or officials of his Department have had with developers on the future of the Hightown Barracks site in Wrexham.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62281","62281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681179","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of merging 101 Battalion REME with 105 Battalion REME in its relations with the communities in (a) Wrexham and (b) North Wales.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62282","62282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681180","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of in-service complaints were not dealt with in the recommended time for disposal within each of the three armed forces in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62239","62239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681181","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2017 to Question 60298, what assessment has been made of the utility of introducing a human rights specific programme module to the training provided to the Burmese Army.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62252","62252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681182","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 5 July 2016 to Question 41410, when his Department last carried out an assessment of (a) whether the Saudi-led coalition in Yemen were targeting civilians and (b) that coalition's level of respect for and compliance with international humanitarian law; and if he will place in the Library copies of documentation used in such assessments.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62242","62242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681183","2017-02-01","Department for Education","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of overseas students currently studying at UK (a) schools and (b) universities.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62247","62247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681184","2017-02-01","Department for Education","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will list the number of faith schools in England by (a) religion and (b) local authority area.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62248","62248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681185","2017-02-01","Department for Education","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of faith schools that were opened in 2015; and where each of those schools are situated.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62249","62249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681186","2017-02-01","Department for Education","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the hourly pay-rate is for her Department's cleaning staff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62265","62265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681187","2017-02-02","Department for Education","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason her Department plans to return budgetary provision allocated to supporting the costs of academisation to HM Treasury.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62224","62224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681188","2017-02-02","Department for Education","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many places were available for trainee teachers who wish to specialise in citizenship education on teacher training courses in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62229","62229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681189","2017-02-02","Department for Education","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure effective teaching of citizenship education in schools in England; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62230","62230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681190","2017-02-02","Department for Education","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department provided for support for deaf awareness training in schools in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) the North West and (c) England in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62190","62190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681191","2017-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the economic value of agricultural exports to the EU in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) the North West and (c) the UK in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62187","62187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681192","2017-02-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) dogs, (b) cats and (c) ferrets were imported (i) non-commercially under the Pets Travel Scheme and (ii) commercially under the Trade in Animals and Related Products Regulations 2011 into the UK in 2016.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62238","62238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681193","2017-02-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the hourly pay-rate is for her Department's cleaning staff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62266","62266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681194","2017-02-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will place in the Library a list of public consultations, White Papers and other documents her Department plans to publish to assist the UK in making effective the Government's plans for the UK to leave the EU within the two year timetable from the triggering of Article 50.","Biography information for Ms Gisela Stuart","Ms Gisela Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62277","62277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681195","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the hourly pay-rate is for his Department's cleaning staff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62268","62268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681196","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2016 to Questions 40437 and 40433, when his Department last made representations to Saudi Arabia (a) expressing concern about the extent of the application of and (b) encouraging abolition of the death penalty in that country.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62253","62253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681197","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2016 to Question 40456, what recent representations the UK has made to Saudi Arabia to accede to the Convention on Cluster Munitions; and on what dates those representations were made.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62254","62254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681198","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Special Representative for Sudan and South Sudan, Chris Trott, raised the ongoing detention without charge of Dr Mudawi Ibrahim Adam during his meeting with the Sudanese Foreign Minister, Ibrahim Ghandour, on 24 January 2017.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62226","62226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681199","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the alleged torture of Dr Mudawi Ibrahim Adam by Sudanese authorities during his ongoing detention without charge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62227","62227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681200","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to increase the size of the UK Representation to the EU once negotiations begin on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62162","62162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681201","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how his Department assesses the work of country criminal justice advisors; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62144","62144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681202","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the capacity of NICE's appraisal processes for (a) muscle-wasting treatments and (b) treatments for other rare diseases.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62147","62147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681203","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to emotional and psychological support for people with (a) muscle-wasting conditions and (b) other rare diseases.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62148","62148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681204","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps (a) he and (b) his Department are taking to promote and implement the accident and emergency-based Cardiff model for violence prevention in England.","Biography information for Craig Williams","Craig Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62157","62157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681205","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library a list of designated centres for the treatment of hidradenitis suppurativa that is difficult to diagnose or manage.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62194","62194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681206","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funds were available to NHS England to finance the annual prioritisation process for specialised services in 2016.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62199","62199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681207","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funds NHS England will provide for the annual prioritisation process for specialised services in 2017.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62200","62200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681208","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many policies are being considered by NHS England's Commissioning department for the annual prioritisation process for specialised services.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62201","62201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681209","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mechanisms NHS England has in place to ensure that clinical commissioning groups are fulfilling their statutory responsibility to commission certain health services to meet the reasonable requirements of the persons for whom it has responsibility in (a) the prescribing of medical nutrition according to NICE Clinical Guidance 32 2006 and (b) commissioning other health services in line with section 13(2) of the Health and Social Care Act 2012.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62211","62211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681210","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the implementation of sustainability and transformation plans on social care costs for local authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62225","62225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681211","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funds were available to NHS England to finance the annual prioritisation process for specialised services in 2015.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62198","62198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681212","2017-02-02","Home Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been recorded as having left the UK by border exit checks in 2015 and 2016 since their introduction in April 2015.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62228","62228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681213","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to NHS England's service specification for specialised dermatology services, if he will place in the Library a list of designated centres for the treatment of hidradenitis suppurativa that is difficult to diagnose or manage.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62255","62255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681214","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on child tooth extraction in hospitals in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62250","62250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681215","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the hourly pay-rate is for his Department's cleaning staff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62269","62269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681216","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the hourly pay-rate is for her Department's cleaning staff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62270","62270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681217","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library a list of public consultations, White Papers and other documents her Department plans to publish to assist the UK in making effective the Government's plans for the UK to leave the EU within the two year timetable from the triggering of Article 50.","Biography information for Ms Gisela Stuart","Ms Gisela Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62278","62278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681218","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many civil servants have been seconded from her Department to the Department for Exiting the European Union.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62259","62259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681219","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what (a) financial and (b) other resources have been allocated to support the implementation of section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016 in 2016-17.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62237","62237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681220","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests have been made for the offence of coercive control in each region and constituent part of the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62234","62234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681221","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much time each police force in England has allocated to train officers on the offence of coercive control.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62233","62233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681222","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of proposals by the Anti-Slavery Commissioners to establish a central repository for modern slavery statements; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62209","62209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681223","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what public appointments she has made since her appointment.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62160","62160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681224","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she last visited the College of Policing.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62163","62163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681225","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish the report received from Kevin Hyland following his visit to hotspots in Greece and Italy in 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62156","62156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681226","2017-02-01","Department for International Development","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the US restoring the Mexico City Policy on the effectiveness of her Department's projects.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62149","62149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681227","2017-02-01","Department for International Development","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to cap the daily rate of consultants working (a) directly for and (b) for contractors working on projects funded by her Department.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62150","62150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681228","2017-02-02","Department for International Development","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of Israel's border restrictions and permit system on urgent medical care for people resident in (a) the West Bank and (b) Gaza.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62175","62175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681229","2017-02-01","Department for International Development","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much government funding is provided for climate action in developing countries.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62257","62257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681230","2017-02-01","Department for International Development","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the implications are for her policies on her Department's assistance for the training of teachers in the developing world to meet 2030 educational targets of UNESCOs Policy Paper 19 of April 2015, The challenge of teacher shortage and quality.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62246","62246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681231","2017-02-01","Department for International Development","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will place in the Library a list of public consultations, White Papers and other documents her Department plans to publish to assist the UK in making effective the Government's plans for the UK to leave the EU within the two year timetable from the triggering of Article 50.","Biography information for Ms Gisela Stuart","Ms Gisela Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62279","62279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681232","2017-02-01","Department for International Development","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the hourly pay-rate is for her Department's cleaning staff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62271","62271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681233","2017-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoner transfer agreements were negotiated in 2015 and 2016; and with which countries those agreements were made.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62164","62164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681234","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for legal aid in cases involving coercive control have been approved by the Legal Aid Authority in the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62232","62232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681235","2017-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time was for a case to be determined from the time appeal papers arrive at the First Tier Tribunal office to determination of that appeal in 2015-16.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62235","62235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681236","2017-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will commence section 281(5) of the Criminal Justice Act 2003 to allow for penalties available under section 32 of the Animal Welfare Act 2006 to come into force.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62231","62231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681237","2017-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans her Department has for the construction of custody facilities at Wrexham Magistrates' Court; what options for that construction her Department is assessing; and what the timetable is for her Department to make decisions on the (a) options and (b) construction of such facilities.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62218","62218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681238","2017-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she last observed proceedings at a First-tier Immigration Tribunal.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62151","62151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681239","2017-02-01","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the level of earnings is of the (a) highest and (b) lowest-paid employees of his Department, its agencies and arms-length bodies; and what the median level of earnings is for such employees.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62215","62215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681240","2017-02-02","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many former or serving members of the armed forces have been prosecuted for Troubles-related offences in each year since 1998.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62188","62188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681241","2017-02-01","Prime Minister","2017-01-30","To ask the Prime Minister, when she last held discussions with President Putin.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62161","62161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681242","2017-02-01","Prime Minister","2017-01-30","To ask the Prime Minister, when she last met the Secretary General of the Commonwealth.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62158","62158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681243","2017-02-01","Prime Minister","2017-01-30","To ask the Prime Minister, when she last held discussions with President Hadi of Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62159","62159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681244","2017-02-01","Prime Minister","2017-01-30","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she raised the use of torture as an interrogation technique by US intelligence services at her meeting with President Trump on 27 January 2017.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62166","62166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681245","2017-02-01","Prime Minister","2017-01-30","To ask the Prime Minister, what the total number of special advisers working at Number 10 is, by (a) gender and (b) ethnic minority background.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62292","62292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681246","2017-02-01","Public Accounts Commission","2017-01-30","To ask the Chairman of the Public Accounts Commission, what the level of earnings is of the (a) highest and (b) lowest-paid employees of the Commission; and what the median level of earnings is for such employees.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62213","62213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681247","2017-02-01","Scotland Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the level of earnings is of the (a) highest and (b) lowest-paid employees of his Department, its agencies and arms-length bodies; and what the median level of earnings is for such employees.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62214","62214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681248","2017-02-01","Scotland Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 61501, on what date he  last discussed the UK's nuclear deterrent with the (a) Prime Minister and (b) Ministry of Defence; whether missile tests formed part of these discussions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62256","62256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681249","2017-02-01","Scotland Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 61526, if he will make it his Department's policy to bring forward legislative proposals to prevent the UK Parliament from passing legislation applying to Scotland that makes provision about a devolved matter without the consent of the Scottish Parliament.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62241","62241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681250","2017-02-01","Department for Transport","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the level of earnings is of the (a) highest and (b) lowest-paid employees of his Department, its agencies and arms-length bodies; and what the median level of earnings is for such employees.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62212","62212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681251","2017-02-01","Wales Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the level of earnings is of the (a) highest and (b) lowest-paid employees of his Department, its agencies and arms-length bodies; and what the median level of earnings is for such employees.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62217","62217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681252","2017-02-01","Women and Equalities","2017-01-30","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the level of earnings is of the (a) highest and (b) lowest-paid employees of her Department, its agencies and arms-length bodies; and what the median level of earnings is for such employees.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62216","62216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681253","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether a public consultation will take place on the proposal to close St Andrew Street job centre in Edinburgh.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62221","62221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681254","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, by what criteria St Andrew Street job centre, Edinburgh, has been selected for closure.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62222","62222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681255","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants living in Edinburgh East constituency are served by St Andrew Street job centre, Edinburgh; and how many of those are (a) disabled and (b) women.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62223","62223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681256","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, where staff based at Cumnock administration centre will be relocated in the event of its closure.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62183","62183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681257","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects to publish an Equality Impact Assessment on the proposal to close Cumnock administration centre.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62191","62191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681258","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will confirm that no compulsory redundancies will result from the closure of Cumnock administration centre.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62192","62192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681259","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, by what criteria Cumnock administration centre was selected for closure.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62193","62193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681260","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many nationals of other EU member states registered for national insurance numbers in (a) Greater London and (b) the London Borough of Newham between (i) July and December 2015, (ii) January and June 2016 and (iii) July and December 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62197","62197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681261","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people using Cambuslang Jobcentre have been informed in writing of the closure of that jobcentre.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62167","62167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681262","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when an equality impact assessment will be published on the proposal to close Cambuslang Jobcentre.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62168","62168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681263","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the expected costs are of the proposal to relocate staff and resources from Cambuslang Jobcentre.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62169","62169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681264","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants are currently served by (a) Cambuslang and (b) Rutherglen Jobcentres; and how many such claimants are (i) disabled and (ii) women.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62170","62170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681265","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment has been made of the effect on the local economy of the proposal to relocate jobs from Cambuslang Jobcentre to Rutherglen Jobcentre.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62171","62171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681266","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether any compulsory redundancies will result from the closure of Cambuslang Jobcentre.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62172","62172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681267","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, by what criteria Cambuslang Jobcentre has been selected for closure.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62173","62173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681268","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the financial allocation to the Work and Health Programme by his Department will be in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62146","62146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681269","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether an equality impact assessment has been undertaken for the proposed relocation of the medical assessment centre from Russell House to Wallacetoun in Ayr.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62152","62152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681270","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the expected costs are of the proposal to relocate staff and resources from Cumnock administration centre.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62153","62153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681271","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment has been made of the effect on the local economy of the proposal to relocate jobs from Cumnock administration centre.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62154","62154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681272","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether a public consultation is planned on the proposal to close Cumnock administration centre.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62155","62155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681273","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with conditions that cause short stature have had their mobility payments withdrawn after their transition from disability living allowance to personal independence payments.","Biography information for John Nicolson","John Nicolson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62243","62243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681274","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a maximum number of face to face assessments for Parkinson's disease sufferers.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62240","62240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681275","2017-02-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the hourly pay-rate is for his Department's cleaning staff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62260","62260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681276","2017-02-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much government funding has been invested in the Capital Markets Climate Initiative since the launch of that initiative.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62251","62251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681277","2017-02-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the contribution of the Minister for Climate Change and Industry of 11 January 2017, Official Report, column 320, what assessment he has made of the nature of the market failure that the Green Investment Bank was set up to rectify; and if he will publish that assessment.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62145","62145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681278","2017-02-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what financial support his Department has made available in 2016-17 to assist employers supporting disabled people.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62184","62184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681279","2017-02-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent meetings and discussions he has had with disability organisations on his Department's industrial strategy.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62185","62185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681280","2017-02-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what provision he has made in his Department's industrial strategy for disabled people.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62186","62186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681281","2017-02-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of leaving the European Atomic Energy Community on the construction of Hinkley Point C.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62219","62219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681282","2017-02-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of leaving the European Atomic Energy Community on projects that require the co-operation of American nuclear energy companies.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62220","62220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681283","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will estimate how many of his Department's staff will be affected by recent changes to immigration rules introduced by President Trump.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62258","62258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681284","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the hourly pay-rate is for his Department's cleaning staff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62272","62272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681285","2017-02-01","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the hourly pay-rate is for his Department's cleaning staff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62267","62267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681287","2017-02-02","Attorney General","2017-01-30","To ask the Attorney General, what the procedure is for presenting a case to the Crown Prosecution Service independently of the police.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62297","62297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681288","2017-02-01","Cabinet Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings of the National Security Council (NSC) have taken place since 13 July 2016; how many of those meetings were chaired by the Prime Minister; and whether there have been any weeks when Parliament has been sitting during that period when the NSC has not met.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62384","62384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681289","2017-02-02","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on the economy of (a) Nottingham and (b) the East Midlands of the UK leaving the EU and reverting to World Trade Organisation rules.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62381","62381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681290","2017-02-02","HM Treasury","2017-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of trends in the revenue collected by HM Revenue and Customs High Net Worth Unit in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62293","62293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681291","2017-02-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to review the current level of business rates for licensed premises.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62283","62283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681292","2017-02-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on different sectors of business of different business rates being in effect in different parts of the UK.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62287","62287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681293","2017-02-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress has been made on his proposals to introduce a British Values Oath.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62387","62387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681294","2017-02-01","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has any plans to introduce grants to support low-income families to access broadband.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62312","62312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681295","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian staff by civil service grade were employed by his Department in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62302","62302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681296","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Navy personnel are currently assigned duties aboard HMS Ocean.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62318","62318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681297","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Order of Battle of the Royal Logistics Corps is of the Army by manpower and basing locations.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62295","62295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681298","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the end-of-year budget was for the (a) Royal Military, (b) Royal Naval, (c) Royal Air Force Police and (d) Ministry of Defence Police in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62319","62319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681299","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Order of Battle of the Royal Armoured Corps is by manpower and basing.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62331","62331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681300","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Order of Battle of the Royal Air Force Regiment is by manpower, task and basing.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62332","62332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681301","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Order of Battle of the Royal Artillery is by manpower and basing.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62333","62333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681302","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Order of Battle of the Corps of Royal Engineers is by manpower and basing.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62334","62334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681303","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on policies to minimise the risk of civilian casualties when conducting operations against Daesh.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62362","62362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681304","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service police there were in (a) each branch of the armed forces and (b) the Special Investigations Branch in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62370","62370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681305","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2017 to Question 59205, whether he plans that JDP 0-30.2, The UK Approach to Unmanned Aircraft System, will make a distinction between the use of remotely piloted air systems (a) within and (b) outside areas of armed conflict.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62363","62363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681306","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the End of Year Budget in each year since 2010 was for the Military Provost Guard Service.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62371","62371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681307","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart on maintaining the Executive Order on US Policy on Pre- and Post-Strike Measures to Address Civilian Casualties.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62364","62364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681308","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel were employed by the Military Provost Guard Service in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62372","62372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681309","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many women are serving in the tri-service regular and reserve forces.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62386","62386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681310","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent each year on (a) A400M Atlas, (b) Ajax, (c) Astute boats 1-3, (d) Astute boats 4-7, (e) Complex Weapons Pipeline (Brimstone 2), (f) Complex Weapons Pipeline (Sea Ceptor), (g) Complex Weapons Pipeline (Land Ceptor), (h) Complex Weapons Pipleline (FASGW Heavy), (i) Complex Weapons Pipeline (FASGW Light), (j) Complex Weapons Pipeline (SRAAAM Sustainment), (k) Core Production Capability, (l) Lightning II, (m) MARS Tanker, (n) Queen Elizabeth-class Aircraft Carriers, (o) Type 26 Global Combat Ship, (p) Typhoon (Fighter aircraft), (q) Typhoon (Future Capability Programme 1), (r) Typhoon (Meteor Integration), (s) Typhoon (Storm Shadow Integration), (t) Typhoon (Brimstone 2 Integration) and (u) Warrior Capability Sustainment Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62350","62350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681311","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel he expects to be routinely allocated to a maritime task group centred on a Queen Elizabeth Class aircraft carrier as described in paragraph 4.40 in the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Review, Cm 9161.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62373","62373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681312","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the strength is of Trained UK Reserve personnel in the (a) Royal Military Police, (b) Royal Navy Police and (c) Royal Air Force Police.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62369","62369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681313","2017-02-01","Department for Education","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department has made on providing student loan finance that is compliant with Islamic law.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62352","62352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681314","2017-02-02","Department for Education","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans formally to respond to the consultation on Implementing the English Baccalaureate which closed on 29 January 2016.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62348","62348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681315","2017-02-01","Department for Education","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that British children living abroad have the same financial help to attend British universities as children who live in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62351","62351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681316","2017-02-02","Department for Education","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to review the national curriculum's citizenship programme of study as proposed in the Government's White Paper Education Excellence Everywhere, published in March 2016.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62346","62346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681317","2017-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to reduce river pollution in the UK.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62298","62298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681318","2017-02-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to ensure that funding for the promotion of agricultural products continues to be made available at the level of that currently provided by the European Commission after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62307","62307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681319","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance he plans to offer to the Government of Burma to help it investigate the murder of Ko Ni.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62285","62285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681320","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Government of Burma on the murder of Ko Ni.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62284","62284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681321","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the cost is to the public purse of each of the last three state visits to the UK.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62300","62300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681322","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, by what date the UK Embassy in Bogota plans to comply with the Colombia Constitutional Court's judgment in the case of Action for protection of fundamental rights initiated by Darwin Ayrton Moreno-Hurtado, against the embassy of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland before the Republic of Colombia, dated 22 July 2015.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62342","62342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681323","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether the recent Executive Order on travel to the US applies to people resident in the UK who were born in Somaliland and (a) are British citizens, (b) are citizens of another EEA country, (c) have indefinite leave to remain in the UK and (d) have another immigration status.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62377","62377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681324","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what funding and other support the Government has provided to the Kenyan Anti-Terrorism Police Unit in the last three years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62359","62359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681325","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 61521, what information his Department holds on the ages of people admitted to adult in-patient mental health wards.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62390","62390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681326","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy for adult in-patient mental health wards to record the ages of the people accessing such services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62391","62391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681327","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2017 to Question 61127, how many beds for in-patients with eating disorders there were in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62392","62392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681328","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether (a) NHS England, (b) his Department and (c) other bodies for which his Department is responsible has issued guidance to hospitals on whether they must seek consent from women who have experienced a miscarriage before tissue from the miscarriage is sent for analysis.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62324","62324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681329","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has replied to the letter to him of 24 November 2016 from the Association of Port Health Authorities; and if he will meet representatives of that body.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62344","62344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681330","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to provide additional financial resources for cerebral palsy treatment research.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62313","62313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681331","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of (a) eating disorders and (b) anorexia among middle-aged people.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62315","62315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681332","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment on whether current levels of organ donations meet the levels of demand for such donations.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62309","62309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681333","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ensure that the well-being of GPs and their staff is safeguarded for those working in GP surgeries extending their opening hours.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62314","62314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681334","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on emergency dentistry in hospitals in each year from 2010 to 2016.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62286","62286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681335","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage more people to become organ donors.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62308","62308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681336","2017-02-01","Cabinet Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of EU citizens who have entered the UK since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62291","62291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681337","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will increase the number of people from minority communities in Iraq being resettled in the UK by extending the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Resettlement Scheme to include Iraqis.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62385","62385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681338","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2017 to Question 60398, for what reasons the Government rejected Ravil Mingazov's request for family reunification in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62358","62358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681339","2017-02-02","Home Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the US Administration on its travel ban for refugees and nationals of Iran, Iraq, Libya, Somalia, Sudan, Syria and Yemen; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62340","62340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681340","2017-02-02","House of Commons Commission","2017-01-30","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, if he will take steps to place an inscription on the statue of Charles Bradlaugh, situated in the Lower Waiting Hall of the Palace of Westminster, recognising his campaign to take his seat in Parliament.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62382","62382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681341","2017-02-01","Department for International Development","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that aid can continue to be provided to Aleppo should the conflict in that city resume.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62325","62325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681342","2017-02-02","Department for International Development","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to her press statement of 16 December 2016 on future UK support to the Occupied Palestinian Territories, that she intends to channel payments to the Palestinian Authority directly through the EU's PEGASE mechanism, if she will set out what her policy is on making such payments after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62399","62399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681343","2017-02-02","Department for International Development","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which contracts have been suspended by Ministers of her Department in the last three months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62380","62380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681344","2017-02-02","Department for International Development","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to increase her Department's spending on water, sanitation and hygiene projects.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62299","62299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681345","2017-02-01","Department for International Development","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her foreign counterparts on UNHCR's winter programme funding.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62326","62326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681346","2017-02-01","Department for International Development","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Aleppo.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62327","62327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681347","2017-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2016, Official Report, column 97, what progress has been made on using patrol dogs to reduce the frequency of drones bringing contraband items on to the prison estate in England and Wales; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62347","62347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681348","2017-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the reasons are for the time taken to commence section 67 of the Serious Crime Act 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62365","62365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681349","2017-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans that section 67 of the Serious Crime Act 2015 will come into force.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62366","62366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681350","2017-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent immigration judges have been practising in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62288","62288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681351","2017-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from Iraq have been transferred to prisons in Iraq from the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62289","62289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681352","2017-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of literacy levels of prisoners in England and Wales in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62301","62301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681353","2017-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from Jamaica have been transferred to prisons in Jamaica from the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62290","62290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681354","2017-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of trends in drug-related deaths of prisoners in England and Wales in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62294","62294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681355","2017-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2017 to Question 61520, in which prisons  she has visited a mental health service since July 2016; and on what date each such visit was made.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62389","62389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681356","2017-02-02","Prime Minister","2017-01-30","To ask the Prime Minister, on what date she issued a formal invitation to the President of the US to make a state visit to the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62379","62379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681357","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with (a) The Speaker, (b) Lord Speaker, (c) the House of Commons Commission, (d) the Serjeant-at-Arms and (e) Black Rod on the use of the Palace of Westminster for an address by the President of the US.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62378","62378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681358","2017-02-01","Prime Minister","2017-01-30","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she discussed with President Trump tackling money laundering by Russian officers implicated in military operations in Syria in her recent visit to the US.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62360","62360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681359","2017-02-01","Prime Minister","2017-01-30","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she raised the Trump administration's potential support for recognising the Russian occupation of Crimea during her recent visit to the US.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62361","62361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681360","2017-02-02","Prime Minister","2017-01-30","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions she had with President Erdogan on (a) human rights, (b) press freedom and (c) democracy in Turkey during her visit to that country on 28 January 2017.","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62341","62341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681361","2017-02-02","Department for Transport","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2017 to Question 60337, if he will make it his policy to publish in full the advice provided to him by Chris Gibb; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62343","62343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681362","2017-02-02","Department for Transport","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Peter Wilkinson notified the Department of any conflicts of interest while assessing the Govia Thameslink Railway bid.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62339","62339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681363","2017-02-02","Department for Transport","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Peter Wilkinson has notified the Department of any conflicts of interest in the last three years.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62338","62338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681364","2017-02-01","Department for Transport","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Government's policy is on the use of driverless cars on UK roads.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62310","62310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681365","2017-02-02","Department for Transport","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2017 to Question 61251, what steps he is taking to ensure that when the smart motorway opens on the M1 between junctions 32 and 35a there will be no increase in NO2 or particulate levels.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62375","62375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681366","2017-02-02","Department for Transport","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of the Department's total budget will be spent on cycling between 2015 and 2020.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62383","62383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681367","2017-02-02","Department for Transport","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2016 to Question 55011, for what reasons his Department provided the information requested in that Question to the Guardian newspaper in response to a Freedom of Information request but did not provide the information in that Answer.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62398","62398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681368","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria were used to select sites for closure in his Department's estates review.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62393","62393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681369","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether there will be compulsory redundancies from proposed closures in his Department's estate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62394","62394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681370","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when an equality impact assessment will be published on the proposal to close offices in his Department's estate.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62395","62395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681371","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which sites due for closure in his Department's estate will be subject to a public consultation.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62396","62396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681372","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants have applied for (a) jobseekers allowance or (b) universal credit (i) by post and (ii) during a home visit in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62388","62388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681373","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the expected costs of the proposed relocation of staff and resources from sites due for closure in his Department's estate.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62397","62397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681374","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants are currently served by the Edinburgh city centre jobcentre on South St Andrew Street.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62330","62330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681375","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans that compulsory redundancies will result from the closure of the Edinburgh city centre jobcentre on South St Andrew Street.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62329","62329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681376","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the average time taken by the Independent Case Examiner to process a complaint relating to the Child Support Agency.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62316","62316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681377","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many peopled waited more than (a) six months, (b) nine months and (c) 12 months for the Independent Care Examiner to process their complaint about the Child Support Agency.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62317","62317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681378","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants there were in each of the Jobcentre Plus branches in Hull City Council broken down by gender for the most recent month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62296","62296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681379","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether officials of his Department visited Eastern Avenue jobcentre, Sheffield before announcing the decision to close it.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62335","62335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681380","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to issue an Equality Impact Assessment on the proposal to close the Edinburgh city centre jobcentre on South St Andrew Street.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62328","62328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681381","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what visits to jobcentres it is his policy to reimburse claimants for travel.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62336","62336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681382","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has conducted an impact assessment of the closure of Eastern Avenue Job Centre, Sheffield; and whether his Department made an assessment of the potential effect of (a) demographics and (b) access to the internet when making the decision to move that Job Centre.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62345","62345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681383","2017-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefits claimants are affected by the decision to close the jobcentre at Eastern Avenue, Sheffield.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62337","62337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681384","2017-02-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2016 to Question 57076, on the Green Investment Bank, how much of the £4.7 billion investment will be directed to low carbon innovation projects.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62367","62367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681385","2017-02-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government has any plans to introduce a scheme similar to the Science and Society Community Challenge grant scheme in the next 12 months.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62311","62311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681386","2017-02-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Department for Exiting the European Union on plans to leave Euratom; and on what dates those discussions took place.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62303","62303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681387","2017-02-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of plans to leave Euratom on UK nuclear capacity, research and business plans.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62349","62349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681388","2017-02-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what support his Department plans to provide industry in developing detailed plans to implement the recommendations in his Department's publication Each Home Counts, published in December 2016.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62368","62368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681389","2017-02-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will set a deadline for industry to develop detailed plans to implement the recommendations in his Department's publication, Each Home Counts review, published in December 2016.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62374","62374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681390","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what export credit support his Department or its predecessors have provided to Alstom Power in Lithuania, Tunisia, Indonesia, Egypt and India since 2000; and whether UK Export Finance have made payments to Alstom Power for losses in relation to projects in those countries.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62353","62353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681391","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether it is the policy of UK Export Finance (UKEF) to take against a company if it discovers that a company it has insured has breached its anti-corruption warranty in cases where there has been no loss to UKEF.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62354","62354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681392","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, on how many occasions since 2005 UK Export Finance has cancelled a policy with an insured company on grounds of admission of or conviction for corrupt activity.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62355","62355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681393","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, on how many occasions UK Export Finance has provided a payment to Rolls Royce under export finance policies since 2000; and what the amounts were of each such payment made; and in relation to which (a) project and (b) country each such payment was made.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62356","62356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681394","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what cover UK Export Finance has given to Rolls Royce since 2000; and what the (a) type of export credit finance, (b) year, (c) amount, (d) country and (e) project was of each instance of such cover.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62357","62357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681395","2017-02-02","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many arms export licences have been granted in the last six months; and what the destination country was of each of those applications.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62376","62376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681396","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assistance has been (a) offered and (b) requested from his counterparts in Australia on the negotiation of trade agreements relating to the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62304","62304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681397","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether all WTO rules and practices pertaining to the UK will continue to do so in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62305","62305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681398","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment the Government has made of which WTO rules and practices pertain to the UK (a) in the UK's own right and (b) through the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62306","62306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681399","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many times UK Export Finance has used its special audit rights to seek further information from companies about their agents and commission in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62323","62323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681400","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what export credit support his Department or its predecessor has provided to Cyril Sweett or related companies since 2000.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62322","62322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681401","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which companies that have requested special handling arrangements when providing UK Export Finance with information about their agents and commission payments.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62320","62320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/681402","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, in how many instances since 2000 UK Export Finance has provided support to a company which was using Unaoil as an agent.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62321","62321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682230","2017-02-02","Cabinet Office","2017-01-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if the Government will take steps to make the consultation process operated through the Sewel Convention a statutory requirement.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908573","908573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682463","2017-02-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the devolved administrations on legislative consent motions for the proposed Great Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908575","908575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682464","2017-02-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the devolved administrations on legislative consent motions for the proposed Great Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908566","908566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683075","2017-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the effect of changes in tribunal fees in people with protected characteristics.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908514","908514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683102","2017-02-02","Women and Equalities","2017-01-30","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if the Government will introduce statutory sex and relationships education to tackle homophobic bullying and sexual harassment in schools.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908526","908526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683202","2017-02-02","Women and Equalities","2017-01-30","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to reduce homophobia in sport.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908527","908527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679668","2017-01-31","Attorney General","2017-01-27","To ask the Attorney General, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of the Law Officers' Departments and arms-length bodies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62059","62059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679669","2017-01-31","Cabinet Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of his Department, agencies and arms-length bodies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62060","62060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679670","2017-02-01","HM Treasury","2017-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the level of earnings is of the (a) highest and (b) lowest-paid employees of his Department, its agencies and arms-length bodies; and what the median level of earnings is for such employees.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61995","61995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679671","2017-01-31","Church Commissioners","2017-01-27","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of the Church Commissioners.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62061","62061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679672","2017-01-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of his Department, agencies and arms-length bodies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62062","62062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679673","2017-02-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of its total annual budget Lancashire County Council received from the Local Government Grant (Local Government Finance Settlement), for each budget heading, in 2016-17; and what such proportion, by budget heading, that council has been allocated to receive in 2017-18.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62087","62087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679674","2017-02-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of parking charges on low income families.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62132","62132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679675","2017-02-01","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of UK landmass has mobile voice and SMS coverage.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62092","62092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679676","2017-02-01","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of households in the top 10 most (a) rural and (b) urban parliamentary constituencies have access to high speed broadband.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62094","62094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679677","2017-01-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of her Department, agencies and arms-length bodies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62063","62063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679678","2017-01-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether there is a vacancy for a Chief Scientific Adviser in her Department.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62084","62084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679679","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) homeless veterans and (b) veterans experiencing mental health problems; and whether each of those issues is supported by the Armed Forces Covenant.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62105","62105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679680","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of fast jets are able to be deployed into immediate action.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62106","62106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679681","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made on the effect on reservist recruitment and retention of paying reservists a quarter day's pay as opposed to a half day's pay for their evening's training.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62090","62090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679682","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average time taken was to conclude an internal formal complaint by each of the armed forces in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62118","62118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679683","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the level of earnings is of the (a) highest and (b) lowest-paid employees of his Department, its agencies and arms-length bodies; and what the median level of earnings is for such employees.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61993","61993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679684","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many in-service complaints recorded by each of the armed forces included an oral hearing; and if he will detail the procedures for securing an oral hearing in each of the armed forces.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62122","62122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679685","2017-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many internal formal complaints have been recorded by each of the armed forces in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62119","62119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679686","2017-02-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much EU funding was received by higher education institutions in (a) the UK and (b) Greater London in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62121","62121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679687","2017-02-01","Department for Education","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether schools are required to inform her Department if their websites and servers are hacked.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62140","62140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679688","2017-02-01","Department for Education","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will write to (a) Wikihow and (b) YouTube to request that those organisations remove from their sites guides on how to hack into school websites and servers.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62123","62123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679689","2017-02-01","Department for Education","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in England have their own website; and what guidance or support her Department has given to schools to ensure that websites and school servers are secure.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62125","62125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679690","2017-02-01","Department for Education","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to prohibit subsidiaries of profit-making companies from contracting with local authorities to run child protection and other children's social care services.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62042","62042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679691","2017-01-31","Department for Education","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to ring-fence a proportion of the revenue raised from the sugar levy to support the least active children to exercise more.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62057","62057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679692","2017-02-01","Department for Education","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how inflation is taken into account in determining pay for teachers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62112","62112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679693","2017-02-01","Department for Education","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the financial effect on schools of the abandonment of her Department's policy of compulsory academisation.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62113","62113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679694","2017-01-31","Department for Education","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of her Department, agencies and arms-length bodies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62064","62064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679695","2017-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of her Department, agencies and arms-length bodies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62065","62065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679696","2017-01-31","Department for Transport","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on air quality of increasing the capacity of the M4 between junctions 3 and 4 by creating a tunnel for additional traffic.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62080","62080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679697","2017-02-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she plans to make to her EU counterparts on securing the right to retain the use of zinc oxide in piglet feed; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61983","61983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679698","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with Lord Patten of Barnes on (a) the rule of law and (b) democracy in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61984","61984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679699","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Government on (a) the rule of law and (b) democracy in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61985","61985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679700","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with members of the Legislative Council of Hong Kong on (a) the rule of law and (b) democracy in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61986","61986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679701","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on (a) the rule of law and (b) democracy in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61987","61987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679702","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the Minister for Asia and the Pacific next plans to visit Hong Kong.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61988","61988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679703","2017-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how UK overseas posts ensure that the families of UK citizens murdered abroad are adequately represented in related prosecution processes.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62011","62011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679704","2017-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reason Trinidad and Tobago High Commission has not been represented in the hearings related to the murder of Adrian St John.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62041","62041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679705","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the level of earnings is of the (a) highest and (b) lowest-paid employee of his Department, its agencies and arms-length bodies; and what the median level of earnings is for such employees.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61994","61994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679706","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure a representative of the British High Commission in Trinidad and Tobago attends the next hearing, on 6 February 2017, relating to the murder of Adrian St John.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61990","61990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679707","2017-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Palestinian Authority after a demonstration hosted by President Abbas' Fatah party to celebrate the 52nd anniversary of its first terror attack on Israel at which terrorists who have killed Israelis were honoured.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62082","62082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679708","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will provide a comprehensive list of the public policy targets established by his Department (a) between 2010 and May 2015 and (b) since May 2015.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62089","62089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679709","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many vacancies there were for prostate cancer surgeons in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland, (d) Northern Ireland and (e) Royal Wolverhampton NHS Trust in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013, (v) 2014, (vi) 2015 and (vii) 2016.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62101","62101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679710","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average number of days is between the date when a patient is first diagnosed with prostate cancer for which surgery is advised and the date on which the first such surgery is available to such a patient in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland, (d) Northern Ireland and (e) Royal Wolverhampton NHS Trust in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013, (v) 2014, (vi) 2015 and (vii) 2016.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62102","62102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679711","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) knee and (b) hip replacements have been carried out on the NHS in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62103","62103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679712","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of prostate cancer surgeons who are trained to carry out prostate cancer surgery using robots use those robots more than once each week.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62104","62104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679713","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average waiting time for (a) knee and (b) hip operations in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62095","62095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679714","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many robotic surgery machines there are.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62108","62108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679715","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of prostate cancer surgeons in England is trained to carry out prostate cancer surgery using robots.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62100","62100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679716","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made on the suitability of support provided for people living with arthritis.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62116","62116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679717","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people in their 50s are screened for bowel cancer.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62083","62083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679718","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what average number of hours per year is each surgical robot used for operations.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62081","62081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679719","2017-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding for research grants into cancer was provided to individuals and organisations in the UK by the European Research Council in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62079","62079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679720","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of his Department, agencies and arms-length bodies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62067","62067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679721","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what effect his Department has identified of the UK leaving the EU on continued collaboration with patients, patient advocates and healthcare professional groups through the European Cancer Concord.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62078","62078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679722","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to promote the access to and sale of healthier food options on hospital sites.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62076","62076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679723","2017-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding was allocated to UK research projects on cancer under the EU's Seventh Framework Programme.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62077","62077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679724","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans NICE has to include guidance on treatment of recurrent ovarian cancer in its review of NICE guidelines.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62049","62049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679725","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the Government has to extend the NHS Cancer Dashboard to include ovarian and other less common cancers.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62050","62050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679726","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with cancer at A&E departments in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62051","62051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679727","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many drug treatments which previously met NICE guidelines have been removed for not meeting those guidelines since 2015.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62052","62052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679728","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the findings of the ovarian cancer regional pilot that took place in 2014 will be published.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62053","62053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679729","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Government's plans on the new appraisal process for cancer drugs to be considered for off-label or off-licence use will be published.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62054","62054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679730","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many of the new cancer drugs that were approved in 2015-16 by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence would have been affected by the proposed new £20 million budget impact threshold.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62055","62055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679731","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the role of universities is in the establishment of Sustainability and Transformation plans.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62035","62035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679732","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how continuing professional development for (a) nurses, (b) midwives and (c) allied health professionals is monitored by his Department.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62034","62034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679733","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding his Department allocates to continuing professional development for (a) nurses, (b) midwives and (c) allied health professionals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62036","62036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679734","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses from other EU countries have been employed by the NHS since 23 June 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62037","62037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679735","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to include steps to tackle smoking prevalence among children and young people in the Government's planned Tobacco Control Plan.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62008","62008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679736","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on the planned pilot of the Be Clear on Cancer abdominal scheme.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62046","62046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679737","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on patients accessing clinical trials on new cancer treatments.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62047","62047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679738","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the per capita spend on public health was in each English region in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62048","62048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679739","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of trends in health inequalities in England between 2005 and 2015; and what steps the Government is taking to reduce health inequalities for vulnerable NHS patients.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61989","61989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679740","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were on the waiting list for (a) knee and (b) hip operations on the NHS in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62139","62139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679741","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adult in-patient psychiatric beds there were in England in each quarter for which information is available in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62131","62131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679742","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many instances of readmission to in-patient psychiatric units there were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62127","62127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679743","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Band 7 NHS psychologists were employed between September 2015 and September 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62130","62130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679744","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on treatment for drug and alcohol addiction in 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62128","62128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679745","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people under 18 were admitted to hospital as a result of self-harm in 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62129","62129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679746","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications which included medical evidence of torture were rejected in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61997","61997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679747","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many rejected asylum applications which included medical evidence of torture were subsequently overturned on appeal in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61998","61998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679748","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications which included medical evidence of torture were received in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61999","61999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679749","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will centrally publish the (a) companies who are required to report and (b) companies who have reported under the Modern Slavery Act 2015.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62004","62004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679750","2017-01-31","Home Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of her Department, agencies and arms-length bodies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62068","62068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679751","2017-01-31","Home Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the holding Answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 39747, on counter-terrorism, when she expects to provide a full Answer.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62141","62141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679752","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2017 to Question 63085, what recent steps she has taken to offer asylum to unaccompanied refugee children who are currently in Greece and Serbia.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62126","62126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679753","2017-01-31","House of Commons Commission","2017-01-27","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of the House of Commons Commission.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62069","62069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679754","2017-02-01","Department for International Development","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much Government funding has been provided to Marie Stopes International for work in which countries outside the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62000","62000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679755","2017-02-01","Department for International Development","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, in which countries outside the UK Government funding has been provided to Marie Stopes International for work on family planning and abortion provision in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62001","62001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679756","2017-02-01","Department for International Development","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the Government funding provided to Marie Stopes International for work outside the UK in each of the last five years has been classified as overseas aid.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62002","62002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679757","2017-02-01","Department for International Development","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much Government funding has been provided to Marie Stopes International in each of the last five years related to work (a) within and (b) outside the UK.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62003","62003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679758","2017-01-31","Department for International Development","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of her Department and arms-length bodies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62070","62070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679759","2017-02-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps are being taken to end the ivory trade in Africa.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62114","62114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679760","2017-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what impact assessment has been carried out on the change to the discount rate on the NHS.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62096","62096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679761","2017-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what budget has been allocated to pay for the construction of new custody facilities at Wrexham Magistrates' Court.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62097","62097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679762","2017-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps have been taken to commission new custody facilities at Wrexham Magistrates' Court.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62098","62098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679763","2017-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of current sentencing for causing a death by dangerous driving.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62091","62091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679764","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of her Department, agencies and arms-length bodies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62072","62072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679765","2017-02-01","Home Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the findings of the Devon and Cornwall Police inquiry into the murder of Tanis Bhandari that omissions in the recording of license conditions on the Police National Computer are likely to recur.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61991","61991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679766","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from Iran have been transferred to prisons in Iran from the UK in each year of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62033","62033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679767","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from India have been transferred to prisons in India from the UK in each year of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62028","62028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679768","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what agreements the Government has with the Government of Albania relating to the transfer of prisoners; and what effect those agreements have had on the number of prisoners exchanged with that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62015","62015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679769","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what agreements the Government has with the Government of Turkey relating to the transfer of prisoners; and what effect those agreements have had on the number of prisoners exchanged with that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62016","62016"
