"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39575","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps she is taking to tackle paedophilia; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189043","189043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39576","2014-02-27","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the recommendation in the report of the Migration Advisory Committee's Limits, on Migration, November 2010, that allowances used for PBS points purposes should be scaled back, what measures have been put in place to prevent any incentives to undercut domestic labour.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189225","189225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39577","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by her Department and (b) operated by a third party on her Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189105","189105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39578","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps are being taken to ensure her Department's officials are present in all court appeals relating to cases where a person has been refused leave to remain in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189038","189038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39579","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals requesting citizenship to the UK were refused on the grounds of failure to pass the Life in the UK text in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189036","189036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39580","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many criminal offences by foreign born nationals were recorded in the London Borough of Havering in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189037","189037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39581","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189165","189165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39582","2014-02-27","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the oral evidence taken by the Public Accounts Committee on 28 March 2011, HC 913-i, whether the Immigration Case Work system is now in place.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189224","189224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39583","2014-02-27","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the effect on (a) UK workers and (b) UK IT services companies of the ability of multinational companies to transfer employees into the UK and gain access to tax free business expenses.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188942","188942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39584","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fraud crimes are (a) reported and (b) investigated in each police force area in the UK annually; and how many convictions for fraud there were in the UK in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189008","189008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39585","2014-02-27","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she last met the Secretary of State for Education to discuss raising awareness of female genital mutilation in schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189005","189005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39586","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to minimise the amount being spent on processing asylum claims.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189039","189039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39587","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an estimate of the number of economic and fraud crimes reported in the last 10 years that remain un-investigated in each police area due to resource constraints or a lack of suitably-qualified personnel.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189009","189009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39588","2014-02-27","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the Member of Walsall North to receive a reply to his letter to the interim director general, UK Visas and Immigration of 24 January 2014 on behalf of a constituent; CTS ref M1157/14.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188951","188951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39589","2014-02-27","Department for International Development","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the progress of the government of Bangladesh in appointing factory inspectors following the Rana Plaza building collapse.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188976","188976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39590","2014-02-26","Department for International Development","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189166","189166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39591","2014-02-26","Department for International Development","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by her Department and (b) operated by a third party on her Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189106","189106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39592","2014-02-27","Department for International Development","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the purpose was of the Memorandum of Cooperation with the London Stock Exchange Group signed on 27 January 2014; and if she will place a copy of that memorandum in the Library.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189221","189221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39593","2014-02-26","Department for International Development","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what aid programmes the Government operates in Eastern Europe.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189049","189049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39594","2014-02-26","Department for International Development","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on reviewing financial aid levels to the British Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189030","189030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39595","2014-02-26","Department for International Development","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189066","189066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39596","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the economic effect to the UK has been of the recent economic performance of (a) Bermuda and (b) the Cayman Islands.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189045","189045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39597","2014-02-26","Department for International Development","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what development aid was provided to the government of Argentina in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189048","189048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39598","2014-02-26","Department for International Development","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in her Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189086","189086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39599","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what preliminary work his Department has undertaken on plans for a new prison at Feltham announced in September 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189216","189216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39600","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189087","189087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39601","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on the construction of Young Offender Institute Glen Parva before the project was cancelled in 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189215","189215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39602","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the annual cost of a place in a secure college.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189205","189205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39603","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Government will publish the draft rules for secure colleges.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189206","189206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39604","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189067","189067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39605","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on the construction of HM Prison Maghull before the project was cancelled in 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189214","189214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39606","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what meetings (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) special advisers have had with (i) G4S, (ii) Serco, (iii) Sodexo, (iv) A4E, (v) Capita, (vi) Mitie, (vii) GEOAmey and (viii) Working Links since September 2013; what the dates of each such meeting were; and what was discussed at each meeting.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189213","189213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39607","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) investigations, (b) charges and (c) convictions there have been for (i) the offence of making or possession of explosive under suspicious circumstances, (ii) weapons training for terrorism and (iii) training for terrorism in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189212","189212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39608","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189107","189107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39609","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189167","189167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39610","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what date contracts for probation work will be signed; and when operations will go live.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188998","188998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39611","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the close of tender date will be for the Transforming Rehabilitation agenda.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188999","188999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39612","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria will be used to identify preferred bidders for probation contracts.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189000","189000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39613","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what risks arising from the outsourcing of probation contracts bidders in the process of transition have brought to the attention of his Department.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189001","189001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39614","2014-02-27","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the difficulties caused to fishermen by current weather conditions.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188946","188946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39615","2014-02-26","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of the current weather conditions on fishermen in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188921","188921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39616","2014-02-26","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189168","189168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39617","2014-02-26","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by her Department and (b) operated by a third party on her Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189108","189108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39618","2014-02-26","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189068","189068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39619","2014-02-26","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in her Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189088","189088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39620","2014-02-26","Scotland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189089","189089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39621","2014-02-26","Scotland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189069","189069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39622","2014-02-26","Scotland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189109","189109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39623","2014-02-26","Scotland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189169","189169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39624","2014-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what recent representations the Electoral Commission has received on the London Borough of Tower Hamlets allowing foreign language translators into polling stations to advise individual electors.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189010","189010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39625","2014-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what guidance the Electoral Commission has produced on the practice of allowing foreign language translators into polling stations to advise individual electors on how to cast their vote.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188935","188935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39626","2014-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of which local authorities allow foreign language translators into polling stations to advise individual electors on how to cast their vote.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188936","188936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39627","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps he has taken against unofficial websites offering government services relating to the application for driving licences.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188990","188990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39628","2014-02-27","Department for Transport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2014, Official Report, column 358W, on Large goods vehicles, when he expects the detailed OCRS report to be published.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188992","188992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39629","2014-02-27","Department for Transport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 406W, on vehicle number plates, what recent progress the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency has made with the UK Border Force and the police on how data can be used to identify foreign registered vehicles that have been in the UK for longer than six months.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188975","188975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39630","2014-02-27","Department for Transport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the risk of serious or fatal injury to powered two wheeler users of Bedfordshire Borough Council's proposal to include raised curbs between lanes in a turbo style roundabout scheme at the intersection of Union Street, Tavistock Street, Clapham Road and Roff Avenue in Bedfordshire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188947","188947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39631","2014-02-27","Department for Transport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Poplar and Limehouse of 12 September 2012, Official Report, column 244W, on motorways: repairs and maintenance, how many people repairing motorways were killed or injured by vehicles in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188950","188950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39632","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has spent on schemes for (a) cyclists, (b) bridleways and (c) pedestrians in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188929","188929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39633","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189170","189170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39634","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189110","189110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39635","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189070","189070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39636","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189090","189090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39637","2014-02-26","Wales Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189092","189092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39638","2014-02-26","Wales Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189072","189072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39639","2014-02-26","Wales Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189112","189112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39640","2014-02-26","Wales Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189172","189172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39641","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189173","189173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39642","2014-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many residents of Barrow and Furness constituency, in each age group, have found permanent employment after being enrolled in the Work Programme since that programme's introduction.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189232","189232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39643","2014-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many residents of Barrow and Furness constituency, in each age group, have sanctioned under the Work Programme since that Programme's introduction.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189233","189233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39644","2014-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many residents of Barrow and Furness constituency, in each age group, have been enrolled on the Work Programme since that Programme's introduction.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189231","189231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39645","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189113","189113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39646","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189073","189073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39647","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189093","189093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39648","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of personal independence payments claims which were not made under the special rules for terminally ill people, were withdrawn by claimants resident in (a) Washington and Sunderland West constituency, (b) the North East and (c) England in each month for which records are available.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188923","188923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39649","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of decided personal independence payments claims, which were not made under the special rules for terminally ill people, have been (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful, by claimants resident in (i) Washington and Sunderland West constituency, (ii) the North East and (iii) England in each month for which records are available.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188924","188924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39650","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payments claims, not made under the special rules for terminally ill people, have been made by residents of (a) Washington and Sunderland West constituency, (b) the North East and (c) England in each month for which records are available.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188925","188925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39651","2014-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the effect on a recipient of universal credit will be if they are also in receipt of widowed parents allowance.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188916","188916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39652","2014-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that his Department complies with the Autism Act 2009.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189016","189016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39653","2014-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of Jobseekers Allowance in postcodes G76, G46, G78, G77 and G44 have been sanctioned by his Department in the last five years; and for what reasons.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188977","188977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39654","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking against unofficial websites offering services relating to the application for national insurance numbers.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189011","189011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39655","2014-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the total costs and benefits of universal credit in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188993","188993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39656","2014-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when jobseekers will be able to speak to a benefit adviser in his Department without paying for a telephone call; and how this facility will be supported.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188979","188979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39657","2014-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 5 December 2013, Official Report, columns 65-6WS, on universal credit, whether the business plan for delivery of universal credit has been reviewed by the (a) Treasury and (b) Major Projects Authority.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188994","188994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39658","2014-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what month the universal credit roll out will start accepting claims from families.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188995","188995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39659","2014-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timetable is for rollout of universal credit to (a) spring 2014, (b) the end of 2014 and (c) the end of 2015.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188996","188996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39660","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has for the future provision of freephones at jobcentres.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188981","188981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39661","2014-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what month the universal credit roll out will start accepting claims from couples.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188997","188997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39662","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with his Canadian counterpart over unfreezing the annual uprating of state pensions of UK citizens living in Canada and Canadian citizens living in the UK.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188988","188988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39663","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to unfreeze the annual uprating of the state pension for UK citizens living in Canada.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188989","188989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39664","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether successors in title to insurers who maintained employer's liability insurance schemes will be liable to contribute to the Diffuse Mesothelioma Payment Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188933","188933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39665","2014-02-26","Attorney General","2014-02-24","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of civil servants in the Law Officers' Departments who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189115","189115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39666","2014-02-26","Attorney General","2014-02-24","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of civil servants in the Law Officers' Departments who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189135","189135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39667","2014-02-26","Attorney General","2014-02-24","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions for illegal taking of game there have been in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189270","189270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39668","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with banks and payday loan companies on measures to ensure that small and medium-sized businesses are not penalised for repaying loans early.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189266","189266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39669","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the Regulatory Co-operation Council provided for in the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership will have a right to override national and EU-level legislation.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189253","189253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39670","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what comparative assessment he has made of the merits of the (a) investor-state dispute settlement contained in Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership and (b) Court of Justice of the European Union as a mechanism for settling investor-state disputes involving EU member states.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189254","189254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39671","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness and desirability of the investor-state dispute settlement clause in the proposed Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189255","189255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39672","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect in the UK of the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership on (a) regulations on hydraulic fracturing, (b) the use of genetically modified crops and (c) price controls on pharmaceutical drugs.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189256","189256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39673","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of whether the investor-state dispute settlement clause in the proposed Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership would allow corporations to take legal action against EU governments which enact or abide by legislation aimed at protecting human or consumer rights or the environment.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189257","189257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39674","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the regulatory harmonisation in the proposed Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership on regulatory standards in the EU.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189258","189258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39675","2014-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will monitor home insurance premiums to ensure that increases relating to risks of flooding are justified; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189245","189245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39676","2014-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of households forced to seek alternative accommodation after their homes were flooded who were referred by their insurers to the Insurance Claim Accommodation Bureau (ICAB); how many such households were found homes by ICAB; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189246","189246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39677","2014-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to monitor the treatment by insurance companies of policy holders whose homes have been flooded; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189244","189244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39678","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189116","189116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39679","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189176","189176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39680","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189136","189136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39681","2014-02-26","HM Treasury","2014-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189191","189191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39682","2014-02-26","HM Treasury","2014-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189131","189131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39683","2014-02-26","HM Treasury","2014-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189151","189151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39684","2014-02-26","HM Treasury","2014-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the role played by the inequality of (a) wealth and (b) income in the 2007 financial crisis.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189202","189202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39685","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the Leasehold Value Tribunal system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189203","189203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39686","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what support his Department plans to provide for local authorities in crisis loans in 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189201","189201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39687","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189137","189137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39688","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the size was of the local government emergency fund in each year for which figures are available; and how much his Department has allocated in such funding in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189196","189196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39689","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189177","189177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39690","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189117","189117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39691","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189118","189118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39692","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189178","189178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39693","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189138","189138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39694","2014-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189139","189139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39695","2014-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will discuss with the Secretary of State for Health a policy of inviting former members of HM Armed Forces to consider a career with the ambulance service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189249","189249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39696","2014-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189179","189179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39697","2014-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189119","189119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39698","2014-02-26","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-24","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what progress he has made on identifying areas not included in the first or second wave of the City Deals programme as eligible for subsequent initiatives.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189252","189252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39699","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189120","189120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39700","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189180","189180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39701","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189140","189140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39702","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189141","189141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39703","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189181","189181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39704","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189121","189121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39705","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189122","189122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39706","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189182","189182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39707","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189142","189142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39708","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many houses built on a flood plain have flooded in (a) England, (b) Wales and (c) Greater London in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Love","Mr Andrew Love","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189198","189198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39709","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many houses that have flooded in the current financial year were built on a flood plain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Love","Mr Andrew Love","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189200","189200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39710","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with organisations representing wildfowling interest about the designation of marine conservation zones.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189259","189259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39711","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the recent increase in butterfly numbers; and what steps he plans to take to further increase the number of butterflies.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189261","189261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39712","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189143","189143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39713","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the statement on 24 February 2014 by Prime Minister Medvedev of Russia that the current situation in Ukraine represents armed mutiny, what assessment he has made of the activities and status of the interim authorities in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189243","189243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39714","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to ensure that British diplomatic contacts with Ministers and officials in Ukraine are held with representatives of the legitimate government of that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189237","189237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39715","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189183","189183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39716","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189123","189123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39717","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189124","189124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39718","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189184","189184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39719","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to lower mortality rates in the Government's dedicated spearhead areas.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189247","189247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39720","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189144","189144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39721","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether sofosbuvir will be made available on the NHS to treat hepatitis C.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189262","189262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39722","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of whether there is a connection between use of the contraceptive pill and fatal blood clots.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189267","189267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39723","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of syphilis have been diagnosed in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189268","189268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39725","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on how many people have suffered concussion injuries while playing sport, by category of sport, in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189260","189260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39726","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure safety of patients and high professional standards in the cosmetic surgery sector.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189265","189265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39727","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to prohibit the offer and sale of stun guns on eBay.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189263","189263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39728","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to counter the threat of letter-bomb attacks on Army recruiting offices on the UK mainland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189264","189264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39729","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of illegal taking of game have been recorded in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189269","189269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39730","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189145","189145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39731","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many press officers were employed in her Department on 1 February 2014.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189242","189242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39732","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum cases were awaiting decision for travel documents on 1 February 2014.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189239","189239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39733","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to appoint a permanent Director General for Visas and Immigration.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189240","189240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39734","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people applied for fast-track visas to the UK in India in 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189241","189241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39735","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189185","189185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39736","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189125","189125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39737","2014-02-26","Department for International Development","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of civil servants in her Department and non-departmental public body who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189126","189126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39738","2014-02-26","Department for International Development","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189186","189186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39739","2014-02-26","Department for International Development","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, on how many occasions Ministers in her Department have visited Gaza in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189250","189250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39740","2014-02-26","Department for International Development","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of civil servants in her Department and non-departmental public body who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189146","189146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39741","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189147","189147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39742","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress his Department has made with the Information Commissioner on development of a code of practice for the electronic monitoring of offenders; and when such a code of practice will be published.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189204","189204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39743","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189187","189187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39744","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189127","189127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39745","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions for illegal taking of game there have been in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189271","189271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39746","2014-02-26","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189128","189128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39747","2014-02-26","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189188","189188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39748","2014-02-26","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189148","189148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39749","2014-02-26","Scotland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189149","189149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39750","2014-02-26","Scotland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189189","189189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39751","2014-02-26","Scotland Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189129","189129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39752","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189130","189130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39753","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189190","189190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39754","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189150","189150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39755","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for how many days the (a) Exeter St Davids to Tiverton Parkway, (b) Exeter St Davids to Salisbury, (c) Taunton to Bristol Temple Meads, (d) Plymouth to Newton Abbot, (e) Exeter St Davids to Newton Abbot and (f) Plymouth to Penzance railway lines were closed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189234","189234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39756","2014-02-26","Wales Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189152","189152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39757","2014-02-26","Wales Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189132","189132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39758","2014-02-26","Wales Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189192","189192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39759","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189193","189193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39760","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many sanctions have been enacted by Jobcentre Plus in (a) Livingston constituency and (b) West Lothian local authority area in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189197","189197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39761","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189133","189133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39762","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189153","189153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39763","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make it his policy to extend the Warm Home Discount to include families where the parents are (a) unemployed and (b) have an annual income of less than 10,000.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189251","189251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39764","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effects of the requirement for claimants to demonstrate availability to work on their right to a holiday from signing on; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189248","189248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39765","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have found work lasting six months or longer through the Work Programme in (a) Livingston constituency and (b) West Lothian local authority area in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189199","189199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39766","2014-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are awaiting a work capability assessment in Barrow and Furness constituency; and how many such people have been waiting in excess of three months for an assessment.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189235","189235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39882","2014-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he has taken to investigate higher charges for non-direct debit domestic customers of energy utility companies.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902739","902739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39883","2014-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will establish a Royal Commission to examine long-term measures to tackle flooding caused by climate change.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902729","902729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40235","2014-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to help vulnerable people reduce their energy bills.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902742","902742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39081","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many applications for Advanced Learning loans have been (a) made and (b) issued to date.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188648","188648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39082","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many full-time equivalent employees were employed by the National Apprenticeship Service in April (a) 2012 and (b) 2013; and how many such staff will be employed in April (i) 2014 and (ii) 2015.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188649","188649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39083","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the Skills Funding Agency budget is in each Core City per head of population.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188651","188651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39084","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding his Department has provided to (a) research councils funding animal research and (b) development of non-animal experimentation methods in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188641","188641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39085","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the Skills Funding Agency budget in each (a) constituent part of the UK, (b) region and (c) local authority area is per head of population.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188644","188644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39086","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many colleges have satisfactorily submitted their student number returns as part of the Data Collections and Funding Transformation Programme to date.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188645","188645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39087","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been paid to each contractor for the delivery of the Data Collections and Funding Transformation Programme to date.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188646","188646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39088","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding is allocated to (a) the Student Opportunity Fund and (b) the Access to Learning Fund in 2014-15.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188643","188643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39089","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the Data Collections and Funding Transformation Programme will be fully operational.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188647","188647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39090","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what reports his Department has received on the owners of ships working the Irish Sea routes paying their staff below minimum wage; and what guidance his Department has issued on the application of minimum wage legislation to the crews of ships operating between two UK ports.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188695","188695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39091","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will discuss with the European Commission the backdating of compensation to energy-intensive industries for the costs associated with the Carbon Floor Price.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188753","188753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39092","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of when the EU state aid decision will be made on compensating energy-intensive industries for the costs associated with the Carbon Floor Price.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188754","188754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39093","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what long-term support his Department will provide for energy-intensive industries.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188755","188755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39094","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps he has taken to increase exports in the construction sector.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188721","188721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39095","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to increase innovation in the construction sector.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188724","188724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39096","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many meetings he has had with UK construction industry executives in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188723","188723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39097","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on the privatisation of student loans.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188804","188804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39098","2014-02-25","Cabinet Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the value of the UK construction industry was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188722","188722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39099","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with which companies the Government has a contract to provide pagers; and what the annual value is of each such contract.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188749","188749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39100","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Government-owned pagers are provided to members of the Civil Service.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188750","188750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39101","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Government departments provide pagers for staff.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188751","188751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39102","2014-02-25","HM Treasury","2014-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of non-reporting of trading figures for car insurance by motor insurance companies; and whether he has assessed if this is in breach of International Financial Reporting Standards 8, Operating Segments.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188620","188620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39103","2014-02-25","HM Treasury","2014-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects to reach agreement with the Ministry of Defence on changes to civil service pay and conditions as part of the DE and S plus model for defence procurement; and if he will publish the details of such an arrangement.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188601","188601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39104","2014-02-25","HM Treasury","2014-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the average person pays each year in (a) fuel duty and (b) alcohol excise duty; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188652","188652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39105","2014-02-26","HM Treasury","2014-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that online companies declare the full value of imported goods on their customs declarations.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188822","188822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39106","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on extending the compensation package for energy-intensive industries to include the Renewables Obligation.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188780","188780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39107","2014-02-25","HM Treasury","2014-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the prevelance of non-reporting of trading figures for car insurance by motor insurance companies; and whether he has assessed if this is in breach of International Financial Reporting Standards 8, Operating Segments.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188736","188736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39108","2014-02-25","Church Commissioners","2014-02-21","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what work the Church Commissioners are undertaking to support flooded communities and farmers.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188650","188650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39109","2014-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many liability orders for council tax payment have been granted by the courts in the last six months.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188617","188617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39110","2014-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people in Plymouth who receive welfare and disability benefits are liable to pay council tax.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188618","188618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39111","2014-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what changes were made to the funding formula for fire and rescue services between 2011-12 and 2012-13.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188671","188671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39112","2014-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of (a) whole time and (b) retained firefighters were (i) women and (ii) black or from an ethnic minority background in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188672","188672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39113","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2013, Official Report, column 443W, on local government: cooperation, how his Department is implementing the commitment, on page 184 of the Strategic Environmental Assessment of the Revocation of the West Midlands Regional Strategy: Post Adoption Statement, to monitor the environmental impacts of the duty to co-operate in the West Midlands and implement measures to address or mitigate any negative effects.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188762","188762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39114","2014-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to protect library services.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188738","188738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39115","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to ensure that (a) only closed cell insulation is used in buildings and flood risk areas and (b) BBA Agrment certificates specify that other types of cavity wall insulation are not certified for use in such areas.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188765","188765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39116","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to publish his Department's revision to planning practice guidance.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188775","188775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39117","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2014, Official Report, column 303W, on sports: scholarships, when she expects a decision to be made on the funding of the Talented Athlete Scholarship Scheme after September 2014.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188852","188852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39118","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how UK Sport's commitment to equality of opportunity, as set out in its Equality and Diversity Strategy, is implemented in its funding decisions.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188853","188853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39119","2014-02-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what measures her Department has in place to ensure that the Arts Council is making appropriate and effective use of Government funds and that is accountable for the expenditure it makes.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188705","188705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39120","2014-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what criteria his Department uses to decide which people will be asked to repay money received under the Financial Retention Incentive scheme.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188681","188681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39121","2014-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people asked to repay money received through the Financial Retention Incentive schemes have previously served in (a) Afghanistan and (b) Iraq.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188682","188682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39122","2014-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have been asked to repay money received as part of the Financial Retention Incentive scheme since 2010; and in which branch of the armed forces each such person served.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188684","188684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39123","2014-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has reclaimed following requests to armed forces personnel to repay money received under the Financial Retention Incentive scheme to date.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188683","188683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39124","2014-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces personnel have been asked to repay in part or in full any money received under the Financial Retention Scheme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188687","188687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39125","2014-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2014, Official Report, column 6, on the Burmese army, what discussions he has had with the Burmese army on (a) investigations into alleged human rights abuses by the army and (b) the need to secure accountability.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188730","188730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39126","2014-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what timetable he has set for the (a) closure and (b) any associated decontamination work of Craigiehall army base  prior to its sale.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188718","188718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39127","2014-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made in identifying potential buyers for Craigiehall army base, Edinburgh.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188737","188737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39128","2014-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 21 November 2014, Official Report, column 56WS, on Police and Guarding Agency, what the future arrangements for the MoD guards service are; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188735","188735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39129","2014-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to help small and medium-sized enterprises enter the competitive tendering process for contracts with his Department.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188773","188773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39130","2014-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) full-time service personnel, (b) reservists and (c) recruits from each of the three armed services have been deployed since 1 February 2014 to support rescue and prevention work following the recent flooding and storms.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188614","188614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39131","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment has he made of the quality of the early years education support available for children diagnosed with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188663","188663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39132","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage early intervention measures for children diagnosed with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188664","188664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39133","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions his Department has had on a training programme for education professionals working with children diagnosed with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188665","188665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39134","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to require exam boards to take account of (a) representations from the child's school and (b) previous schoolwork when assessing the special circumstances tariff they can apply in each particular situation.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188675","188675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39135","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of the training materials available to assist education professionals supporting children and young people diagnosed with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188666","188666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39136","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what provisions his Department has in place to support the parents of children and young people diagnosed with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188667","188667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39137","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the revision to the statutory guidance for schools on fulfilling their duty to secure access to independent careers guidance for their students will be published.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188693","188693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39138","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether state-funded schools use pupils' postcodes to determine individual pupils' target grades.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188621","188621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39139","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding was transferred from the Education Funding Agency (a) to each local authority and (b) in total to assist the education of young people with learning difficulties and disabilities aged between 16 and 25 in the current financial year.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188638","188638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39140","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much each local authority spent on educating young people with learning difficulties and disabilities aged between 16 and 25 in the current financial year.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188639","188639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39141","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he will hold the consultation on new guidelines for home to school transport announced by the Minister for Schools in October 2013.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188850","188850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39142","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will use the findings of the March 2013 Teacher Workload survey to inform (a) current cross union talks, (b) departmental decision-making processes and (c) any further review of existing policies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188764","188764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39143","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the performance of converter academies with schools which are eligible to convert but which have chosen to retain their maintained status.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188757","188757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39144","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2014, Official Report, column 360W, on teachers: surveys, when his Department will complete its analysis of the 2013 Teacher Workforce survey.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188763","188763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39145","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy that school transport for pupils aged 16 and over should become a statutory function for local authorities following the raising of the school leaving age.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188756","188756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39146","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of the community primaries that have had their academy status applications declined by his Department are rated (a) outstanding and (b) good by Ofsted.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188759","188759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39147","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish the 2013 Teacher Workload survey.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188731","188731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39148","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the recommendations of the British Chambers of Commerce Skills and Employment Manifesto published in January 2014.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188728","188728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39149","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish an action plan to address the recommendations of the UN Committee on the Rights of the Child to the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Wright","Simon Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188727","188727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39150","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative assessment he has made of the recent changes in the performance of sponsored academies and low-performing schools which choose to keep maintained status.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188758","188758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39151","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what comparative assessment he has made of the costs of transitting energy to the Grid from combined cycle gas turbine plants in (a) Scotland and (b) the rest of the UK; and what discussions he has had on reducing Government subsidy to such plants in Scotland.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188748","188748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39152","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 239, on energy company charges, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of money suppliers have in credit as a result of direct debit overpayments.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188830","188830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39153","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 239, on energy company charges, what estimate his Department has made of the number of customers who are in credit to their supplier.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188831","188831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39154","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 239, on energy company charges, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of suppliers' policies on refunding credit on consumer accounts in surplus.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188832","188832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39155","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 575W, on energy: prices, what estimate his Department has made of the number non-domestic customers on fixed-price deals.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188845","188845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39156","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 575W, on energy: prices, what estimate his Department has made of the number domestic customers on fixed-price deals.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188846","188846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39157","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 575W, on energy: prices, what estimate his Department has made of the number of non-domestic customers on non-tariff contracts with their energy supplier.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188844","188844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39158","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 575W, on energy: prices, what estimate his Department has made of the average yearly difference in prices between fixed price and standard variable tariffs for domestic consumers.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188843","188843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39159","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of smart meters installed by each energy company in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188774","188774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39160","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what his policy is on the recommendation of the European Council President that binding targets of 40 per cent for energy efficiency and 30 per cent for renewable energy should be set.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188858","188858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39161","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2013, Official Report, column 754W, on the Green Deal scheme, how much of the 200 million allocated to the Green Deal in November 2011 was spent in (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188835","188835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39162","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2013, Official Report, column 754W, on the Green Deal scheme, how much of the 200 million allocated to the Green Deal in November 2011 was budgeted for (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13, (c) 2013-14, (d) 2014-15 and (e) 2015-16.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188834","188834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39163","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the Boiler Replacement Scheme covers houses which use bottled LPG; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188787","188787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39164","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 239, on energy company charges, if he will make it his policy to require suppliers to refund credit on customer accounts.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188833","188833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39165","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the risk of flooding at the site for the new nuclear power plant at Hinkley Point.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188803","188803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39166","2014-03-04","HM Treasury","2014-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he will fix the carbon floor price for the next period.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188726","188726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39167","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when phase two of the Renewable Heat Incentive Grant will be rolled out; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188662","188662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39168","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to ensure that the new Fuel Poverty Target addresses the specific needs of people affected by muscular dystrophy and other neuromuscular conditions.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188676","188676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39169","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had on extending the winter fuel payment to people (a) on the higher rate of disability living allowance for care or mobility and (b) the enhanced rate of personal independence payment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188674","188674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39170","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the number of properties that have disconnected from the gas grid in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188633","188633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39171","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Business Case for the Government's financial support to the Sustainable Forest Landscapes facility  of the World Bank's Biocarbon Fund.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188611","188611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39172","2014-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, in what work streams job losses in the Environment Agency have taken place in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188609","188609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39173","2014-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many job losses there have been in the Environment Agency in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188610","188610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39174","2014-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations he has made to the EU Commission on the UK applying for and drawing down monies from the European Solidarity Fund following the recent flooding and storm damage; and what the deadline is for making any such bid.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188600","188600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39175","2014-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of animals (a) slaughtered in the UK and (b) exported abroad for slaughter in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188661","188661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39176","2014-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what advice he has received on the relative precedence of the provisions (a) enacted in the Government of Wales Act 2006 and (b) proposed in the Water Bill in respect of the right of the Secretary of State for Wales to intervene on issues of water supply to England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188673","188673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39177","2014-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will introduce derogations from the current licensing regime for dredging (a) main and (b) non-main rivers.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188619","188619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39178","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to provide funding for the Derby City flood defence project Our River Our City.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188785","188785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39179","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had on only declaring land to be of flood risk if it is prone to river as opposed to surface water flooding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188786","188786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39180","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the environmental effect of continuous flooding techniques and the use of underground aquifers associated with the fracking process.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188820","188820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39181","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of when the Thames Barrier will need to be (a) upgraded, (b) supplemented and (c) replaced.","Biography information for Dame Joan Ruddock","Dame Joan Ruddock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188746","188746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39182","2014-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the methodology of the joint World Health Organisation and Iraqi Ministry of Health report into birth defects in Iraq.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188849","188849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39183","2014-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any UK Government Ministers or officials had discussions with their US counterparts on the joint World Health Organisation and Iraqi Ministry of Health report into birth defects in Iraq prior to its publication.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188848","188848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39184","2014-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any UK Government Ministers or officials made any representations to the World Health Organisation or Iraqi Ministry of Health on their report into birth defects in Iraq prior to that report's publication.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188847","188847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39185","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Energy Industries Council on the UK Action Plan on Business and Human Rights.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188770","188770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39186","2014-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what categories of people are allowed to leave Homs under the terms of the recent cease-fire agreement.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188626","188626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39187","2014-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the prevalance of religious persecution in Indonesia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188634","188634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39188","2014-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on Israel meeting its obligations under the 2005 Agreement on Movement and Access.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188692","188692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39189","2014-02-25","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of potential logistical difficulties facing refugees from the Syrian conflict applying for asylum in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188592","188592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39190","2014-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the position of Syrian men of military age who are trapped in Homs and are seeking to escape; and what reports he has received on the presence of a route out from the conflict zone.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188593","188593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39191","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent written communication he has received from clinicians and healthcare professionals on the introduction of a meningitis B vaccine.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188612","188612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39192","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether funding for care.data is in place for 2014-15 and future financial years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188587","188587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39193","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the compatability of the care.data programme with current human rights legislation.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188606","188606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39194","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether hospital records will be made available as part of care.data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188607","188607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39195","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to count the number of flying care visits.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188608","188608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39196","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued on the circumstances whereby a Do Not Resuscitate notice may be placed in a patient's file; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188591","188591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39197","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what target he has set of the level of public awareness of care.data before GPs can proceed with the upload of patient data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188586","188586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39198","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he received advice from the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation (JCVI) on the introduction of a meningitis B vaccination programme on the NHS following the JCVI meeting of 11 February 2014.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188613","188613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39199","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NICE on developing new guidelines for diagnosing B12 deficiency including (a) an active B12 test, (b) Methylmalonic Acid tests and (c) assessment of the clinical picture; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188588","188588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39200","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason hospital trusts use a pain score of 1 to 5 for hysteroscopy procedure rather than 1 to 10.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188697","188697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39201","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued on diagnosis and treatment of patients found to have cancer of unknown primary foundation.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188670","188670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39202","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has given to clinical commissioning groups on the number of pain management sessions which should be (a) funded and (b) funded for patients with painful progressive conditions.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188622","188622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39203","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what safeguards exist to protect patients from having Do Not Resuscitate notices placed in their file without their meaningful consent.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188623","188623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39204","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to implement a national screening programme for HIV.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188627","188627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39205","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has funded on male fertility and sperm counts in the last 10 years; and if he will publish the findings of such research.","Biography information for Simon Wright","Simon Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188628","188628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39206","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the reasons are for differences in the rate of (a) diagnosed HIV and (b) proportion of late diagnosed HIV in Leeds compared to the national average; and what steps he is taking to address such differences.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188629","188629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39207","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding his Department has provided to (a) research councils funding animal research and (b) development of non-animal experimentation methods in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188642","188642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39208","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued on the management of autism spectrum disorders within joint strategic needs assessments.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188660","188660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39209","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether patient data extracted as part of the care.data programme will be made available to countries outside the UK.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188605","188605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39210","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request that NHS England installs universal systems to measure differences in the management of cholesterol in primary care in different clinical commissioning groups in England in April 2014.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188659","188659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39211","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mechanisms will be in place in primary care to measure and treat high cholesterol in patients at high risk of premature death from heart disease after April 2014.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188657","188657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39212","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether a NHS Atlas of Variation for Cardiovascular Disease will be published in 2014.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188658","188658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39213","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, under which circumstances (a) the police and (b) the security services will be able to access patient data extracted as part of care.data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188654","188654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39214","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many disclosures of NHS Secondary Uses Service data to non-NHS bodies have taken place in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188655","188655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39215","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many audits of the use of NHS Secondary Uses Service data have been carried out in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188656","188656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39216","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential need and benefits of routinely testing babies at birth for congenital heart disease; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188771","188771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39217","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the annual cost to the NHS of routinely testing babies at birth for congenital heart disease; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188772","188772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39218","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2014, Official Report, column 549W, on surgical dressings,  whether wound dressings were provided free of charge for patients in post-operative care before clinical commission groups were established.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188857","188857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39219","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many term intrapartum deaths occurred each year in the UK since 2008.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188776","188776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39220","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the mortality rate of women aged over 75 in the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188777","188777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39221","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of overall all-age mortality in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188778","188778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39222","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent progress he has made on providing mobility and flexibility in middle grade contracts for doctors.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188819","188819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39223","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on research into (a) oesophageal cancer and (b) other cancers in each of the last five years; and how much his Department will spend on such research in 2014.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188789","188789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39224","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many perinatal deaths occurred within the first week of birth; how many Apgar scores were recorded in respect of such cases; and in how many of these cases neonatal cooling treatment was undertaken in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188779","188779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39225","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the diagnosis and treatment of oesophageal cancer in (a) Hampshire and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188788","188788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39226","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of scarlet fever were treated by the NHS in each region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188802","188802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39227","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he intends to take to raise awareness of oesophageal cancer.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188784","188784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39228","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for the introduction of summary care records for the sharing of patients' records with community pharmacies.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188707","188707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39229","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with its international counterparts on the mandatory fortification of flour with folic acid.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188706","188706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39230","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with UK and European food producers and importers on the mandatory fortification of flour with folic acid.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188708","188708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39231","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects to reach a decision on the mandatory fortification of flour with folic acid.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188709","188709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39232","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential health costs and benefits of the mandatory fortification of flour with folic acid.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188710","188710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39233","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what conditions of public awareness and consent must be met before the care.data extraction of patient data begins.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188729","188729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39234","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the meeting of the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation on 11 February 2014 and the report from the Chief Medical Officer Our Children Deserve Better, if he will ensure that all children in England have access to a meningitis B vaccine.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188824","188824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39235","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost of an emergency ambulance call-out is.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188760","188760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39236","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the care.data database requires patients to opt out rather than opt in.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188739","188739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39237","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of procedures to allow patients to opt out of the care.data database.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188740","188740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39238","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he will take to consult patients and doctors during the six-month delay to the start of care.data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188685","188685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39239","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for a GP appointment in Leeds.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188699","188699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39240","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to make shingles vaccination available to people between the ages of 70 and 79; and what his planned timetable is for achieving that end.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188698","188698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39241","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when Public Health England will publish the modelling work it has undertaken on the effect of increased treatment on averting the future burden of hepatitis C-related end-stage liver disease.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188690","188690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39242","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he will take over the next six months to improve public awareness of care.data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188688","188688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39243","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what process NHS England uses to identify the funds required to treat hepatitis C as set out in the manual for prescribed specialised services in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188689","188689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39244","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received on the mandatory fortification of flour with folic acid.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188711","188711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39245","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential for improved levels of patient safety by allowing pharmacists access to the electronic patient record.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188713","188713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39246","2014-02-25","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times she has met representatives from the Police Federation in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188680","188680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39247","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average cost of an emergency police call out is.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188741","188741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39248","2014-02-25","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of changes in the number of animals used in scientific research as a result of the measures published in Working to Reduce the Use of Animals in Scientific Research.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188733","188733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39249","2014-02-25","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department made of the proposals submitted by the British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection during the preparation of Working to Reduce the Use of Animals in Scientific Research.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188732","188732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39250","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department gives the Independent Police Complaints Commission (IPCC) on handling complaints about an investigation conducted by the IPCC.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188747","188747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39251","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who will represent the UK at the Interpol General Assembly in November 2014.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188799","188799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39252","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with Ministers of the Department for Education regarding children subject to sexual exploitation.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188854","188854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39253","2014-02-25","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many black and ethnic minority officers are employed at chief superintendent level in the police service in England, Wales and Scotland; and what is the total number of chief superintendent posts in the service.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188827","188827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39254","2014-02-25","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many black and ethnic minority officers are employed at superintendent level in the police service in England, Wales and Scotland; and what is the total number of superintendent posts in the service.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188828","188828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39255","2014-02-25","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many black and ethnic minority officers are employed at chief inspector level in the police service in England, Wales and Scotland; and what is the total number of chief inspector posts in the service.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188829","188829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39256","2014-02-25","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many black and ethnic minority officers are currently employed in the police service in England, Wales and Scotland.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188825","188825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39257","2014-02-25","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many black and ethnic minority officers are currently employed in the police service in England, Wales and Scotland at chief police officer level; in which forces they are located; and what is the total number of chief police officer posts in the service.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188826","188826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39258","2014-02-25","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding her Department has provided to (a) research councils funding animal research and (b) development of non-animal experimentation methods in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188640","188640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39259","2014-02-25","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on whether the Syrian conflict is an exceptional situation in relation to asylum and refugee applications.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188625","188625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39260","2014-02-25","Department for International Development","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what provisions are in place to prevent water contamination and provide access to drinking water in Gaza.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188691","188691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39261","2014-02-25","Department for International Development","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the availability of fresh drinking water for Palestinians in Gaza.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188694","188694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39262","2014-02-25","Department for International Development","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure UK aid to Palestinian social assistance programmes is not used to compensate convicted terrorists.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188635","188635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39263","2014-02-25","Department for International Development","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much the Government gives annually in aid directly to the Palestinian authority; and how her Department audits how such money is spent.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188637","188637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39264","2014-02-25","Department for International Development","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the role of UK aid to Palestine in encouraging a climate conducive to achieving a peaceful resolution to the Israel-Palestine conflict.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188636","188636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39265","2014-02-26","Department for International Development","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will place in the Library a copy of each of the partnership agreements between her Department and major UK food and clothes retailers, announced to the London Stock Exchange Group on 27 January 2014.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188851","188851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39266","2014-02-25","Department for International Development","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2014, Official Report, columns 467-8W, on developing countries: abortion, whether the humanitarian principles observed by UK-funded organisations permit the procurement of abortions which are unlawful in the jurisdiction in which the aid is being given; and whether UN Security Council Resolution 2122(2013)imposes additional obligations in any other relevant respect.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188734","188734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39267","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the capacity is of each women's prison in England and Wales.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188761","188761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39268","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on the implementation of the so-called Eve's Law.","Biography information for Mark Reckless","Mark Reckless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188752","188752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39269","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent on preliminary work associated with plans for a new prison at Feltham to date.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188745","188745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39270","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which members of staff holding the positions of (a) Director, (b) Deputy Director, (c) Activities Manager, (d) Head of Reducing Re-offending, (e) Head of Safer Custody, (f) Head of Security, (g) Head of Community Engagement and (h) Head of Performance at the time of HM Prison Oakwood taking its first inmates had previous experience of working in a new prison when it took its first inmates.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188743","188743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39271","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will assess how psychiatric input would improve the Assessment Care in Custody Teamwork process.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188714","188714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39272","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the budget for judges' lodgings was in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14; and how much is so budgeted for 2014-15.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188744","188744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39273","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which members of staff holding the positions of (a) Director, (b) Deputy Director, (c) Activities Manager, (d) Head of Reducing Re-offending, (e) Head of Safer Custody, (f) Head of Security, (g) Head of Community Engagement and (h) Head of Performance at the time of HM Prison Oakwood taking its first inmates had previous experience of (i) working, (ii) less than one year service, (iii) between one and five years service and (iv) over five years working in the prison system.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188742","188742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39274","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many occasions judges' lodgings were used in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188767","188767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39275","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent on judicial pensions in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14; and what estimate he has made of such spending in each of the next five financial years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188768","188768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39276","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent on preliminary work associated with the building of a new prison in Wrexham to date.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188769","188769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39277","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer to the right hon. Member for Delyn, of 6 February 2014, Official Report, column 325W, on freedom of information, if he will (a) compile, (b) publish and (c) maintain in the public domain a comprehensive list of companies wholly owned by more than one public authority which are covered by the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188855","188855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39278","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many places are available in mother and baby units in the custodial estate in England and Wales.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188790","188790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39279","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer to the right hon. Member for Delyn, of 6 February 2014, Official Report, column 325W, on freedom of information, how members of the public can find out whether a company is wholly owned by more than one public authority and covered by the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188856","188856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39280","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many inmates applied for a place in a mother and baby unit in the custodial estate in England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188781","188781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39281","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women are currently held in each women's prison in England and Wales.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188782","188782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39282","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time taken is to determine an appeal of an initial award made by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188602","188602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39283","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent progress the independent medical panels in whiplash cases have made; and what steps he is taking to ensure that interested parties not invited to participate in the Working Group can input into its work and be kept informed of its progress.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188595","188595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39284","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of initial award decisions by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority where the claimant has legal representation are (a) appealed and (b) successfully appealed.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188603","188603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39285","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what homicide services are being funded by his Department to help families bereaved through homicide committed before April 2010.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188616","188616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39286","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the remit and objectives of the working group on independent medical panels in whiplash cases.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188597","188597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39287","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of initial award decisions by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority are (a) appealed and (b) successfully appealed.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188589","188589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39288","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who he has appointed to the working group on independent medical panels in whiplash cases.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188598","188598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39289","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to help families bereaved through homicide after the Homicide Service has finished its work in their case.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188615","188615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39290","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time between application to initial award has been for awards issued by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188590","188590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39291","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he the minutes of any meetings Ministers in his Department have had to discuss independent medical panels in whiplash cases.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188599","188599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39292","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what meetings he of Ministers in his Department have had with (a) solicitors and (b) other parties representing claimants in personal injury cases since January 2013.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188594","188594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39293","2014-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the purpose and composition of any sub-group of the working group on independent medical panels on whiplash cases will be.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188596","188596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39294","2014-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for a place in a mother and baby unit in the custodial estate in England and Wales were (a) accepted and (b) refused in each year between 2010 and 2013.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188783","188783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39295","2014-02-25","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is to ensure that rail companies and station operators are improving access for disabled passengers.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188604","188604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39296","2014-02-25","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what risk assessment was carried out on the proposal for a motorway hard shoulder running on the M25 between junctions 23 and 27; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188669","188669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39297","2014-02-25","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the risk assessments submitted from the (a) Highways Agency and (b) Metropolitan Police on the proposal for a hard shoulder running on the M25 between junctions 23 and 27.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188668","188668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39298","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) net franchise payment and (b) revenue support sums are for the extension of First Capital Connect's Thameslink franchise from 31 March to 14 September 2014.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188801","188801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39299","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of the Highways Agency's budget has been spent on (a) each scheme aimed at improving weather resilience and (b) each scheme responding to additional pressures on roads as a result of climate change in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188800","188800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39300","2014-02-26","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Highways Agency was consulted on the decision to allow the sale and consumption of alcohol in motorway service areas.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188821","188821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39301","2014-02-25","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many extra seats would be created (a) in total and (b) as a proportion of current passenger capacity if double-decker carriages were installed on the West Coast Main Line.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188703","188703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39302","2014-02-25","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to prevent motorcyclists from riding across (a) public areas, (b) community parks and (c) areas of outstanding natural beauty.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188704","188704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39303","2014-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to extend railcard discounts to reservists.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188686","188686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39304","2014-02-25","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the total cost of rolling stock for double-decker carriages on the (a) West Coast Main Line and (b) High Speed 2.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188700","188700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39305","2014-02-25","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to (a) lower the tracks to accommodate double-decker carriages on the West Coast Main Line and (b) heighten tunnels, bridges and catenary where appropriate.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188701","188701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39306","2014-02-25","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the annual cost is to the Highways Agency of the removal of graffiti from its property.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188716","188716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39307","2014-02-25","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the annual cost to Network Rail is of the removal of graffiti from its property.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188717","188717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39308","2014-02-25","Department for Transport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons he approved the High Speed 2 route via Crewe rather than via Stoke-on-Trent; and if he will publish the quantitative and comparison data on both options.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188725","188725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39309","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, column 59W, on personal independence payment, how long the claimant journey was expected to take under the Lot 1 Contract with Atos; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188823","188823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39310","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to introduce an 080 Freephone number for callers to the Child Support Agency and Child Maintenance Service from (a) landlines and (b) mobile telephones.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188719","188719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39311","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total call minutes connected to the Child Maintenance Service has been since December 2012; and what the average time (a) speaking to an adviser and (b) waiting before speaking to an adviser has been in that time.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188720","188720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39312","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department has issued to tribunals on the period of time between a tribunal's decision and the forwarding of their Statement of Reasons to the jobcentre.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188678","188678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39313","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people wait more than (a) three and (b) six months to receive employment and support allowance following a successful tribunal appeal as a result of late receipt by a jobcentre of the Statement of Reasons from the tribunal.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188679","188679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39314","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of new claims for personal independence payment involve a face-to-face consultation assessment.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188702","188702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39315","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in respect of each of the telephone lines run by the Child Support Agency in 2012-13, what the total call minutes (a) connected, (b) speaking to an adviser and (c) on hold awaiting an adviser for each telephone line run by the Child Support Agency was in 2012-13.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188712","188712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39316","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average cost per minute is to telephone the Child Support Agency or Child Maintenance Service from a (a) landline and (b) mobile telephone.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188715","188715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39317","2014-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the structural vacancy rate in London.","Biography information for Baroness Jowell","Dame Tessa Jowell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188766","188766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39318","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received on changes to guidance for the Access to Work scheme on the employment of support workers for disabled people where they are needed on a full-time basis.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188696","188696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39319","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether a person who has successfully appealed a decision to refuse them employment and support allowance (ESA) can only receive their ESA once the jobcentre has received the Statement of Reasons from the Tribunal Service.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188677","188677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39320","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to help women adversely affected by the increase in retirement age to 66 by 2020.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188624","188624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39321","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what definition of disabled is used for the purposes of jobseeker's allowance and employment and support allowance sanctions statistics.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188631","188631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39322","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department's announcement on 27 January 2014, that it will introduce alternative 0345 telephone numbers for its major call lines from March 2014, will include such a number for the (a) Child Support Agency and b) Child Maintenance Service from that date.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188632","188632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39323","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the number of people in England to whom the under-occupancy penalty was incorrectly charged; and what his policy is on the payment of compensation to such people.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188653","188653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39324","2014-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the number and proportion of people over the age 55 who are unemployed in Hartlepool constituency; what change there has been in such figures in each of the last five years; and what steps he is taking to reduce such figures.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188630","188630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39326","2014-02-26","Attorney General","2014-02-21","To ask the Attorney General, how many publications the Law Officers' Departments has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188893","188893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39327","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2013, Official Report, columns 869-70W, on arms trade: trade fairs, what the specific roles and responsibilities are of (a) his Department, (b) other government departments, (c) Clarion Events and (d) other parties for ensuring compliance with and enforcing the Export Control Order 2008 in respect of (i) the Defence and Security Equipment International arms fair and (ii) an alleged breach of arms control legislation at that arms fair in 2013; and if he will place a copy of the memorandum of understanding between his Department's Export Control Organisation and Clarion Events in the Library.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188909","188909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39328","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188892","188892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39329","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of privatising the Student Loans Company on the cost of debts to debtors.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188805","188805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39330","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the proportion of retail products in the UK which are compliant with EU energy efficiency standards.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188791","188791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39331","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what share of the 100 million Enterprise Capital Fund was allocated to Merseyside.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188810","188810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39332","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he will take to ensure that the impartiality of the Land Registry is protected following any privatisation.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188798","188798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39333","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will require the use of non-toxic alternatives to ehtylene glycol in anti-freeze products to reduce toxicity of ingestion by small children and pets.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188904","188904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39334","2014-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to require the addition of a bittering agent to ethylene glycol-based anti-freeze products to prevent ingestion by small children and pets.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188906","188906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39335","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188894","188894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39336","2014-02-26","HM Treasury","2014-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings (a) he, (b) other Ministers of his Department and (c) officials of his Department have had with outside organisations on tax-free childcare since the closure of his Department's consultation on that issue; and which organisations were involved.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188874","188874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39337","2014-02-25","HM Treasury","2014-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188889","188889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39338","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188895","188895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39339","2014-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2014, Official Report, column 418W, on fracking, what estimate he has made of how many local authorities would be willing to host a shale gas site if permitted to retain (a) 100 and (b) 50 per cent of business rates from shale gas production.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188865","188865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39340","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households in (a) Leicester West constituency and (b) the UK are on district council electricity schemes; and how many such properties have gas meters that can no longer be used.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188808","188808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39341","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to support the tourism industries affected by the recent floods; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188816","188816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39342","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with tourism bodies to discuss the floods.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188817","188817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39343","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many publications her Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188896","188896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39344","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, who set the eligibility criteria for the Queen's Diamond Jubilee Medal; and whether consideration was given to making it available to veterans.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188876","188876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39345","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to bring forward legislative proposals to reform the Football Association's rule on football credits in insolvency cases.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188875","188875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39346","2014-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188877","188877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39347","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Gateshead of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 699W, on education: finance, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the annual funding for early education for (a) two and (b) three and four year olds which reaches providers.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188871","188871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39348","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Task and Finish Group for Childminder Agencies last met; and how often that group has met since the introduction of the Children and Families Bill.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188861","188861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39349","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what investigation reports have been carried out by his Department or its agencies into irregularities at academies or free schools; to which schools they relate; and whether and on what date each report was published.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188859","188859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39350","2014-02-26","HM Treasury","2014-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to provide a substantive answer to Question 179832 tabled on 10 December 2013 for answer on 16 December 2013.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188869","188869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39351","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much match funding the Government's 8 million investment in the expansion of early years places in London has generated in each local authority area.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188870","188870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39352","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188878","188878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39353","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of the two year olds within the 20 per cent most disadvantaged group are accessing a free early education place in each (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) local authority area.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188897","188897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39354","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what level of inspection fees for (a) individual childminders and (b) childminder agencies Ofsted are considering; and how much it costs Ofsted to carry out inspections of each type of childcare provision.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188901","188901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39355","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government's 8 million fund to increase supply of early education places in London has been distributed to local authorities; and how much each local authority has received.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188910","188910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39356","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the independent evaluation of the childminder agency pilots will report to his Department; and when the results will be published.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188900","188900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39357","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188879","188879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39358","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the annual energy statement, Official Report, column 1095, 31 October 2013, what recent discussions he has had with suppliers about 24-hour switching.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188836","188836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39359","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the annual energy statement, Official Report, column 1095, 31 October 2013, when he expects 24-hour switching to be in place for all suplliers.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188837","188837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39360","2014-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what consultations he undertook before the announcement in December 2013 of the contribution by the Government of 75 million to the new Sustainable Forest Landscapes initiative of the World Bank's Biocarbon Fund; and what the outcome of those consultations was.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188838","188838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39361","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he will place limits on the amount of excess charges insurance companies can apply to their policies under the Flood Re scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188807","188807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39362","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what financial assistance his Department makes available to enable people to protect homes from flooding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188806","188806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39363","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of fracking techniques on the likelihood of flooding.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188818","188818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39364","2014-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188880","188880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39365","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential contribution of the Flood Awareness Service and Flood Shops proposed by UK Flood Barriers Ltd and their partners in assisting householders to improve individual property protection against flooding.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188872","188872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39366","2014-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 August 2013, Official Report, column 114W, on meat: slaughter, whether he has received the report of the EU Commission study on the methods of slaughter labelling; and what steps he plans to take following that study.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188867","188867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39367","2014-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what depth his Department uses when defining the term deep-sea to determine which areas require special conservation measures; and what steps the Government is taking to (a) protect deep-sea species and habitats and (b) end the most destructive fishing gears at those depths.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188868","188868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39368","2014-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whose responsibility it is to maintain balancing tanks and sustainable urban development systems; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188903","188903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39369","2014-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the government of Israel on the treatment of Palestinian children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188905","188905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39370","2014-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188881","188881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39371","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will use the upcoming session of the Human Rights Council to extend the country-specific human rights monitoring and reporting mechanisms on North Korea and the periodic reports of the Secretary General and the United Nations High Commissioner for Human Rights.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188797","188797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39372","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the kidnap and alleged execution of the Jesuit Priest Father Paolo Dall'Oglio; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188812","188812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39373","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the group Open Doors on the current situation of Christians in Syria.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188814","188814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39374","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of Christians who have fled Syria.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188815","188815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39375","2014-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the consequences of Israel's blockade for Gaza.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188840","188840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39376","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will place alleged crimes against humanity in North Korea on the agenda of the United Nations Security Council.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188794","188794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39377","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss the Report of the Commission of Inquiry on Human Rights in the Democratic People's Republic of Korea with his Chinese counterpart.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188795","188795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39378","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to use the upcoming session of the Human Rights Council to extend the mandate for the Special Rapporteur on the situation of human rights in North Korea.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188796","188796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39379","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the validity and procedural process of elections to clinical commissioning groups in England from the constituent parts making up these bodies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188811","188811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39380","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many publications his Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188882","188882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39381","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with EU institutions on maintaining free consumer access to electronic cigarettes without a prescription.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188862","188862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39382","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2014, Official Report, column 464W, on medical records: databases, whether care.data will be used in improving the care given to individual patients or in improving the overall provision of care.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188866","188866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39383","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will collect statistics on the number of care visits which are shorter than 15 minutes.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188907","188907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39384","2014-02-25","Department of Health","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides on the length of time of care visits.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188908","188908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39385","2014-02-25","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many publications her Department has produced for the purposes of monitoring or promoting staff equality and diversity in each of the last five years; and what the cost of producing such publications was in each such year.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188883","188883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39386","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has to offer asylum to Christians looking to flee the fighting in Syria; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188813","188813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39387","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in prison in the latest period for which data is available served a time longer than their full sentence.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188792","188792"
