"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164364","2014-11-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Indian and Pakistani  counterparts on a resolution to the situation in Kashmir.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215726","215726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164365","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS staff are eligible for incremental pay awards; and how many of those will receive at least (a) one per cent and (b) three per cent pay increases this year.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215716","215716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164366","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on implementing the recommendations of the Berwick report into Improving the Safety of Patients in England, published in August 2013.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215725","215725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164367","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency about the prescription of oral medications for type 2 diabetes that carry an increased risk of hypoglycaemia.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215647","215647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164368","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has conducted on links between aggressive teenage behaviour and the use of violent video games.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215743","215743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164369","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Care Quality Commission's risk register relating to primary care, when primary care practices were informed of their ratings; when national and local media were informed of the ratings relating to specific practices nationally or in their locality; and what rights primary care practices have to appeal against the theoretical assessments undertaken nationally without those specific practices having been inspected or given the opportunity to review the data on which the risk assessment was made.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215717","215717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164370","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to increase the use of patient experience surveys in the NHS to inform patient safety initiatives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215718","215718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164371","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the relationship between cost savings to the NHS and improved patient safety; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215712","215712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164372","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the contribution of 7 November 2014 by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health, Official Report, column 116, what the evidential basis is for the statement that the restraining factor is the lack of information for clinicians about off-label use.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215692","215692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164373","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS staff will receive a one per cent or higher pay award through non-consolidated increases or incremental pay awards this year.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215693","215693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164374","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans NHS England has to consult (a) charities and (b) patients during the two month notice period for de-prioritisation of drugs from the Cancer Drugs Fund list.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215687","215687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164375","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which patient groups and patient representative organisations his Department consulted before publication of Personalised Health and Care 2020: a framework for action.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215651","215651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164376","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he and Ministers in his Department have had with NHS England about the implications for re-evaluating the Cancer Drugs Fund list on breast cancer patients; what the content of those discussions was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215686","215686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164377","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the feasibility of transposition of the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (NICE) Quality Standard on Fertility into a Clinical Commissioning Group (CCG) outcome indicator as a means of encouraging adherence to NICE's recommendation that all CCGs should fund three full cycles of IVF for eligible couples.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215676","215676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164378","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2014 to Question 213785, what the terms of reference are for the Pneumococcal sub-committee's review; if he will place in the Library a copy of the terms of reference of that review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215649","215649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164379","2014-11-27","Department for Transport","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to help prevent drivers with type 2 diabetes losing their licence as a result of hypoglycaemia.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215646","215646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164380","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the rates of (a) pulmonary embolism, (b) blood-stream infection and (c) foreign body left in after procedure has been in England in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215682","215682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164381","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospitals have been rated poor with regards to open and honest reporting of patient safety incidents in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215683","215683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164382","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information (a) his Department and (b) NHS England holds on the cancer survival rate of people aged over 75; how this information is being used to improve cancer survival rates of such people; what assessment his Department has made of the quality if this information; and what steps his Department is taking to improve the quality of this information.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215684","215684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164383","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans NHS England has to consult (a) charities and (b) patients after the Cancer Drugs Fund panel meets on 15 and 16 December 2014 and before decisions on which drugs remain on the Cancer Drugs Fund list are made public.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215694","215694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164384","2014-11-26","Cabinet Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) one year and (b) five year mortality rates are for cancer patients aged over 75 years.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215685","215685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164385","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase investment in pancreatic cancer research in the UK.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215620","215620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164386","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will commission early diagnosis research projects specific to pancreatic cancer.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215621","215621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164387","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve awareness of hypoglycaemia among patients with type 2 diabetes.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215645","215645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164388","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support the Health Research Agency in its efforts to harmonise and streamline the regulation and governance of research in the NHS.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215632","215632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164389","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of physician associate students who go into employment within the NHS after completing their degree.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215637","215637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164390","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason bursary and student loan arrangements are different for science graduates who pursue a further degree in medicine and science graduates who pursue a further degree in physician associate studies.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215638","215638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164391","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many physician associate NHS posts are unfilled.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215639","215639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164392","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will review the Government's funding for pancreatic cancer research following the recommendations of the report, Pancreatic Cancer Research: A roadmap to change, published by the All Party Parliamentary Group on Pancreatic Cancer.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215640","215640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164393","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the recommendations in the report of the All Party Parliamentary Group on Pancreatic Cancer, Pancreatic Cancer Research: A roadmap to change.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215641","215641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164394","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve communication support for people with motor neurone disease.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215757","215757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164395","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what quality and outcome measures NHS England plans to use to ensure maintenance of clinical quality and quality of service in the proposed transition from specialised to clinical commissioning groups commissioning for dialysis.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215753","215753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164396","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce NHS waiting lists for psychological treatments and reduce the number of patients who commit suicide while on such lists.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215745","215745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164397","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment NHS England has made of the level of need for specialist renal services to deal with the complications and emergencies associated with dialysis; and how such services will be commissioned from April 2015.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215754","215754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164398","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department has provided to enable access to chemoprevention drugs in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215755","215755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164399","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence to amend its drug approval system to ensure (a) more cancer drugs and (b) more drugs for cancers of unmet need pass its appraisal process.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215751","215751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164400","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has made to his German counterpart on thalidomide damage in the UK.","Biography information for Sandra Osborne","Sandra Osborne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215750","215750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164401","2014-11-26","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that a person's criminal record as used by the police and the courts includes convictions made under any previous names; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215746","215746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164402","2014-11-26","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what average length of time is taken to process Disclosure and Barring Service applications in each police area.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215752","215752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164403","2014-11-26","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure its services are available online; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215665","215665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164404","2014-11-26","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of changes in the number of anti-Semitic incidents in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215618","215618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164405","2014-11-26","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussion she has had with social media companies about anti-Semitic comments on social media forums.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215619","215619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164406","2014-11-27","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that British nationals living abroad are aware of visa requirements for foreign national spouses when they return to the UK.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215650","215650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164407","2014-11-27","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff have been employed by her Department's press office in each of the last five years; how many such staff were paid more than (a) £40,000, (b) £50,000, (c) £75,000 and (d) £100,000 in each such year; and what the total cost of her Department's press office was in those years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215705","215705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164408","2014-11-27","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many human trafficking investigations have been commenced by the National Crime Agency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215706","215706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164409","2014-11-27","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what public awareness campaigns her Department has run in each of the last five years; how much each such campaign cost; and how much her Department spent on public awareness campaigns in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215728","215728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164410","2014-11-27","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many seasonal staff in the Border Force are employed on zero hour contracts.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215702","215702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164411","2014-11-27","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of changes in the number of seasonal staff in the Border Force on (a) queuing times and (b) customs activities.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215704","215704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164412","2014-11-27","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2014 to Question 210147, what agencies received grants made by central government bodies under the Prevent programme; and whether those grants are included under the central government heading in that Answer.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215729","215729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164413","2014-11-27","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers received financial support in each local authority in England and Wales in (a) 2010 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215713","215713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164414","2014-11-26","Department for International Development","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports or assessments have been commissioned into child protection proceedings in the Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies since 1994; when each such report or assessment was commissioned; which jurisdiction was the subject of each such report or assessment; and which external agency was involved in each case.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215721","215721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164415","2014-11-26","Department for International Development","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that a Gaza donor conference takes place in the near future; and what additional steps she has taken to (a) provide support for Palestinian children and (b) raise the importance of such support with her international counterparts.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215698","215698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164416","2014-11-26","Department for International Development","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect on the health services in developing countries of doctors and nurses being recruited to work in the UK instead of their own country.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215691","215691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164417","2014-11-26","Department for International Development","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much aid has been given to countries affected by the Ebola epidemic in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215624","215624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164418","2014-11-26","Department for International Development","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure its services are available online; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215666","215666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164419","2014-11-26","Department for International Development","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the salary was at each payband used in her Department in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Richard Ottaway","Sir Richard Ottaway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215749","215749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164420","2014-11-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for which written questions tabled by the hon. Member for Shipley in 2014, and answered with a promise to write a letter, a letter has (a) been and (b) not been sent.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215747","215747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164421","2014-11-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure its services are available online; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215667","215667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164422","2014-11-26","Northern Ireland Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps her Department is taking to ensure its services are available online; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215668","215668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164423","2014-11-26","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken to protect synagogues from terrorist attacks.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215744","215744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164424","2014-11-26","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken to reduce the number of sham marriages in the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215733","215733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164425","2014-11-26","Scotland Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps his Department is taking to ensure its services are available online; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215669","215669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164426","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure its services are available online; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215670","215670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164427","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what route options have been considered for the new railway between Bedford and Cambridge.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215633","215633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164428","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much government financial support has been budgeted for cycling initiatives in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215622","215622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164429","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Irish government on the joint operation of the UK and Irish coastguard services.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215724","215724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164430","2014-11-27","Department for Transport","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what reports he has received of operational difficulties arising from the Belfast Coastguard's expanded area of coverage.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215730","215730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164431","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what traffic flow data his Department holds for each section of the A14 in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215697","215697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164432","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vehicles have failed MOT tests because of the removal of diesel particulate filters in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215675","215675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164433","2014-11-27","Wales Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on the operation of cross-border rail services.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215703","215703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164434","2014-11-26","Wales Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent assessment he has made of the case for electrification on the North Wales coast mainline.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215617","215617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164435","2014-11-26","Wales Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps his Department is taking to ensure its services are available online; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215672","215672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164436","2014-11-27","Wales Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have held (i) orally and (ii) in writing with the Welsh Government about the electrification of the North Wales coast mainline.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215643","215643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164437","2014-11-26","Home Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps she has taken to reduce levels of domestic violence.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215627","215627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164438","2014-11-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure its services are available online; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215673","215673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164439","2014-11-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what evaluation his Department has made of the Job Services Australia model for classifying jobseekers; and what consideration he has given to the introduction of that model in the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215635","215635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164440","2014-11-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he responded to the observation of the former EU Commissioner for Employment, Social Affairs and Inclusion in a lecture at Greenwich University on 28 November 2013 that there is room for more ambition on youth employment policies in the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215707","215707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164441","2014-11-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is Department's policy that Jobcentre Plus officials should liaise with Health and Social Service agencies when benefit sanctions are applied to vulnerable individuals.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215708","215708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164442","2014-11-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to reduce poverty among (a) adults and (b) children in Hackney North and Stoke Newington constituency.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215727","215727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164443","2014-11-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2014 to Question 212396, what the mean number is of front line work coaches involved in testing in each stage of user acceptance testing.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215648","215648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164444","2014-11-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many former workers of the Remploy factory in Aberdare are (a) looking for work, (b) currently in work, (c) retired, (d) in receipt of employment and support allowance and (e) in receipt of jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215748","215748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164445","2014-11-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the number of households in the private rented sector which have been evicted by their landlords in retaliation for asking a landlord to improve poor or dangerous conditions in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215758","215758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164446","2014-11-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to protect renters in the private rented sector from being evicted in retaliation for making complaints to landlords about their properties.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215759","215759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164447","2014-11-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what ships have been assigned to Atlantic Patrol Tasking North for what duration in the last five years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215776","215776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164448","2014-11-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are currently billeted with the US Marine Corps at (a) MAG-26, (b) VMFAT-101, (c) MAG-39 and (d) MAWTS-1; and what are their roles.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215777","215777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164449","2014-11-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when each of the initial production batch of four F-35B aircraft will be delivered to the UK.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215778","215778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164450","2014-11-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when HMS Talent and HMS Triumph will be based at HMNB Clyde; and when and where those vessels will be decommissioned.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215779","215779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164451","2014-11-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much ammunition was allocated to courses involving the training of artillery personnel and forward observation officers to call in fire in each year since 31 March 2011; and what the cost of such ammunition was.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215780","215780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164452","2014-11-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many expressions of interest in applying to join the Reserve Forces there were from applicants working in Cardiff South and Penarth constituency in each month since January 2011.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215762","215762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164453","2014-11-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on each long lead item for the Successor submarine; and how much his Department has spent on the Successor submarine programme to date.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215788","215788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164454","2014-11-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Successor submarine will have 12 missile tubes; whether those submarines will be sent on patrol filled with 12 missiles; whether those submarines will be armed with nuclear warheads; and whether those submarines can set sail with empty missile tubes.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215789","215789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164455","2014-11-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate the potential cost of procuring (a) 12, (b) 32 and (c) 48 Trident II D5 missile tubes for the Successor submarines.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215790","215790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164456","2014-11-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 5 of the 2010 Strategic Defence and Security Review, what the saving was to the public purse of reducing the number of operational launch tubes on submarines to eight during the spending review period; and whether the £3.2 billion saving in the 10 years from 2010 was contingent on each Successor submarine having eight missile tubes armed with eight Trident D5 II missiles armed with 40 warheads.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215791","215791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164457","2014-11-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many and what species of non-domestic mammals have been imported to the UK from (a) within and (b) outside the EU in each year since 2010; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215760","215760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164458","2014-11-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to collect information on whether animals imported from (a) inside and (b) outside the EU were bred in captivity or caught from the wild.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215761","215761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164459","2014-11-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take following the recent death of Hasan Al-Shaikh in Bahrain as a result of alleged police torture; and how the use of torture in Bahrain will change his policy towards that country.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215742","215742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164460","2014-11-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the arrest of Zainab Al-Khawaja in Bahrain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215740","215740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164461","2014-11-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the arrest and torture of 13 women in Bahrain for organising a public referendum; and what assessment he has made on the prevalence of the use of torture in Bahrain.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215741","215741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164462","2014-11-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the statements by the government of Iran that that country's nuclear activities are for exclusively civilian nuclear purposes.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215771","215771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164463","2014-11-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the German government on securing funding for British victims of thalidomide.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215770","215770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164464","2014-11-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the recent finding of the UN Working Group on Arbitrary Detention that Tagi Al Maidan is being arbitrarily detained in Bahrain, if he will make representations to the government of that country seeking the release of Mr Al Maidan.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215783","215783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164465","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission an independent inquiry into the performance of acute hospital services in North West London in response to the closure of Hammersmith and Central Middlesex accident and emergency departments.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215786","215786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164466","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will suspend the implementation of his Department's Shaping a Healthier Future programme until NHS England's investigation into the performance of North West London accident and emergency departments is complete.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215787","215787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164467","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's press release dated 28 August 2014, entitled Thousands more patients to benefit from additional £160 million for cancer drugs, whether the funding referred to (a) is new funding for medicines or (b) has been diverted from the purchase of other medicines.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215781","215781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164468","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2014 to Question 215281, how many financial sanctions have been imposed for failure to achieve 95 per cent compliance with Care Programme follow-up within seven days of discharge.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215768","215768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164469","2014-11-27","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of unfilled posts in the mental health workforce in the NHS.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215775","215775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164470","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's publication, Flu Plan Winter 2014, published in April 2014-15, if he will introduce free flu vaccinations to people with learning disabilities on the same terms as for other clinical risk groups.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215772","215772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164471","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage the uptake of the flu vaccine among people with learning disabilities.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215773","215773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164472","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to tackle inequalities in access to mental health services in the BAME community.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215774","215774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164473","2014-11-26","Department for International Development","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports she has received on the humanitarian situation within the civilian population of eastern Ukraine.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215739","215739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164474","2014-11-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department plans to carry out an equality impact assessment on the effect of the new scheme for recall adjudicators proposed in the Criminal Justice and Courts Bill.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215782","215782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164475","2014-11-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the economic effect on small businesses of reforms to funding of insolvency litigation implemented by the Legal Act, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215769","215769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164476","2014-11-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2014 to Question 215057, if he will make an estimate of the Exchequer effect of the change in the number of serious crimes that will now be dealt with by way of the Criminal Justice System rather than the prison disciplinary system.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215784","215784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164477","2014-11-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2014 to Question 215057, whether his Department made an estimate of the cost to the Exchequer of the proposals in the press release entitled, Crackdown on violence in prisons before making that press release.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215785","215785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164478","2014-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2014 to Question 214230, which courts he believes to be over 100 years old.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215767","215767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164479","2014-11-26","Women and Equalities","2014-11-24","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what steps her Department is taking to tackle discrimination of disabled people in the UK workforce.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215738","215738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/165920","2014-11-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to meet the Chief Executive of Premiership Rugby; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 906274","906274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/165931","2014-11-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of mobile phone coverage in rural areas.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 906287","906287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/166046","2014-11-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of whether the level of tribunal fees acts as a disincentive to women bringing a sex discrimination claim.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 906308","906308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/166058","2014-11-27","Women and Equalities","2014-11-24","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what steps her Department has taken to promote the use of role models for women in business.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 906309","906309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/166482","2014-11-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will commission a review of the management and financial structures of British horse racing.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 906284","906284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/166483","2014-11-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for International Development on allegations of abuse of migrant workers working on preparations for international sporting events in Qatar.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 906285","906285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/166484","2014-11-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of when there will be universal broadband coverage in the UK.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 906286","906286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/166485","2014-11-27","Women and Equalities","2014-11-24","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what recent discussions she has had with her international counterparts on protecting the rights of women and girls overseas.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 906316","906316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164111","2014-11-25","Attorney General","2014-11-21","To ask the Attorney General, how many Suspicious Activity Report intelligence packs relating to corruption in which countries the Serious Fraud Office has received from the National Crime Agency in the last four years.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215599","215599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164112","2014-11-25","Attorney General","2014-11-21","To ask the Attorney General, how many requests the Serious Fraud Office has received for mutual legal assistance in relation to corruption from which countries in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215609","215609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164113","2014-11-25","Attorney General","2014-11-21","To ask the Attorney General, on how many occasions the prosecuting authorities have offered a company the opportunity to enter into Deferred Prosecution Agreement negotiations in the last five years.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215607","215607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164114","2014-11-25","Attorney General","2014-11-21","To ask the Attorney General, how many self-reports from companies relating to bribery the Serious Fraud Office has received since its submission to the OECD Phase 3 Report on Implementing the OECD Anti-Bribery Convention, published in March 2012; and how many of those reports relate to (a) current and (b) closed investigations.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215614","215614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164115","2014-11-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how he plans to keep the people who lost money following the failure of firms involved in Scottish Power's cashback warranty scheme updated on progress on the review of whether there will be further investigations of that matter.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215591","215591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164116","2014-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with larger construction firms on the effect of late payments on small and medium-sized enterprises in the sector.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215523","215523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164117","2014-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2014 to Question 213960, what plans he has to meet the Minister of State for Care and Support to discuss minimum wage enforcement in the care sector.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215559","215559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164118","2014-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2014 to Question 213960, where in the Social Care Commitment reference is made to employer compliance with minimum wage legislation.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215560","215560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164119","2014-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2014 to Question 213960, when the review of HM Revenue and Customs service level agreement for national minimum wage enforcement will be concluded.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215561","215561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164120","2014-11-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November 2014 to Question 212005, what assessment he has made of the effect of the length of time for which grants are awarded on the diversity of their recipients.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215537","215537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164121","2014-11-25","Cabinet Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate, based on the annual survey of hours and earnings published on 19 November 2014, the number and proportion of (a) people, (b) men and (c) women in (i) work, (ii) full-time work and (iii) part-time work in each (A) local authority area and (B) parliamentary constituency earning less than the UK living wage in 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215522","215522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164122","2014-11-25","Cabinet Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215564","215564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164123","2014-11-25","Cabinet Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Office of National Statistics plans to publish data on the mortality rate for deaths in 2013 involving (a) C.difficile and (b) MRSA in (i) England and (ii) Wales, by NHS trust.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215524","215524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164124","2014-11-26","Cabinet Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of (a) generalist and (b) technical employees and contract staff in the Government Digital Service are (i) Black and minority ethnic and (ii) female.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215569","215569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164125","2014-11-25","HM Treasury","2014-11-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215583","215583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164126","2014-11-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of the funding provided to local government by central government was ring-fenced in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215612","215612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164127","2014-11-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many properties have been listed as an asset of community value under the provisions of the Localism Act 2011 since that act entered into force.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215565","215565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164128","2014-11-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the oral Answer of 10 November 2014, Official Report, column 1164, on firefighters' pensions, how many hours of training in firefighting the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, the hon. Member for Portsmouth North, completed.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215585","215585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164129","2014-11-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215571","215571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164130","2014-11-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215572","215572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164131","2014-11-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much Arts Council England funding was awarded to organisations in (a) the London Borough of Hackney, (b) London and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215550","215550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164132","2014-11-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations his Department has received from or on behalf of Odyssey Maritime Exploration on regulations pertaining to the management of shipwrecks.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215520","215520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164133","2014-11-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 24 October 2014, whether English Heritage agreed with (a) his decision to allow the Maritime Heritage Foundation to proceed with the next phase of the Project Design and (b) the granting of permission to recover at-risk surface items from the wreck site in accordance with the Project Design.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215515","215515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164134","2014-11-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what meetings he has had with Lord Lingfield since July 2014; who was present at each of those meetings; where each of those meetings was held; and what was discussed at each of those meetings.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215516","215516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164135","2014-11-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will provide a list of the meetings the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State, Lord Astor of Hever, has had with Lord Lingfield since May 2010; who was present at each of those meetings; where each of those meetings was held; and what was discussed at each of those meetings.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215517","215517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164136","2014-11-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department included a provision for oversight when it transferred the deed of gift for HMS Victory.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215518","215518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164137","2014-11-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations his Department has received from or on behalf of Odyssey Maritime Exploration about regulations pertaining to the management of shipwrecks.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215519","215519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164138","2014-11-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215573","215573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164139","2014-11-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2014 to Question 213404, for what reason £14.7 million of the additional costs of the recent training programme for Libyan Armed Forces personnel remain to be negotiated between his Department and the Libyan government.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215597","215597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164140","2014-11-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2014 to Question 213404, when his Department expects to conclude negotiations with the Libyan government about repayment of the remaining £14.7 million of the additional costs of the recent training programme for Libyan Armed Forces personnel.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215598","215598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164141","2014-11-25","Cabinet Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Office has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in his Office since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215574","215574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164142","2014-11-25","Department for Education","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in her Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215575","215575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164143","2014-11-26","Department for Education","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2014 to Question 214915, who the representatives from religious and non-religious communities were that she consulted about proposed content for the new religious studies GCSE.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215570","215570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164144","2014-11-25","Department for Education","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that funding calculations for (a) primary and (b) secondary schools track demand and pupil numbers closely.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215586","215586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164145","2014-11-25","Department for Education","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to prevent and reduce Islamophobia in primary and secondary schools.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215544","215544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164146","2014-11-25","Department for Education","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department took to ensure that primary and secondary schools in England marked anti-bullying week; and what steps her Department is taking to tackle homophobic bullying in schools.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215545","215545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164147","2014-11-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of energy production came from micro-generation in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215566","215566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164148","2014-11-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the size of the pig stock in the (a) Yorkshire and Humber region and (b) UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215567","215567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164149","2014-11-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the size of the dairy herd in the (a) Yorkshire and Humber region and (b) UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215568","215568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164150","2014-11-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in her Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215576","215576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164151","2014-11-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215577","215577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164152","2014-11-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the effectiveness of radio broadcasts to North Korea as a means of engagement with ordinary North Koreans on issues such as human rights.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215562","215562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164153","2014-11-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to implement its objective of improving human rights in North Korea in addition to talks with counterparts in the North Korean government.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215563","215563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164154","2014-11-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2014 to Question 210318, on what date the Embassy informed the Saudi government of the investigation; and by what means it did so.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215613","215613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164155","2014-11-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the government of Turkey regarding their support for the Democratic Union Party (PYD) in Kobane.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215608","215608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164156","2014-11-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of international support for the Nigerian authorities in tackling Boko Haram.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215552","215552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164157","2014-11-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the government of Turkey on  combatting ISIL.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215600","215600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164158","2014-11-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the government of Turkey about (a) relations with Kurds in the region and (b) the Kurdistan Workers' Party; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215601","215601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164159","2014-11-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the government of Russia about reports of heavy weapons, ammunition and personnel entering Ukraine from Russia.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215602","215602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164160","2014-11-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made in the last 12 months to the government of the People's Republic of China on organ harvesting practices in that country.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215521","215521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164161","2014-11-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking with the Malaysia authorities with the aim of preventing inappropriate activity on the wrecks of HMS Repulse and HMS Prince of Wales.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215526","215526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164162","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with stakeholders about the future of the National Cancer Peer Review programme.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215527","215527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164163","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the Health and Social Care Information Centre to lease further procedure data on waiting times for hip and knees treatments; and what the reason for the time taken to release that data is.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215529","215529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164164","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence to assess the clinical and cost-effectiveness of emerging novel antibiotics in order to prove their value and inform the appropriate adoption of such products within the parameters of local and national NHS antibiotic stewardship programmes.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215553","215553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164165","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to develop a long-term replacement for the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215535","215535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164166","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) number of accidents caused by hypoglycaemia annually and (b) cost to the NHS of those accidents.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215536","215536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164167","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence about improving clinical guidelines on managing hypoglycaemia among patients with type 2 diabetes.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215539","215539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164168","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulance calls outs there have been that involved patients with type 2 diabetes suffering hypoglycaemia in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215540","215540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164169","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2014 to Question 212409, whether any clinical policies developed in the last three years have not followed this process.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215616","215616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164170","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) doctors and (b) nurses (i) began and (ii) completed their qualifications in each of the last 20 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215610","215610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164171","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many UK citizens who trained to be nurses left the profession before their retirement age in each of the last 20 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215611","215611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164172","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will assess the effect that the creation of a centrally maintained list of priority pathogens would have on encouraging innovation within the field of antibiotic research and development.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215593","215593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164173","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when it was decided to delay the publication of winter pressure weekly reports.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215603","215603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164174","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any NHS and Foundation Trusts have submitted data to NHS England for winter pressure weekly reports.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215604","215604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164175","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward proposals to regulate the Physicians' Associate profession.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215605","215605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164176","2014-11-26","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward proposals to regulate health visitors and entry to that profession.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215606","215606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164177","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215578","215578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164178","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons prescriptions for blood-testing strips are being refused or restricted for individuals with diabetes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215555","215555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164179","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue guidance to GPs to remind them that prescriptions for blood-testing strips should not be restricted for other than clinical reasons.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215556","215556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164180","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of diabetics who have had prescriptions for blood-testing strips withdrawn or restricted.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215557","215557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164181","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will take steps to make blood-testing strips more widely available for individuals with diabetes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215558","215558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164182","2014-11-25","Cabinet Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the rate of cancer survival is in hospitals in (a) East London NHS Foundation Trust, (b) London and (c) England.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215546","215546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164183","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to address difficulties of access to off-patent drugs.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215525","215525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164184","2014-11-25","Home Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce homophobic hate crime; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215547","215547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164185","2014-11-25","Home Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests and prosecutions related to homophobic hate crime there have been in (a) Greater London, (b) the London Borough of Hackney and (c) England since 2004.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215548","215548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164186","2014-11-25","Home Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of homophobic hate crime have been recorded by the Metropolitan Police in (a) Greater London, (b) the London Borough of Hackney and (c) England since 2004.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215549","215549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164187","2014-11-25","Home Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in her Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215579","215579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164188","2014-11-26","Home Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what (a) the budget and (b) staffing is for the Police ICT Company in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215531","215531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164189","2014-11-25","Home Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of Islamophobic hate crime were recorded by the police in (a) Greater London, (b) Hackney and (c) England in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215542","215542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164190","2014-11-25","Home Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce Islamophobic hate crime; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215543","215543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164191","2014-11-25","Home Office","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests and prosecutions there have been for Islamophobic hate crime in (a) Greater London, (b) Hackney and (c) England in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215541","215541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164192","2014-11-25","Department for International Development","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in her Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215580","215580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164193","2014-11-25","Department for International Development","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answers of 21 October 2014 to Questions 210509 and 23 October 2014 to Question 211186, what measures are in place for oversight of her Department's aid allocation.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215615","215615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164194","2014-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215581","215581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164195","2014-11-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on the effect of the reforms to insolvency litigation in Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 on tackling director misconduct and the return of money owed to small businesses.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215538","215538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164196","2014-11-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the announcement of 2 September 2014 on armed forces learning, what the cost was to (a) the public purse and (b) 10 Downing Street of (i) commissioning and (ii) producing the British Armed Forces Learning Resource 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215551","215551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164197","2014-11-25","Department for Transport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215582","215582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164198","2014-11-25","Department for Transport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department provides the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency on sharing citizens' data with (a) insurance companies and (b) other organisations which are outside government.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215592","215592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164199","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many coastguards have left the service since the Coastguard Reform programme began; and how many entrants to the Coastguard service there have been in that period.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215589","215589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164200","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what levels of staffing the Maritime and Coastguard Agency had in place at the Maritime and Coastguard Agency Maritime Operations Centre at Fareham on 1 November 2014; and what levels of staffing the Agency expects to be in place at the Maritime and Coastguard Agency Maritime Operations Centre at Fareham in (i) January 2015 and (ii) March 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215596","215596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164201","2014-11-25","Department for Transport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how each new grade on which new entrants to the Coastguard Service are employed compares with the mainstream, non-maritime Civil Service equivalents.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215588","215588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164202","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of staff currently employed at the Maritime and Coastguard Agency Maritime Operations Centre at Fareham (a) received the amount of training and (b) attained the level of qualification required in order to carry out their duties when the centre takes on its full operational responsibilities in December 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215590","215590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164203","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the employment grades are of (a) coastguards who have left the service since the Coastguard Reform programme began and (b) new entrants to the Coastguard service in that same period at the time of their first employment.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215594","215594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164204","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many hours of shift time were staffed below risk-assessed level at (a) Humber, (b) Belfast, (c) Liverpool, (d) Swansea and (e) Dover maritime rescue coordination centres in October 2014.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215595","215595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164205","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department provides to the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency on driving and hypoglycaemia.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215533","215533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164206","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to enable people to request that data referring to them held by the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency is not shared with organisations outside government.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215532","215532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164207","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department provides to the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency about oral medication for type 2 diabetes and the risk of hypoglycaemia.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215534","215534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164208","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2014 to Question 213231, what Digital by Default Service his Department has developed; and what Assisted Digital support is in place for each such service.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215530","215530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164209","2014-11-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2014 to Question 209437, what the limit is on the transfer fee included in the procurement agreement; and what the costs of that fee are.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215554","215554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164210","2014-11-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to encourage recipients of universal credit to use jam jar accounts.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215528","215528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164211","2014-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to reduce poverty among adults and children in (a) London and (b) the London Borough of Hackney.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215587","215587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164212","2014-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on transporting, installing and removing works of art from the Government Art Collection for the display of artwork in his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215584","215584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156911","2014-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions under legislation prohibiting alcohol sales to intoxicated persons there have been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215475","215475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156912","2014-11-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on what occasions have (a) EU companies seeking to trade in the US and (b) US companies seeking to trade in the EU claimed to have been discriminated against by the courts of the host nation in the last five years.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215459","215459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156913","2014-11-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on financial redress for creditors from April 2015 of changes to funding of insolvency litigation in the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215424","215424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156914","2014-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will list all meetings between Ministers in his Department and representatives of Kuwaiti defence companies in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215411","215411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156915","2014-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what meetings (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have had with Bayer plc in the last five years.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215405","215405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156916","2014-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on the effect of the changes to insolvency litigation in the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 on the Government's ability to tackle director misconduct.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215435","215435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156917","2014-11-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the future of the Post Office card account after March 2015.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215421","215421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156918","2014-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will list all meetings between Ministers in his Department and representatives of Qatari defence companies in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215409","215409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156919","2014-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received form private sector mail delivery companies on delivering mail in urban areas of the UK; and what assessment he has made of the effect of such proposals on the Royal Mail's ability to deliver Universal Service Provision in rural areas.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215390","215390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156920","2014-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Statement of 7 April 2014 on higher education student support: changes to Disabled Students' Allowance (DSA), what assessment he has made of the effect of the changes announced in that statement on (a) the level of non-medical support given to students in higher education and (b) decision by disabled students to enter or remain in higher education.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215511","215511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156921","2014-11-24","Cabinet Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the value was of Government procurement with small and medium-sized enterprises in each financial year from 2010-11.","Biography information for Baroness Burt of Solihull","Lorely Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215371","215371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156922","2014-11-25","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much and what proportion of the total annual expenditure of the European Insurance and Occupational Pensions Authority was spent on activities relating to the motor insurance market in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215381","215381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156923","2014-11-25","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much and what proportion of the total annual expenditure of the Prudential Regulation Authority was spent on activities relating to the motor insurance market in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215382","215382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156924","2014-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much and what proportion of the total annual expenditure of the Competition and Markets Authority was spent on activities relating to the motor insurance market in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215383","215383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156925","2014-11-25","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much and what proportion of the total annual expenditure of the Financial Conduct Authority was spent on activities relating to the motor insurance market in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215384","215384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156926","2014-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much and what proportion of the total annual expenditure of the Financial Reporting Council was spent on activities relating to the motor insurance market in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215385","215385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156927","2014-11-24","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much and what proportion of the total annual expenditure of the Financial Services Consumer Panel was spent on activities relating to the motor insurance market in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215392","215392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156928","2014-11-27","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to create a powerhouse for Birmingham and the West Midlands.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215379","215379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156929","2014-11-25","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on measures to improve the EU's response to money laundering and terror financing.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215387","215387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156930","2014-11-25","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many investigations into money laundering have been initiated by the Financial Conduct Authority in each of the last five years; and how many such investigations have led to enforcement action.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215388","215388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156931","2014-11-24","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much HM Revenue and Customs is planning to pay to National Savings and Investments to administer the proposed childcare payments scheme.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215400","215400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156932","2014-11-24","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what review his Department has conducted of the financial arrangements of the funding for the Hinkley C nuclear plant.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215441","215441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156933","2014-11-24","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) maximum and (b) average number of call options a customer can choose from when making a telephone call to HM Revenue and Customs' customer service helpline.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215457","215457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156934","2014-11-24","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average holding time has been for calls made to HM Revenue and Customs' customer service helpline in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215455","215455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156935","2014-11-24","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many operators were employed to answer calls made to HM Revenue and Customs' customer service helpline in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215456","215456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156936","2014-11-25","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households were subject to reductions in child benefit because of an apprentice aged under 18 being in the household in 2013-14.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215478","215478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156937","2014-11-25","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Financial Conduct Authority last reviewed the performance of banks in managing high risk money-laundering situations.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215484","215484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156938","2014-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken to assist communities affected by the winter floods as a result of the decisions of the Ministerial Recovery Working Group.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215491","215491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156939","2014-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much of the Severe Weather Recovery Scheme awarded to local authorities for costs incurred during the winter floods has been (a) allocated to and (b) received by local authorities.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215490","215490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156940","2014-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much of the Business Rates Relief Fund for flooded businesses has been (a) allocated to local authorities and (b) received by businesses.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215500","215500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156941","2014-11-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much of the £10 million support for small and medium-sized enterprises for clean-up in flooded areas has been (a) allocated and (b) received by small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215502","215502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156942","2014-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households have received a repair and renew grant intended for homeowners and businesses which were flooded in winter 2013-14.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215503","215503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156943","2014-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much of the Council Tax Relief Fund for people whose homes have been flooded has been (a) allocated to local authorities and (b) received by residents.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215506","215506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156944","2014-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to announce the Government's response to the consultation on the future of local welfare assistance schemes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215508","215508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156945","2014-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the role of his Department is in overseeing the compliance of local authorities with rules governing fair competition when awarding contracts for the development of public land.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215428","215428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156946","2014-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received on the award by GLA Land and Property Limited of the contract for commercial development of the Royal Albert Dock site to Advanced Business Park.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215429","215429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156947","2014-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the gender pay gap for employees of local authorities in (a) Stoke Newington and Hackney North constituency, (b) Hackney local authority area, (c) London and (d) England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215368","215368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156948","2014-11-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much of the Tourism Industry Fund for Businesses in flood affected parts of England has been (a) allocated to local authorities and (b) received by businesses.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215504","215504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156949","2014-11-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much of the Flood Relief for Sport has been (a) allocated to local authorities and (b) received by sports facilities.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215501","215501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156950","2014-11-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many housing adaptations his Department has carried out for wounded service personnel in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215480","215480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156951","2014-11-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department takes to monitor the safety and performance of the UK's nuclear deterrent and weapons programme.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215481","215481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156952","2014-11-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what research his Department has conducted or reviewed into the effect of military naval sonar on the navigation of whales and other cetaceans since 2004.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215488","215488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156953","2014-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces personnel have been prescribed Lariam or Mefloquine in each year since 2000; how many such soldiers have reported (a) hallucinations, (b) psychosis and (c) suicidal thoughts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215391","215391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156954","2014-11-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which other (a) NATO and (b) non-NATO nations are investing in defence assets in the Hebrides.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215437","215437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156955","2014-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Afghan interpreters served alongside the British Army in the last 12 months of operations in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215465","215465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156956","2014-11-25","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list all meetings between Ministers in his Department and representatives of Kuwaiti defence companies in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215410","215410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156957","2014-11-25","Department for Education","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) primary and (b) junior schools in Heywood and Middleton constituency have class sizes in excess of 30 pupils.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215476","215476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156958","2014-11-24","Department for Education","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2014 to Question 213558, when her Department's guidance on the impact of the 2014 EU Procurement Directives on the procurement by local authorities of school places for children and young people with special educational needs will be published.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215427","215427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156959","2014-11-24","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the number of professional social work placements, excluding the Step-Up and Frontline programmes, required in 2014-15; and how many places it expects to be provided by (a) local authorities, (b) third sector organisations and (iii) other organisations.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215399","215399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156960","2014-11-24","Department for Education","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to encourage increased female representation in (a) science and technology and (b) other traditionally male-dominated sectors; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215369","215369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156961","2014-11-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of households in fuel poverty in (a) Pendle constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215375","215375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156962","2014-11-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the cost of extending the Warm Homes Discount to park home residents.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215425","215425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156963","2014-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what instances there have been of well integrity failure at onshore oil and gas drill sites operated by Cuadrilla Resources in the UK since 2011; what the nature of such instances were; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215513","215513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156964","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she has found a joint venture partner for the Food and Environment Research Agency; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215498","215498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156965","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has spent on reducing nitrogen dioxide and improving air quality in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215499","215499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156966","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department plans to spend on capital investment to improve flood defences in each year from 2015-16 to 2020-21.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215496","215496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156967","2014-11-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many of the 890 flood defences damaged as result of the winter floods in 2013-14 have been repaired to date.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215512","215512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156968","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which Ministers in her Department have received media or communication training paid for by her Department.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215497","215497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156969","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of the Support for Fisherman Fund to replace lost and damaged fishing gear has been received by fishermen and businesses to date.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215492","215492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156970","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when her Department plans to make a final decision on the preferred bidder for the joint venture partner for the Food and Environment Research Agency.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215493","215493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156971","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of the Farming Recovery Fund to cover the cost of restoration of agricultural land following the winter floods has been received by farmers and businesses to date.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215494","215494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156972","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department spent on the implementation of badger culls for bovine TB control, and the costs to police forces of these culls in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215462","215462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156973","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department spent on bovine TB control in (a) 2010-11 and (b) 2011-12.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215461","215461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156974","2014-11-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Environment Agency has investigated any potential or actual cases of water contamination at onshore oil and gas drilling sites operated by Cuadrilla Resources since 2011; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215514","215514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156975","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the use of antibiotics in farm animals is strictly for therapeutic purposes.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215507","215507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156976","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to respond to the International Panel on Climate Change's report entitled Climate change 2014: Impacts, adaption and vulnerability.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215495","215495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156977","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will review Marine Management Organisation policy on unannounced visits and inspections.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215374","215374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156978","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what bids her Department has received from the private sector to be a joint venture partner for the Food and Environment Research Agency.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215463","215463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156979","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to bring forward legislative proposals to repeal the Hunting Act 2004 this session.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215464","215464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156980","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will meet representatives of the Woodland Trust and Country Living magazine to discuss a register of England's most important trees.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215453","215453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156981","2014-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has received on the Woodland Trust and Country Living magazine's campaign for a register of England's most important trees; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215454","215454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156982","2014-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received of theft of metal and other valuable items from HMS Repulse and HMS Prince of Wales which were sunk off the coast of Malaysia in December 1941.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215466","215466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156983","2014-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of British ambassadors and high commissioners were educated at (a) private school, (b) state school, (c) the universities of Oxford and Cambridge and (d) other universities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215445","215445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156984","2014-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress he has made on reopening HM Embassy in Tehran.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215450","215450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156985","2014-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Iranian counterpart on the case of Ghoncheh Ghavami.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215448","215448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156986","2014-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of how many members of his Department's advisory board on the appointment of ambassadors and high commissioners were educated at (a) private school, (b) state school, (c) the universities of Oxford and Cambridge and (d) other universities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215447","215447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156987","2014-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help end the practice of breast-ironing in Western, Eastern and Central African countries.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215394","215394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156988","2014-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of Iran's financial and material support for Hamas.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215509","215509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156989","2014-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when HM Embassy in Tehran will be reopened.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215451","215451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156990","2014-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what issues remain to be addressed before the Government can reopen HM Embassy in Tehran.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215452","215452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156991","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish his response to the Law Commission Review of the Regulation of Health Care Professionals published in April 2014; and what his policy is towards the proposal that the Nursing and Midwifery Council should close the specialist public health nursing part of their register.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215479","215479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156992","2014-11-24","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the forecast of a £29 million deficit for Kings College Hospital; and what steps he is taking to protect health services in Bromley.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215449","215449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156993","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he issues on the commissioning of novel antibiotics designed to treat life-threatening infections at a national level through NHS England's specialised commissioning system.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215485","215485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156994","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Government's response to the House of Commons Science and Technology Committee report, Ensuring access to working antimicrobials, Cm, 8919, whether his Department is working on potential alternative pricing and reimbursement mechanisms for novel antibiotics in advance of the conclusion of the O'Neill Review; and what plans he has to explore new funding mechanisms with industry in the interim.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215487","215487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156996","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps NHS England has taken to ensure a safe transition of responsibility for dialysis commissioning to clinical commissioning groups from April 2015.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215402","215402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156997","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have had with Bayer plc in the last five years.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215403","215403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156998","2014-11-24","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what dates since 2 July 2014 he has discussed with charities the use of off-patent drugs for new indications; and what the content of these discussions was.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215396","215396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156999","2014-11-24","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice or research his Department has commissioned from external bodies on the potential effects on the NHS of the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215373","215373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157000","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training and educational support will be provided by NHS England to commissioners in clinical commissioning groups to assist them in effectively commissioning dialysis from April 2015.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215404","215404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157001","2014-11-24","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the gender pay gap for employees of NHS England in (a) Stoke Newington and Hackney North constituency, (b) Hackney local authority area, (c) London and (d) England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215370","215370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157002","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to negotiate an agreement on the price of the vaccine for meningococcal B.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215474","215474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157003","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made by NHS England of the specialist skills and knowledge required to commission dialysis.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215401","215401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157004","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse was of prescriptions issued for paracetamol in England in each of the last two years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215406","215406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157005","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions have been issued for paracetamol in England in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215407","215407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157006","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve mental health services for young people.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215408","215408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157007","2014-11-25","Cabinet Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of lung cancer patients survived for at least two years after diagnosis in each foundation trust area in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215436","215436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157008","2014-11-24","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue guidance to hospitals so that a case of E.coli bacteria triggers the procedures that would be followed if a case of MRSA were discovered.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215426","215426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157009","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in (a) each surgery in the North Derbyshire Clinical Commissioning Group area and (b) each Clinical Commissioning Group area in England were unable to get a GP appointment within 48 hours in each month since 2010.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215434","215434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157010","2014-11-25","Department of Health","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of lung cancer patients in each foundation trust area received radiotherapy treatment in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215440","215440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157011","2014-11-24","Home Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an estimate of what it would have cost to have continued paying police widows' pensions to those widows or widowers who lost their serving husbands or wives between 1987 and 2006, before officers had the option to opt in to a scheme which permitted payments to continue to a surviving spouse on remarriage.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215397","215397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157012","2014-11-24","Home Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will amend visa regulations affecting citizens of Australia and New Zealand to allow them to stay in the UK.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215446","215446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157013","2014-11-24","Home Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to answer Question 214026, tabled by the hon. Member for Newport West on 10 November 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215443","215443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157014","2014-11-25","Home Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department expects to be shown successive versions of the final report and associated documents in the historic child abuse inquiry.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215413","215413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157015","2014-11-25","Home Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Suspicious Activity Reports relating to the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002 have been submitted to the National Crime Agency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215386","215386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157016","2014-11-25","Home Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2014 to Question 213850, what estimate she has made of the total number of vehicles entering the UK which were not subject to screening by either body scanning machines or dogs in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215376","215376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157017","2014-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to publish the Macur Report before May 2015.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215377","215377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157018","2014-11-24","Home Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will commission a study to establish the prevalence of breast-ironing in the UK amongst the Western, Eastern and Central African disapora communities.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215393","215393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157019","2014-11-25","Department for International Development","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff worked in her Department's central disability team in (a) June 2014 and (b) November 2014.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215389","215389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157020","2014-11-24","Department for International Development","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department is doing to help end the practice of breast-ironing in Western, Eastern and Central African countries.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215395","215395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157021","2014-11-25","Department for International Development","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has appointed a senior disability champion for her Department.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215378","215378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157022","2014-11-24","Department for International Development","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to the government of Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215422","215422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157023","2014-11-24","Department for International Development","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to provide further support to the government of Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215423","215423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157024","2014-11-24","Department for International Development","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the Public Private Infrastructure Advisory Facility budget has been spent on (a) private and (b) public schemes for energy infrastructure in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215460","215460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157025","2014-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on the future of Hindley Young Offender's Institute.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215510","215510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157026","2014-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, by what date officials carrying out the youth offending team stock take, announced by the Minister for Prisons, Probation and Rehabilitation on 17 November 2014, are to report.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215430","215430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157027","2014-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the job titles are of the officials from his Department who will be responsible for carrying out the fieldwork for the youth offending team stock take, announced by the Minister for Prisons, Probation and Rehabilitation on 17 November 2014.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215433","215433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157028","2014-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data will be recorded in the youth offending team stock take, announced by the Minister for Prisons, Probation and Rehabilitation on 17 November 2014, aside from the data currently provided quarterly to the Youth Justice Board.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215431","215431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157029","2014-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria will be used to decide which youth offending teams will be assessed as part of the youth offending team stock take, announced by the Minister for Prisons, Probation and Rehabilitation on 17 November 2014.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215432","215432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157030","2014-11-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the findings of the recent report by HM Inspectorate of Prisons on HMP Hewell.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215380","215380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157031","2014-11-24","HM Treasury","2014-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Annex to the communiqué published following the G20 Summit in Brisbane in November 2014, what steps the Government is taking to implement the call for the inclusion of strengthened collective action and pari passu clauses in international sovereign bonds and for their use to be actively promoted by the international community and private sector.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215372","215372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157032","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to bring scooters and motorcycles under present regulations on low emission zones.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215439","215439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157033","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2014 to Question 211928, what discussions his Department has had with its Scottish counterpart on the Rosyth-Zeebrugge freight service operated by DFDS and that company’s announcement on the viability of that route following the introduction of the sulphur dioxide emission regulations.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215415","215415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157034","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve daytime and overnight facilities for road freight drivers.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215438","215438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157035","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has been made of the potential effect on (a) employment, (b) maritime freight volumes and (c) passenger numbers at UK ports on the (i) North Sea, (ii) Channel and (iii) Irish Sea from the European Commission's Draft Regulation on market access to port services and the financial transparency of ports.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215398","215398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157036","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2014 to Question 211928, what recent progress has been made with the European Commission over the scope for State Aid in respect of ferry routes from the UK which are deemed to be vulnerable as a result of the new international and EU sulphur regime; and what his policy is on the linking of such provision to (a) employment and (b) training for UK-based seafarers.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215416","215416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157037","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2014 to Question 211928, which ferry routes from the UK are deemed to be vulnerable as a result of the introduction of new international and European Union sulphur regimes.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215417","215417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157038","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2014 to Question 211928, if he will make it his policy to make the provision of financial assistance from domestic public sources to shipping companies for compliance costs associated with the imminent sulphur dioxide emission regulations contingent upon guarantees of (a) employment and (b) training for UK-based seafarers.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215418","215418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157039","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2014 to Question 211928, which shipping companies have (a) applied for and (b) received funds from the Trans-European Network programme for meeting the costs of compliance with new regulations on sulphur dioxide emissions from shipping.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215419","215419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157040","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether risk-assessed staffing levels have changed at any maritime rescue co-ordination centre in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215468","215468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157041","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions each maritime rescue co-ordination centre (MRCC) has called on other MRCCs to provide mutual support under established pairing arrangements in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215470","215470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157042","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Maritime and Coastguard Agency is taking to retain the specialist knowledge, skills and experience of staff in those maritime rescue co-ordination centres scheduled to close.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215469","215469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157043","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2014 to Question 211928, what funding has been secured to date from the Trans-European Network (TEN-T) programme to help shipping companies operating from UK ports to meet the cost of acquiring sulphur dioxide abatement technologies; and what proportion of such funding has been allocated to (a) each innovative technology and (b) infrastructure for liquefied natural gas bunkering to date.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215458","215458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157044","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many and what proportion of occasions each maritime rescue co-ordination centre (MRCC) has been unable to help another MRCC requesting mutual support in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215471","215471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157045","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether those maritime rescue co-ordination centres that are scheduled to close will remain fully operational until their closure.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215472","215472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157046","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans the Maritime and Coastguard Agency has to (a) relocate and (b) decommission equipment in those maritime rescue co-ordination centres scheduled to close.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215473","215473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157047","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much of the funding made available to improve rail resilience to flooding has been (a) allocated to Network Rail and (b) spent to date.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215505","215505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157048","2014-11-26","Department for Transport","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assistance the Government is providing to port companies and shipping operatives in responding to the introduction of the EU low-sulphur fuel regulation.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215489","215489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157049","2014-11-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to provide (a) assistance and (b) guidance for employers to help them provide flexible and high quality part-time work for women with young children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215367","215367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157050","2014-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to improve the performance of the Work Programme for jobseekers aged over 50.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215477","215477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157051","2014-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage employers to implement the living wage; and what estimate he has made of the number of employees who earn less than the living wage.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215412","215412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157052","2014-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were recorded as being unemployed under the jobseeker's allowance criteria in each year for which information is available; and how many people were taken off jobseeker's allowance as a result of their partner's income in each of those years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215444","215444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157053","2014-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been paid in sanctions applied to jobseekers' allowance claimants in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215467","215467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157054","2014-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people (a) were eligible for and (b) participated in the Work Programme in each parliamentary constituency in the East of England in each month since October 2012.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215442","215442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157055","2014-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with ministerial colleagues on the future of the Post Office card account.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215420","215420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157056","2014-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has given to local authorities on supporting vulnerable residents after his Department's funding for local welfare assistance schemes ends in April 2015.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215414","215414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157057","2014-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2014 to Question 213491, how many representations he has received on the future of the winter fuel allowance claimed by UK citizens living in mainland France on a UK state pension.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215482","215482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157058","2014-11-25","Cabinet Office","2014-11-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many new jobs have been created in each parliamentary constituency in the East of England since October 2012.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215486","215486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/157059","2014-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2014 to Question 213491, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals on amending the eligibility criterion derived from average winter temperatures.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215483","215483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156582","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission research on (a) innovative pathways to diagnose cancer earlier and (b) encouraging the use of such pathways in the NHS.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215202","215202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156583","2014-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page Ev 94 of Attachment 1 to the written evidence submitted by the British Pugwash Group, in the Sixth Report of the Foreign Affairs Committee, Session 2009-10, Global Security: UK-US relations, HC 114, on what occasions and for what purposes US nuclear weapons laboratories have used experimental facilities at the UK Atomic Weapons Establishment at Aldermaston to conduct tests that were prohibited in the US.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215163","215163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156584","2014-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department holds details on the total annual value of welfare benefits claimed in each EU member state by British citizens.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215270","215270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156585","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to impose a statutory obligation on the employers of home care workers to provide free influenza vaccinations to their home care employees.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215142","215142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156586","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will require it to be a condition of commissioning home care provision that employers of home care workers pay for influenza vaccinations for their domiciliary workforce.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215143","215143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156587","2014-11-21","HM Treasury","2014-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 17 November 2014, Official Report, column 49, what workarounds the Government is proposing so that Argentina can avoid technical default without paying vulture funds in full.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215171","215171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156588","2014-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what use his Department has made of the National Wellbeing Index introduced by the Office for National Statistics since its introduction in 2011; and what the principal policies are that his Department has introduced to improve the wellbeing of Britain's armed forces and veterans since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215315","215315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156589","2014-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of local housing allowance and shared accommodation rate on the density of young people living in houses of multiple occupation in seaside towns.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215164","215164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156590","2014-11-21","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-11-19","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what registration rate was achieved by use of (a) Department for Work and Pensions and (b) local authority data matching in the confirmation dry run; and what rate was achieved by using all levels of data matching in the confirmation live run.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215316","215316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156591","2014-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps are being taken to ensure that UK visitors to Egypt are aware of the dangers of H5N1 bird flu virus.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215219","215219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156592","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what studies he has commissioned on the potential benefits of using dogs to establish early signs of cancer in humans.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215220","215220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156593","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with hon. Members from Sinn Fein and the SDLP on the National Crime Agency in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215221","215221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156594","2014-11-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent conversation he has had with Ofcom on the introduction of a gaining provider-led switching system in the mobile sector.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215197","215197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156595","2014-11-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on consumers of the implementation of a gaining provider-led switching system in the mobile sector.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215198","215198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156596","2014-11-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to support the introduction of gaining provider-led switching systems since the publication of his Department's report, Connectivity, Content and Consumers in July 2013.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215247","215247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156597","2014-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2014 to Question 211635, what progress he has made on reviewing the cost-benefit analysis of the recruitment and training of minors; and when he plans to publish that report.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215248","215248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156598","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) target and (b) actual average waiting time for asylum seekers to receive an appointment for an initial screening interview is.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215259","215259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156599","2014-11-21","Department for Transport","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the minimum manning levels are for each Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215225","215225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156600","2014-11-21","Department for Transport","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the minimum manning levels are for the Maritime Operations Centre in Fareham.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215226","215226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156601","2014-11-24","Department for Education","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to ensure consistency between marking and remarking of A levels; and what recourse is available to students who have missed out on university places due to variable grade marking.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215238","215238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156602","2014-11-21","Cabinet Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate how many (a) men and (b) women in (i) full-time and (ii) part-time employment in each parliamentary constituency earned less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage in (A) 2013 and (B) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215207","215207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156603","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2014 to Question 210999, if he will publish the timetable for his further consideration of the collection of data on people registering as visually impaired who are veterans.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215161","215161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156604","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to include an option to identify vision-impaired veterans on the registration document with NHS England and the Health and Social Care Information Centre.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215162","215162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156605","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Department for Education on changes in funding for speech therapy for children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215167","215167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156606","2014-11-24","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-11-19","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, whether the Government plans to publish its response to the McKay Commission report; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215242","215242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156607","2014-11-24","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that a sufficient number of clinical psychologists is available to meet the needs of the NHS.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215241","215241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156608","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs there were in the Hull local authority area in each of the last five years; what the ratio of GPs to population was in that area in those years; and what the ratio of GPs to population was for England in those years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215319","215319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156609","2014-11-24","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) consultants, (b) registrars, (c) other doctors and (d) nurse practitioners were employed in accident and emergency roles by Hull and East Yorkshire Hospitals Trust in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215329","215329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156610","2014-11-24","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff in her Department were employed in non-frontline roles in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215331","215331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156611","2014-11-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost of enabling vitims of human trafficking to access legal aid in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215330","215330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156612","2014-11-26","Cabinet Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of (a) men and (b) women in (i) full-time and (ii) part-time work in each (A) local authority area and (B) parliamentary constituency earning less than the living wage.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215175","215175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156613","2014-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the prospect of Iran neutralising its stockpile of 20 per cent enriched uranium.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215336","215336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156614","2014-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received about Iran's Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei's nine point plan for the destruction of Israel.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215151","215151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156615","2014-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of how much his Department has spent on specific steps to tackle the Ebola outbreak in West Africa to date.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215222","215222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156616","2014-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of how much his Department has spent on specific steps to tackle the Ebola outbreak in West Africa to date.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215224","215224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156617","2014-11-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the cost to the public purse has been of compensating farmers for TB in their herds in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215306","215306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156618","2014-11-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the cost of TB in cattle herds on the UK agri-food industry in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215307","215307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156619","2014-11-21","Department for International Development","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of how much her Department has spent on specific steps to tackle the Ebola outbreak in West Africa to date.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215223","215223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156620","2014-11-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what access arrangements are in place for broadband subscribers to make complaints via Openreach about poor quality of service.","Biography information for Dame Angela Watkinson","Dame Angela Watkinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215154","215154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156621","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, by what process she plans that businesses will report exploitation in their supply chains as a result of the Modern Slavery Bill.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215322","215322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156622","2014-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, under what criteria and procedures an hon. Member can seek reference to the Secretary of State of a planning application that has been rejected by a planning authority.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215239","215239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156623","2014-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information he holds on when Shropshire unitary authority will be in a position to bank an agreed five year land supply.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215240","215240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156624","2014-11-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what account she takes when deciding on measures to reduce the mortality in bass stocks of the (a) value to the UK economy and the economies of other member states of recreational angling compared to commercial fishing, (b) mortality of bass stocks caused by recreational anglers compared to that caused by commercial fishing and (c) tax receipts from recreational angling compared to those from commercial fisheries.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215206","215206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156625","2014-11-21","HM Treasury","2014-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Tynemouth constituency paid the top rate of income tax in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215256","215256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156626","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prisoners held in HM Prison and Young Offender Institution Swinfen Hall have been diagnosed with (a) ADHD and (b) Asperger's Syndrome.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215255","215255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156627","2014-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in Tynemouth constituency have had income support capped since the introduction of the benefit cap.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215254","215254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156628","2014-11-21","Attorney General","2014-11-19","To ask the Attorney General, what bodies can prosecute without the approval of the Crown Prosecution Service.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215172","215172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156629","2014-11-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations his Department has received on the timing of the introduction of the carbon compliance element of the zero carbon standard for new homes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215227","215227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156630","2014-11-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the evidence he has received on the practicality of introducing the carbon compliance element of the zero carbon standard for new homes in 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215228","215228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156631","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of access on the NHS to new treatments for patients with rarer cancers.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215320","215320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156632","2014-11-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to more effectively regulate claims management companies.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215148","215148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156633","2014-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list all meetings between Ministers in his Department and representatives of Qatari defence companies in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215271","215271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156634","2014-11-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will list all open individual export licences with Qatar in force in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215272","215272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156635","2014-11-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will list all open individual export licences with Kuwait in force in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215273","215273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156636","2014-11-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will list all standard individual export licences with Qatar in force in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215274","215274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156637","2014-11-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will list all standard individual export licences with Kuwait in force in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215275","215275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156638","2014-11-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2014 to Question 198624, by which process his Department estimates wholesale (a) electricity and (b) gas prices.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215253","215253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156639","2014-11-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2014 to Question 198624, if he will place in the Library a copy of his Department's estimate of wholesale (a) electricity and (b) gas prices in each month between January 2007 and November 2014.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215252","215252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156640","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the duties relating to adult social care currently carried out by local authorities that could be transferred to charities in order to increase efficiency and quality of care.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215170","215170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156641","2014-11-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the UK's annual quota for skate and rays was in each ICES area in each year since 2000; and what the annual take up of the annual allocations by the UK was in each ICES area.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215166","215166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156642","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with representatives of the European Commission on the prospects of the UK receiving an exemption for competitive domestic ports from the proposed European Port Services Regulations.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215297","215297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156643","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proposals the Government has drawn up to apply for an exemption for competitive UK ports from the proposed European Port Services Regulations.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215296","215296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156644","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with (a) port operators and (b) relevant trade unions since the meeting of the Council of Ministers to discuss the proposed European Port Services Regulations on 8 October 2014.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215293","215293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156645","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what bilateral discussions he has had with his counterparts in other EU member states on the proposed European Port Services Regulations since the meeting of the Council of Ministers on 8 October 2014.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215294","215294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156646","2014-11-24","Department for Transport","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the possible scope of any exemption for UK competitive ports from the proposed European Port Services Regulations.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215295","215295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156647","2014-11-24","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS (a) has spent and (b) plans to spend on tackling Ebola in (i) Sierra Leone, (ii) the UK and (iii) elsewhere in this financial year.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215174","215174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156648","2014-11-24","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people under the age of 16 in each county were victims of sexual offences in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215152","215152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156649","2014-11-24","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from which countries from outside the UK have been granted UK citizenship in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215213","215213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156650","2014-11-24","Department for International Development","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department (a) has spent and (b) plans to spend on Ebola in (i) Sierra Leone, (ii) the UK and (iii) elsewhere in this financial year.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215173","215173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156651","2014-11-21","House of Commons Commission","2014-11-19","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what the average daily number of letters sent from the House of Commons to each government department is.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215204","215204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156652","2014-11-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people under 16 have been convicted of a sexual offence in each police authority in the most recent year available.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215366","215366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156653","2014-11-24","Cabinet Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the rate of (a) employment and (b) unemployment is for people aged (i) 50, (ii) 51, (iii) 52, (iv) 53, (v) 54, (vi) 55, (vii) 56, (viii) 57, (ix) 58, (x) 59, (xi) 60, (xii) 61, (xiii) 62, (xiv) 63, (xv) 64 and (xvi) 65.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215277","215277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156654","2014-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the rise in long-term unemployment for 18 to 24 year olds shown in the labour market statistics on 12 November 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215278","215278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156655","2014-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Jobcentre Plus staff were promoted to a higher grade in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-14.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215279","215279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156656","2014-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of Jobcentre Plus advisers was from a black and minority ethnic group in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215276","215276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156657","2014-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total amount of benefit withheld as a result of benefit sanctions was in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215334","215334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156658","2014-11-21","Department for Transport","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Philippine Overseas Employment Administration on the recruitment of seafarers to work on (a) UK flagged and (b) non-UK flagged vessels in the short sea shipping sector.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215317","215317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156659","2014-11-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2014 to Question 209429, and the Housing Standards Review Technical Consultation issued in September 2014, if he will make it his policy that a national standard to replace the existing space standards used by local authorities apply to new dwellings created by conversion from other uses under permitted development rights.","Biography information for Mr Nick Raynsford","Mr Nick Raynsford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215249","215249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156660","2014-11-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities he has written to about the frequency of their publications since entry into force of the Local Audit and Accountability Act 2014.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215230","215230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156661","2014-11-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to support the work of the UK Men's Sheds Association.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215138","215138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156662","2014-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much of the net additional cost of military operations was allocated to Defence Medical Rehabilitation Centre Headley Court in financial year 2012-13.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215139","215139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156663","2014-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much of the net additional cost of military operations allocated to Defence Medical Rehabilitation Centre Headley Court was spent on commissioned treatments and services from private sector healthcare providers in financial year 2012-13.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215140","215140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156664","2014-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much of the net additional cost of military operations allocated to Defence Medical Rehabilitation Centre Headley Court was spent on (a) living and mobility aids and (b) rehabilitation programmes and other associated healthcare services in financial year 2012-13.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215141","215141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156665","2014-11-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the speed of delivery of superfast broadband to rural areas in East Hertfordshire.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215209","215209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156666","2014-11-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to help young people develop pre-employment and basic skills to help them into work; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215215","215215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156667","2014-11-24","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of sexual abuse against children and young people have been reported to police in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215208","215208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156668","2014-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether there is a preferred business which has shown interest in Shipyard Portsmouth following the closure of the period for expressions of interest in acquiring ownership of the shipyard.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215229","215229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156669","2014-11-24","Department for Education","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to her Department was of the Bailey Review on the commercialisation and sexualisation of childhood.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215282","215282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156670","2014-11-24","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which (a) accident and emergency departments, (b) NHS trusts, (c) NHS foundation trusts and (d) mental health trusts he has visited in an official capacity in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215280","215280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156671","2014-11-24","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer to Question 213815, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the proportion of eligible discharges which are not followed up within seven days.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215281","215281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156672","2014-11-24","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which medical professionals are required to undergo re-certification or re-validation; and how often each such group of professionals are required to undergo such re-certification or re-validation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215332","215332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156673","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has commissioned on supporting young people moving from children's to adult's mental health services.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215357","215357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156674","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the take up of childhood vaccinations in (a) Lambeth, (b) Greater London and (c) the UK for each ethnic group.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215362","215362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156675","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the take up of childhood vaccinations in (a) Lambeth, (b) Greater London and (c) the UK among those subject to immigration control; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215363","215363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156676","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the take up of the HPV vaccine in (a) Lambeth, (b) Greater London and (c) the UK for each ethnic group.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215364","215364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156677","2014-11-21","Department for Education","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department has issued to (a) primary schools, (b) secondary schools, (c) sixth form colleges and (d) pupil referral units on dealing with (i) racist bullying, (ii) homophobic bullying, (iii) gender-based bullying and (iv) sexual exploitation.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215257","215257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156678","2014-11-21","Department for Education","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people under the age of 18 in (a) the UK, (b) England and Wales, (c) London, (d) each London borough and (e) Streatham constituency have been enrolled at Pupil Referral Units in the latest period for which figures are available; and what proportion of such children have achieved five or more GCSEs.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215358","215358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156679","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support she gives to local authorities to tackle female genital mutilation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215350","215350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156680","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support she gives to the police to tackle female genital mutilation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215351","215351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156681","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of incidents of female genital mutilation that were carried out on women and girls residing in (a) Lambeth, (b) Greater London and (c) the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215349","215349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156682","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of knife crime were recorded by the Metropolitan Police in (a) Greater London and (b) Lambeth in each year from 2005 to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215344","215344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156683","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of gun crime were recorded by the Metropolitan Police in (a) Greater London and (b) Lambeth in each year from 2005 to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215345","215345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156684","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how her Department defines gang related incidents when recording incidences; how many incidents of gang related crime were recorded by the Metropolitan Police in (a) Greater London and (b) Lambeth in each year from 2005 to 2014.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215346","215346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156685","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce violence against women and girls in the London Borough of Lambeth; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215359","215359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156686","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she plans to take to ensure that a multi-agency approach is taken to address gender-based violence; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215360","215360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156687","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests there have been in (a) Lambeth, (b) Greater London and (c) the UK related to female genital mutilation; and how many such arrests have led to prosecution.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215347","215347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156688","2014-11-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of (a) time limits on length of stay and (b) quotas for local women within refuges or victims of domestic violence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215361","215361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156689","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase the number of arrests and prosecutions related to female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215348","215348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156690","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of prisoners had mental health difficulties upon arrival in adult prison in each year from 2005 to 2014 to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215352","215352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156691","2014-11-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to tackle sexual exploitation and sexual offences in (a) adult prisons and (b) youth offender institutions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215356","215356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156692","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police positions in Greater London were vacant in March of each year from 2005 to 2014.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215341","215341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156693","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Metropolitan Police officers there were serving in Lambeth in Safer Neighbourhood Teams in March of each year from 2005 to 2014.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215342","215342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156694","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police positions in Lambeth were vacant in March of each year from 2005 to 2014.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215343","215343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156695","2014-11-21","Home Office","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Metropolitan Police officers there were serving in Greater London in Safer Neighbourhood Teams in March of each year from 2005 to 2014.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215340","215340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156696","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department has provided to prisons to offer care to prisoners with mental health problems.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215354","215354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156697","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure prisoners diagnosed with mental health difficulties continue to receive support upon their release from custody; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215355","215355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156698","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people in custody in youth offender institutions had mental health difficulties upon arrival in custody in each year from 2005 to 2014 to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215353","215353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156699","2014-11-21","HM Treasury","2014-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has made to the Irish government about the double-Irish system of reducing the UK tax obligations of multinational corporations.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215311","215311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156700","2014-11-21","HM Treasury","2014-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of UK tax revenue foregone as a result of the double-Irish system.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215312","215312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156701","2014-11-21","HM Treasury","2014-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will request the EU's inspection teams to provide details of all preferential tax deals between (a) Luxembourg, (b) the Netherlands and (c) Ireland and multinational corporations which trade in the UK.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215308","215308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156702","2014-11-21","HM Treasury","2014-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has made to the government of Luxembourg about that country's tax agreements with multinational corporations who trade in the UK.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215309","215309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156703","2014-11-21","HM Treasury","2014-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what evidence he has given to the EU inquiry into the extent and means of tax avoidance by multinational corporations through Luxembourg and Ireland.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215310","215310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156704","2014-11-24","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills in the debate on the Second Reading of the Off-patent Drugs Bill on 7 November 2014, Official Report, column 1124, what the evidential basis was of his statement that the resorting to legislation to demand regulatory measures carries the risk of some serious and unintended consequences.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215337","215337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156705","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps health and wellbeing boards take to monitor their progress on raising awareness of diabetes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215146","215146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156706","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to educate vulnerable people about winter flu jabs; and what he expects the result of those steps to be.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215127","215127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/156707","2014-11-21","Department of Health","2014-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients waited longer than 18 weeks for treatment in hospitals in (a) Barking, Havering and Redbridge University Hospitals NHS Trust and (b) England.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 215125","215125"
