"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174183","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of secondary school mathematics teachers hold a mathematics degree in each local authority in England.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221130","221130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174184","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of secondary school physics teachers hold a physics degree in each local authority in England.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221131","221131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174185","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of secondary school chemistry teachers hold a chemistry degree in each local authority in England.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221132","221132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174186","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary school teachers in each parliamentary constituency in the East of England have a science degree.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221128","221128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174187","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people started the National Professional Qualification for Headship in the financial year (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11 and (c) 2011-12.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221149","221149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174188","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people (a) applied for and (b) completed the National Professional Qualification for Headship in the financial year (i) 2009-10, (ii) 2010-11, (iii) 2011-12, (iv) 2012-13 and (v) 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221150","221150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174189","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people applied for the National Professional Qualification for Headship in the first half of financial year 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221151","221151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174190","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many independent careers advisers were employed in schools in the academic year (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221152","221152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174191","2015-01-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what reports he has received of abuses of the non-domestic renewable heat incentive scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221116","221116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174192","2015-01-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many overpayments have been made under the non-domestic renewable heat incentive scheme; and how many overpayments have been recovered.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221117","221117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174193","2015-01-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the value is of (a) overpayments made, (b) overpayments recovered and (c) outstanding payments under the non-domestic renewable heat incentive scheme.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221118","221118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174194","2015-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information his Department holds on the extent of additional expenditure that will be incurred by EDF in order to meet its obligations under the capacity market regime.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221110","221110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174195","2015-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has received from animal enforcement bodies and charities on the Pet Animals Act 1951.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221096","221096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174196","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 5 December 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms C Lyes.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221082","221082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174197","2015-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has summoned the Saudi Ambassador in London in order to make representations over the public flogging of Raif Badawi.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221090","221090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174198","2015-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the compliance with international law of the conviction and sentencing of Raif Badawi.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221091","221091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174199","2015-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on a likely release date for Billy Irving and his 34 colleagues from the anti-piracy ship held in India since October 2013.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221134","221134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174200","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK will provide observers for the forthcoming general election in Nigeria.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221111","221111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174201","2015-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on the (a) number of resettlement places that EU member states are offering Syrian refugees and (b) EU's response to other aspects of the Syrian refugee crisis.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221126","221126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174202","2015-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the UN High Commissioner for Refugees following the introduction of visa requirements for Syrian nationals entering Lebanon.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221127","221127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174203","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with Aldi as part of the Responsibility Deal.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221105","221105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174204","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with Tesco as part of the Responsibility Deal.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221106","221106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174205","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with Morrisons as part of the Responsibility Deal.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221107","221107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174206","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with Sainsbury's as part of the Responsibility Deal.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221101","221101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174207","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with Waitrose as part of the Responsibility Deal.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221102","221102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174208","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with Lidl as part of the Responsibility Deal.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221103","221103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174209","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with ASDA as part of the Responsibility Deal.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221104","221104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174210","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of patients with mental illness who prefer to be treated by (a) drug and (b) talking therapies.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221075","221075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174211","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have waited for Improving Access to Psychological Therapies interventions for more than (a) 28, (b) 90 and (c) 180 days in each clinical commissioning group area.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221076","221076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174212","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the (a) recovery and (b) mortality rates of cancer patients who (i) suffer and (ii) do not suffer from depression.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221077","221077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174213","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the (a) recovery and (b) mortality rates of patients who have had a heart attack who (i) suffer and (ii) do not suffer from depression.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221078","221078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174214","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients with a mental illness receive (a) drug, (b) talking and (c) mindfulness therapy.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221071","221071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174215","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the number of people his Department estimates suffer from mental illness are being treated by the NHS.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221072","221072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174216","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to expand the use of Improving Access to Psychological Therapies to include people with (a) co-morbid physical illness, (b) schizophrenia and other near psychotic problems and (c) older people.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221073","221073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174217","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the overall health budget was spent on psychological therapies in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221074","221074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174218","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what powers (a) he has and (b) members of the public have to require clinical commissioning groups to improve access to psychological therapies.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221092","221092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174219","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which parliamentary constituencies are (a) completely and (b) partly within a clinical commissioning group area.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221093","221093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174220","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that hospitals in Greater Manchester meet the Government's A&E waiting time target.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221094","221094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174221","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with local authorities in Greater Manchester on increased attendances in A&E over the winter and delayed discharges.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221095","221095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174222","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much each surplus building and piece of land owned by his Department is worth; where each such building and piece of land is located; and which such building and piece of land he intends to dispose of.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221099","221099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174223","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Monitor, the Care Quality Commission and NHS England on hospitals in Greater Manchester which have not met the Government's A&E waiting time target.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221081","221081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174224","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the success and cost-effectiveness of the (a) Healthy Child Programme and (b) Healthy Start Programme.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221066","221066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174225","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of time GPs spend with patients who have a mental illness.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221070","221070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174226","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether there is a cap on the number of Improving Access to Psychological Therapies sessions for each patient.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221068","221068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174227","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for Improving Access to Psychological Therapies interventions.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221069","221069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174228","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much NHS Property Services spent on (a) redundancy payments to staff, (b) temporary staff and (c) external consultants in each year since it was established.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221083","221083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174229","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much NHS Property Services has paid Jo Stones and Vince Lammas for consultancy services; and how their services were procured.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221084","221084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174230","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of (a) adults and (b) children with (i) diabetes, (ii) anxiety disorder, (iii) depression, (iv) schizophrenia, (v) personality disorder, (vi) alcohol dependence and (vii) hard drug dependency who were untreated in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221067","221067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174231","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many families have received assistance from the Family Nurse Partnership in each year since the inception of the scheme; and what plans he has to continue to expand provision.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221065","221065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174232","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues to NHS trusts on the sharing with children's centres (a) the names and addresses of new parents and (b) other live birth data.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221063","221063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174233","2015-01-20","Home Office","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people under the age of 18 have been returned to (a) their country of nationality and (b) a third country by her Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221147","221147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174234","2015-01-21","Home Office","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will re-assess the procedures established to review the numbers of Syrians offered resettlement places in the UK as part of the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Relocation scheme to ensure that the scheme is responsive to need.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221125","221125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174235","2015-01-20","Department for International Development","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps her Department has taken to ensure a rapid humanitarian response for refugees displaced as a result of violence carried out by Boko Haram.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221113","221113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174236","2015-01-20","Department for International Development","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department has had with the Nigerian government about protection for humanitarian workers in northern Nigeria.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221114","221114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174237","2015-01-20","Department for International Development","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the effect has been of changes in the security situation and displacement of people following recent attacks by Boko Haram on UK Government-funded programmes for education in northern Nigeria.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221112","221112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174238","2015-01-20","Department for International Development","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to combat the spread of drug-resistant malaria.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221079","221079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174239","2015-01-20","Department for International Development","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support she is giving to the humanitarian response in South Sudan to avert the risk of famine.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221044","221044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174240","2015-01-20","Department for International Development","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to press the parties in the South Sudan conflict to protect civilians and allow unhindered humanitarian access.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221045","221045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174241","2015-01-20","Department for International Development","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to work with Cabinet colleagues towards a concerted global effect to restore peace in South Sudan by international investment in rebuilding hospitals, schools and livelihoods in addition to humanitarian aid and peacekeeping operations.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221046","221046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174242","2015-01-20","Department for International Development","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether income received from returnable investments will be treated as negative overseas development assistance and deducted from that years contribution to the 0.7 per cent aid target.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221047","221047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174243","2015-01-20","Department for International Development","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, in which financial year her Department expects to receive income from its returnable financial investments.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221048","221048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174244","2015-01-20","Department for International Development","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she plans to publish her Department's indicators for the strategic framework for economic development.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221049","221049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174245","2015-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2014 to Question 214963, what the (a) actual offence charged, (b) number of previous convictions, (c) number of previous knife crime convictions, (d) age of the offender, (e) other offences were charged and sentenced at the same time and (f) other information which formed part of the sentencing decision was in each case at Bradford Crown Court for which an immediate custodial sentence was not handed down.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221097","221097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174246","2015-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2014 to Question 214936, how many such cautions were issued in each police force area.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221098","221098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174247","2015-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of distress warrants that were passed to private debt collection agencies were returned to his Department as uncollected in each of the last three years; and what proportion of those penalties were subsequently collected by the National Crime and Enforcement Service.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221100","221100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174248","2015-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of staff of his Department having access to HM Revenue and Customs information on individuals who have defaulted and are in employment on the level of collection rates of fines and compensation set by the courts.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221135","221135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174249","2015-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in each prison in England and Wales were segregated in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221133","221133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174250","2015-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which offences prisoners serving a sentence of 12 months or less had committed (a) on the latest date for which information is held and (b) during the latest year for which information is held.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221109","221109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174251","2015-01-20","Department for Transport","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which five companies were used most often to provide temporary workers for his Department in the last financial year; and how much was paid in agency fees to those companies in that period.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221055","221055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174252","2015-01-20","Department for Transport","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of whether the (a) embankments, slip roads and hard shoulders and (b) other parts of the M67 motorway from the Denton interchange to the River Tame meet statutory standards of cleanliness.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221108","221108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174253","2015-01-20","Department for Transport","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many additional seats he expects will be made available on trains from Woking to London Waterloo in non-peak hours in each of the years from 2015 to 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221140","221140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174254","2015-01-20","Department for Transport","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many additional seats he expects will be made available on trains from Woking to London Waterloo during peak hours in each of the years from 2015 to 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221141","221141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174255","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to pilot different approaches to the use of sanctions in in work conditionality for universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221148","221148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174256","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received from the Trussell Trust about the adequacy of his Department's hardship payments scheme since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221119","221119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174257","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to pilot approaches to in work conditionality in which the conditionality will be applied by staff other than Jobcentre Plus staff; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221120","221120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174258","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects in work conditionality to be applied to all appropriate claimants of universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221121","221121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174259","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 7.12 of the Explanatory Memorandum to the Universal Credit (Work-Related Requirements) In Work Pilot Scheme Amendment Regulations 2015, if he will place in the Library a copy of the strategy for testing alternative approaches to universal credit in work conditionality.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221122","221122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174260","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the shared accommodation rate reflects the real cost of renting shared accommodation.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221129","221129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174261","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many letters giving one month's notice of case closure have been sent to Child Support Agency clients.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221087","221087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174262","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many six months' notice warning letters of case closure have been sent to Child Support Agency customers in each month since 30 June 2014.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221086","221086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174263","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 5.3 of the Government response to the 17th Report of the Public Accounts Committee, Cm 8988, what steps his Department is taking to alert Segment 1 (nil assessed) Child Support Agency clients to the fact that an estimated third of them would qualify for more child maintenance if they applied to the new statutory child maintenance scheme.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221089","221089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174264","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the 390 child maintenance service cases noted in Figure 5 of the Report by the National Audit Office on Child Maintenance 2012 Scheme: Early Progress, HC 173, published on 20 June 2014, what legal enforcement action has been taken in those cases; and in how many of those cases child maintenance arrears have been paid in (a) full and (b) part as a result of that action.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221088","221088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173872","2015-01-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs in Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency which are part of the supply chain for the oil and gas industry.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220863","220863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173873","2015-01-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the (a) type and (b) value of support provided by UK Export Finance for projects, goods or services supplied to the coal mining sector was in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220902","220902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173874","2015-01-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the (a) type and (b) value of support provided by UK Export Finance was for projects, goods or services supplied to the coal mining sector in this financial year to date.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220903","220903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173876","2015-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 1 October 2014 to Question 206270, what (a) inquiries have been made and (b) investigations have been carried out by (i) Ministers in his Department, (ii) officials in his Department and (iii) Business Bank staff into allegations of misselling relating to the Enterprise Finance Guarantee Scheme since 2012.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220927","220927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173877","2015-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 1 October 2014 to Question 206270, what discussions and meetings (a) Ministers in his Department, (b) officials in his Department and (c) Business Bank staff have had with (i) participating lenders and (ii) business organisations where allegations of misselling relating to the Enterprise Finance Guarantee Scheme were discussed since 2012.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220928","220928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173878","2015-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 1 October 2014 to Question 206270, what (a) safeguards and (b) monitoring processes and producers are operated by his Department or the Business Bank in relation to the Enterprise Finance Guarantee Scheme; what scrutiny of lenders takes place routinely; and what data his Department collects on the operation of the Enterprise Finance Guarantee Scheme by lenders.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220929","220929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173879","2015-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 1 October 2014 to Question 206270, what the operational responsibilities of lenders under the Enterprise Finance Guarantee Scheme are; and what steps his Department has taken to ensure these are upheld.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220930","220930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173880","2015-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will carry out an investigation into allegations of misselling to businesses by lenders relating to loans made under the Enterprise Finance Guarantee Scheme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220931","220931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173881","2015-01-20","Cabinet Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women under the age of 25 were diagnosed with cervical cancer in (a) the borough of Barnsley and (b) the UK in 2013 and 2014.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220932","220932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173887","2015-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much UK Export Finance has spent on advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220872","220872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173888","2015-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if the Government will launch an inquiry into the price of fuel to identify the reasons for the disparity between global oil prices and the domestic prices paid by motorists.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220890","220890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173889","2015-01-20","HM Treasury","2015-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2015 to Question 218249, how many complaints about non-payment of the minimum wage to HM Revenue and Customs have been made in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220892","220892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173891","2015-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his letter of 24 October 2014 to the chief finance officers of English billing authorities, which local authorities have offered a business rate discount to premises with a free-to-use cash machine since the sending of that letter; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220871","220871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173892","2015-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assistance has been (a) requested from or (b) offered by his Department to South Oxfordshire and Vale of White Horse District Councils following the fire at their offices in Crowmarsh Gifford.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220895","220895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173894","2015-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many community-led developments have completed as a result of the Community Right to Build.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220920","220920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173895","2015-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many community groups have exercised the Community Right to Build.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220921","220921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173896","2015-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many bids there have been to the fund to assist community groups with the Community Right to Build; how many such bids were successful; and how much has been allocated from that fund.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220918","220918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173898","2015-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many community referendums there have been as a result of the Community Right to Build.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220919","220919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173899","2015-01-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what support the Heritage Lottery Fund has given to organisations in Folkestone and Hythe constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Damian Collins","Damian Collins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228077","228077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173900","2015-01-22","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what support the Arts Council has given to organisations in Folkestone and Hythe constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Damian Collins","Damian Collins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228075","228075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173901","2015-01-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what support Sport England has given to organisations in Folkestone and Hythe constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Damian Collins","Damian Collins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228076","228076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173903","2015-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects his Department to respond to the recommendations of the 2014 report of the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Gurkha Welfare.","Biography information for Damian Collins","Damian Collins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228074","228074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173906","2015-01-19","Department for Education","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to give local authorities responsibility to plan, commission and build facilities to tackle classroom overcrowding; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220885","220885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173907","2015-01-19","Department for Education","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has a mechanism in place to be notified of instances when a local authority does not issue a final statement of special educational needs within the statutory time limit of 26 weeks.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220888","220888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173908","2015-01-19","Department for Education","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department provides to local authorities in instances when a local authority does not issue a final statement of special educational needs within the statutory time limit of 26 weeks.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220889","220889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173910","2015-01-19","Department for Education","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy that VAT should be applied to sixth form colleges in the same terms as mainstream schools with sixth forms.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220901","220901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173911","2015-01-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the contribution of 6 November 2014 by the Minister of State in his Department, Official Report, column 949, what assistance the Department has made available to UK Coal for the preparation of an application for state aid.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220904","220904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173912","2015-01-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the contribution of 6 November 2014 by the Minister of State in his Department, Official Report, column 949, what his Department's policy is on the provision of state aid to UK Coal in respect of Thoresby and Kellingley coal mines.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220905","220905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173913","2015-01-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the contribution of 6 November 2014 by the Minister of State in his Department, Official Report, column 949, what resources the Government is making available to UK Coal in support of the provision of state aid to UK Coal in respect of Thoresby and Kellingley coal mines.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220906","220906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173914","2015-01-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to page 45 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts for 2012-13, what proportion of the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority's budget was spent on decommissioning and cleaning up nuclear plants in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220907","220907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173916","2015-01-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority's budget he expects to be spent on decommissioning and cleaning up nuclear plants in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220908","220908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173917","2015-01-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority's Site Licence Companies spent on support and overhead costs in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220909","220909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173918","2015-01-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority's Site Licence Companies plan to spend on support and overhead costs in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220910","220910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173919","2015-01-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority's Site Licence Companies were awarded in efficiency fees and support and overhead cost reduction fees in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220911","220911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173920","2015-01-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2014 to Question 219579, if he will make it his policy to direct energy suppliers to withdraw charges imposed on customers solely for the purpose of covering the cost of gas metering and billing where a customer does not use that service.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220887","220887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173921","2015-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether his Department has received any expression of interest in pursuing shale gas development and exploration in (a) Northamptonshire and (b) the borough of Kettering.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220933","220933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173922","2015-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the future operating life of Dungeness B nuclear power station; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Damian Collins","Damian Collins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220873","220873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173923","2015-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will consult representatives from the compostable plastic bags industry as part of her Department's review of industry standards for the biodegradability of plastic material; and on how many occasions (a) Ministers and (b) officials have met representatives of (i) oxo-biodegradable and (ii) compostable plastic bag companies in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220900","220900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173925","2015-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she expects commercial planting of GM crops to begin in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220938","220938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173926","2015-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reason her Department's internal report on the impact of fracking on rural communities has been made public only in redacted form; what the criteria are for imposing such redactions; and if she will make it her policy to publish the report in full.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220937","220937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173927","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts about reforming the European Union.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220886","220886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173928","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the political situation in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220884","220884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173929","2015-01-19","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many vacant A&E consultant posts there were in the NHS excluding London (a) on the most recent date for which figures are available and (b) in each of the previous six years.","Biography information for Baroness Jowell","Dame Tessa Jowell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220878","220878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173930","2015-01-19","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many vacant A&E consultant posts there are in (a) London and (b) England; and how many such vacant posts there are in each category in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Baroness Jowell","Dame Tessa Jowell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220879","220879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173931","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Simon Holden, Chief Executive of NHS Property Services, has been paid for home to office travel expenses since taking up the post; for what reasons he is allowed to claim for such expenses; what salary he receives; and which other staff members at NHS Property Services claim for travel expenses.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220913","220913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173932","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect the four per cent year-in-year efficiency savings requirement has had on (a) staffing levels, (b) patient care and (c) waiting times in NHS trusts.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220912","220912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173933","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much each non-executive director of NHS Property Services has been paid in each year since it was established; and who authorises pay increases for non-executive directors.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220916","220916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173934","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what role was performed by Charles Siddons at NHS Property Services; what salary and benefits he received in that role; what process took place to select him for that role; and what the job description is for that role.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220914","220914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173935","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what role was performed by Tim Litherland at NHS Property Services; what salary and benefits he received in that role; what process took place to select him for that role; and what the job description is for that role.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220915","220915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173936","2015-01-20","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether it remains her policy that the Historical Institutional Abuse Inquiry chaired by Sir Anthony Hart is the most appropriate place where all allegations surrounding Kincora should be examined.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220898","220898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173937","2015-01-20","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will include Kincora Boys' Home in the independent inquiry into historical child sex abuse, established by the Home Office, in order to allow potential witnesses not to be constrained by the Official Secrets Act.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220899","220899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173938","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the accommodation of young people from Scotland in secure units in England.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220864","220864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173939","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people ordinarily resident in Scotland have been accommodated in secure units in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220865","220865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173940","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in which secure units young people ordinarily resident in Scotland have been accommodated in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220866","220866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173941","2015-01-20","Department for Transport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will commission work to compare the cost and success of hard shoulder running on smart motorways with the Siemens eHighway.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220896","220896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173942","2015-01-20","Department for Transport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will commission trials of the Siemens eHighway in the UK similar to those conducted in California.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220897","220897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173943","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what limits are in place in relation to noise from (a) aircraft and (b) motor vehicles.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220880","220880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173944","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what examples his Department holds of best practice in respect of work carried out to reduce traffic noise for residents living alongside main roads.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220881","220881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173945","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what penalties will be incurred for consistent delays on passenger services between (a) Brighton and London Victoria at (i) 07:14, (ii) 07:29 and (iii) 07:44 and (b) London Victoria and Brighton at (i) 17:32, (ii) 17:44 and (iii) 18:02 between January 2014 and December 2014 where delays were attributable to (A) train operating companies and (B) Network Rail; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220882","220882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173946","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will (a) make an assessment of and (b) discuss with the Office of Rail Regulation the punctuality record of the (i) 07:14, 07:29 and 07:44 Brighton to London Victoria and (ii) 17:32, 17:44 and 18:02 London Victoria to Brighton rail services in 2014.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220883","220883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173947","2015-01-23","HM Treasury","2015-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the reason is for the additional charge for payment of vehicle tax by direct debit over 12 or six monthly instalments; and for what purposes the funds from that additional charge are used.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220917","220917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173948","2015-01-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 32 of Work Programme Evaluation: Operation of the commissioning model, finance and programme delivery, published by his Department in December 2014, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy of the finding that Jobcentre Plus managers' views on the effectiveness of the Work Programme tended to be fairly negative.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220893","220893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173949","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to improve employment support for Work Programme participants claiming employment and support allowance who have a 12 month prognosis of a return to work.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220894","220894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173950","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency who will reach the state pension age within 12 months from the introduction of the single-tier pension and will be eligible to receive the full rate of state pension.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220867","220867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173951","2015-01-19","HM Treasury","2015-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many agents providing guidance through the Pension Wise scheme will be based in Scotland.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220868","220868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173952","2015-01-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what conclusions about effective approaches to universal credit in work conditionality he has drawn from the labour market trials which started between May 2013 and January 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220869","220869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173953","2015-01-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to publish evaluations of the universal credit in work conditionality pilots.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220870","220870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173954","2015-01-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what changes he has made to his Department's policies or procedures in response to those representations about the adequacy of his Department's hardship payments scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220891","220891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173955","2015-01-19","Attorney General","2015-01-15","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the effect of the stalking offences introduced by the implementation of the Protection of Freedoms Act 2012 on the number of other offences charged under the Protection from Harassment Act 1997.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220966","220966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173956","2015-01-19","Attorney General","2015-01-15","To ask the Attorney General, what the sex was of the (a) complainant and (b) defendant in each of the cases of stalking brought since the implementation of the Protection of Freedoms Act 2012; and what the outcome was in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220996","220996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173957","2015-01-20","Cabinet Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of civil servants is employed on flexible working arrangements.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220925","220925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173958","2015-01-20","Cabinet Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of civil service jobs is advertised as offering flexible working.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220926","220926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173959","2015-01-19","HM Treasury","2015-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on golf clubs of differences in VAT rules applying to propriety-owned and member-owned golf clubs; and if he will meet the hon. Member for Upper Bann to discuss this matter.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220953","220953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173960","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many bids under the Community Right to Challenge have been assessed by local authorities.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220946","220946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173961","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many bids under the Community Right to Challenge have been made local authorities.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220947","220947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173962","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many disposal notices he has issued as a result of bids under the Community Right to Reclaim Land.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220951","220951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173963","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many sites have been disposed of as a result of disposal notices issued by his Department under the Community Right to Reclaim Land.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220952","220952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173964","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many of the procurement processes that have been triggered by the Community Right to Challenge resulted in a successful bid by groups that had exercised that right.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220945","220945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173965","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many requests under the Community Right to Reclaim Land he has received.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220948","220948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173966","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many pieces of land that have been disposed of under that Community Right to Reclaim Land were sold to the community groups that submitted the bid to his Department.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220949","220949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173967","2015-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken to maximise the use of Build Now, Pay Later models on surplus public land; and how many sites have been disposed of through these models since 2010.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220922","220922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173968","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to answer Question 217220, tabled on 4 December 2014 by the hon. Member for Wolverhampton North East.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220939","220939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173969","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to answer Question 217219, tabled on 4 December 2014 by the hon. Member for Wolverhampton North East.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220940","220940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173970","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to answer Question 217184, tabled on 4 December 2014 by the hon. Member for Wolverhampton North East.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220941","220941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173971","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to answer Question 217185, tabled on 4 December 2014 by the hon. Member for Wolverhampton North East.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220942","220942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173972","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many requests under the Community Right to Reclaim Land he has assessed from (a) individuals and (b) community groups.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220950","220950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173973","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to answer Question 217181, tabled on 4 December 2014 by the hon. Member for Wolverhampton North East.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220943","220943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173974","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many procurement processes have been triggered as a result of the Community Right to Challenge.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220944","220944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173975","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the amount of undeveloped brownfield land which his Department considers suitable for development.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220984","220984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173976","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to bring forward housing development on sites where construction has been delayed.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220985","220985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173977","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many injunctions against unauthorised developments were pursued by local authorities in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220994","220994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173978","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to bring forward housing development on brownfield land.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220983","220983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173979","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of sites where planning permission for housing development has been granted but where construction has been stalled for more than five years.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220989","220989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173980","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of sites for which planning permission for housing development has been granted but where construction has been stalled for more than one year.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220990","220990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173981","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of homes not yet under construction but for which planning permission has been granted.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220991","220991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173982","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of sites where planning permission for housing development has been granted but construction has not yet started.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220992","220992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173983","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of homes for which planning permission has been granted but on which construction has been stalled for more than one year.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220987","220987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173984","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of homes for which planning permission has been granted but on which construction has been stalled for more than five years.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220988","220988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173985","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress his Department has made on improving access standards for new homes as part of the Housing Standard Review.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221026","221026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173986","2015-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications there were to set up rabbit farms in England in each of the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221040","221040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173987","2015-01-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Portable Antiquities Scheme.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220935","220935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173988","2015-01-19","Department for Education","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what financial rewards her Department makes available to kinship carers.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220970","220970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173989","2015-01-19","Department for Education","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential for misuse of the kinship carer system.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221002","221002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173990","2015-01-19","Department for Education","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of cases in which two or more babies born to the same mother were put into kinship care.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221007","221007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173991","2015-01-19","HM Treasury","2015-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, to what purpose revenue from the auctioning of carbon emissions allowances have been put; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220961","220961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173992","2015-01-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the definition of energy subsidies used by his Department is the same as the definition set out in the report, Subsidies and costs of EU energy: an interim report, published by the European Commission on 10 October 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220963","220963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173993","2015-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what tonnage of coal was extracted from Parc Slip Opencast site in Mid-Glamorgan in each year since 1985; what levy was imposed in each of those years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221043","221043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173994","2015-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the loss of state funding by the ACRE Network on that organisation's ability to deliver support to rural communities.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221041","221041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173995","2015-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward species-specific legislative proposals to (a) prohibit the use of barren cages for new rabbit farm developments and (b) make other provision for protecting the welfare of farmed rabbits.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221036","221036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173996","2015-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, in which countries rabbit meat sold in the UK in each of the five most recent years for which data is available was produced.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221037","221037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173997","2015-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to ensure that consumers are fully informed of the manner in which rabbit meat on sale in England was raised.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221038","221038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173998","2015-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many rabbit farms are operating in England.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221039","221039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173999","2015-01-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recorded number of sea bass was discarded in the (a) Irish and (b) Celtic Sea by UK registered vessels in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221010","221010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174000","2015-01-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recorded number of sea bass were discarded in the (a) Irish and (b) Celtic Sea by Irish vessels in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220981","220981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174001","2015-01-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what level of fishing mortality reduction her Department considers sufficient for the conservation and recovery of sea bass stocks.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220957","220957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174002","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Chinese government about human rights in that country.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220993","220993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174003","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he next expects the Friends of Syria Group to meet next.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220982","220982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174004","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Icelandic counterpart on strengthening business relations between that country and the UK.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220995","220995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174005","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on negotiations on the future of Iran's nuclear programme.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220980","220980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174006","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Russian government about its annexation of Crimea.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220986","220986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174007","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the P5 nuclear weapon states will next meet in London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Joan Ruddock","Dame Joan Ruddock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220923","220923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174008","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether there will be a joint P5 statement on the Vienna Conference on the Humanitarian Impact of Nuclear Weapons.","Biography information for Dame Joan Ruddock","Dame Joan Ruddock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220924","220924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174009","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Russian government about (a) human rights in general and (b) LGBT rights in that country.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221027","221027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174010","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Saudi Arabian government about freedom of speech in that country.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221028","221028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174011","2015-01-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in the government of Afghanistan on ensuring that adequate training is available to national security forces following the UK's withdrawal of military personnel from combat roles in that country.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221019","221019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174012","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Thai government on human trafficking.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221020","221020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174013","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the US administration on strengthening diplomatic ties between the US and UK.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221021","221021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174014","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Egyptian government on freedom of speech in that country.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221022","221022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174015","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Burmese government on the persecution of the Rohingya people in that country.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221018","221018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174016","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of human rights in North Korea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221042","221042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174017","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he next plans to meet the Sri Lankan Minister of External Affairs.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221023","221023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174018","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Mexican counterpart on (a) the kidnapping of students in Iguala in September 2014 and (b) human rights in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221015","221015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174019","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Mexican counterpart on strengthening UK-Mexico business relations.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221016","221016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174020","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Egyptian government on freedom of religion in that country for (a) atheists and (b) Christians.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221035","221035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174021","2015-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterparts in the government of Afghanistan on the operation of ISIL in the south of that country.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221017","221017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174022","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect that the recently announced reductions in staffing levels at the Dudley Group of Hospitals will have on (a) patient care and (b) waiting times.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221034","221034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174023","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of additional demand for NHS counselling services resulting from survivors of historic child sexual abuse recently coming forward; and what argument he has made of the effectiveness of NHS mental health services in meeting that demand.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221030","221030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174024","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of 111 referrals to A&E departments in NHS hospitals in Sussex over the Christmas and New Year period in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221029","221029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174025","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that recipients of social care are able to access complaints advocacy, equivalent to the measures for health complaints advocacy established under the Health and Social Care Act 2012.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220934","220934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174026","2015-01-19","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many non-emergency admissions to hospital via A&E departments were made in each NHS hospital in (a) Suffolk, (b) Bedfordshire, (c) Cambridgeshire, (d) Essex, (e) Hertfordshire and (f) Norfolk in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220973","220973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174027","2015-01-19","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans NHS England has to respond to patient groups and charities who are concerned about the removal of clinically effective drugs from the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220954","220954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174028","2015-01-19","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps NHS England plans to take to ensure that patients and clinicians are aware of the drugs delisted from the Cancer Drugs Fund as announced on 12 January 2015.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220955","220955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174029","2015-01-19","Department of Health","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were admitted to hospital for alcohol-related conditions through A&E in NHS hospitals in (a) Suffolk, (b) Bedfordshire, (c) Cambridgeshire, (d) Essex, (e) Hertfordshire and (f) Norfolk in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220976","220976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174030","2015-01-19","Home Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the proportion of incidents marked as domestic violence cases which related to (a) male perpetrators against female partners, (b) female perpetrators against male partners and (c) other cases of domestic violence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220969","220969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174031","2015-01-19","Home Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many registered sex offenders there are in the UK; how many people on the Violent and Sex Offenders Register have committed sexual offences against children; and what the reoffending rate is for people on that register who have committed such offences in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221006","221006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174032","2015-01-19","Home Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions her Department has used police cells to hold immigrants in each police force area in (a) Suffolk, (b) Bedfordshire, (c) Cambridgeshire, (d) Essex, (e) Hertfordshire and (f) Norfolk in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220974","220974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174033","2015-01-19","Home Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many firearms were confiscated in each police force area in (a) Suffolk, (b) Bedfordshire, (c) Cambridgeshire, (d) Essex, (e) Hertfordshire and (f) Norfolk during the most recent firearms amnesty in November 2014.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220975","220975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174034","2015-01-19","Home Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the sex was of the complainant and the accused in each case of stalking reported after the implementation of the Protection of Freedoms Act 2012; and what proportion of such cases which were investigated resulted in the accused being (i) charged with the offence and (ii) cautioned.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220972","220972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174035","2015-01-20","Home Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of new cases of historic child abuse which have come forward in the last 12 months; and what recent assessment she has made of the capabilities of police forces to deal with such cases.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221031","221031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174036","2015-01-20","Home Office","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what instructions or guidance officials of her Department have given to members of the Independent Inquiry Panel into child sexual abuse about speaking in public about the work of that Panel.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221032","221032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174037","2015-01-19","Department for International Development","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what aggregate outcomes she has set for her Department's strategic framework for economic development.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221009","221009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174038","2015-01-19","Department for International Development","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what arrangements she is planning for the publication of indicators relating to her Department's strategic framework for economic development; and when she plans to publish such indicators.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221008","221008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174039","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) offence and (b) sentencing outcome of each terrorist-related offence dealt with in court was in the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220964","220964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174040","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national prisoners from each country were convicted of each offence type from September 2013 to September 2014.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220971","220971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174041","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners had reached the state pension age (a) on the latest date and (b) during the most recent year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220967","220967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174042","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners are currently serving sentences in the UK that were (a) handed down by the International Criminal Court or (b) heard at the Hague.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220965","220965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174043","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of those convicted of a knife crime offence were sentenced to prison for (a) up to six months, (b) up to and (c) over 12 months in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220997","220997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174044","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of assaulting a police officer in the last year for which figures are available; and what proportion of those people received a prison sentence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220998","220998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174045","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2014 to Question 214859, how many foreign national prisoners from each country were convicted of each offence in the violence offence group from April 2013 to March 2014.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221004","221004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174046","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the reoffending rate was for sex offenders whose original conviction was for sexual offences against children in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221005","221005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174047","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what types of offence resulted in confiscation orders being made in 2012-13; and how much was collected as a result of those orders.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220978","220978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174048","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will commission research to establish the main reasons foreign offenders commit offences in the UK.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220968","220968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174049","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what circumstances a foreign criminal serving a prison sentence for an offence committed outside the UK could serve their sentence in the UK.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221003","221003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174050","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders were sentenced to a custodial sentence for each offence by each magistrates' court in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221000","221000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174051","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders were sentenced to a custodial sentence of 12 months or less for each offence by each Crown Court in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221001","221001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174052","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders given custodial sentences for offences committed during the public disorder in London in August 2011 were given terms of imprisonment of 12 months or less.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220999","220999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174053","2015-01-19","Prime Minister","2015-01-15","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to his oral evidence to the Liaison Committee of 16 December 2014, HC887, if he will publish the evidential basis for his statement that 10 per cent of UK electricity coming from onshore wind is enough as part of a balanced energy supply; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220962","220962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174054","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many ultra low emission vehicles of what models have been registered under the Plug-in Car Grant.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220960","220960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174055","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had on the ring-fencing of slots for domestic air services to Heathrow Airport in the event of a third runway being opened at that airport with (a) Heathrow Airport, (b) the Airports Commission, (c) ACL and (d) devolved and regional bodies.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220979","220979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174056","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the existing contracts for the removal of litter on the strategic road network.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221013","221013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174057","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the Highways Agency was of the removal of graffiti from road signage and structures for which it has maintenance responsibility in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221012","221012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174058","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what arrangements are in place to ensure that the (a) embankments, slip roads and hard shoulders and (b) other areas of the M67 motorway from the Denton interchange to the River Tame are swept and adequately litter-picked.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221011","221011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174059","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the levels of litter on the strategic road network.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221014","221014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174060","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the need for specialist support within the Work Programme for people with mental health problems in receipt of employment and support allowance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221024","221024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174061","2015-01-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what resources from the UK's allocatons of EU Structural Funds have been used to support food banks.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221033","221033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174062","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will assess the implications for his policies of the recommendations in the report by MIND entitled We've got work to do, published in December 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221025","221025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174063","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department or local and district management set any numerical targets, expectations, aims or benchmarks set for Labour Market Decision Makers for the number of sanction referrals that should result in a sanction being applied.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220977","220977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174064","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of jobseeker's allowance in Scotland have (a) received a sanction and (b) disputed a sanction in each month of (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15 by month; and how many such claimants had a sanction overturned as a result of it being reconsidered or appealed.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220958","220958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174065","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of Employment and Support Allowance in Scotland have (a) received a sanction and (b) disputed a sanction in each month of (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15 by month; and how many such claimants had a sanction overturned as a result of it being reconsidered or appealed.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220959","220959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174066","2015-01-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average number of job searches required of jobseeker's allowance claimants is in (a) each English region and (b) each age group.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220936","220936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174067","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claimants of personal independence payments waited more than 16 weeks for a face-to-face assessment by each provider since the introduction of that payment.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220956","220956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173659","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much of the funding allocated to tackle beds in sheds has been (a) allocated and (b) spent to date.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220713","220713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173660","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many times the beds in sheds taskforce has met since its inception; and on what dates.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220714","220714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173661","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average (a) output in number of units per annum and (b) annual turnover is of the firms that have been allocated funds through the Builders Finance Fund.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220715","220715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173662","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much of the funds for the Builders Finance Fund has been (a) allocated and (b) spent.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220716","220716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173663","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homes he expects to be built through funding from the Builders Finance Fund; and how many such homes have been started.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220717","220717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173664","2015-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Written Statement of 13 March 2014, Official Report, columns 32-4WS, on building regulations, whether local authorities will remain able to impose reasonable requirements for a proportion of energy used in development to be energy from renewable energy sources generated on-site.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220786","220786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173665","2015-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the contribution of 13 January 2015 by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, Official Report, columns 218-22WH, on care sector, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Communities and Local Government and the Department of Health on the effect of commissioning decisions by local authorities on the level of compliance with the national minimum wage in the care sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220728","220728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173666","2015-01-19","HM Treasury","2015-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the contribution of 13 January 2015 by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, Official Report, column 222WH, on care sector, on what date each of the 94 cases was first raised with HM Revenue and Customs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220729","220729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173667","2015-01-19","HM Treasury","2015-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the contribution of 13 January 2015 by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, Official Report, columns 218-22WH, on care sector, if he will make it his policy to enable third parties to make formal complaints about breaches of national minimum wage rules and for them to be kept informed of the progress and outcome of investigations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220730","220730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173668","2015-01-19","HM Treasury","2015-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the contribution of 13 January 2015 by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, Official Report, columns 218-22WH, on care sector, when the last round of proactive investigation work by HM Revenue and Customs (a) began and (b) finished; when the current proactive work began; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220731","220731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173669","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the oral Answer by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health of 13 January 2015, Official Report, HC Deb column 703, on mental health care (pregnant women), if he will publish his Department's plans and the funding committed for ensuring that every maternity unit has staff specially trained in perinatal mental health skills by 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220765","220765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173670","2015-01-19","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps the Government has taken to tackle nuisance calls; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220821","220821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173671","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 January 2015 to Question 219648, who the members of the care.data Programme Board are; and (a) by whom and (b) by what process those board members were appointed.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220819","220819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173672","2015-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to his Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219706, what estimate he has made of the number of people who went into debt in order to pay for a funeral in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220814","220814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173673","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 January 2015 to Question 219648, what criteria will be used by the National Data Guardian to evaluate whether it is right and safe to collect care.data information from GP practices.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220820","220820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173674","2015-01-19","Home Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department takes into account reports produced or evidence submitted by non-governmental human rights organisations in deciding on claims for asylum made on the grounds of political persecution or a risk to someone's life.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220849","220849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173675","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department has issued on the treatment in the criminal treatment system of women experiencing domestic violence.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220702","220702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173676","2015-01-19","Home Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made on implementation of the violence against women and girls action plan.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220703","220703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173677","2015-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support her Department makes available to service families experiencing, or at risk of, domestic violence.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220678","220678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173678","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funding his Department has provided for refuges for women fleeing domestic violence in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220699","220699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173679","2015-01-19","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many officials of her Department in (a) the UK and (b) each station worldwide deal with FGM as part of their remit.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220700","220700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173680","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what practice directions are in place on the allocation of judges in civic and family courts to domestic violence cases; and how many judges on average are involved in such cases.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220701","220701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173681","2015-01-19","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to identify and prosecute cold callers claiming to represent a Government debt service.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220719","220719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173682","2015-01-19","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2015 to Question 219653, what the budget is for the advertising campaign to promote a greater take-up of superfast broadband.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220723","220723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173683","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to work with partners in the region to ensure that sufficient aid for reconstruction reaches Gaza following the recent conflict.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220672","220672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173684","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, persuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 218547, if he will adapt the Early Access to Medicines Scheme to better accommodate off-patent indications of drugs, by creating incentives for pharmaceutical companies to submit applications to the scheme.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220673","220673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173686","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients with diseases relating to malnutrition were treated in the NHS in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220681","220681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173687","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to publish figures for pre-slaughter mortality of animals in the food industry.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220726","220726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173688","2015-01-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the potential contribution to the economy of the investment in science announced in the Autumn Statement 2014; and what steps he plans to take to maximise that contribution.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220848","220848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173689","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to government officials in Bahrain on the stripping of Bahraini nationality from Bahrainis who are not dual nationals, for allegedly damaging state security.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220695","220695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173690","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with government officials in Bahrain about a future visit by the UN Special Rapporteur on Torture.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220696","220696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173691","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what (a) financial and (b) other assistance his Department is providing to the Bahraini government for (i) security sector and prison reform, (ii) judicial independence and rule of law and (iii) good governance and related matters.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220679","220679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173692","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations have been or will be made to relevant Bahraini government officials about the arrest and detention of the Al-Wefaq Secretary-General Sheikh Ali Salman.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220680","220680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173693","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what terms of reference have been set for his Department's research project on the effect of telematics on young drivers; and when he plans to publish the outcomes of each of that project's phases.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220799","220799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173694","2015-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 5.3.2 of the report of the Prime Minister's Task Force on Tackling Radicalisation and Extremism, published in December 2013, how many one-to-one sessions have been conducted to challenge extremist views in each prison since April 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220815","220815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173695","2015-01-16","Department for Education","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 5.1.2 of the report of the Prime Minister's Task Force on Tackling Radicalisation and Extremism, published in December 2013, how many people have been barred from managing or teaching at independent schools because of involvement with or links to extremism under the new regulations.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220816","220816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173696","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 5.3.2 of the report of the Prime Minister's Task Force on Tackling Radicalisation and Extremism, published in December 2013, what the budget of the Ibaana programme is; to which prisons that programme has been rolled out; and how many prisoners have completed that programme.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220828","220828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173697","2015-01-19","Home Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 4.2 of the report of the Prime Minister's Task Force on Tackling Radicalisation and Extremism, published in December 2013, in how many areas of the country delivery of Prevent has been made a legal requirement.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220829","220829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173698","2015-01-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 4.2 of the report of the Prime Minister's Task Force on Tackling Radicalisation and Extremism, published in December 2013, in which local authorities the Government has intervened because they are deemed not to be taking the problem of radicalisation seriously.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220830","220830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173699","2015-01-19","Home Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 2.3 of the report of the Prime Minister's Task Force on Tackling Radicalisation and Extremism, published in December 2013, which organisations have received support and advice to exclude extremists; and what funding for that purpose each such organisation has received.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220831","220831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173700","2015-01-16","Cabinet Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 2.3 of the report of the Prime Minister's Task Force on Tackling Radicalisation and Extremism, published in December 2013, whether the strengthened powers for the Charity Commission on which the Government plans to consult will include the ability to examine suspicious activity reports.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220817","220817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173701","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff of his Department have been assigned to implementation of the recommendations of the independent review of the operation of jobseekers' allowance sanctions, published in July 2014; what estimate he has made of the number of staff hours that have been spent on that implementation to date; and what funding his Department has allocated to that implementation.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220839","220839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173702","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of the recommendations accepted in the Government's response to the Independent review of the operation of jobseeker's allowance sanctions, published in July 2014, his Department plans to have implemented by May 2015.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220796","220796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173703","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to recommendation 11 of the Government's response to the Independent review of the operation of jobseeker's allowance sanctions, published in July 2014, what potential warnings and non-financial sanctions options his Department has considered in response to that recommendation.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220795","220795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173704","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Government's response to the Independent review of the operation of jobseeker's allowance sanctions, published in July 2014, when he plans to publish the communications review referred to in that document.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220797","220797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173705","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made on the implementation of the recommendations which the Government (a) accepted, (b) accepted in principle and (c) accepted and were already underway in its response to the publication entitled, Independent review of the operation of jobseeker's allowance sanctions, published in July 2014.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220798","220798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173706","2015-01-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on investor-state dispute settlement in the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220794","220794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173707","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take account of the shortage of vets in Devon and Cornwall when considering enforcement of fines for a failure to submit bovine TB tests in time.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220698","220698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173708","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff of HS2 Ltd are employed on personal service contracts.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220709","220709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173709","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff of HS2 Ltd on personal service contracts are paid more than 1,000 a day.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220710","220710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173710","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the cost of building the London terminus for High Speed 2 at Euston.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220711","220711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173711","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any employers have indicated an intention to transfer activities from London to Birmingham after the opening of Phase 1 of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220712","220712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173712","2015-01-19","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made by the taskforce reporting to his Department on tackling nuisance telephone calls.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220835","220835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173713","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the Government's approach to negotiating a cost-effective price for the meningococcal B vaccine Bexsero takes account of fluctuations in disease levels characteristic of that virus and the recent emergence of another strain of meningitis which may be treated using Bexsero.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220784","220784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173714","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which post in his Department is responsible for leading negotiations on setting a cost-effective price for the meningococcal B vaccine Bexsero; and when the next meeting to continue those negotiations is scheduled.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220785","220785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173715","2015-01-19","HM Treasury","2015-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is his Department's policy to seek to recover VAT on bitcoin transactions.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220822","220822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173716","2015-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his strategy for testing approaches to universal credit in-work conditionality includes testing employer involvement in the application of conditionality.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220753","220753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173717","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what dates and in what locations the universal credit in work pilots are due to start.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220704","220704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173718","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost of applying in work conditionality once universal credit has been fully rolled out.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220705","220705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173719","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to pilot the application of universal credit in work conditionality by staff other than Jobcentre Plus advisers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220706","220706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173720","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his strategy for testing approaches to universal credit in work conditionality includes testing of a requirement to leave one job and start another in order to increase pay; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220707","220707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173721","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the long-term health care needs of victims of Operation Protective Edge; what funding and other assistance her Department is giving to address those needs; and over what time period that funding and assistance will be given.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220762","220762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173722","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Spanish counterpart on (a) the position of that country in relation to the administration of Western Sahara and (b) whether Spain has submitted information to the UN about conditions in that territory, as is required of an administering power.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220763","220763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173723","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he received from the general public and others in (a) Wales, (b) Scotland and (c) England before deciding to put the Union flag on driving licences, in favour of that change.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220802","220802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173724","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of (a) the initial extra and (b) the subsequent ongoing annual costs of putting the Welsh flag on the driving licence for drivers in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220800","220800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173725","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the date by which all driving licences in Britain will carry the Union flag through the process of licence renewal.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220801","220801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173726","2015-01-16","HM Treasury","2015-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was raised from taxes on dividend income in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220787","220787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173727","2015-01-16","HM Treasury","2015-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many enforcement actions in respect of IR35 legislation there have been in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220790","220790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173728","2015-01-16","HM Treasury","2015-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the tax yield was from IR35 legislation in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220788","220788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173729","2015-01-16","HM Treasury","2015-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many IR35 status enquiries HM Revenue and Customs has made in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220789","220789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173730","2015-01-19","HM Treasury","2015-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on (a) recruitment agency fees, (b) outplacement agency fees for displaced or redundant staff and (c) staff training in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220853","220853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173731","2015-01-16","Cabinet Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many individuals or small and medium-sized enterprises contracting with, or providing consultancy services to, Government departments have been paid daily fees greater than 100 in the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220840","220840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173732","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on (a) recruitment agency fees, (b) outplacement agency fees for displaced or redundant staff and (c) staff training in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220832","220832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173733","2015-01-19","Cabinet Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much 10 Downing Street spent on (a) recruitment agency fees, (b) outplacement agency fees for displaced or redundant staff and (c) staff training in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220855","220855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173734","2015-01-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department spent on (a) recruitment agency fees, (b) outplacement agency fees for displaced or redundant staff and (c) staff training in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220856","220856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173735","2015-01-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department spent on (a) recruitment agency fees, (b) outplacement agency fees for displaced or redundant staff and (c) staff training in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220857","220857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173736","2015-01-16","Department for Education","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government plans to take to support newly-qualified teachers in seeking employment.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220755","220755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173737","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on preventing unhealthy eating among children of primary school age.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220756","220756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173738","2015-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to promote the engagement of higher education colleges with the agri-foods sector.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220757","220757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173739","2015-01-16","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which high-speed rail projects are planned to be completed in 2015.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220759","220759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173740","2015-01-16","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which high-speed rail projects are planned to commence in 2015.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220758","220758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173741","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is offering to the Nigerian government in response to the recent killings by Boko Haram in Nigeria.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220760","220760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173742","2015-01-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress the Government has made on its work to provide justice for the victims of the 1976 Kingsmill Massacre.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220724","220724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173743","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to ensure that doctors and surgeons are not working excessive hours.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220725","220725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173744","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to protect red squirrels in the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220818","220818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173745","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to tackle the persecution of Christians in Somalia.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220766","220766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173746","2015-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to provide care and support for members of the armed forces who have a mental illness.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220791","220791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173747","2015-01-16","Department for Education","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the per pupil funding for (a) primary and (b) secondary school pupils in Kingswood constituency was in (i) 2010 and (ii) 2015.","Biography information for Chris Skidmore","Chris Skidmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220727","220727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173748","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding was allocated for the NHS in Kingswood constituency in (a) 2010 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Chris Skidmore","Chris Skidmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220674","220674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173749","2015-01-16","Department for Education","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much was spent on the pupil premium in each local authority ward in Kingswood constituency in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Chris Skidmore","Chris Skidmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220676","220676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173750","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the per capita spend on NHS services was in Kingswood constituency in (a) 2010 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Chris Skidmore","Chris Skidmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220675","220675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173751","2015-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what circumstances disability living allowance is payable for a child who has dyslexia.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220691","220691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173752","2015-01-16","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the environmental effect of the Government's road investment strategy announced on 1 December 2014.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220783","220783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173753","2015-01-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with the Chief of the Air Staff on transferring responsibility for the risk of Typhoon mid air collision to that role.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220805","220805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173754","2015-01-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 7 of Director General, Military Aviation Authority, Air Safety Annual Report, August 2013-August 2014, published in January 2015, what assessment he has made of the implications of the conclusions of that report on his policy on mitigating mid-air collisions; and if he will require a full Airborne Collision Avoidance System to be fitted in all operational Typhoon aircraft.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220806","220806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173755","2015-01-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which posts have held responsibility and for how long for the risk of mid-air collisions on each fast jet type in each of the last five years; and what the reason was for the change of ownership in each case.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220804","220804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173756","2015-01-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when responsibility for the risk of Typhoon mid-air collision was passed from Air Officer Commanding No 1 Group to the Chief of the Air Staff; and for what reason that change was made.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220803","220803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173757","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic, humanitarian or consular assistance his Department has provided to Ms Maud Kells, the missionary from County Tyrone who was shot and wounded in the Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220809","220809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173758","2015-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many community grant applications have been received from HQ 38 (Irish) Brigade in Northern Ireland; how many such applications were successful; and how much was disbursed in respect of those applications in each year since the inception of that scheme.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220754","220754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173759","2015-01-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will extend the ban on the use of unenriched battery cages for laying hens, as set out in Schedule 3 to the Welfare of Farmed Animals (England) Regulations 2007 (S.I., 2007, No. 2078), to quail egg production.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220854","220854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173760","2015-01-19","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request that Simon Stevens, Chief Executive of NHS England, reply to the letter of 21 November 2014 from the hon. Member for Birmingham, Hodge Hill, on A&E services at Heartlands Hospital in Birmingham.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220708","220708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173761","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to reduce religious persecution across the world.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220807","220807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173762","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the flogging of Raif Badawi in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220843","220843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173763","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the use of corporal punishment for penal purposes.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220844","220844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173764","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what account she takes of promoting freedom of speech when deciding on allocations of overseas aid.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220845","220845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173765","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote freedom of speech in the Middle East.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220842","220842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173766","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to promote freedom of speech in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220841","220841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173767","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the case of Raif Badawi in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220847","220847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173768","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the sale of arms by UK companies to countries with governments which consistently violate the human rights of their citizens.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220846","220846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173769","2015-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to improve the recovery of court fines; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220694","220694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173770","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with representatives of French recreational sea bass anglers on the management of sea bass stocks.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220777","220777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173771","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she has received the report Bass Discards published by the Irish Bass Group; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220774","220774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173772","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what reports she has received on the Irish government's views on a total ban on commercial fishing for sea bass.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220775","220775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173773","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with her French counterparts on that country's policy on management of sea bass stocks.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220776","220776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173774","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219112, how the review of domestic management measures for bass will engage with other government departments, stakeholders and other interested parties from outside her Department.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220769","220769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173775","2015-01-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the process and timetable is for implementation of emergency EU measures to manage sea bass stocks.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220780","220780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173776","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219112, when she expects the review of domestic management measures for bass to be completed.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220770","220770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173777","2015-01-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on the implementation of emergency EU measures to manage sea bass stocks.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220781","220781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173778","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219112, if she will publish a list of all the documents that the review of domestic management measures for bass will take into account.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220771","220771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173779","2015-01-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what contribution the UK made to the design and scope of emergency EU measures to manage sea bass stocks.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220782","220782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173780","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219112, if she will ensure that all documents taken into account by the review of domestic management measures for bass will be published.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220772","220772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173781","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on levels of by-catch of sea bass in other fisheries in Irish waters in the last three years.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220773","220773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173782","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219112, what management measures will be examined in the review of domestic management measures for bass.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220778","220778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173783","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with her Irish counterparts on the management of sea bass stocks.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220767","220767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173784","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the International Council for the Exploration of the Sea since the EU Agriculture and Fisheries Council meeting on 15 December 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220779","220779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173785","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what reports she has received on the Irish government's policy for the management of sea bass stocks in their territorial waters.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220768","220768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173786","2015-01-19","Department for Education","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will publish the data gathered through the Property Data Survey Programme before the end of February 2015.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220718","220718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173787","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2015 to Question 217822, what was the value outstanding of impositions relating to (a) fines, (b) compensation orders, (c) victim surcharge orders and (d) prosecution costs orders in each local criminal justice board area at the end of each financial year from 2009-10.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220833","220833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173788","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2015 to Question 217822, what the total value was of outstanding financial impositions in each local criminal justice board area at the end of (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220834","220834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173789","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who bid for the contract arising from his Department's Compliance and Environment Services Project in response to the notice published in the Official Journal of the EU; and which bidders remain in the competition.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220850","220850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173790","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to award a contract arising from his Department's Compliance and Enforcement Services Project.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220838","220838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173791","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to promote awareness among motorists of cyclist safety.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220859","220859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173792","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of disabled people referred to the Work Programme moved into employment between January and December 2014.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220858","220858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173793","2015-01-19","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will ensure that the needs of cyclists are considered when infrastructure contracts are awarded.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220851","220851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173794","2015-01-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of successful applications to UK universities were made by British people from BME communities in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220852","220852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173795","2015-01-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what arrangements are in place to fund the expansion of the Combined Cadet Force; and what the estimated total cost of that expansion is.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220837","220837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173796","2015-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2015 to Question 219724, whether those Reapers have been relocated to the UK for maintenance, strategic or other reasons.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220793","220793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173797","2015-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to offer or provide personnel from Reaper Squadron 39 to the US Air Force as a gift of services in response to current operational requirements.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220792","220792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173798","2015-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Answer of 12 January 2015 to Question 219725, which UK officials will attend the MQ-9 Users Group meeting.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220764","220764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173799","2015-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2014 to Question 213733, if he will seek the agreement of the US administration to release a copy of the current revised Reaper Agreement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220761","220761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173800","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for continuous positive airways pressure therapy for those diagnosed with obstructive sleep apnoea.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220688","220688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173801","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce a fast track service for continous positive airways pressure therapy for people who drive for a living.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220689","220689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173802","2015-01-16","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many fatal road traffic accidents were caused by drivers falling asleep at the wheel in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220690","220690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173803","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of waiting times between diagnosis and treatment for obstructive sleep apnoea for people who drive for a living.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220687","220687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173804","2015-01-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department is providing support to former employees of City Link to find new employment.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220721","220721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173805","2015-01-19","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent changes to residency requirements for free access to the NHS on UK citizens working as missionaries overseas.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220722","220722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173806","2015-01-16","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to improve signalling on the railway between (a) Exeter and Plymouth and (b) Reading and Exeter; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of improved signalling on those routes.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220811","220811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173807","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport constituency have been diagnosed with chest infections in 2014.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220812","220812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173808","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with chest infections in 2014.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220813","220813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173809","2015-01-16","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to increase capacity on the railway between Exeter and Plymouth.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220810","220810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173810","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effects of fracking on rural communities; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220692","220692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173811","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Greek counterpart on elections in that country in January 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220693","220693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173812","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what budget was allocated by her Department to the International Labour Organisation (ILO) in each financial year from 2009-10; and what budget is allocated to the ILO for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220735","220735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173813","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what budget was allocated by her Department to the Global Small and Medium Enterprise Financial Initiative in each financial year from 2009-10; and what budget is allocated to that organisation for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220744","220744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173814","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what budget was allocated by her Department to the Global Value Chains Initiative in each financial year from 2009-10; and what budget is allocated to that organisation for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220736","220736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173815","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what budget was allocated by her Department to the Private Infrastructure Development Group in each financial year from 2009-10; and what budget was allocated to that organisation for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220743","220743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173816","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much public expenditure was allocated from her Department to Unilever in each financial year from 2009-10; and how much public expenditure is allocated to that company for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220734","220734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173817","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much public expenditure was allocated from her Department to the London Stock Exchange Group in each financial year from 2009-10; and how much public expenditure is allocated to that Group for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220733","220733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173818","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what budget was allocated by her Department to the Africa Enterprise Challenge Fund in each financial year from 2009-10; and what budget is allocated to that organisation for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220740","220740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173819","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what budget was allocated by her Department to the Investment Facility to Utilise UK Specific Expertise in each financial year from 2009-10; and what budget is allocated to that organisation for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220748","220748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173820","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what budget was allocated by her Department to Our Poorest State Inclusive Programme in each financial year from 2009-10; and what budget is allocated to that organisation for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220741","220741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173821","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what budget was allocated by her Department to the Samridhi Fund in each financial year from 2009-10; and what budget is allocated to that organisation for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220749","220749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173822","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what budget was allocated by her Department to the International Trade Centre in each financial year from 2009-10; and what budget is allocated to that organisation for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220742","220742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173823","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what budget was allocated by her Department to the New Alliance for Food Security and Nutrition in each financial year from 2009-10; and what budget is allocated to that organisation for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220739","220739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173824","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what budget was allocated by her Department to the Multilateral Investment Guarantee Agency in each financial year from 2009-10; and what budget is allocated to that organisation for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220738","220738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173825","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what total amount her Department has invested in returnable capital, loans and capital, since 2010.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220747","220747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173826","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what budget was allocated by her Department to AMPLIFY in each financial year from 2009-10; and what budget is allocated to that organisation for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220745","220745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173827","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what budget was allocated by her Department to the Arab Women's Enterprise Fund in each financial year from 2009-10; and what budget is allocated to that organisation for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220737","220737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173828","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, in which returnable capital funds her Department has invested since 2010.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220746","220746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173829","2015-01-16","HM Treasury","2015-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how his Department defines non-fiscal spend.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220808","220808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173830","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political rights of and economic opportunities for Tamils in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220697","220697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173831","2015-01-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether Ordnance Survey is conducting aerial photography of the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Arbuthnot of Edrom","Mr James Arbuthnot","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220720","220720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173832","2015-01-19","HM Treasury","2015-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the total funds provided by Government for (a) corporate welfare grants and support schemes and (b) tax forgone.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220824","220824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173833","2015-01-19","HM Treasury","2015-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of government financial support to business through grants and tax forgone.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220825","220825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173834","2015-01-19","HM Treasury","2015-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the Exchequer of tax relief to businesses since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220826","220826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173835","2015-01-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how often he reviews the cost effectiveness of corporate welfare schemes; and what the criteria are for such schemes to be continued.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220827","220827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173836","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients in Easington constituency have accessed the Cancer Drugs Fund in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220685","220685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173837","2015-01-16","HM Treasury","2015-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has received on the PAYE status of (a) divers and (b) diving supervisors working in the offshore energy industry.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220682","220682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173838","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had about extending the remit of the Cancer Drugs Fund to include access to other cancer treatments such as advanced stereotactic radiotherapy.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220683","220683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173839","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients in Easington constituency have received treatment using advanced stereotactic radiotherapy in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220684","220684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173840","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had on improving access to advanced stereotactic radiotherapy for patients in the North East of England.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220686","220686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173841","2015-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had on how the Government will consult the public about the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220750","220750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173842","2015-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential economic costs and benefits of the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership for the North East of England.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220751","220751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173843","2015-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which organisations he has consulted on the negotiations on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220752","220752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173844","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will issue a direction to the Chief Executive of Network Rail to reply to the letter of 3 June 2014 from the right hon. Member for Tonbridge and Malling, and his subsequent letter pressing for a reply, regarding the establishment of a business and innovation centre at the Station Masters House at Edenbridge Town Station.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220732","220732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173845","2015-01-19","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were admitted to hospital for (a) alcohol-specific and (b) alcohol-related reasons in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220836","220836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173846","2015-01-19","Home Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of registered sex offenders who travel abroad each year.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220823","220823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173847","2015-01-19","Department of Health","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were admitted to A&E departments for (a) alcohol-specific and (b) alcohol-related reasons in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220860","220860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173848","2015-01-19","Department for Education","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were excluded from school for (a) possession and (b) supply of illegal drugs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220861","220861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173849","2015-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of selling alcohol to an intoxicated person in each of the last five years for which data are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220862","220862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174404","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his priorities are for the UK's relationship with Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907114","907114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174410","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in other EU member states on proposals to amend EU treaties.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907093","907093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174576","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take in response to the conclusions of the Vienna Conference on the Humanitarian Impact of Nuclear Weapons, held in December 2014.","Biography information for Dame Joan Ruddock","Dame Joan Ruddock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907116","907116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174577","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the military capability of Hamas.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907115","907115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174578","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of persecution of Christian communities in the Middle East.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907109","907109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174579","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to tackle the persecution of Christians overseas.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907111","907111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174580","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the human rights violations in Jammu and Kashmir.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907108","907108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174581","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the French government on joint counter-terrorism and surveillance activities.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907112","907112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174582","2015-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he next plans to discuss co-operation on security issues with his counterpart in the Pakistan government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907110","907110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173344","2015-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of start-up loans have been taken up by black and minority ethnic people in the last five years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220513","220513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173345","2015-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2015 to Question 219632, whether his Department received any direct or indirect information from people or organisations other than City Link or the administrators (a) orally or (b) in writing before 23 December 2014 that there was a possibility of City Link being placed into administration.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220534","220534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173346","2015-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Insolvency Service provides value for money for creditors of liquidated companies.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220547","220547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173347","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to ensure that shops secure the physical safety of their customers during future Black Friday promotions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220588","220588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173348","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to provide retraining opportunities for (a) former employees of City Link and (b) others who have been made redundant in the parcel delivery sector.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220644","220644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173349","2015-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students started a level 4 apprenticeship in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2011-12 in each parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220667","220667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173350","2015-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students started a level 5 apprenticeship in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2011-12 in each parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220668","220668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173351","2015-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students started a level 6 apprenticeship in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2011-12 in each parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220669","220669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173352","2015-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received from creditors of companies which go into insolvency about the Insolvency Act 1986.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220648","220648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173353","2015-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received from creditors of companies which have gone into liquidation about the priority of payments in cases of liquidation.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220650","220650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173354","2015-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that students undertaking a level 6 diploma in professional dance are consistently regarded as being in higher or further education for the purpose of housing benefit and access to student loans and financial support.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220663","220663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173355","2015-01-16","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's guidance on delivering public value from spending proposals, under what circumstances procuring a system precedes completion of the full business case.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220666","220666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173356","2015-01-16","Cabinet Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will discuss with his counterparts in the devolved administrations the possibility of extending the National Citizen Services to those administrations.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220542","220542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173357","2015-01-16","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-01-13","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what representations his Department has received on allegations of disproportionate investment towards Local Enterprise Partnership board members by (a) the Greater Lincolnshire Local Enterprise Partnership and (b) other Local Enterprise Partnerships; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220532","220532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173359","2015-01-15","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) UK total managed expenditure in nominal sterling, (b) gross domestic product in nominal sterling and (c) percentage total managed expenditure is expressed as a percentage of the gross domestic product; and what the reasons are for the variances from the Public Expenditure Statistical analysis published by his Department in 2014.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220518","220518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173360","2015-01-16","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the Chief Executive of Invest NI.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220521","220521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173361","2015-01-16","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has made to the European Court of Justice in response to its consideration of the VAT treatment of bitcoin transactions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220557","220557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173362","2015-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward proposals to curb excessive pay increases for senior executives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220594","220594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173363","2015-01-15","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to devolve corporation tax to the Northern Ireland Executive.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220597","220597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173364","2015-01-15","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total amount of non-fiscal spending in each year from 2009-10 to 2014-15 is (a) in real terms and (b) as a proportion of total government spending.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220622","220622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173365","2015-01-21","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses were ordered by the Financial Services Ombudsman to award consumers fair compensation up to the 100,000 limit in each year from 2001 to 2011.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220649","220649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173366","2015-01-15","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's non-fiscal spend was in real terms in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13, (e) 2013-14 and (f) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220647","220647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173367","2015-01-15","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria his Department uses to assess the effectiveness of quantitative easing.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220643","220643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173368","2015-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make the provision of broadband and other appropriate telecommunications access mandatory for all new housing and commercial developments.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220548","220548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173369","2015-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department gives to local authorities and housing associations on emergency access to tower blocks and flats for emergency services.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220575","220575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173370","2015-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent steps the Government has taken to tackle Islamophobia.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220514","220514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173371","2015-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has spent on marketing for the Right to Buy scheme in (a) Hammersmith and Fulham and (b) Hammersmith constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220529","220529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173374","2015-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many children live on (a) Army, (b) Royal Navy, (c) Marines and (d) Royal Air Force bases (i) in the UK and (ii) abroad.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220559","220559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173375","2015-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many families are resident on (a) Army, (b) Royal Navy, (c) Marines and (d) Royal Air Force bases (i) in the UK and (ii) abroad.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220560","220560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173376","2015-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to make a formal public acknowledgement of the sacrifice made by British troops deployed to Afghanistan in recent years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220592","220592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173377","2015-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support his Department is offering to Nigeria to help combat Boko Haram.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220628","220628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173378","2015-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to ensure members of the armed forces helping with the Ebola outbreak have adequate protection against the disease.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220629","220629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173379","2015-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether UK armed forces will be employed in training Iraqi and peshmerga brigades to fight against ISIS.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220607","220607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173380","2015-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 13 January 2015, HCWS183, by the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on Nuclear Decommissioning Authority, whether he expects any changes to the programme for the Submarine Dismantling Project as a result of changes announced to NDA Management at Sellafield.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220664","220664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173381","2015-01-15","Department for Education","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of pupils in each primary school in Stourbridge constituency met the required standard of phonic decoding in the 2013-14 academic year.","Biography information for Margot James","Margot James","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220602","220602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173382","2015-01-16","Department for Education","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on keeping Holocaust education part of the national curriculum.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220579","220579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173383","2015-01-16","Department for Education","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to mark Holocaust Memorial Day on 27 January 2015.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220580","220580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173384","2015-01-16","Department for Education","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils in England in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools were classed as persistent truants in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220558","220558"
