"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055118","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to his oral contribution of 5 February 2019, what powers the Domestic Abuse Commissioner will have to investigate matters relating to Practice Direction 12J.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217050","217050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055121","2019-02-08","Department for International Trade","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the new UK-Israel agreement-in-principle contains a territorial clause limiting its application to within Israel’s pre-June 1967 borders.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216931","216931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055124","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the press release entitled Health Secretary announces goal to end HIV transmissions by 2030, published in January 2019, who the members of the expert group will be; when that group will commence work; whether that group is planned to in place until 2030; and whether minutes of that group's meetings will be publicly available.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216932","216932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055127","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the price of cattle and sheep products of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217051","217051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055131","2019-02-08","Department for International Trade","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how his Department defines the territorial scope of pre-existing agreements between the UK and Israel.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216933","216933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055134","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the (a) devolved Administrations and (b) local authority leaders to ensure the continuation of clean air policy across the UK in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217052","217052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055137","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what funding his Department allocates for the restoration of historical (a) retail and (b) hospitality outlets on high streets.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217053","217053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055140","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the detention of (a) unsafe and (b) non-compliant electrical consumer goods at ports and borders in Scotland; and whether he has plans to allocate additional funding for those activities.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217054","217054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055143","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the volume of (a) unsafe and (b) non-compliant electrical consumer goods entering Scotland at its ports and borders.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217055","217055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055146","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what support is made available by the Office for Product Safety and Standards to the Scottish Government to improve safety at ports and borders in scotland.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217056","217056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055150","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions (a) he, (b) ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have had with the representatives of the Scottish Government on the sale of unsafe electrical goods online; and whether he has plans to bring forward legislative proposals for the regulation of the sale of those products online.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217057","217057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055153","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made on the cost to the Scottish economy of the sale of (a) counterfeit and (b) substandard electrical products.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217058","217058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055156","2019-02-08","Women and Equalities","2019-02-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether the EnAble Fund for Elected Office is available to (a) parliamentary candidates (i) seeking selection for the next General Election, (ii) standing in parliamentary by-elections; and if she will publish the Equality Impact Assessment conducted on the scope of that Fund.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217059","217059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055159","2019-02-08","Women and Equalities","2019-02-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the Written Statement of 17 May 2018 on Access to Elected Office for Disabled People, HCWS695, on what date the 12-month programme of work to help political parties encourage and support their candidates started.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217060","217060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055163","2019-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list the (a) countries with which UK armed forces will carry out joint exercises in 2019, (b) dates of those exercises and (c) nature of those exercises.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217061","217061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055166","2019-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Government's (a) aims and (b) objectives will be at the 70 Anniversary Meeting of NATO in April 2019.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216901","216901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055169","2019-02-07","Treasury","2019-02-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the availability of Sharia-compliant home purchase plans.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217062","217062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055173","2019-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 213887 on Jobseeker's Allowance: Disqualification, whether it is her Department’s policy to sanction claimants of universal credit who decline to accept a job with a zero hours contract; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216934","216934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055176","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions has he had with his Malaysian counterpart on the ban on Israeli athletes competing in Paralympics qualifying events in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216959","216959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055179","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect on public safety of the decision to release Abu Bakar Bashir from prison.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216960","216960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055182","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which categories of motorised vehicles are exempt from a requirement to hold third party public liability insurance.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216961","216961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055185","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Thai counterpart on the effect of reform to the law on asylum seekers on refugees in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216962","216962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055188","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2018 to Question 208286 on Rolling Stock: Procurement, what discussions his Department has had with (a) Transport Scotland, (b) Transport for Wales and (c) other devolved transport authorities to ensure a sensible cascade of rolling stock in the event of a delay to the delivery of new trains.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217063","217063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055191","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice,  pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2019 to Question 210641 on Prisons: Drugs, what information his Department holds on the number of incidents where staff may have been exposed to psychoactive substances.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217064","217064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055193","2019-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2019 to Question 210641 on Prisons: Drugs, how many ambulances attended each prison as a result of (a) staff injuries and (b) staff injuries due to exposure to psychoactive substance in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217065","217065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055194","2019-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2019 to Question 210641 on Prisons: Drugs, how many members of staff at each prison were admitted to hospital as a result of exposure to psychoactive substance in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217066","217066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055195","2019-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the new Prison Education Framework and Dynamic Provisioning System contracts on the continuity of education provision in prisons; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217067","217067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055197","2019-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department will take to evaluate the effectiveness of the new Prison Education Framework and Dynamic Provisioning System commissioning model.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217068","217068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055198","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the report entitled, Way to go: improving public transport access to London’s airports, published by London Travel Watch on 18 January 2019, what estimate he has made of the number of people using public transport to reach London airports.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217069","217069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055200","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Pacer trains will continue in service on the northern rail network after December 2019.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217070","217070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055201","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether companies that gain contracts to provide prison education will be required to recognise trades unions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217071","217071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055202","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans to issue a (a) derogation and (b) short-term dispensation for passenger rolling stock which is not compliant with the (i) Rail Vehicle Accessibility Regulations and (ii) Persons with Reduced Mobility Technical Specification for Interoperability after 31 December 2019.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217072","217072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055203","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions have taken place between his Department, Network Rail and Hitachi on electromagnetic compatibility modifications to the Great Western Class 800 fleet.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217073","217073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055205","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what adjustments were required to the IEP contract with Agility Trains to install filters on the Class 800 trains for use on the East Coast mainline; and what the cost was of those installations.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217074","217074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055206","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department undertook a Strategic Environmental Assessment of the draft road investment strategy 2.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217075","217075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055207","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many penalty notices issued as a result of images taken by the camera at the A282 Trunk Road Dartford Crossing Southbound were (a) challenged and (b) found to have been incorrectly issued.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216963","216963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055209","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of penalty notices issued in the last 12 months as a result of images taken by cameras across the country have been challenged by drivers on the grounds that (a) the vehicle was not theirs and (b) the registration number had been read incorrectly.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216964","216964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055210","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding was allocated by his Department to each county in England for (a) Alzheimer's and (b) dementia care per head of the diagnosed population in 2018.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217076","217076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055211","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the funding was per head of population diagnosed with (a) Alzheimer's and (b) other forms of dementia for occupational therapy in each county in England in the 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217077","217077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055212","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many slaughterhouses have (a) complied and (b) not complied with the order to install CCTV; and what steps the Food Standards Agency has taken against those who have failed to comply with that order.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216935","216935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055214","2019-02-07","House of Commons Commission","2019-02-05","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what estimate the Commission has made of the additional cost to the House of Commons of sitting through what was originally intended to be the February recess.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217078","217078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055215","2019-02-07","Cabinet Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office,  what estimate he has made of the additional cost to Government Departments of the House of Commons sitting through what was originally intended to be the February recess.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217079","217079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055216","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the present stage is of Petroleum Oil and Gas Licence 193 within his Department's regulatory roadmap for onshore oil and gas exploration.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217080","217080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055217","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the present stage is of all the Petroleum Oil and Gas Licence areas within his Department's regulatory roadmap for onshore oil and gas exploration.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217081","217081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055218","2019-02-07","Women and Equalities","2019-02-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to her Written Statement of 23 July 2018 on Government Response to Caste Consultation, HCWS898, if she will ensure that (a) the Anti Caste Discrimination Alliance and (b) other non-Government organisations working with victims of caste-based discrimination are able to comment on and input into that draft guidance.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217082","217082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055219","2019-02-07","Women and Equalities","2019-02-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to her Written Statement of 23 July 2018 on Government Response to Caste Consultation, HCWS898, whether the guidance for employers, service providers and public authorities will be statutory guidance linked to the relevant sections of the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217083","217083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055220","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to Sporting Future: A New Strategy for an Active Nation, published in December 2015, what progress his Department has made on establishing a network of employers that will bring together organisations keen to support and encourage their staff to be more physically active.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217148","217148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055221","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department has allocated for special needs provision in schools in Nottinghamshire in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217149","217149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055223","2019-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of people who have a neurological condition applying for assessment for (a) personal independence payment and (b) employment and support allowance who are assessed by an appropriate health care professional for that neurological condition in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216965","216965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055224","2019-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions (a) she, (b) Ministers and (c) officials of her Department have had with charities and third sector bodies on the overall competence and expertise of health care professionals who assess people with neurological conditions for (i) personal independence payment and (ii) employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216966","216966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055225","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether a decision has been made by the Oil and Gas Authority in relation to Petroleum Oil and Gas Licence (PEDL) 193 to move that PEDL into the Production Term on 1 July 2019.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217084","217084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055226","2019-02-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many (a) economy class, (b) business class and (c) first-class tickets for air travel his Department has purchased in each of the past two years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217085","217085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055227","2019-02-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many (a) standard and (b) first-class tickets for train travel his Department has purchased in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217086","217086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055230","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to bring wild animals within the scope of the Animal Welfare (Licensing of Activities Involving Animals) (England) Regulations 2018 once the Welfare of Wild Animals in Travelling Circuses (England) Regulations 2012 expire in January 2020.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216967","216967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055231","2019-02-07","Treasury","2019-02-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much of the £650 million that HMRC has collected from employers since 2016 in relation to disguised remuneration schemes has come from (a) PAYE and national insurance contributions on loans made to employees under an employment benefit trust scheme and (b) penalties and fines due to the failure of employers to register those schemes under the disclosure of tax avoidance schemes process.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216968","216968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055232","2019-02-07","Treasury","2019-02-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of employers who paid employees through an employment benefit trust scheme have paid the PAYE contributions deemed due.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216969","216969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055234","2019-02-07","Treasury","2019-02-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Loan Charge 2019, whether employees will be exempt from paying taxes in relation to those loans in cases where employers have paid PAYE on loans given to their employees through an employment benefit trust scheme since 1999.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216970","216970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055235","2019-02-07","Treasury","2019-02-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Loan Charge 2019, whether he has published a list of scheme providers that have paid taxes on loans given to individuals through an employment benefit trust scheme since 1999.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216971","216971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055236","2019-02-07","Treasury","2019-02-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Loan Charge 2019, what safeguards his Department has put in place to prevent double taxation in cases where the taxes now due on employment benefit trust loans have already been collected from scheme providers.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216972","216972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055237","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to increase the production of energy from low-carbon renewable sources.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217150","217150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055238","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department spent on advertising directly to men who have sex with men to inform them of recent changes to the rules on blood donation.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216936","216936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055239","2019-02-07","Department for International Development","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to provide humanitarian support to vulnerable children in the demilitarised zone in Idleb, Syria.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217088","217088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055240","2019-02-07","Department for International Development","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support Somalia in preparing for future droughts.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217089","217089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055241","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of the motorway network in England and Wales are Smart motorways.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217090","217090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055242","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timeframe is for the roll-out of Smart motorways throughout England and Wales.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217091","217091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055243","2019-02-07","Department for International Development","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to prevent child marriage in Somalia.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217092","217092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055244","2019-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2019 to Question 212389, what estimate she has made of the number of couples affected in (a) 2019-20, (b) 2020-21 and (c) 2021-22 of the changes to be introduced in May 2019 to the eligibility for pension credit of couples where one partner has reached state pension age and the other has not.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217093","217093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055245","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his oral contribution of 17 January 2019, Official Report, column 1346, what the evidential basis was for his statement that the costs of the proposed Swansea Tidal Lagoon project were three times that of Hinkley Point C.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216891","216891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055246","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of a case being taken to the First-tier Special Educational Needs and Disability tribunal .","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216902","216902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055248","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his oral contribution of 17 January 2019, Official Report, column 1346, what the evidential basis is for the statement that a full programme of tidal lagoons would make a tiny contribution to the UK's energy supply at a much greater cost than nuclear generation.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216892","216892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055249","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support the UK steel industry in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217094","217094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055250","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to support parents and carers in the education, health and care need assessment process.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216903","216903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055251","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children and young people who have speech, language and communication needs as their primary need are (a) 0-5, (b) 5-16, (c) 16-18 and (d) 18-25 years old; and how many have Education, Health and Care plans there are for each of those age groups.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216904","216904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055253","2019-02-08","Cabinet Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Government press release New expert brought in to boost government’s relationship with small businesses, published in February 2019, for how many hours per week the Small Business Crown Representative is employed by the Government; and what the salary of that position is.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217151","217151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055254","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which EU countries the Government has secured bilateral health agreements with in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216905","216905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055255","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to allocate additional funding to support biomedical research into the diagnosis and treatment of myalgic encephalomyelitis.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216906","216906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055256","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what measures his Department plans to use to evaluate the effectiveness of its guidance entitled Improving the home learning environment, published on 14 November 2018.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216907","216907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055257","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times Government ministers (a) sought and (b) were granted authorisation under the Consolidated Guidance between 2015 and 2017.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216908","216908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055258","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 May 2018 to Question HL7925, how the organisation that is managing the integrated physical and mental health assessments for looked-after children identifies and meets the speech, language and communication needs of those children.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216909","216909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055259","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of political prisoners in Bahrain.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217152","217152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055260","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2019 to Question 209278 on Mental Health Services, (a) what proportion of people aged 18 and over in contact with National Health Service-funded secondary mental health services the 4,224 figure represents and (b) how his Department defines a speech related disability.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216910","216910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055262","2019-02-07","Treasury","2019-02-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has made to support the Steel Industry once it loses access to the Research Fund for Coal and Steel as part of the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217095","217095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055263","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people who previously had (a) no, (b) between one and four, (c) between five and nine, (d) between 10 and 15, (e) between 16 and 25, (f) between 26 and 50, (g) between 51 and 75, (h) between 76 and 100 and (i) 101 or more convictions, were convicted in each of the last three years but did not receive an immediate custodial sentence.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217153","217153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055264","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons his Department destroyed files on Sri Lanka dating from the 1970s and 1980s.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217096","217096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055266","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timeframe is for the (a) completion of the programme of works and (b) new facilities to be open to patients at the Royal Liverpool Hospital.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216973","216973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055267","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, at what speeds High Speed 2 trains are planned to operate on the High Speed 2 Phase one section.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216883","216883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055269","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timeframe is for the commencement of tunnelling works for HS2 in Buckinghamshire.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216884","216884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055270","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what comparative assessment he has made of year on year trends in the level of business insolvencies in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216974","216974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055271","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the most recent estimate is of the number of HS2 Ltd workers planned to be housed near the Phase one line in the Chesham and Amersham and Aylesbury constituencies.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216885","216885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055272","2019-02-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to encourage local authorities to carry out housing needs assessments in villages that have not been allocated housing within local plans, but where there is likely to be a local need for housing.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217097","217097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055274","2019-02-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to promote housing development in areas where there is an identified local need but no housing allocation in the local plan.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217098","217098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055275","2019-02-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities use access to broadband and mobile connectivity as a criterion within their settlement hierarchy assessments.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217099","217099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055276","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which local authorities have been required to sign non disclosure agreements with HS2 Ltd since 2010.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216886","216886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055277","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the results of the review into the business case for High Speed Two Phase 1 will be published.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216887","216887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055278","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the US withdrawal from the Intermediate Range Nuclear Forces Treaty, whether US intermediate-range nuclear weapons be accepted for deployment within UK land borders.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217100","217100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055279","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2019 to Question 211069 on Speech Therapy: Training, which professionals does he envisage the statutory Code of Practice will detail as those who can become Approved Mental Capacity Professionals.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216911","216911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055281","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will list the (a) Government departments, b) executive agencies and (c) non-departmental public bodies that have contributed to the Cross-Government Suicide Prevention Plan.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216975","216975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055282","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish an estimate of the costs to the economy of the closures of Euston station due to High Speed Two preparations.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216888","216888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055283","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department has spent on preparations for the Adult Social Care Green Paper since 7 March 2017.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216976","216976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055285","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of his Department’s budget has been spent on preparations for the Adult Social Care Green Paper since 7 March 2017.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217101","217101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055286","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many ministerial meetings have been held between his Department and (a) HM Treasury, (b) the Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government and (c) the Prime Minister’s Office in relation to the Adult Social Care Green Paper since 7 March 2017.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217102","217102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055287","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many meetings have been held between his Department and civil society organisations in relation to the Adult Social Care Green Paper since 7 March 2017.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217103","217103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055288","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which residential and nursing homes he has visited in an official capacity since 9 July 2018; and what the date was of each such visit.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217104","217104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055289","2019-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to NHS Digital's Adult Psychiatric Morbidity Survey 2014, what assessment she has made of the factors contributing to attempted suicide rates of employment and support allowance claimants relative to the non-claimant population.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216977","216977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055290","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to end the use of wild animals in circuses in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216893","216893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055291","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the competitiveness of solar power.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216978","216978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055293","2019-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times her Department has received information on the activities of benefit claimants from territorial police forces in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216979","216979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055294","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the causes of recent supply shortages of Ganfort and Toptiqom.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216912","216912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055295","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what fees (a) have already been paid and (b) are due to be paid to (i) WSP and (ii) WilkinsonEyre for design work on High Speed Two.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216894","216894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055296","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether proposals for projects using Official Development Assistance funds are evaluated by civil servants within his Department.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217105","217105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055297","2019-02-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many ongoing workstreams there are throughout central Government on preparations for leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216980","216980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055298","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department's Official Development Assistance-funded projects are evaluated by civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217106","217106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055299","2019-02-08","Department for International Development","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what staff resources her Department provides to (a) the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, (b) the Foreign and Commonwealth Office and (c) the Home Office to support the evaluation of Official Development Assistance-funded (i) project proposals and (ii) completed projects.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217107","217107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055301","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of speech and language therapists in the NHS.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216937","216937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055302","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Bahraini counterpart on reports of sexual violence against female detainees in Bahrain.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217154","217154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055303","2019-02-08","Treasury","2019-02-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish his review of the costs of High Speed Two.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216895","216895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055305","2019-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on the assessment study on the future of Hyde Park Barracks, as part of the Defence Estate Optimisation programme.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216981","216981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055306","2019-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of their annual recruitment target for regular personnel in 2018-19 has so far been achieved by (a) the Royal Navy, (b) the Army, (c) the Royal Air Force and (d) the Royal Marines.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216982","216982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055307","2019-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 214641 on Personal Independence Payment: Appeals, what estimate she has made of the clearance times for mandatory reconsiderations for personal independence payments (a) nationally and (b) in the North East of England in (i) November 2018, (ii) December 2018 and (iii) January 2019.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217155","217155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055308","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his oral contribution of 4 February 2019, Official Report column 73, how many car manufacturers operating in the UK have (a) applied successfully, (b) applied unsuccessfully and (c) not applied for support through those programmes conducted independently of the Government.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216983","216983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055310","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the quantity of drugs having to be disposed of by NHS pharmacies; and what reasons are given for the disposal of those drugs.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216984","216984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055311","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to enable NHS pharmacies to redistribute sealed quantities of drugs that would otherwise become surplus and remain unused, for approved medical purposes (a) in the UK or (b) as part of the UK's international development programme.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216985","216985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055312","2019-02-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answers of 24 January 2019 to Question 210599 and 04 February 2019 to Question 214122, whether his Department has informed building owners of the categorisation of the non-aluminium composite material cladding samples that they submitted to the Building Research Establishment for testing.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217108","217108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055313","2019-02-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2019 to Question 210599 and the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 214122, whether his Department has established the European fire classification of each of the 1,421 non-aluminium composite material cladding samples submitted to the Building Research Establishment for testing.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217109","217109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055314","2019-02-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 214559 on Buildings: Insulation, what assessment was carried out by his Department's Independent Expert Advisory Panel to conclude that the BS 8414 is a robust test; if he will publish that assessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217110","217110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055315","2019-02-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 214559 on Buildings: Insulation, whether the BS 8414 test methodology has changed since the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217111","217111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055317","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support he plans to provide to enable the new radiotherapy operational delivery networks to work collaboratively across multiple centres.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217112","217112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055318","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to ensure that the new radiotherapy operational delivery networks have an adequate level of IT infrastructure to work collaboratively.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217113","217113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055319","2019-02-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on children receiving social care of the decision to distribute the social care support grant via the adult social care relative needs formula rather than the children’s services relative needs formula.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217114","217114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055320","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many disabled candidates have undertaken written assessments in the recruitment process for jobs in the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency in the last 24 months; and of those candidates how many (a) necessitated reasonable adjustments to be made and (b) were appointed.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217115","217115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055321","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many applicants for jobs at the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency have (a) declared themselves as disabled and (b) been successful (i) in the sift and (ii) at interview at each grade in each year since the agency was established.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217116","217116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055322","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many applicants for jobs at the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency who declared themselves as disabled applied under the guaranteed interview scheme in each year since the agency was established.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217117","217117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055323","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many candidates at each grade have been successful at interview for job roles in the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency under its Guaranteed Interview scheme.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217118","217118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055324","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff grievances were lodged with the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency by grade of staff who (a) lodged those grievances and (b) had those grievances lodged against them in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217119","217119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055325","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff grievances were upheld by the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency by grade of staff lodging those grievances in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217120","217120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055327","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff grievances raised at the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency (DVSA) were lodged by (a) contingent labour staff and (b) the DVSA against contingent labour staff.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217121","217121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055328","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff grievances raised at the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency related to bullying and harassment in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217122","217122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055329","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff grievances raised at the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency for bullying and harassment in each of the last two financial years were upheld; and what the grade of the staff member raising those grievance was.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217123","217123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055331","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the driving test pass rate  by the gender of the candidate (a) was before 4 December 2017 when changes to the test were introduced to include following instructions on a Sat Nav and (b) is currently.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217124","217124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055332","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) male and (b) female driving examiners are employed by the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217125","217125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055333","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many driving examiners with Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency delegated examiner status are (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217126","217126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055334","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many driving examiners have Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency delegated examiner status; and how many delegated examiners conduct (a) car tests, (b) LGV tests and (c) motorcycle tests.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217127","217127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055335","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the pass rate is for (a) car tests, (b) LGV tests and (c) motorcycle tests conducted by Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency delegated examiners.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217128","217128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055336","2019-02-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he has had discussions with EU Ministers on the Schengen 90/180 rule and extending UK citizen's rights; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216938","216938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055337","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the pass rate for driving tests conducted Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency delegated examiners (a) was before 4 December 2017 when changes to the test were introduced to include following instructions on a Sat Nav and (b) is currently.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217129","217129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055338","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on proposals made by Border Force on technological solutions to monitor the movement of people across the border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216986","216986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055339","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the remit of the National County Lines Coordination Centre is.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217156","217156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055341","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether funding for the new radiotherapy operational delivery networks will be allocated from the £20.5 billion of additional funding announced by the Government in 2018.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217130","217130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055342","2019-02-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in the Banff and Buchan constituency have received Cold Weather Payments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217131","217131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055344","2019-02-07","Scotland Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what progress has been made in the devolution of cold weather payments to the Scottish Government.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217132","217132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055345","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the number of animals slaughtered without prior stunning in the UK of the UK's recent agreement with Saudi Arabia to lift the ban on lamb exports to that country.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216987","216987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055346","2019-02-08","Northern Ireland Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the timetable is for (a) her Department's publication of its response to its consultation on addressing the legacy of Northern Ireland's past and (b) the Government bringing forward legislative proposals on that matter.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216988","216988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055347","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department provides to local authorities on the restriction of vehicle exhaust fumes close to school premises at the opening and closing times of those premises.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216989","216989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055348","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2018 to Question 199271 and paragraph 20 of the National Crime Agency’s January 2019 report entitled County lines drug supply, Vulnerability and Harm 2018, whether he plans to gather information about children under 10 years of age involved in county lines.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216939","216939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055349","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Drug Dealing Telecommunications Restriction Orders Regulations 2017 on preventing the growth of the county lines drug trade.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216940","216940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055350","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to work with mobile phone network providers to help minimise disruption to those networks for British customers in the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216990","216990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055352","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent meetings his Department has had with representatives of (a) Addison Lee, (b) BlaBlaCar, (c) Gett, (d) HOPP (Taxify), (e) Kabee, (f) mytaxi and (g) other taxi, minicab and private hire vehicle companies on the county lines drug trade.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216941","216941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055353","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent meetings his Department has had with representatives of (a) Abellio Greater Anglia, (b) Great Northern, (c) London Overground and (d) Network Rail on the county lines drug trade.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216942","216942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055354","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to introduce a national missing persons database.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216943","216943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055355","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2018 to Question 202794 on the NHS's comprehensive assessment of supply lines, whether his Department conducted analysis of the data on supply chain reviews throughout the health and care system; and whether his Department plans to publish the results of the analysis it has so conducted.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217133","217133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055356","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether all sheep meat exported to India under the Government's new agreement announced on 5 December 2018 will be from animals that were stunned before slaughter.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216991","216991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055357","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2018 to Question 202793 on Hospitals: Medical Equipment, when the Government plans to publish its plans on keeping an open border to maintain the supply of medical equipment to the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217134","217134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055358","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much HS2 Ltd has spent on agency staff since July 2018; and how many agency staff from which agencies that spending was so spent on.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216896","216896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055359","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2019 to Question 204488 and with reference to (a) waiting times, (b) staff vacancies and (c) medicine supplies, how specifically leaving the EU will lay the foundation for a strong NHS.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217135","217135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055360","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 214031 on Mental Health and Employers Independent Review, on what date the Work Leadership Council next plans to meet.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217136","217136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055361","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether (a) he, (b) ministers of his Department and (c) officials of his Department have met representatives of Uber in the last two years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216992","216992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055363","2019-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to increase the cyber skill capability of the armed forces.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216993","216993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055364","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to support tech start-ups.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216994","216994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055365","2019-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of FGM offences in the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216995","216995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055366","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers have served in Havering in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216996","216996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055367","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many offences involving acid attacks have been committed in (a) London and (b) Havering Borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216997","216997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055368","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many offences involving religious extremism have been committed in (a) London and (b) Havering Borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216998","216998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055369","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the outcomes of the live facial recognition trial recently undertaken by police forces.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216999","216999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055370","2019-02-07","Department for International Development","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has plans to provide financial assistance for a new parliament in the British Overseas Territory of Montserrat.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217000","217000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055371","2019-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to ask the US Air Force to speed up repairs of the runway on Ascension Island.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217001","217001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055373","2019-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department is making on improving communications with the Department for International Development on matters relating to the British Overseas Territories of St Helena and Ascension Island airports.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217002","217002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055374","2019-02-07","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the potential financial effects of the backstop on UK trading opportunities with the rest of the world after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217003","217003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055375","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the UK Government's official recognition of Juan Guaido as interim president of Venezuela, what steps the UK Government is taking to support the promotion of peace in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217004","217004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055377","2019-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government is taking steps to ensure that EU companies will no longer have an automatic right to bid on defence and security contracts after the 29 March 2019 in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217005","217005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055378","2019-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the size of the Royal Navy fleet (a) was in 2013 and (b) is in 2019.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217006","217006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055379","2019-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to strengthen the defence and security relationship between the UK and Japan.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217007","217007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055381","2019-02-07","Department for International Trade","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to improve communications with the Department for Exiting the European Union to ensure that areas of dual responsibility are most effectively addressed.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217008","217008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055382","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date his Department began the practice of using Zimbabwean embassy officials to interview Zimbabwean failed asylum seekers; what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the safety of those individuals of engaging with the Zimbabwean Embassy; what discussions he has had with the Zimbabwean diaspora on this practice; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216944","216944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055973","2019-02-11","Attorney General","2019-02-05","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 213932 on Crown Prosecution Service: West Midlands, what the change has been in the number of offences for each crime type in (a) the West Midlands and (b) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217441","217441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1052351","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what comparative assessment (a) his Department and (b) Public Health England has made of the health effects of (a) PM 0.1 and (b) PM 1 in those parts of England (i) with and (ii) without waste incineration plants.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 215078","215078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054021","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-02-04","What steps his Department is taking to increase the quality of apprenticeships.","Biography information for Trudy Harrison","Trudy Harrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908970","908970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054022","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-02-04","What recent comparative assessment he has made of education funding in England and in other countries.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908971","908971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054023","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-02-04","What steps his Department has taken to strengthen the teaching profession.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908972","908972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054024","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-02-04","What steps his Department is taking to increase the quality of apprenticeships.","Biography information for James Morris","James Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908973","908973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054025","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-02-04","What recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of teaching early literacy through phonics.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908974","908974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054026","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-02-04","What steps his Department has taken to raise educational standards in schools.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908975","908975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054027","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-02-04","What recent comparative assessment he has made of education funding in England and in other countries.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908976","908976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054028","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-02-04","What steps he is taking to ensure that (a) academies and (b) local authority maintained schools comply with section 2 of the Further Education and Technical Act 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908969","908969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054559","2019-02-06","Treasury","2019-02-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that UK firms are prevented from avoiding tax by merging with dormant EEA companies under EU Single Market Rules.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216230","216230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054560","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the paper entitled The UK future skills-based immigration system, published by the Home Office on 19 December 2018, what discussions he has had with his Cabinet colleagues on the effect of the recently announced skills-based immigration system on (a) the food and farming sector and (b) the UK’s security of food supply.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216166","216166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054562","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the end of NHS student bursaries for radiography courses on (a) the number of diagnostic tests undertaken  and (b) trends in the level of the workforce recruitment and retention in radiotherapy.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216168","216168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054563","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has for the planting of trees and other natural carbon capturing plants.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216358","216358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054564","2019-02-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure proposed new permitted development rights do not adversely affect the quality of housing with respect to (a) size and (b) safety regulations.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216359","216359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054565","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to support local authorities who have overspent on SEND budgets.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216360","216360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054566","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the total overspend of SEND budgets by local authorities in the financial year 2017-18.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216361","216361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054567","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to slow biodiversity loss in the UK.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216362","216362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054568","2019-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to provide a support package for farmers in the event of an livestock disease outbreak.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216169","216169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054569","2019-02-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding his Department has allocated to the Moorside Nuclear Power station project in Cumbria since February 2017.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216170","216170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054570","2019-02-06","Department for International Development","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department are taking to tackle the stigma associated with HIV in developing countries to ensure that to ensure people seek access to treatment.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216231","216231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054571","2019-02-06","Department for International Development","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to tackle inequality and discrimination against disabled people in developing countries.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216232","216232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054572","2019-02-06","Department for International Development","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development,  what steps her Department is taking to develop long-term economic sustainability in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216233","216233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054573","2019-02-06","Department for International Development","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment her Department has made of how technology can be used to help achieve the UK’s development priorities in respect of (a) health, (b) agriculture and (c) disaster preparedness.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216234","216234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054574","2019-02-07","Women and Equalities","2019-02-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the timetable is for the publication of the Government's response to the Gender Recognition Act consultation.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216235","216235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054576","2019-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to introduce compulsory recycling for commercial trade waste producers.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216236","216236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054577","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his policy is on the provision on the NHS of spinal implants for pain relief.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216237","216237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054578","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information he holds on the number of people admitted to hospital as a result of the heatwave during summer 2018.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216238","216238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054579","2019-02-06","Cabinet Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many cases of skin cancer there have been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216239","216239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054580","2019-02-06","Cabinet Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many children aged 16 and under have been diagnosed with cancer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216240","216240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054581","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been living with a diagnosis of rheumatoid arthritis in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216241","216241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054582","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to prevent deaths in twin babies.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216242","216242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054583","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the rate of post-operative infection in cancer patients.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216243","216243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054584","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has received on the correlation between sugar intake and Alzheimer's.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216244","216244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054585","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support people in preventing glucose spikes in their blood sugar.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216245","216245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054586","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he is taking steps to ensure a reduction in the overall amount of anti-depressants prescribed for children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216246","216246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054587","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with its counterpart in Ecuador on building economic ties with the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216247","216247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054588","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with its counterpart in China on reducing the effects of climate change.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216248","216248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054589","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Algerian counterpart on illegal immigration from that country to the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216249","216249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054590","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his (a) US and (b) Saudi Arabian counterparts on the effect of Iranian activity on the accessibility to shipping of the Persian Gulf.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216250","216250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054591","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has had recent discussions with the Government of Tunisia on encouraging increased UK tourism to that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216251","216251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054592","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that advances in medicines by Israel are shared with the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216252","216252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054593","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Government of Turkey on the strength of its (a) economy and (b) currency.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216253","216253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054594","2019-02-06","Department for International Development","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions her Department has had with the Government of Iraq on tackling the (a) number of displaced people and (b) need for housing in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216254","216254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054595","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Government of Pakistan since the last election in that country; and what recent (a) military and (b) economic assistance has been offered to improve co-operation between the UK and Pakistan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216255","216255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054596","2019-02-06","Treasury","2019-02-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much gift aid have charities based in Scotland received in each of the last three years.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216364","216364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054597","2019-02-06","Department for International Development","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress she has made on expanding administrative operations for her Department in Scotland.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216365","216365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054598","2019-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the article in the Express entitled A fifth of British troops are too unfit to fight warns former Armed Forces chief, published on 25 February 2018, whether a fifth of soldiers are unfit for overseas action; and what work his Department is doing to ensure soldiers are fit for action.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216134","216134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054599","2019-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential fiscal effect of leaving the EU without a deal on his Department's operation and management of prisons.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216366","216366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054600","2019-02-06","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what was the total number of attempts by persons who were suspected migrants to enter Kent by small boat in (a) October 2018, (b) November 2018, (c) December 2018 and (d) January 2019.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216256","216256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054601","2019-02-06","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many payments have been made to France under Article 7 of the Sandhurst Treaty 2018 under each heading.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216257","216257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054602","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Pakistan on the maintenance of human rights in Pakistan.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216258","216258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054603","2019-02-06","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what action has been taken under Article 8 of the Sandhurst Treaty 2018; and what payments have been made by each of the contracting states in connection with such action.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216259","216259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054604","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Egypt on the maintenance of human rights in Egypt.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216260","216260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054605","2019-02-06","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish details of the joint approach that has been implemented under Article 8 of the Sandhurst Treaty 2018; and if he will place copies of the (a) minutes and (b) other relevant documents relating to that joint approach the Library.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216261","216261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054606","2019-02-06","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the number of visa applicants who have not received an Immigration Surcharge Number as a result of that number being provided to those applicants' legal representatives and not those applicants directly; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216262","216262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054607","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans his Department has for future cooperation and collaboration on security and defence policy with the EU27 nations in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216263","216263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054608","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps is his Department taking to maintain capacity for effective diplomatic relations with EU27 countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216264","216264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054609","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has for the electrification of the Transpennine express line.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216265","216265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054610","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the NAO report entitled Pressures on children’s social care, published on 23 January 2019, what level of local variation his Department regards as acceptable in the amount of money spent per child in residential care.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216266","216266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054611","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the NAO report entitled Pressures on children’s social care, published on 23 January 2019, whether his Department has identified what level of local variation it regards as acceptable in the thresholds for action within children’s social care.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216267","216267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054612","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference page 36 of the NAO report entitled Pressures on children's social care, published on 23 January 2019, what progress his Department has made on the effect of deprivation on (a) demand for and (b) activity within children's social care.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216268","216268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054613","2019-02-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2018 to Question 908852, what assessment he has made of the effect of plans for increased housing in Swale on access to primary health care in that area.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216269","216269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054614","2019-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of non-road traffic workplace accident claims that will be affected by the increase to the small claims limit.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216270","216270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054615","2019-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the percentage of non-road traffic accident cases for workplace claims that will move from the fast track to small claims track due to the proposed increases to the small claims limit.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216271","216271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054616","2019-02-06","Treasury","2019-02-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of delaying the introduction of Making Tax Digital.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216367","216367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054617","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Times article entitled Abortion is like crimes of Nazis, campaigners tell pupils in school, published on 31 January 2019, if he will take steps to ensure Ofsted consider the accuracy of health education information provided at those schools.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216272","216272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054618","2019-02-06","Department for Transport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the publication of the Government response to the consultation on the application of EU Regulation 1071/2009 and proposed exemptions for community transport providers operating for non-commercial purposes.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216368","216368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054619","2019-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2019 to Question 213323 on Universal Credit, what steps her Department takes to monitor and record repayments of Support for Mortgage Interest.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216273","216273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054620","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who has responsibility for assisting EU citizens with reduced capacity complete their applications to the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216369","216369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054621","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance his Department has provided to local authorities to help them assist vulnerable EU citizens complete their applications to the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216370","216370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054622","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to address the high level of cocaine found in eels in the River Thames.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216371","216371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054623","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) budget and (b) force-level allocations of the Police Transformation Fund are for each year since its inception including planned spend for 2019-20.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216372","216372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054625","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons the EU Exit: ID Document Check app does not work on a desktop or laptop computer.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216274","216274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054627","2019-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have been on a DS1500 for over three years have had their benefits (a) reviewed and (b) withdrawn; and what conditions did they have.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216173","216173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054628","2019-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which medical bodies and clinicians the Chief Medical Officer liaised with to develop the guidance in the benefit system on terminal illness.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216174","216174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054629","2019-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer on 11 January 2019 to Question 203813, how many applications were subsequently successful of claimants who died after registering but prior to her Department making a decision on their claim.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216175","216175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054630","2019-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer on 11 January 2019 to Question 203813, how many claimants who died after registering but prior to her Department making a decision on their claim subsequently received a payment to their estate.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216176","216176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054631","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Home Affairs, with reference to his oral contribution of 5 September 2018, Official Report, column 169, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the new power to detain people at the UK border to determine whether they are engaged in hostile state activity on the security of the UK.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216177","216177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054632","2019-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2019 to Question 203813, how many people applied for carer’s allowance in relation to personal independence payment claimants who died after registering but prior to her Department making a decision on their claim.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216178","216178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054633","2019-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are on the severe conditions criteria list; how long those people have been on that list; and what conditions they have.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216179","216179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054634","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish the final part of his review of the support for children in need.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216373","216373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054635","2019-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department determines that a claimant has a health condition or disability that qualifies them to apply for personal independence payment at the point of (a) testing, (b) diagnosis or (c) treatment.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216180","216180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054636","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to allocate funding to (a) local authorities and (b) clinical commissioning groups to achieve the national target of reducing the number of smokers during pregnancy to six per cent by 2022; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216135","216135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054637","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for School Standards of 28 January 2019, Official Report, column 622, how many temporarily excluded pupils were not in full-time education by the sixth school day of their exclusion in 2017-18.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216374","216374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054638","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, under what circumstances his Department will request the return of funding allocated to local authorities that dispose of or change the use of buildings or assets funded wholly or partly through Sure Start capital grants.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216375","216375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054639","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the most recent assessment is of the benefit cost ratio for phase 2B of HS2; and whether an assessment has been made of the potential merits of running 14 trains an hour at 195mph.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216275","216275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054640","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to review his Department's guidance on behaviour and discipline in schools.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216376","216376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054641","2019-02-06","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to assessment the effectiveness of the allocation of funds from the Early Intervention Fund.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216377","216377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054642","2019-02-06","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential relationship between school exclusions and youth violence.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216378","216378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054643","2019-02-06","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) average time is and (b) longest time it has taken for a family subject to No Recourse to Public Funds conditions to achieve settled status.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216276","216276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054644","2019-02-06","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children are living in households with parents subject to No Recourse to Public Funds.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216277","216277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054645","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make representations to the Children’s Commissioner on that office undertaking an assessment of the effect on children of their parents being subject to no recourse to public funds.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216278","216278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054646","2019-02-11","Cabinet Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the amount of funding over £50,000 allocated to country programmes under the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund in 2018-19.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216181","216181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054647","2019-02-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the (a) budget and (b) costs have been for his Department's offices on King Charles Street, London in 2019.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216182","216182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054648","2019-02-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which properties on his Department's assets register were worth over £5 million at 31 March 2018.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216183","216183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054649","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timeframe is for the Crossrail station at Slough to be operational.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216379","216379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054650","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance his Department has issued to people applying under EU Settled Status Scheme who have resided in the UK for more than five years but would only qualify as EU national for less than five years.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216279","216279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054651","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance his Department has issued to people applying for EU Settled Status who are not computer literate.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216280","216280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054652","2019-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make representations to Motability on the allocation of funding to provide vehicles to children under the age of three that rely on bulky medical equipment from donations received from Motability operations.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216380","216380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054653","2019-02-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2019 to Question 212620 on Mash Holdings: Company Accounts, what steps have been taken to ensure that MASH Holdings will file those accounts with Companies House; and what the timeframe is for those accounts to be publicly available.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216281","216281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054654","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the accuracy of reports that the Indonesian Armed Forces used Chemical weapons on West Papuan civilians on 15 December 2018.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216381","216381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054655","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether EU nationals that have resided in the UK for (a) under and (b) over 10 years will be able to travel outside of the UK on a two week vacation without that affecting their (i) right to return and (ii) other legal rights to reside in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216282","216282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054656","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of electricity used in England and Wales was derived from renewable energy sources in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216136","216136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054657","2019-02-07","Treasury","2019-02-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has any plans to establish a UK Infrastructure Bank.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216137","216137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054658","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will list the (a) unsuccessful bids and (b) cost of those bids to the Home Office Early Intervention Youth Fund.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216382","216382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054659","2019-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much money has been reimbursed to the public purse by the US Administration for the cost of services provided by the Ministry of Defence Police at RAF Menwith Hill in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216383","216383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054660","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  if he will hold meetings with families of children with ceroid lipofuscinosis type 2 disease on the availability of Brineura on the NHS.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216384","216384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054661","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timeframe is for NICE to publish its review of the Highly Specialised Technologies process.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216385","216385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054662","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has plans to second a portion of its workforce to the Department for Exiting the European Union over the next six weeks.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216118","216118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054663","2019-02-07","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the current total headcount is of his Department's workforce.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216119","216119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054664","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many civil servants from his Department have been seconded to the Department for Exiting the European Union since 1 January  2019.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216120","216120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054665","2019-02-07","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many (a) current and (b) former civil servants have been seconded to work at his Department since its creation.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216121","216121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054666","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many civil servants in his Department work on the (a) free school and (b) adoption policy streams; and how many civil servants worked on those streams in June 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216122","216122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054667","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect the delivery of his Department's policy streams of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216123","216123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054668","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of staff from his Department that will be seconded to the Department for Exiting the European Union to prepare for UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216138","216138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054669","2019-02-06","Cabinet Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants will be transferred from the Department for Education to the Department for Exiting the European Union.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216139","216139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054670","2019-02-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to maintain funding for the Community Housing Fund after March 2020.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216386","216386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054671","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2019 to Question 212586 on Incinerators: Health Hazards, will he will publish the (a) reports and (b) evidence considered by Public Health England.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216110","216110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054672","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2018 to Question 212589 on Incinerators: Health Hazards, which reports provided via the url link in that Answer reference PM0.1 and PM1 emissions from incinerators.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216111","216111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054673","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report entitled, Statement on the evidence for differential health effects of particulate matter according to source or component, published by COMEAP in March 2015, if he will direct (a) Public Health England and (b) COMEAP to commission research into the levels of toxicity of particulate matter from different sources.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216112","216112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054674","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his policys of the results of the study entitled Characterisation of elemental in PM2.5 in a medium sized Swedish city dominated by a modern waste incinerator plant, published in X-Ray Spectrometry in 2006.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216124","216124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054675","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2019 to Question 212303 on Air Pollution: Research, what proportion of the £1billion will be allocated to research into the health effects of ultrafine particles from incinerators.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216125","216125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054676","2019-02-06","Department for International Development","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on programmes tackling malaria in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216283","216283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054677","2019-02-06","Department for International Development","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on programmes tackling Neglected Tropical Diseases in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216284","216284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054678","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much the NHS spent on private contractors for residential care for patients with a diagnosis of autism in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216285","216285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054679","2019-02-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many full-time equivalent employees his Department employed in each directorate of his Department in each financial since 2009-10; and what estimate he has made of the number of full-time equivalent staff that will be employed in those directorates in each financial year to 2020-21.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216126","216126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054680","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2019 to Question 211336 on Commonwealth Games 2022, what discussions he held with the Prime Minister prior to the appointment of Non-Executive Directors to the Birmingham Organising Committee for the 2022 Commonwealth Games.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216387","216387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054681","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has plans to introduce screening questions to patients at A&E Departments to reduce waiting times.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216184","216184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054682","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on patient health of regular instances of concussion.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216185","216185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054683","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support is provided to women who suffer from postnatal depression.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216186","216186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054684","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of enabling pharmacists to issue low-strength prescription drugs to reduce the workload for GPs.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216187","216187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054685","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking reduce the use of antibiotics by people that have (a) a cold and (b) influenza.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216188","216188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054686","2019-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people who assaulted emergency services staff were given custodial sentences in 2018.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216189","216189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054687","2019-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the attack on Londonderry courthouse on 20 January 2019.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216190","216190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054688","2019-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were successful in an application to be exempt from jury duty in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216191","216191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054689","2019-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people failed to appear for their court hearings in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216286","216286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054690","2019-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were given prison sentences for benefit fraud in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216287","216287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054691","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications to the Windrush Compensation Scheme there have been by people in (a) London and (b) Hornsey and Wood Green constituency.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216388","216388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054692","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the decision was taken to restart deportation charter flights to the Caribbean; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216389","216389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054693","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure compliance with the recommendation made by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence in 2017 that GP practices improve recording of autism; whether a register of people with a diagnosis of autism has been implemented; what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of health inequality for autistic people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216288","216288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054694","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the security of the UK of the US suspension of its obligations under the Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces Treaty.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216390","216390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054695","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many residents of Hornsey & Wood Green constituency have been scheduled for deportation on the restarted deportation charter flights to the Caribbean.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216391","216391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054696","2019-02-06","Department for International Trade","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent assessment she has made of the effect on the Everything But Arms Agreement of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216392","216392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054697","2019-02-06","Department for International Development","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has allocated to tackling malaria in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216393","216393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054698","2019-02-06","Department for International Development","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has allocated to (a) bilateral assistance, (b) multilateral organisations, and (c) research and development to tackle malaria in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216394","216394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054699","2019-02-06","Department for International Development","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the funding allocated by her Department to tackle malaria was allocated to health system strengthening programmes in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216395","216395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054700","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will use the UK's period of time as Chair-in-Office of the Commonwealth to ensure that progress is made on the commitment agreed to at the Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting 2018 to halve incidences of  malaria by 2023.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216396","216396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054701","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportions of students (a) withdrew from study in the Frontline programme and (b) were asked to leave the Frontline programme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216289","216289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054702","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the fine of up to £10,000 for students leaving the Frontline programme before the end of the 2 years was introduced; how much money has been recouped under that clause to date; and whether that money has been returned to his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216290","216290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054703","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academic staff Frontline have, and what the qualifications of those staff are.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216291","216291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054704","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of academic staff in the Frontline programme have left the programme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216292","216292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054705","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local authorities use Xantura and other predictive algorithm technologies in children’s social care; what evidence his Department is aware of to support the use of those technologies; and what the total cost to the public purse of those technologies was in the latest period for which data is available.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216293","216293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054706","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure alcohol product labels warn consumers of the health risks of alcohol.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216397","216397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054707","2019-02-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential effects on health and safety standards of leaving the EU (a) under the Withdrawal Agreement and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216127","216127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054708","2019-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps his Department has taken to promote rehabilitation of young offenders.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216398","216398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054709","2019-02-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of her Department's support for people on legacy benefits with high support needs who will be required to transfer to universal credit during managed migration.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216128","216128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054710","2019-02-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle loneliness in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216399","216399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054711","2019-02-06","Attorney General","2019-02-04","To ask the Attorney General, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the sentence delivered in the case of R v Broadhurst in December 2018.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216140","216140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054712","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of visitors to national parks from deprived areas.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216129","216129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054713","2019-02-06","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether The Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 (EU Exit) Regulations 2019 (a) make policy changes, (b) decrease scrutiny of project licences, (c) decrease the provision of statistics and reporting of information on the methods of killing specified in section 2C licences, (d) weaken advancement in the area of alternative methods by removing a requirement on the Secretary of State to identify and nominate suitable laboratories to carry out validation studies on alternative strategies, (e) potentially have other effects on animals in laboratories, compared to the legislation being amended or replaced.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216294","216294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054714","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase awareness of the risks of ketamine amongst the adult population.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216130","216130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054715","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase teacher recruitment in secondary schools.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216295","216295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054716","2019-02-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department’s announcement on 14 January 2019, of the £2.4 million to be given to councils to tackle rogue landlords, how much and what proportion will be allocated to (a) councils in the Sheffield City Region and (b) Barnsley Metropolitan Borough Council.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216296","216296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054717","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding his Department has allocated to Barnsley Metropolitan Borough Council for adult social care in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216297","216297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054718","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what funding his Department has allocated to arts and culture projects in Barnsley Metropolitan Borough Council in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216298","216298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054719","2019-02-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate her Department has made of the total number and proportion of universal credit claimants that are now in employment as a result of the introduction of that benefit.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216131","216131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054720","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that every young person with vision impairment has access to the same learning materials as their sighted peers, adapted to their reading needs.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216192","216192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054721","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps is he taking to ensure that young people with a visual impairment receive appropriately adapted national tests and exam papers, including past papers.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216193","216193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054722","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government plans to announce the successful bids for the redistribution organisation fund.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216299","216299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054723","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the pilots of new mental health assessments for looked-after children, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that those new models will be able to assess the mental health needs of unaccompanied young people.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216194","216194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054724","2019-02-06","Treasury","2019-02-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the tax implications of the announcement by Hermes of a self-employed plus status for its workers.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216400","216400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054725","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to lower the risk of self-harm and suicide among unaccompanied and separated children in the UK.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216195","216195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054726","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Strengths and Difficulties Questionnaire in effectively detecting effects of psychological trauma in young people from a refugee background.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216196","216196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054727","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Strength and Difficulties Questionnaire in properly recognising trauma-related mental health conditions in looked-after children.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216197","216197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054728","2019-02-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of using an alternative weather station to the one based in Leuchars for the KY6 – KY8 postcodes in the annual review for cold weather payments.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216401","216401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054729","2019-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will publish the findings of the most recent annual review on cold weather payments.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216402","216402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054730","2019-02-07","Treasury","2019-02-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 75 of the Government's Civil Society Strategy published in August 2018, what the timetable is for the review of Social Investment Tax Relief.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216300","216300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054731","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 15 of the Government's Civil Society Strategy published in August 2018, whether his Department has established a responsible business Leadership Group.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216301","216301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054732","2019-02-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 15 of the Government's Civil Society Strategy published in August 2018, what plans his Department has to invite social enterprise representatives to the responsible business Leadership Group.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216302","216302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054733","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 77 of the Government's Civil Society Strategy published in August 2018, what steps his Department has taken to convene key civil society stakeholders to explore the potential for a common vision and mission for strengthening the leadership of social sector organisations and the potential for specific government interventions.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216303","216303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054734","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 78 of the Government's Civil Society Strategy published in August 2018, what steps his Department has taken to convene key stakeholders to explore how they can collectively help to develop strong local support systems for social sector organisations.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216304","216304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054735","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy that cervical cancer patients receive treatment within 20 days of diagnosis.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216141","216141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054736","2019-02-06","Department for Transport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timeframe is for the Crossrail station in Langley to be operational.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216403","216403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054737","2019-02-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the press statement entitled, Brokenshire unveils £500 million affordable homes funding boost, published in January 2019, how many of the 11,000 homes will be built in (a) the North West (b) the Liverpool City Region and (c) Wallasey constituency.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216142","216142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054738","2019-02-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the press announcement entitled, Councils in England to receive over £50 million to support Brexit preparations, published in January 2019, how much of the £56.5 million that will be given to councils will be allocated to (a) councils in the LiverpoolCity Region and (b) Wirral Council.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216143","216143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054739","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 84 of the Government's Civil Society Strategy published in August 2018, what steps his Department has taken to work through the Digital Skills Partnership to help civil society organisations to build their skills, boosting collaboration between the government, civil society, and business to tackle the digital skills gap.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216305","216305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054740","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to secure the supply of food to hospitals in the event that UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216144","216144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054741","2019-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to secure the supply of food to prisons in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216145","216145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054742","2019-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the report produced by the Pentagon's Operational Test and Evaluation Office on F-35s, what assessment he has made of the service life of the RAF's fleet of F-35B aircraft.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216198","216198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054743","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in the Moroccan Government on the detention of Ahmed Aliouat.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216306","216306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054744","2019-02-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether (a) independent schools and (b) free schools are eligible for business rate relief, and whether his Department has plans to review that status.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216113","216113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054746","2019-02-06","Department for International Trade","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on the inclusion of the National Health Service in a future trade agreement between the US and the UK.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216405","216405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054747","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many joint operations between the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority and Immigration Enforcement there were in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216307","216307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054748","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were arrested on immigration offences and later reclassified as potential victims of modern slavery in (a) 2014, (b) 2015, (c) 2016, (d) 2017 and (e) 2018.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216308","216308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054749","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the annual budget has been for the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority for each of the last three years; and how many staff that Authority has employed in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216309","216309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054750","2019-02-06","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of Fire and Rescue services choosing to re-engage fire service staff following their retirement on that service’s commitment to equality and diversity.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216406","216406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054751","2019-02-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the annual budget has been for the Health and Safety Executive in each of the last three years; and how many staff that body has employed in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216310","216310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054752","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the annual budget has been for the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate in each of the last three years; and how many staff that Inspectorate has employed in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216311","216311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054753","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the Government plans to report on imports of conventional arms under the Arms Trade Treaty.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216407","216407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054754","2019-02-07","Department for International Trade","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2019 to Question 211704 on World Economic Forum: Advertising, how many contracts his Department has signed in the past two years with advertisers or advertising suppliers; and how many of those contracts include a non-disclosure or confidentiality clause of the kind referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216312","216312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054755","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has received representations on patient anxieties about access to medicines including for epilepsy and depression; and what plans the Government has for communication on the availability of such medicines.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216146","216146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054756","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts from signatories of the Arms Trade Treaty on improving mechanisms for gathering data on arms imports; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216408","216408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054757","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government remains committed to annual reporting obligations for imports of conventional arms under the Arms Trade Treaty.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216409","216409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054758","2019-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Government's press release entitled Government launches world leading plan to tackle air pollution, published in 14 January 2019, what the evidential basis is for the statement that agriculture is responsible for 88% of ammonia emissions.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216410","216410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054759","2019-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Italian counterpart on the rescue of the 47 migrants by the Sea-Watch 3 vessel.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216411","216411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054760","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of violations by Russia of the Intermediate Range Nuclear Forces Treaty since 2014.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216105","216105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054761","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department is considering issuing specific guidance on the practice of animal tethering.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216147","216147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054762","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the US Administration on their recent decision to suspend the Intermediate Range Nuclear Forces Treaty.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216106","216106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054763","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to (a) ensure that social workers are adequately trained to respond to cases of trafficked children that subsequently go missing and (b) improve the recording and reporting practices by local authorities on trafficked children.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216148","216148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054764","2019-02-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that deaths of rough sleepers are recorded.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216149","216149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054765","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2019 to Question 208387 and the Answer of 1 February 2019 to Question 212418, if he will publish the number of (a) business class, (b) economy class and (c) first-class tickets for air travel his Department has purchased in each of the past four years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216412","216412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054766","2019-02-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of homeless people in Newcastle-under-Lyme between 2015 and 2019.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216150","216150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054767","2019-02-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the letter of 14 January 2019 from the hon. Member for Greenwich and Woolwich on Section 20 of the Landlord and Tenant Act 1985 Technical Group.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216413","216413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054768","2019-02-06","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the number of UK residents who have returned to the UK in the last 12 months after fighting with Daesh overseas.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216313","216313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054769","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost of extending his Department's lease on Sanctuary Buildings was.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216314","216314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054770","2019-02-07","Cabinet Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what use is planned for the Old Admiralty buildings subsequent to their refurbishment.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216414","216414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054771","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to date has been of refurbishing the Old Admiralty buildings, and from what Departmental budget that expenditure has been incurred.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216415","216415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054772","2019-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of WTO tariffs on farmers in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216315","216315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054773","2019-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will consider undertaking research into animal feeds to reduce methane emissions.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216316","216316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054774","2019-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will consider estalishing a national food policy.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216317","216317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054775","2019-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of food consumed in the UK is produced domestically.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216318","216318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054776","2019-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the decision by the US Government to withdraw from the Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces Treaty on UK security.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216319","216319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054777","2019-02-06","Department for Transport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance has been provided to airlines on transporting passengers at risk of anaphylactic shock.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216320","216320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054778","2019-02-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to implement safeguards in situations where her Department makes backdated payments of benefits to vulnerable people with mental health issues or drug or alcohol dependencies.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216416","216416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054779","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the estimated cost of (a) stockpiling emergency trauma packs  (b) importing those packs in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216107","216107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054780","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department taking to ensure a secure supply of radioisotopes used for cancer treatment in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216108","216108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054781","2019-02-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2019 to Question 908935 on  Social Media: Information Warfare, when he plans to publish the White Paper on Online Harms White Paper.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216109","216109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054782","2019-02-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January to Written Question 908935 on Social Media: Information Warfare, which organisations from (a) the tech industry (b) civil society and (c) academia his Department has held discussions with on disinformation on social media.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216114","216114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054783","2019-02-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January to Written Question 908935 on Social Media: Information Warfare, what assessment has his Department has made of the effect of disinformation on social media on the efficacy of political elections.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216115","216115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054784","2019-02-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January to Written Question 908935 on Social Media: Information Warfare, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of disinformation on social media on the efficacy of news reporting.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216116","216116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054785","2019-02-06","Treasury","2019-02-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts during negotiations on the UK leaving the EU on the maintenance of European pensions in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216199","216199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054786","2019-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to provide support to UK citizens in receipt of EU pensions in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216200","216200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054787","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that its £1.5 million contribution to the Elton John AIDS Foundation to support the Evening Standard’s AIDSfree campaign will help achieve the target of zero new HIV transmissions by 2030.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216321","216321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054788","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the human rights of the people of Jammu and Kashmir; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216322","216322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054789","2019-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what contingency plans her Department has to support UK citizens receiving pensions from EU Member States who cannot access those pensions in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216201","216201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054790","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in the Philippines following recent terrorist attacks in that country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216202","216202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054791","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Philippines on the protection of religious groups in that country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216203","216203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054792","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of his Department's progress towards the target of 75% of pupils studying the EBacc combination of GCSEs by 2022.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216323","216323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054793","2019-02-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on the creative arts sector of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216417","216417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054794","2019-02-07","Cabinet Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2019 to Question 206350, on Department for Exiting the European Union, what the (a) age profile (b) gender and (c) location was of customer audiences that were targeted by the Road to Brexit Facebook page since 21st November 2017.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216324","216324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054795","2019-02-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of UK-based businesses based in (a) Lewisham Deptford constituency, (b) the London Borough of Lewisham, (c) London and (d) the UK that are considering relocating out of the UK in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216418","216418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054796","2019-02-06","Department for Transport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the transport infrastructure capital account spending was in Solihull in each year between 2009 and 2018.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216325","216325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054797","2019-02-06","Department for Transport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase the provision of bus services in Solihull.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216326","216326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054798","2019-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will require the British Horseracing Authority to record the numbers of horses that leave horseracing each year.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216419","216419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054799","2019-02-06","Department for Transport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people travelling by train (a) to and (b) from Solihull were eligible for delay repay refunds in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216327","216327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054800","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his 30 January 2019 news story entitled £38 million T Level Capital Fund launches, how much of that £38 million he plans to allocate to schools in Solihull.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216328","216328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054801","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) initial and (b) additional allocated budgets for special needs provision in Solihull schools have been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216329","216329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054802","2019-02-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much has been allocated in new homes bonus payments to Solihull metropolitan borough council in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216330","216330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054803","2019-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to compel the British Horseracing Authority to publish the names and details of all horses killed in racing and in training; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216420","216420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054804","2019-02-06","Department for Transport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information he holds on the number of passenger (a) arrivals and (b) departures at (i) Solihull, (ii) Olton and (iii) Shirley railway stations in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216331","216331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054805","2019-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many hours were flown by the Air Cadets gliding fleet in 2018.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216332","216332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054806","2019-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the number of hours of Tutor Air Experience Flights undertaken by Air Cadets in 2018.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216333","216333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054807","2019-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will hold discussions with representatives of the British Horseracing Authority on the compilation of information on horses that are sent (a) for breeding, (b) abroad and (c) slaughter after the finish racing.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216421","216421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054808","2019-02-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to recognise the Cornish as a national minority.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216334","216334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054809","2019-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made by the RAF in bringing Volunteer Gliding Squadrons back to fully operational condition.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216335","216335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054810","2019-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to prohibit the use of the whip in horseracing in the UK.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216422","216422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054811","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeship starts there were in (a) England and Wales and (b) Solihull constituency in each academic year since 2015.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216336","216336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054812","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 189648 on Natural England: Finance, what is meant by broadening the scope of Natural England's income base.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216204","216204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054813","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people received an incorrectly issued fixed penalty notice for travel on the Dartford Crossing.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216205","216205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054814","2019-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 189648 on Natural England: Finance, whether Natural England has plans to charge for its services.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216206","216206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054815","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of (a) employers and (b) organisations that offer retraining programmes that are funded by the adult skills budget.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216423","216423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054816","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the timely implementation of the City Thameslink Service from Maidstone East before the end of 2019.","Biography information for Mrs Helen Grant","Mrs Helen Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216337","216337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054817","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the provision of financial education for children in care.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216338","216338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054818","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which of the 10 most prevalent forms of cancer for adults (a) women and (b) men have a national screening programme.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216132","216132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054819","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of the adult skills budget was spent on (a) level 2, (b) level 3, (c) level 4 and (d) level 5 qualifications in each of the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216424","216424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054821","2019-02-07","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps he is taking to ensure the continued mobility of (a) musicians, (b) comedians and (c) other UK creative workers to (i) tour and (ii) undertake (A) performances, (B) shoots and (C) other short-term projects in EU countries in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216208","216208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054822","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made representations to the Thai government on the arbitrary arrests of Ahmadi Muslim refugees.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216339","216339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054823","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to support the Fight Fatigue campaign which aims to raise awareness of the effect of fatigue and shift working on the NHS workforce.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216340","216340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054824","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hospitals in England have rest facilities for staff working night shifts; and whether those facilities are available (a) before, (b) during and (c) after those shifts.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216341","216341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054825","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reason there is no specific reference to the steel industry in the EU Exit: Long-term economic analysis reports published by the Government in November 2018.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216209","216209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054826","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make representations to Sanofi Pasteur on undertaking new research into the risks of adverse events, including psychosis, from using the vaccine Stamaril.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216210","216210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054827","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of the adult skills budget is spent on short course programmes.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216425","216425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054828","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has made to Sanofi Pasteur on ensuring that new technology is developed to eliminate the risks of adverse events, including psychosis, from the use of the vaccine Stamaril.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216211","216211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054829","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will commission research into new vaccines for yellow fever in the event that Sanofi Pasteur does not undertake research into its yellow fever vaccine.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216212","216212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054830","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of including psychosis in the list of potential side effects published on the use of Stamaril as a vaccine for yellow fever.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216213","216213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054831","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits on including yellow fever in the list of vaccines under the Vaccine Damage Payment Act 1979 for which compensation may be paid.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216214","216214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054832","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2019 to Question 213460 on Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs: Secondment, when the number of staff who are being seconded to the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs to work on programmes related to the UK leaving the EU will be determined.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216426","216426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054833","2019-02-06","Department for International Trade","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2018 to Question 202327 on UK Trade and Investment Defence and Security Organisation: Staff, whether the total workforce of 155 in the Defence and Security Organisation includes the Export Support Team.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216427","216427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054834","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of universities at risk of insolvency.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216342","216342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054835","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to ensure that schools remain responsible for pupils who leave their school roll until they have found a new permanent place.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216343","216343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054836","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2019 to Question 213380 on Teachers: Academies, what estimate he has made of the number of academy trusts that provide induction for new teachers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216344","216344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054837","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what requirements his Department places on academy schools in relation to providing statutory induction for new teachers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216345","216345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054838","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of changing the provisions of the Vaccine Damage Payment compensation scheme so that people who suffer a psychiatric injury as a result of an adverse event involving a vaccine can also be fairly compensated for the effects of (a) loss of earnings, (b) the stigma of mental illness and (c) incarceration.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216215","216215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054839","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information he holds on research into safer alternatives to the Stamaril vaccine; and if the Government will provide funding for such research.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216216","216216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054840","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of schools off-rolling pupils on the standard of those pupils' education.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216428","216428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054841","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made a recent assessment of the effectiveness of the regulatory regime in ensuring that drug companies continuously take steps to minimise the risks from their products.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216217","216217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054842","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the use of isolation rooms in primary and secondary schools on decreasing incidences of disruptive behaviour.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216429","216429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054843","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of isolation rooms on pupils with learning difficulties.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216430","216430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054844","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the maximum amount of time that a school could decide to place a disruptive pupil in an isolation room is.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216431","216431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054845","2019-02-06","Treasury","2019-02-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps he has taken to tackle providers of loan scheme arrangements which have (a) promoted and (b) enabled tax avoidance schemes.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216432","216432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054846","2019-02-06","Treasury","2019-02-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to (a) review all loan charge cases and (b) ensure that individual cases are pursued proportionately to their circumstances.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216433","216433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054847","2019-02-06","Department for Education","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for the School System met to discuss efficiency savings since his speech to the Schools and Academies Show on 21 November 2018.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216346","216346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054848","2019-02-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when his Department will respond to the petition presented on 12 September 2018 on Jackson Lane Car Park.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216218","216218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054849","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of knife crimes in which victims were killed or wounded were associated with the supply of illegal narcotic drugs in each year from 2015.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216104","216104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054850","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 214092 on Telecommunications: National Security, whether the Government's existing comprehensive range of powers to protect national security includes the exclusion of a company supplying UK telecoms critical national infrastructure with equipment on national security grounds.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216434","216434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054851","2019-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to increase the pension for former Gurkha soldiers; and if will he make a statement.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216435","216435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054852","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made with the Minister for the Cabinet Office on the effect on democracy of the prevalence of deepfake videos.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216117","216117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054853","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the role of public service broadcasters on the provision of educational content for children.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216151","216151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054854","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the continuing efficacy of prominence rules in ensuring that viewers can access easily public service content.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216152","216152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054855","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Settled Status App requests applicants to provide proof of residence for six months for the year 2019.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216347","216347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054856","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to increase the accessibility of counselling for young people (a) with mental health problems and (b) that are at risk of taking their own lives.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216133","216133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054857","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he has taken to prevent attacks on refugees and asylum seekers in the UK.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216348","216348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054858","2019-02-06","Department for International Trade","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, when he plans to publish the text of the continuity agreements with (a) Chile and (b) the Eastern and Southern Africa group; and what the process will be for the (i) debate and (ii) ratification of those agreements.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216436","216436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054859","2019-02-06","Department for International Trade","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what progress he has made on the roll-over of agreements with (a) Ghana, (b) Côte D’Ivoire and (c) Kenya.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216437","216437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054860","2019-02-06","Department for International Trade","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on developing (a) countries and (b) sectors on roll-over agreements not being signed by 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216438","216438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054861","2019-02-07","Department for International Trade","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to safeguard the preferential access afforded to developing countries in sensitive sectors in the event that the UK is required to apply tariffs on leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216439","216439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054862","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2019 to Question 213342, for what reasons his Department has no plans to extend the National Child Measurement Programme to measure children (a) after birth, (b) before school and (c) during adolescence.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216349","216349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054863","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2019 to Question 213341, for what reasons his Department has no plans to reinstate the UK-wide Infant Feeding Survey.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216350","216350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054864","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 8 of the January 2019 NAO report on the management of health screening, what steps he is taking to increase the proportion of women who receive the results of cervical screening tests within 14 days from 55 per cent to the target rate of 98 per cent.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216351","216351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054865","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 8 of the January 2019 NAO report on the management of health screening, whether his Department plans to transfer power to Public Health England to enforce recommended changes in the NHS.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216352","216352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054866","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the forthcoming NHS workforce strategy will contain specific reference to sexual health clinicians.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216353","216353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054867","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether Nissan will be required to pay back any of the £2.6 million allocated to it by the Government to encourage the production of the Nissan X-Trail and Qashqai models in Sunderland.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216354","216354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054868","2019-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many British soldiers have been stationed in Germany in each of the last 10 years; and what the cost to the public purse has been of maintaining those troops in each of those years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216219","216219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054870","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) regular (b) reserve ex servicemen were classified with mental health problems by ICD code in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216221","216221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054871","2019-02-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many ex servicemen were recorded as having mental health problems in each Service by ICD code in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216222","216222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054873","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what asssessment he has made of the factors affecting adolescent suicide rates in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216153","216153"
