"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27396","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many men aged 63 who are in receipt of contribution-based employment and support allowance have been called for a work capability assessment in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177920","177920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27397","2013-12-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what changes in assumptions were made when his Department revised its estimate of the RAB charge to 35 per cent.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177925","177925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27398","2013-12-04","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2013, Official Report, column 152W, on mental health services: young people, what practical and physical conditions must be met before a patient under 18 years old is recorded as in part of an adult ward set aside for child and adolescent mental health services' patients; and how many (a) under 16 year olds and (b) 16 to 17 year olds were admitted to part of an adult ward set aside for child and adolescent mental health services' patients in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177921","177921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27399","2013-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many applications for judicial review have been notified to his Department in relation to the designation of marine conservation zones.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177922","177922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27400","2013-12-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what changes to assumptions on (a) forecast earnings data and (b) historic track records on repayment collection were incorporated in his Department's revision of the RAB charge up to 35 per cent.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177926","177926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27401","2013-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will assess the lessons for the UK of the government of France's National Plan for the Reduction of the Risks of Antibiotic Resistance in Veterinary Medicine; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177923","177923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27402","2013-12-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department's latest RAB charge estimate incorporates the Office for Budget Responsibility's March 2013 earnings forecast.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177927","177927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27403","2013-12-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the upward adjustment of the RAB charge included an adjustment to take into account the eight per cent historic underestimates of repayment.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177928","177928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27404","2013-12-05","Department for Education","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what measures his Department is planning to take to address any shortfall of primary school places in the London Borough of Croydon over the next three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177929","177929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27405","2013-12-09","Home Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential risks of illegal adult content and child abuse associated with the use of TOR.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179704","179704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27406","2013-12-09","Home Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the use of TOR on the internet.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179705","179705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27407","2013-12-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the proposed increase in spectrum annual licence fees on consumer prices and investment in mobile coverage provided by UK mobile network operators.","Biography information for Mr Dai Havard","Mr Dai Havard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179706","179706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27408","2013-12-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of whether Ofcom's assessment of the annual licence fee consultation adequately considered the effect of the licence fee on consumer prices and mobile coverage.","Biography information for Mr Dai Havard","Mr Dai Havard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179707","179707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27409","2013-12-09","HM Treasury","2013-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on lending of the Mortgage Market Review and the changes which come into effect in April 2014.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179708","179708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27410","2013-12-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many start-up loans have been granted to businesses in (a) Portsmouth South constituency and (b) Hampshire in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177930","177930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27411","2013-12-04","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the per capita spend on mental health services in (a) Portsmouth South constituency, (b) Hampshire and (c) England was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177931","177931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27412","2013-12-04","Department for Transport","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what analysis or research his Department has conducted or commissioned on the benefits of the application of winter tyres to (a) motor cars, (b) commercial passenger vehicles and (c) heavy goods vehicles to road safety.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179686","179686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27413","2013-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the National Statistician's advice regarding the decision not to publish the reserves recruitment statistics, originally due to be published on 14 November 2013.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177932","177932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27414","2013-12-04","Department for Transport","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase awareness of the benefits of applying winter tyres to motor vehicles.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179687","179687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27415","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time in receipt of jobseeker's allowance is for current claimants in Portsmouth South constituency who are (a) women, (b) men, (c) aged between 16 and 24 and (d) aged over 50.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177933","177933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27416","2013-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to secure the full implementation of the Code for Sustainable Homes.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179688","179688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27417","2013-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of (a) recent trends in the supply of and demand for larger properties in the Merseyside area and (b) whether his Department is aware of any plans for demolition of over-large properties for which there is over-supply as a result of the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177934","177934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27418","2013-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy not to bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Planning and Energy Act 2008 until the Code for Sustainable Homes is fully implemented.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179689","179689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27419","2013-12-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many voluntary sector organisations are currently in the Work Programme supply chain; and what proportion of that supply chain they constitute.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179700","179700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27420","2013-12-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the current budget is for his Department for 2012-13 to date; what the spend against profits has been for the months for which figures are available; and what the current projection is for spend against budget for the year end.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179701","179701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27421","2013-12-04","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the risk of a pandemic if NDM-1 enzyme transferred to a highly contagious bacterium against which modern antibiotics would be ineffective.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177924","177924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27422","2013-12-05","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff have been transferred to private sector employers in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179702","179702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27423","2013-12-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many libel settlements and of what value the Crown Prosecution Service made in each year between 2007 and 2012.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179703","179703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27424","2013-12-05","HM Treasury","2013-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received in favour of abolishing air passenger duty bands D and C and moving all countries in those bands into air passenger duty band B.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179717","179717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27425","2013-12-05","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many telephone conversations he has had with chief executives or chairs of (a) NHS trusts and (b) NHS foundation trusts in the last month.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179718","179718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27426","2013-12-04","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many care homes reported the absence of a registered manager for (a) less than three, (b) three to six, (c) six to nine, (d) nine to 12 and (e) more than 12 months in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177945","177945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27427","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to support mental health service users throughout the process of their claim for benefits.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177946","177946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27428","2013-12-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will provide a list of approved installer organisations able to install new oil boilers in Somerset under the Green Deal and energy company obligation schemes.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177935","177935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27429","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to support people who have difficulty accessing the benefits system.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177947","177947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27430","2013-12-04","Department for Transport","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many passenger journeys are expected to be made on High Speed 2 on average each day once the line is complete; and what the capacity of the line will be in terms of numbers of passenger journeys per day.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177948","177948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27431","2013-12-05","Home Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the estimated cost was of (a) chartered aircraft and (b) staff for the aborted deportation of Ifa Muaza.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177955","177955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27432","2013-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department gives to local mineral planning authorities on how to balance Government policy on shale gas drilling applications against local opinion in respect of shale gas.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177936","177936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27433","2013-12-04","Department for Transport","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of passengers travelling on High Speed 2 are expected to be (a) business and (b) leisure travellers.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177949","177949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27434","2013-12-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions his Department has had with the Student Loans Company on the projections and trends in student support for students studying with alternative providers during academic year 2012-13.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177937","177937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27435","2013-12-04","Department for Transport","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of passengers travelling on the West Coast Main Line were (a) business and (b) leisure travellers in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177950","177950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27436","2013-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many owner-occupied homes (a) nationally and (b) in Greater Manchester have received direct mail regarding the Right to Buy scheme since May 2010; and if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of sending such letters.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177951","177951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27437","2013-12-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will retrospectively publish his Department's projections for enrolments among students studying for higher learning qualifications at private colleges in academic year (a) 2011-12 and (b) 2012-13.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177938","177938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27438","2013-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has spent on producing and sending direct mail regarding the Right to Buy scheme to homes (a) nationally, (b) in Greater Manchester and (c) in the Manchester Central constituency since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177952","177952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27439","2013-12-05","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) mean and (b) median waiting time to been seen was in (i) type 1 and (ii) all accident and emergency departments in each quarter of the last six years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177956","177956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27440","2013-12-04","Home Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether prior permission had been granted by the Nigerian authorities for the arrival of Ifa Muaza following his deportation; and for what reasons the Nigerian authorities did not give permission for the flight to land.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177939","177939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27441","2013-12-04","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the level of funding per head is for each clinical commissioning group allocated by NHS England from its 2013-14 budget; and what the equivalent figures are for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177953","177953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27442","2013-12-12","Department for Transport","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with its EU counterparts on support for a five per cent cap on biofuels.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177957","177957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27443","2013-12-04","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will support the campaign to direct more resources to frontline services via GPs.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177940","177940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27444","2013-12-04","Department for Transport","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many passenger journeys were made on the West Coast Main Line on average each day in the most recent period for which figures are available; and what the maximum capacity of the line is in terms of daily passenger journeys.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177954","177954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27445","2013-12-04","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to increase resources for general practice up to 11 per cent of total funding by 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177941","177941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27446","2013-12-04","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department is considering introducing a requirement for care homes to install closed circuit television monitoring for the purposes of patient safety and staff reassurance.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177942","177942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27447","2013-12-04","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department collects concerning charging for healthcare services by GPs for residents in care homes; what assessment his Department has made of the scale of that practice; what steps he is taking to ensure consistent access standards for primary care services for residents of care homes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177943","177943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27448","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who have exited the benefits system without securing employment in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177944","177944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27449","2013-12-04","Department for Education","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason he failed to order his Department to give the police more information in September 2013 about the fraud allegations at Kings Science Academy, Bradford when he was briefed that this possibility was raised with his Department by the police in September 2013.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177967","177967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27450","2013-12-04","Department for Education","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the legal basis is for the imposition of fines on parents for unauthorised absences from school of their children.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177968","177968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27451","2013-12-04","Department for Transport","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2013, Official Report, column 190W, on driving tests, what losses were incurred to his Department during the procurement process; for what reason an investigation into the conduct of officials engaged in the procurement process was required; and if he will publish the results of that investigation.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177958","177958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27452","2013-12-04","Department for Education","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what right of appeal parents have against fines levied on them by schools for unauthorised absences from school of their children.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177969","177969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27453","2013-12-04","Department for Education","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what further penalties parents may face if they refuse to pay fines levied on them for unauthorised absences from school of their children.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177970","177970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27454","2013-12-04","Department for Education","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has provided to education authorities, academies and free schools  on the levying of fines on parents for unauthorised absences from school of their children.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177971","177971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27455","2013-12-04","Department for Education","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether there is an upper limit to the fines that can be imposed on parents for the unauthorised absence from school of their children.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177972","177972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27456","2013-12-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the practice of the Advertising Standards Authority (ASA) of consulting only one designated expert when assessing claims of medical efficacy in advertising and marketing material; and if she will request the ASA to adopt a robust peer-reviewed assessment process for such claims in line with the assessments made by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence and other public bodies.","Biography information for David Tredinnick","David Tredinnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177959","177959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27457","2013-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 431W, on Afghanistan, how many aircraft of each type suffered damage.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177973","177973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27458","2013-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions (a) Ministers and (b) senior officials in his Department have had with representatives of the Scottish Government regarding the division of Ministry of Defence assets in the event of Scottish independence.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177960","177960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27459","2013-12-05","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2013, Official Report, column 154W, on MMR vaccine, what the baseline estimate of MMR coverage in 10 to 16 year olds was in each month since April 2013.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177974","177974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27460","2013-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Scottish Government's White Paper entitled Scotland's Future, page 238, what discussions (a) Ministers and (b) senior officials in his Department have had with representatives of the Scottish Government regarding the establishment of integrated services in the event of Scottish independence.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177961","177961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27461","2013-12-05","Attorney General","2013-12-02","To ask the Attorney General, if he will review the sentences of the individuals convicted in relation to the death of Mr David Morgan on 18 June 2013.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177975","177975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27462","2013-12-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has issued to local authorities to cover the qualification for priority need assistance to lesbian, gay, bisexual or transgendered people over the age of 18 and with no dependants who have been forced to leave their home because of their sexual orientation or gender identity.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177984","177984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27463","2013-12-04","Department for International Development","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to reduce preventable newborn mortality in Nigeria.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177962","177962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27464","2013-12-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of what the average household (a) gas and (b) electricity bill was in the North West public electricity supply region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177976","177976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27465","2013-12-04","Department for International Development","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to reduce preventable newborn mortality in Kenya.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177963","177963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27466","2013-12-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the average annual spend on energy per household in each public electricity supply region for households paying (a) in arrears and (b) by pre-pay meter.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177977","177977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27467","2013-12-05","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has given clinical commissioning groups and other bodies responsible for the commissioning of NHS services the ability to ensure commissioned services are performed by practitioners registered either with the Health and Care Professions Council or the Accredited Voluntary Register where appropriate.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177985","177985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27468","2013-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the total cost of UK intervention in Afghanistan since 2001 to the latest date for which figures are available; and what estimate he has made of likely costs of UK intervention in Afghanistan until 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177964","177964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27469","2013-12-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Spanish government has undertaken to perform to ensure that British diplomatic bags are not searched again.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177978","177978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27470","2013-12-05","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the proportion of pregnant women who are given the contact details of a named midwife whom they can contact with any concerns.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177986","177986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27471","2013-12-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department plans to take to tackle ticket touting during the 2014 Rugby World Cup.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177979","177979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27472","2013-12-05","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure pregnant women receive continuity of care throughout their pregnancy and the postnatal period.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177987","177987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27473","2013-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has paid out in redundancy and resettlement grants to former military personnel in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177965","177965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27474","2013-12-05","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on ensuring that women have a choice of where to give birth.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177988","177988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27475","2013-12-05","HM Treasury","2013-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the loss of revenue to the Exchequer of raising the income tax threshold to (a) £15,000 and (b) £20,000 for people over the age of 65.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177980","177980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27476","2013-12-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of UK citizens living abroad who are affected by their state pensions not being uprated in line with inflation.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177981","177981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27477","2013-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in which countries British soldiers are engaged in peace-keeping missions; and what the total cost to the public purse has been of each deployment of UK defence personnel in each case.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177966","177966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27478","2013-12-05","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure appropriate support is available during the first three years of parenthood, from pregnancy until a child turns two.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177989","177989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27479","2013-12-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people that will be in receipt of a state pension in (a) 2015, (b) 2020, (c) 2030 and (d) 2050.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177982","177982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27480","2013-12-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the allocation of funding was for his Department's science budget in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15; and whether it is his policy that that budget will be ring-fenced in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177990","177990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27481","2013-12-05","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what governance arrangements professional bodies are required to meet before being approved on the accredited voluntary register by the Professional Standards Authority.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177983","177983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27482","2013-12-04","Cabinet Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many suicides there were in Vale of Clwyd constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177991","177991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27483","2013-12-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress his Department has made towards achieving the EU target of reducing food waste by 50 per cent by 2025.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178003","178003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27484","2013-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether aftercare providers under his Department's contract supporting victims of trafficking require a data subject access request before releasing information from a victim's file in order for other organisations outside the contract to provide assistance to the victim.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177992","177992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27485","2013-12-04","Home Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department's counting rules include a separate category of crime for (a) human trafficking and (b) other forms of modern slavery.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177993","177993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27486","2013-12-04","Home Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when a national referral mechanism decision is made about whether a person is a victim of trafficking, who is responsible for informing the first responder or other relevant professional of that decision.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177994","177994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27487","2013-12-04","Home Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the success of the human trafficking free phone number 0800 783 2589 since it was launched in June 2011; and how widely that number is publicised.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177995","177995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27488","2013-12-04","Home Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the UK Visas and Immigration specialist trafficking team is now fully operational; and how many staff are working on human trafficking issues within that team.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177996","177996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27489","2013-12-04","Home Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children under 18 years have been referred to the National Referral Mechanism (NRM) as being trafficked for (a) domestic servitude and (b) other forms of exploitation since the NRM came into operation.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177997","177997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27490","2013-12-04","Home Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether National Referral Mechanism (NRM) statistics are adjusted to reflect circumstances in which a victim of trafficking is initially given a negative NRM decision but then receives a subsequent decision that they are conclusively a victim of trafficking either in a court of law or as a result of a competent authority settling before a judicial review.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177998","177998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27491","2013-12-04","Home Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied minors, excluding those from other EU member states, have entered the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 177999","177999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27492","2013-12-04","Home Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied minors departed from the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178000","178000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27493","2013-12-04","Home Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of cases of rape reported to the police relate to rapes which occurred over (a) five and (b) 10 years ago.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178001","178001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27494","2013-12-04","Home Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what definition her Department uses for cases of historic sexual violence.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178002","178002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27495","2013-12-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of work experience opportunities for university students in the UK on the attractiveness of UK universities to international students.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178025","178025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27496","2013-12-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of international students residing in the private rented sector in Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178026","178026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27497","2013-12-04","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will have discussions with research councils and other appropriate research bodies on providing specific funding for (a) the study of risk factors in Alzheimer's disease and (b) clinical trials to assess the role of managing those risks in preventing that disease.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178014","178014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27498","2013-12-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make it his policy to require higher education institutions in England to make data available to prospective students on the availability of jobs in fields relevant to the courses they offer.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178004","178004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27499","2013-12-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the evidence used by his Department in formulating its policy to require landlords to check visas of prospective tenants prior to renting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178027","178027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27500","2013-12-04","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 19 November 2013, Official Report, column 862W, and 21 November 2013, Official Report, column 1010W, on secondment, what the estimated cost is of providing the information requested in those questions.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178005","178005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27501","2013-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the under-occupancy penalty on social cohesion in neighbourhoods in which a high proportion of tenants are affected by that policy.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178015","178015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27502","2013-12-05","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the (a) average cost per student and (b) total cost to the NHS of treating international students studying at UK universities in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178028","178028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27503","2013-12-04","Cabinet Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people aged (a) 16 or 17 and (b) 18 or over were added to the electoral register in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178006","178006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27504","2013-12-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the possession of substantial assets by Traveller and Gypsy communities is a factor taken into account in the assessment of planning applications made on behalf of such communities.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178029","178029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27505","2013-12-04","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effects of long-term use of mobile telephones, hand-held computers and other digital hardware on mental health.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178016","178016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27506","2013-12-04","Cabinet Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many voters were removed from the electoral register for reasons other than death in each of the last 10 years for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178007","178007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27507","2013-12-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Iranian government on the case of Sakineh Mohammadi Ashtiani.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178030","178030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27508","2013-12-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2013, Official Report, column 1086W, on television: advertising, what assessment she has made of the effect on children of the increase in the number of advertisements watched on average.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178017","178017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27509","2013-12-04","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2013-12-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what recent assessment he has made of the potential benefits of data sharing for the purposes of electoral registration (a) within local government departments, (b) between local government and central government departments and (c) between local government departments and other agencies.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178008","178008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27510","2013-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the average cost of moving house for people who move as a consequence of the under-occupancy penalty; and if he will make it his policy to provide a subsidy for such costs.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178009","178009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27511","2013-12-04","HM Treasury","2013-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the levels of household debt in (a) Vale of Clwyd and (b) each region of the UK in each year since 2010; and what such levels are forecast to be in each year until 2015.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178018","178018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27512","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to ensure that (a) Jobcentre Plus carry out an assessment of claimants' levels of computer literacy before requiring them to search for jobs online and (b) those claimants are not sanctioned as a result of being unable to search for jobs online.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178010","178010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27513","2013-12-04","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of long-term trends in patient satisfaction levels in the NHS.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178019","178019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27514","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the report of the European Foundation for the Improvement of Working and Living Conditions entitled Quality of Life in Europe: subjective well-being, published on 7 November 2013.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178011","178011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27515","2013-12-04","Department for Education","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 May 2013, Official Report, column 765W, on pupils: health, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the reduction in references to children's well-being in Ofsted inspectors' guildlines in 2011 and 2012.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178020","178020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27516","2013-12-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what consultation his Department undertook (a) before and (b) after the implementation of recent changes to renewable heat initiative scheme funding for biomass boilers.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178024","178024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27517","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people underwent work capability assessments who had a (a) musculo-skeletal condition and (b) mental health condition in each (i) county and (ii) parliamentary constituency in Wales to date.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178012","178012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27518","2013-12-04","Cabinet Office","2013-12-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the life satisfaction of people in the (a) bottom and (b) top quartile of earnings in each year from 2007 to the latest period for which information is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178021","178021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27519","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the recent ruling in OR v. Secretary of State for Work and Pensions and Isle of Anglesey County Council.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178031","178031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27520","2013-12-04","Department of Health","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the statement by Mr James Palmer of 15 October 2013 on the Specialised Services Commissioning Innovation Fund, what the level of unplanned expenditure on specialised commissioning has been in 2013 to date; what the forecast level of such expenditure is at the end of the current financial year; by how much the specialised commissioning budget is expected to be overspent in (a) 2013-14 to date, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15; what steps NHS England is taking to reduce the level of unplanned expenditure; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178013","178013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27521","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of mass summonses issued by local authorities to enforce rent arrears owing to the implementation of the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178022","178022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27522","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations his Department has received from (a) hon. Members and (b) other sources on the interaction of the Work Programme and Jobs Growth Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178023","178023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27523","2013-12-04","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2013-12-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what steps the Electoral Commission takes to promote British democracy overseas.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178032","178032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27524","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will commission an investigation into possible links between the under-occupancy penalty and cases of suicide.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178033","178033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27525","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2013, Official Report, columns 520-21W, on work capability assessment, if he will make it his policy to collect such information.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178034","178034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27526","2013-12-04","Department for Transport","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2013, Official Report, column 1051W, on large goods vehicles, for what reason his assessment that longer semi-trailers are able to match the performance of existing semi-trailers differs from the assessments in paragraphs 23 and 24 of his Department's consultation on the possibility of allowing an increase in the length of articulated lorries and in paragraph 3.2.6 of his Department's publication, Longer Semi-trailers feasibility study and impact assessment, published in March 2011.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178035","178035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27528","2013-12-05","HM Treasury","2013-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Funding for Lending scheme on lending to small businesses.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 901447","901447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28235","2013-12-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to protect interns' right to fair pay.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 901467","901467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28236","2013-12-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the recommendations of the report from the Business Taskforce entitled Cut EU red tape, published in October 2013.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 901450","901450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27174","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to discounting codes on future take-up of (a) arts, (b) design, (c) music and (d) drama subjects.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179585","179585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27175","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received on changes to discounting codes for (a) arts, (b) design, (c) music and (d) drama subjects.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179586","179586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27176","2013-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of defence reforms on military bases in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179587","179587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27177","2013-12-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on energy pricing and investment in green technology.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179588","179588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27178","2013-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts from NATO member states on Ukraine.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179589","179589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27179","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to support the research-led teaching for art and design teachers in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179590","179590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27180","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that the qualifications of School Direct trained teachers will be recognised abroad.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179591","179591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27181","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many art and design teachers have been recruited through School Direct since September 2012.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179592","179592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27182","2013-12-03","HM Treasury","2013-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to replace Gift Aid with a system of personal income tax deductions for charitable giving.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179593","179593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27183","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure high-quality arts teachers are recruited into the profession.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179594","179594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27184","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support teachers and schools to access continuing professional development in (a) arts and (b) design subjects.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179595","179595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27185","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to measure the effect of national teaching schools on the quality of (a) art and (b) design teaching in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179596","179596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27186","2013-12-04","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding his Department has provided to (a) open new secondary schools, (b) expand existing secondary schools, (c) open new primary schools and (d) expand existing primary schools in London in the most recent 12 months for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179597","179597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27187","2013-12-04","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will provide additional funding for new primary school places in the London Borough of Croydon; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179598","179598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27188","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have received representations from individuals or organisations on the use of credit checks by companies in the recruitment process.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179599","179599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27189","2013-12-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will place in the Library a copy of the information his Department has shared with the Ground Sources Heat Pump Association relating to data arising from the metering programme of heat pumps installed under the Renewable Heat Premium Scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179600","179600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27190","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to review what further guidance or legislation is needed to regulate the use of credit checks as part of the recruitment process by individual employers.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179601","179601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27191","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department has had with the Secretary of State for Education on preparing school children for future employment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179602","179602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27192","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what his Department plans to spend its funding allocation from the European Union Youth Employment Initiative.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179603","179603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27193","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much EU funding has been awarded to his Department in each year since May 2010; and how much such funding was specifically for tackling (a) youth unemployment and (b) long-term unemployment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179604","179604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27194","2013-12-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what length of fibre optic cable was laid in (a) Haltemprice and Howden constituency, (b) the East Riding of Yorkshire, (c) England and (d) the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179605","179605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27195","2013-12-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to encourage its employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179633","179633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27196","2013-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of expenditure on his Department's procurement contracts valued in excess of £5 million was placed with small and medium-sized enterprises based in each government office region in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179606","179606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27197","2013-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the level of commission claimed by advisors on the auto enrolment pensions market.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179607","179607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27198","2013-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the cost to the Exchequer of implementing the new single-tier state pension.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179608","179608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27199","2013-12-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the effect of current energy prices on people over 65.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179609","179609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27200","2013-12-03","Cabinet Office","2013-11-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to encourage its employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179634","179634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27201","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that careers services in schools increases awareness of vocational and technical education.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179610","179610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27202","2013-12-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to encourage its employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179635","179635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27203","2013-12-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to encourage its employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179636","179636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27204","2013-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to encourage its employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179637","179637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27205","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to encourage its employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179638","179638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27206","2013-12-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department is taking to encourage its employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179639","179639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27207","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of primary schools offered wrap-around childcare services in (a) May 2010 and (b) the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179611","179611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27208","2013-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage its employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179640","179640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27209","2013-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage its employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179641","179641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27210","2013-12-03","Department of Health","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179642","179642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27211","2013-12-03","Home Office","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to encourage employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179643","179643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27212","2013-12-03","Department for International Development","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to encourage employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179644","179644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27213","2013-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to encourage employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179645","179645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27214","2013-12-03","Department for Transport","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage its employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179646","179646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27215","2013-12-03","HM Treasury","2013-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to encourage its employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179647","179647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27216","2013-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to encourage its employees to make tax-free donations direct from their salaries.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179648","179648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27217","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that there is a sufficient supply of child care places for the 40 per cent most disadvantaged two year olds.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179612","179612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27218","2013-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the work programme for people claiming employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179613","179613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27219","2013-12-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent progress he has made in negotiations on firefighters' pensions.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179614","179614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27220","2013-12-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homes have been completed as a result of the new homes bonus to date.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179615","179615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27221","2013-12-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to prevent the proliferation of betting shops near areas with high levels of deprivation.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179616","179616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27222","2013-12-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent changes to permitted development rights on the number of betting shops on the high street.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179617","179617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27223","2013-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Iranian counterpart on providing equality for all Iranian citizens without discrimination based on race, gender or religion.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179618","179618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27224","2013-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of (a) the human rights situation in Iran, (b) discrimination against women and religious minorities in that country and (c) the resolution recently adopted by the Third Committee of the UN General Assembly on this matter.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179619","179619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27225","2013-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will hold talks with his Iranian counterparts aimed at amending Article 13 of the 1979 Iranian Constitution to include other religious minorities.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179620","179620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27226","2013-12-03","Department for Transport","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has plans to support low carbon hydrogen for electric vehicles and hydrogen fuel cell vehicles.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179621","179621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27227","2013-12-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the effect that the Warm Homes Discount scheme has had on (a) keeping older people warmer and safer during the winter months, (b) reducing levels of fuel poverty across the UK and (c) reducing excess winter deaths.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179629","179629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27228","2013-12-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent meetings she has had with the Secretary of State for Education on the Cultural Plan.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179622","179622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27229","2013-12-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the costs and benefits of business rate relief for charities.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179623","179623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27230","2013-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons his Department does not monitor veterinary use of antibiotics.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179624","179624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27231","2013-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has for the future of levy funding of the Sea Fish Industry Authority.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179625","179625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27232","2013-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the outstanding amounts of uncollected council tax are for each London borough for (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179630","179630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27233","2013-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what timetable he has set plans for the triennial review of the Sea Fish Industry Authority.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179626","179626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27234","2013-12-03","HM Treasury","2013-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on how many occasions he has met Dieter Helm in his capacity as Chair of the Natural Capital Committee since May 2010.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179627","179627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27235","2013-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Witham of 3 June 2013, Official Report, column 923W, on alcoholic drinks: young people, how many people were convicted of buying alcohol on behalf of a minor in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179631","179631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27236","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what advice he has given to Ofsted on a potential conflict of interest on the part of those overseeing the organisation who are also members of academy chains; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179628","179628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27237","2013-12-04","Home Office","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many family visit visa applications to the UK there were in the years ending 8 July (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013, by (i) overall number of decisions made, (ii) number of family visit visa grants, (iii) number of family visit visa refusals, (iv) number of family visit visa applications withdrawn and (v) number of family visit visa applications which lapsed.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179632","179632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27238","2013-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure the accountability and effectiveness of private contractors working for the Probation Service.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179649","179649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27239","2013-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Probation Service is fit for purpose in (a) Huddersfield and (b) the rest of the UK.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179650","179650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27240","2013-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department takes to ensure that Regulation 28 coroners' investigations and the implementation of recommendations of those investigations are carried out in a timely and efficient manner.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179651","179651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27241","2013-12-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of whether current arrangements for information provision by energy suppliers are sufficient to ensure that their customers are aware of the dangers arising from carbon monoxide.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179652","179652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27242","2013-12-03","Home Office","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent consultation she has had with the devolved administrations on the prevention of human trafficking.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179653","179653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27243","2013-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the EU Commission and the European Parliament on human trafficking and modern day slavery.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179654","179654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27244","2013-12-03","Cabinet Office","2013-11-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the potential effect of Scottish independence on (a) the public sector and (b) departmental offices based in Scotland which deal with clients in the whole of the UK.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179655","179655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27245","2013-12-03","Department for Transport","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Article 9 of the European Regulation on the Sound Level of Motor Vehicles requires acoustic vehicle alerting systems for mobility scooters.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179656","179656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27246","2013-12-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the health and well-being of people living near fracking sites is not adversely affected by that practice.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179657","179657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27247","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have died over the last 10 years owing to workplace accidents in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) England.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179658","179658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27248","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, at what level winter fuel payments were set in each category in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179659","179659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27249","2013-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of 18 to 24 year olds flowed off jobseeker's allowance within (a) three months, (b) six months, (c) nine months and (d) 12 months in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179660","179660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27250","2013-12-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2013, Official Report, column 296W, on air pollution: Greater London, what solutions to London's air quality problems were discussed or agreed; and what agreement was reached about which body will meet the cost of EU fines for infractions of the Air Quality Directive in London.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179665","179665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27251","2013-12-03","Department for Transport","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what service level targets his Department has set for the Driving and Vehicle Licensing Agency.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179661","179661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27252","2013-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that community sentences are effectively supervised.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179662","179662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27253","2013-12-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what agreements were made at the UN Climate Change Conference in Warsaw on reducing emissions from deforestation and forest degradation.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179663","179663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27254","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will allow flexible funding for local education authorities.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179664","179664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26978","2013-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the Prawer plan in the Negev region of Israel.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179390","179390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26979","2013-12-03","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the number of full-time equivalent GPs per 1,000 patients in (a) Nottingham and (b) the East Midlands in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179391","179391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26980","2013-12-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions his Department has had with bioliquids producers on the inclusion of support for used cooking oil-derived bioliquids in electricity market reform.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179392","179392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26981","2013-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with its European counterparts on the European year against food waste in 2014.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179393","179393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26982","2013-12-03","Department for Transport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects work on the diversion of overhead electric lines in connection with High Speed 2 to commence.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179394","179394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26983","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many meetings his Department's officials have had with teachers' representative organisations on pay, pensions and conditions of service in the last two years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179395","179395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26984","2013-12-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he intends to publish the (a) first interim report by the Ecorys UK consortium on the Troubled Families programme and (b) official statistics on the Troubled Families programme.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179396","179396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26985","2013-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of levels of air pollution in Bristol against threshold limits.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179397","179397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26986","2013-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of UK children were living in (a) relative and (b) absolute poverty in each year since May 1983.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179398","179398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26987","2013-12-03","Department for Transport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, by what date he expects to announce a decision on the installation of lifts for disabled passengers at Goring and Streatley stations.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179399","179399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26988","2013-12-03","Department for Transport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what works on High Speed 2 are planned to commence before the passage of the Hybrid Bill through Parliament is complete.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179401","179401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26989","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many meetings he or his officials have had with the NASUWT and NUT on their trade dispute since 14 October 2013.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179402","179402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26990","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many meetings he has had with teachers' representatives on pensions, pay and conditions of service in the last two years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179403","179403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26991","2013-12-03","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ensure that the terms of reference for the review of plain packaging of tobacco products allow an examination of the incidence of the use of illegal and unbranded cannabis by young people.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179404","179404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26992","2013-12-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of proposed changes to legal aid and judicial review on parents' (a) ability to use the judicial review process and (b) ability to access legal aid when they believe that their local authority is failing in its duties to a child; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179400","179400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26993","2013-12-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce on-the-spot fines for individuals, businesses and organisations that do not comply with the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179435","179435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26994","2013-12-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many social housing units have been built in the New Forest District Council area in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179436","179436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26995","2013-12-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many social housing units have been built in the Test Valley Borough Council area in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179437","179437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26996","2013-12-02","House of Commons Commission","2013-11-28","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what steps the House of Commons Commission is taking to reduce the costs incurred in publishing answers to written parliamentary questions.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179438","179438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26997","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many meetings his Department has had with the Department of Health on introducing an uptake rule for National Institute for Health and Care Excellence approved diagnostic technologies to support the objective of the Government's Strategy for UK Life Sciences to promote innovation in the NHS.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179439","179439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26998","2013-12-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the extent of fly-grazing in (a) England, (b) Hampshire and (c) Portsmouth South constituency.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179425","179425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26999","2013-12-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assistance her Department will provide to help local radio stations to switch to DAB in (a) Portsmouth South constituency and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179426","179426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27000","2013-12-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what pre-conditions he has set before the UK will provide training to the Burmese Army.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179427","179427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27001","2013-12-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Burmese counterpart on the case of Bauk Ja.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179428","179428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27002","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which civil society organisations in Burma receive how much funding from her Department.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179429","179429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27003","2013-12-02","Department for Education","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the success of schools being responsible for providing information, advice and guidance in future careers since April 2012.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179430","179430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27004","2013-12-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the future growth in London's housing stock will be.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179431","179431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27005","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how the Government aid to the Philippines will be distributed; and how this aid will be monitored to ensure that it reaches those most in need.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179415","179415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27006","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations she made to the government of Burma on the need to reduce military expenditure and increase spending on health and education.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179432","179432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27007","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the skills shortages in the engineering industry; and what recent discussions he has held with education leaders and employers on this matter.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179416","179416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27008","2013-12-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to attend events in Londonderry as part of the UK City of Culture 2013 in that city.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179433","179433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27009","2013-12-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on London house prices of overseas investment in new build homes in the capital.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179417","179417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27010","2013-12-02","Department for Education","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the shortfall in available school places was for those needing a school place in Bradford Education Authority area in September 2013.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179418","179418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27011","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many start up loans have been granted to businesses in (a) Westmorland and Lonsdale constituency and (b) Cumbria in the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179434","179434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27012","2013-12-02","Department for Education","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the projected increase in school places needed to meet demand in the Bradford Education Authority area will be in September (a) 2014, (b) 2015, (c) 2016, (d) 2017 and (e) 2018.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179419","179419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27013","2013-12-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many local radio stations in Portsmouth broadcast on DAB.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179405","179405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27014","2013-12-02","Department for Education","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many existing schools in the Bradford Education Authority area are planning to meet increased demand for school places by increasing their current capacity.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179420","179420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27015","2013-12-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent estimate she has made of the proportion of (a) Hampshire and (b) Portsmouth South constituency that is covered by DAB radio reception of comparable quality and range to FM coverage.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179406","179406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27016","2013-12-02","Department for Education","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new academy and free schools based in the Bradford Education Authority area are currently applying to his Department.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179421","179421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27017","2013-12-02","Department for Transport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the business case for the Y-shaped route for High Speed 2 (a) with and (b) without the section of line between Winterbottom and Bamfurlong.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179407","179407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27018","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on the effects of EU policy relating to aluminium of the global competitiveness of the EU aluminium industry.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179422","179422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27019","2013-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been in receipt of out-of-work benefits for (a) one year, (b) two years and (c) three years or more in (i) Haltemprice and Howden constituency, (ii) Yorkshire and the Humber and (iii) England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179441","179441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27020","2013-12-02","Department for Transport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of the section of the High Speed 2 line between Winterbottom and Bamfurlong.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179408","179408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27021","2013-12-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the conclusions of the recently published report of the London Finance Commission entitled Raising the Capital; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179423","179423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27022","2013-12-02","Department for Transport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the economic benefits of the section of the High Speed 2 line between Winterbottom and Bamfurlong.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179409","179409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27023","2013-12-02","Department for Education","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in the Bradford Education Authority area currently teach some of their pupils in portakabins and other temporary accommodation.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179424","179424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27024","2013-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Israeli government regarding the implementation of the recommendations in the report on Children in Military Custody, published in June 2012 with funding from his Department.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179440","179440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27025","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people currently studying at universities in the UK are registered disabled.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179410","179410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27026","2013-12-02","Department for Transport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department had made of the incremental cost to benefit ratio of the section of the High Speed 2 line between Winterbottom and Bamfurlong.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179411","179411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27027","2013-12-03","HM Treasury","2013-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the rate of job growth was in (a) Haltemprice and Howden constituency, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) England in 2013; and what estimate he has made of such growth in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179442","179442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27028","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken with universities to increase support for those studying with disabilities.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179412","179412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27029","2013-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that those offering guidance on universal credit have adequate knowledge to deliver the best advice for claimants.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179413","179413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27030","2013-12-03","HM Treasury","2013-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people employed since (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013 in (i) Haltemprice and Howden constituency, (ii) East Riding of Yorkshire and (iii) England have paid less tax as a result of changes in the personal allowance.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179443","179443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27031","2013-12-02","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to regulate the pricing and purchasing of drugs by pharmaceutical companies.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179414","179414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27032","2013-12-03","Cabinet Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people employed by (a) small and (b) medium-sized businesses operating in (i) Haltemprice and Howden constituency, (ii) East Riding of Yorkshire and (iii) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179444","179444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27033","2013-12-03","Department for Transport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the economic effect on (a) Haltemprice and Howden constituency, (b) East Riding of Yorkshire and (c) Yorkshire and the Humber following the completion of the planned road improvements in Yorkshire and the Humber in 2014.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179445","179445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27034","2013-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will commission a comparative study on the relationship between (a) Ceuta and Melilla with Spain and (b) Gibraltar and the UK, and of how the UK might raise at EU level the issue of legal problems arising from Spain's relationship with Ceuta and Melilla.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179446","179446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27035","2013-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the construction of a wall along the Line of Control in Jammu and Kashmir; and whether he has made representations to the Indian government on this matter.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179447","179447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27036","2013-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people given a criminal conviction for benefit fraud were given (a) a custodial and (b) a non-custodial sentence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179448","179448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27037","2013-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people received a criminal conviction for benefit fraud for amounts of (a) £0 to £1,000, (b) £1,101 to £5,000, (c) £5,001 to £10,000 and (d) over £10,000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179449","179449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27038","2013-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases of benefit fraud were identified in each of the last five years; and what proportion of such cases were prosecuted in court.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179450","179450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27039","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to measure the efficiency and effectiveness of each local enterprise partnership; what steps his Department is taking to encourage all local enterprise partnerships to adopt best practices; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179451","179451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27040","2013-12-02","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have waited longer than four hours in accident and emergency departments in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179452","179452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27041","2013-12-02","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the findings of the Transitional Risk register's warning on the link between the Health and Social Care Act 2012 and accident and emergency performance.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179453","179453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27042","2013-12-02","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the number of nurses working in the NHS.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179454","179454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27043","2013-12-02","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase staffing levels in emergency medicine.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179455","179455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27044","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many education, health and care plans for young people have been implemented to date.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179458","179458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27045","2013-12-02","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the number of days lost in discharges from the acute sector.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179456","179456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27046","2013-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times people have opted-in to the probation victim contact scheme in each year since its establishment.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179459","179459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27047","2013-12-03","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessments she has made of the main root causes of crime.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179460","179460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27048","2013-12-02","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients are registered with each general practitioner surgery in  Fareham constituency; what the capacity of each surgery is; and how many such surgeries are oversubscribed.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179457","179457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27049","2013-12-03","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessments she has made of links between criminality and (a) household poverty, (b) educational attainment, (c) unemployment, (d) family environment and (e) area deprivation.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179461","179461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27050","2013-12-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what analysis she has made of the effect of a lack of DAB coverage on local radio stations; and when she intends to roll-out increased DAB transmitters to ensure that local stations receive the same coverage as national stations.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179462","179462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27051","2013-12-02","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the availability of treatments for hepatitis B and C in London.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179473","179473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27052","2013-12-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will meet representatives of small commercial FM radio stations to discuss the impact of the digital radio switchover and Government support for this sector before her Department's announcement, scheduled for 16 December 2013, on the switchover.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179490","179490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27053","2013-12-03","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the policy is of the National Fraud Intelligence Bureau on taking evidence from a reporting body (a) by telephone and (b) in writing.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179491","179491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27054","2013-12-02","Cabinet Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs to be moved offshore under the contract with Shared Services Connected Limited to provide shared services for the Department for Work and Pensions and other government bodies.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179463","179463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27055","2013-12-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent representations his Department has received from the London Borough of Hillingdon about delays by the Planning Inspectorate in determining appeals within that borough.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179474","179474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27056","2013-12-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent representations his Department has received from local authorities about delays by the Planning Inspectorate in determining appeals.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179475","179475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27057","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he is considering measures to reduce grants available to students from low-income backgrounds.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179486","179486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27058","2013-12-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2013, Official Report, column 960W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, what approximate distance beyond the primary areas of operation identified for the Black Hornet that unmanned aerial vehicle has flown in UK airspace.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179476","179476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27059","2013-12-03","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will release a transcript of the evidence about Kings Science Academy in Bradford submitted to Action Fraud and then passed on to the National Fraud Intelligence Bureau by telephone on 25 April 2013 from the Department for Education.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179492","179492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27060","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding will be allocated to the higher education teaching budget for the next financial year.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179487","179487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27061","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has for the future of the Access to Learning Hardship Fund.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179488","179488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27062","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will stop the recruitment of students for higher national diploma and higher national certificate courses by private colleges for the remainder of 2013-14; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179464","179464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27063","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has for the future of the National Scholarship Programme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179489","179489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27064","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will place controls on the number of students enrolling for higher learning qualifications at private colleges.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179465","179465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27065","2013-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he discussed Wrexham Magistrates' Court and police cells in Wrexham with the Chair of the Wrexham Magistrates at meetings in the last year; and what steps he took following any such discussion.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179493","179493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27066","2013-12-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2013, Official Report, column 269W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, which military remotely piloted aircraft systems not in service have been operated in national airspace outside Military Aviation Authority-approved danger areas or segregated airspace; and what the purpose of each such operation overseen by the Minister for the Armed Forces was.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179477","179477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27067","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students enrolled at private colleges have had their loans halted in academic year 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179478","179478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27068","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of students expected to enrol on courses at private colleges awarding higher national diplomas and certificates in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179466","179466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27069","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of providing financial support to students enrolled at private colleges in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179479","179479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27070","2013-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what was the rate of (a) repayment and (b) default for crisis loans provided in the financial years (i) 2009-10, (ii) 2010-11, (iii) 2011-12 and (iv) 2012-13.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179467","179467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27071","2013-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the consequences of continuous payment authorities for those in receipt of social security payments.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179468","179468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27072","2013-12-02","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2013, Official Report, column 862W, on secondment, what estimate she has made of the cost of answering the original question.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179480","179480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27073","2013-12-03","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2013, Official Report, column 301W, on Kings Science Academy, for what reason the National Fraud Intelligence Bureau did not request further information from the Department for Education when Action Fraud reported to the Department for Education that there was not enough information to progress the case further on 5 September 2013.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179494","179494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27074","2013-12-02","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has given West Yorkshire Police a transcript of the evidence submitted to Action Fraud and then passed onto the National Fraud Intelligence Bureau via telephone on 25 April 2013, from the Department of Education about Kings Science Academy in Bradford.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179469","179469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27075","2013-12-02","Department for Education","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the conclusions of the report entitled One System, Many Pathways, published by the Skills Commission on 26 November 2013.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179481","179481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27076","2013-12-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average length of time involved in the processing and determination of planning appeals by the Planning Inspectorate was in each year since 2008.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179470","179470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27077","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which Government departments in Burma have received assistance from, or are funded by, her Department; and what the nature of that assistance and level of that funding is.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179482","179482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27078","2013-12-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning inspectors there were in the Planning Inspectorate in each year since 2008.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179471","179471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27079","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which companies have so far received support from the Myanmar Centre for Responsible Business.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179483","179483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27080","2013-12-02","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of potential variations in access to treatments for hepatitis B and C in England.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179472","179472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27081","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department provides for the rehabilitation of released political prisoners in Burma.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179484","179484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27082","2013-12-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where British training for Burmese army soldiers will take place in 2014.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179485","179485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27083","2013-12-03","Department for Transport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2013, Official Report, column 978W, on railways: standards, on which dates (a) he and (b) officials from his Department met representatives of the Office of Rail Regulation to discuss the lowering of punctuality targets on the East Coast and West Coast main lines.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179495","179495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27084","2013-12-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the public purse has been to date of the Doncaster cluster prison competition.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179496","179496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27085","2013-12-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff of (a) the Prison Service or (b) his Department have been involved to date in work related to the Doncaster cluster prison competition.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179497","179497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27086","2013-12-02","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many operations were cancelled at University Hospitals Birmingham NHS Foundation Trust in the most recent period for which figures are available; how many such operations were cancelled more than once; and what comparative assessment he has made between those figures and the national per capita average number of cancellations of operations for non-clinical reasons.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179506","179506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27087","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what comparative information her Department holds on donations made by other member states of the EU towards alleviating suffering as a result of Typhoon Haiyan.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179499","179499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27088","2013-12-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support his Department provides to programmes currently being undertaken by the unmanned aerial systems industry for the development of civil use of unmanned aerial or maritime systems.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179507","179507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27089","2013-12-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding her Department has allocated to Belfast's Super Connected City strategy; and what assessment she has made of that strategy.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179498","179498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27090","2013-12-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what comparative assessment he has made of the differences in energy prices between the regions of the UK and the reasons for those differences.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179500","179500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27091","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many secure children's homes are run by (a) the private sector, (b) the voluntary sector and (c) local authorities.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179508","179508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27092","2013-12-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many female recruits to the RAF in each of the countries of the UK have received compensation for injuries suffered whilst participating in marching drills.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179501","179501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27093","2013-12-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions Ministers in his Department have held with Israeli ministers since the announcement of the Iran nuclear agreement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179502","179502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27094","2013-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of how often Jobcentre Plus advisers refer Work Programme participants to non-contracted local voluntary sector organisations for additional support.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179509","179509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27095","2013-12-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of regulation governing the protection of caravan owners on holiday parks.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179510","179510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27096","2013-12-03","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the rise in the number of council-funded residents who live in residential care and now rely on a top-up to cover the full costs of their care home place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179511","179511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27097","2013-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance was provided by his Department to local authorities to assist them in setting up local welfare provision schemes to replace crisis loans and community care grants.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179512","179512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27098","2013-12-02","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many operations were cancelled for non-clinical reasons at Queen Elizabeth Hospital Birmingham in each of the last five years for which figures are available; how many such operations were cancelled more than once; and what comparative assessment he has made between those figures and the national per capita average number of cancellations of operations for non-clinical reasons.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179503","179503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27099","2013-12-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department, when commissioning probation services from the private sector, will (a) evaluate and (b) monitor contractor performance; and what penalties will be incurred if agreed performance targets are not met.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179504","179504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27100","2013-12-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what research his Department has conducted into commissioning probation services from the private sector using payment by results; and whether that research concluded that this would (a) be more cost-effective and (b) lower current levels of reoffending.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179505","179505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27101","2013-12-03","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS posts were recruited by Odgers Berndston in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011 and (d) 2012; and how much was paid to Odgers Berndston in each such year.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179523","179523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27102","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to prioritise the prevention of severe acute malnutrition in high-burden countries where her Department has a bilateral presence.","Biography information for Baroness Jowell","Dame Tessa Jowell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179514","179514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27103","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department takes to ensure that non-discriminatory healthcare is provided to survivors of rape in conflict.","Biography information for Baroness Jowell","Dame Tessa Jowell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179515","179515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27104","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on the (a) prevention and (b) treatment of severe acute malnutrition in (i) 2012 and (ii) 2013.","Biography information for Baroness Jowell","Dame Tessa Jowell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179516","179516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27105","2013-12-02","Women and Equalities","2013-11-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps her Department is taking to ensure business owners comply with the Equality Act 2010 in respect of guide dog and hearing dog owners.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179517","179517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27106","2013-12-02","Women and Equalities","2013-11-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will review the effects of the Equality Act 2010 on owners of guide dogs and hearing dogs.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179518","179518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27107","2013-12-03","Department for Transport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2013, Official Report, column 306W, on High Speed 2 railway line, what organisation paid for the service advertised by HS2 Ltd as a free bus service provided to help people travel to and from the event on 30 November 2013 (a) from Annesley Woodhouse, Badger Box to Bilborough College and (b) from Strelley, Main Street to Bilborough College to attend the High Speed 2 consultation event on the route from West Midlands to Manchester, Leeds and elsewhere; and what the cost of this service was.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179524","179524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27108","2013-12-03","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how funding by the Ministry of Defence as part of the UK response to Typhoon Haiyan is (a) accredited towards the UK international aid target and (b) will be reimbursed to the Ministry of Defence by her Department.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179513","179513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27109","2013-12-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people are on the housing waiting list; and how many such people have been on the list for over two years in (a) Southampton City Council area, (b) Havant Borough Council area, (c) Fareham Borough Council area and (d) Gosport Borough Council area.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179519","179519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27110","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps her Department has taken to prevent severe acute malnutrition.","Biography information for Baroness Jowell","Dame Tessa Jowell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179520","179520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27111","2013-12-02","HM Treasury","2013-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2013, Official Report, column 943W, on secondment, how many staff in his Department were seconded from trades unions in the same period.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179521","179521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27112","2013-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the amount of social security payments spent on repaying interest on credit.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179522","179522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27113","2013-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease in receipt of employment and support allowance (ESA) and placed in the work related activity group have subsequently come off ESA after returning to work.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179525","179525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27114","2013-12-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many housing unit buildings starts there have been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179526","179526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27115","2013-12-03","Cabinet Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people aged 24 and under have been unemployed for over a year (a) at the most recent date for which data is available and (b) in each of the last 20 years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179527","179527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27116","2013-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has for the work-related activity group in employment and support allowance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179528","179528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27117","2013-12-03","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether evidence gathered for the proposed Modern Slavery Bill and the evidence on contemporary slavery supplied by the Anti-Trafficking Monitoring Group will inform the UK response to proposals for a new instrument to supplement the International Labour Organization Forced Labour Convention.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179554","179554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27118","2013-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of introducing a jobseeker classification instrument as in the case in Australia.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179529","179529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27119","2013-12-03","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many civil servants were employed by his Department and at what cost on 1 October (a) 2010 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179555","179555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27120","2013-12-03","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many emergency medicine consultants have (a) opted not to practise, (b) retired and (c) left to work overseas in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179556","179556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27121","2013-12-03","Attorney General","2013-11-28","To ask the Attorney General, how many officials in the Law Officers' Departments have worked, or are currently working, on the legal challenge lodged with the European Court of Justice on 25 September 2013 on new EU rules on pay in the banking sector.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179557","179557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27122","2013-12-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2013, Official Report, column 633W, on Afghanistan, what advances in technology have triggered reviews of UK policy on establishing positive identification and determination of status in the last two years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179530","179530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27123","2013-12-02","HM Treasury","2013-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many sports clubs in (a) Portsmouth South constituency and (b) Hampshire will be affected by the recent changes to the Community Amateur Sports Clubs qualifying rates.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179531","179531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27124","2013-12-03","HM Treasury","2013-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many officials in his Department have worked, or are currently working, on the legal challenge lodged with the European Court of Justice on 25 September 2013 on new EU rules on pay in the banking sector.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179558","179558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27125","2013-12-03","Department for Transport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2013, Official Report, column 306W, on high speed 2: railway line, for which meetings or community meetings along both phase 1 and phase 2 of the route of High Speed 2 free bus services were offered to attendees.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179559","179559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27126","2013-12-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will place in the Library an updated version of the ready reckoner on students loans and debt repayment published in 2010 reflecting his most recent estimate on future earnings, fees and RAB charges.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179560","179560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27127","2013-12-02","Department for Education","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how he will respond to the Skills Commission's recommendations that his Department immediately acknowledge the crisis in information, advice and guidance, and undertake a full review of provision.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179532","179532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27128","2013-12-03","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian needs of displaced Bedouin from the Neqab; what assessment she has made of the reasons for their displacement; and whether she has raised that matter with the Israeli government.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179561","179561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27129","2013-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which military aircraft the traffic collision avoidance system have installed.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179562","179562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27130","2013-12-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of the representations the Prime Minister received (a) supported and (b) opposed the Assisted Dying Bill [Lords]; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179533","179533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27131","2013-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the installation of the traffic collision avoidance system was first recommended for the Tornado fast jet fleet; by whom it was recommended; and how much work has been undertaken to install it to date.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179563","179563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27132","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of her Department's budget for the Occupied Palestinian Territories is allocated for poverty-reduction programmes in East Jerusalem.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179540","179540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27133","2013-12-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will list the UK companies that participated in the UK - Overseas Territories Business Forum on 28 November 2013.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179534","179534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27134","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of her Department's budget for the Occupied Palestinian Territories is allocated for non-governmental, non-UN and non-Palestinian Authority programmes in East Jerusalem.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179535","179535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27135","2013-12-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2013, Official Report, column 902W, on secondment, how many secondments were in place on (a) 30 September 2012 and (b) 30 September 2011.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179541","179541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27136","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when her Department last reviewed and assessed the impact of its spending in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179536","179536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27137","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether development programmes for Palestinians in East Jerusalem are eligible for funding by her Department.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179537","179537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27138","2013-12-02","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2013-11-28","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2013, Official Report, columns 131-3W, on electoral register, in which local authorities electoral registration officers did not meet performance standard 3 on house-to-house calls for non-registration in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179542","179542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27139","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's budget for the Occupied Palestinian Territories is allocated for employment and training programmes in East Jerusalem.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179538","179538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27140","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what projects were funded by the Conflict Pool in Israel and the Occupied Palestinian Territories in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179539","179539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27141","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 16 October 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr K Joslin.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179543","179543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27142","2013-12-02","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 17 October 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr K Bello.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179545","179545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27143","2013-12-02","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2013, Official Report, column 906W, on asylum, what steps she is taking to ensure that all failed asylum applicants are recorded whether they leave the UK voluntarily or otherwise.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179544","179544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27144","2013-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the estimate was of the cost of installing the Traffic Collision Avoidance System on the Tornado fast jet fleet when it was first recommended; and what his latest estimate is on the cost of that installation.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179564","179564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27145","2013-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Board of Inquiry's findings into the collision of two Tornado jets on 3 July 2012 over the Moray Firth.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179565","179565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27146","2013-12-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2013, Official Report, column 551W, on unmanned aerial vehicle, what the (a) unit, (b) service and (c) rank was of each of the US personnel based at the (i) Air Warfare Centre, (ii) Air Battlespace Training Centre or (iii) elsewhere at RAF Waddington.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179546","179546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27147","2013-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the standard operating procedure is for activating the traffic collision avoidance system for RAF aircraft in (a) combat and (b) training missions.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179566","179566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27148","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department plans to give to Marie Stopes International for (a) abortion, (b) family planning and (c) other reproductive health services in the next 12 months; what assessment she has made of the value for money of such expenditure since June 2011; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179547","179547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27149","2013-12-03","Department of Health","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2013, Official Report, columns 1003-4W, on health visitors, how many health visiting students are training and expected to join the workforce between September and November 2014.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179567","179567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27150","2013-12-02","HM Treasury","2013-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Funding for Lending Scheme on house prices in each region and constituent part of the UK in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179548","179548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27151","2013-12-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which international organisations of which the UK is currently a member (a) accept and (b) do not accept applications for membership by aspirant members which are still legally part of another state but whose population has voted to secede from that state.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179550","179550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27152","2013-12-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which international organisations the UK is a member of.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179551","179551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27153","2013-12-03","Department for Transport","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many properties are wholly or partially within the proposed HS2 Voluntary Purchase Zone in the constituencies of (a) Chesham and Amersham, (b) Beaconsfield, (c) Aylesbury and (d) Buckingham.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179568","179568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27154","2013-12-02","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the Government's policy is on discussing individual immigration cases with Ministers from the (a) Scottish Government, (b) Welsh Government and (c) Northern Ireland Executive.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179552","179552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27155","2013-12-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when those countries who were not founder members of the World Trade Organisation, formerly known as the General Agreement on Trade and Tariffs, first made their application for membership; what the period for time was which expired between the application being made and being accepted; what the period of ratification was of each such agreement; and what the duration was between lodging the application and becoming a member in each case.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179549","179549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27156","2013-12-02","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate she has made of the number of Bulgarian and Romanian migrants who will come to the UK after accession; and what estimate she has made of the number of those migrants who will claim welfare benefits.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179553","179553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27157","2013-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times the National Tactical Response Group was called out to each prison in London in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179575","179575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27158","2013-12-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department plans to support the Royal College of Psychiatrists' proposal to promote a show garden at the RHS Chelsea Flower Show in 2015 in support of veteran's mental health; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179569","179569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27159","2013-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what budget was allocated to the National Tactical Response Group in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-14; and what that budget is expected to be in 2014-15.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179576","179576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27160","2013-12-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make a statement on the Assisted Dying Bill [Lords].","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179570","179570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27161","2013-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to promote awareness of new local authority welfare provisions introduced in the recent Social Fund reform on his Department's website.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179577","179577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27162","2013-12-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how Milton Keynes College has performed against its contracted performance targets in the delivery of education services in HMP Oakwood since that prison opened.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179578","179578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27163","2013-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what enforcement action has been taken following the visit by HM Revenue and Customs and officers from his Department to employment agencies in the Corby area between 28 and 30 May 2013; how many fines have been issued; whether any legal proceedings are completed or pending; how much money has been recovered and returned; how many follow up visits have taken place; and if he will publish a report of the Joint task force of his Department and HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179571","179571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27164","2013-12-02","Department for Education","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools moved from a three tier to a two tier system during 2012-13; how many schools are committed to making such a change during 2013-14; and how many schools are engaged in consultations concerning the possibility of making this change at some point in the future.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179572","179572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27165","2013-12-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2013, Official Report, column 167W, on local government: Tower Hamlets, if he will place in the Library all responses his Department received from councils on that consultation document.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179573","179573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27166","2013-12-03","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2013, Official Report, column 545W, how many passengers arriving by general aviation who were assessed as high-risk by the UK Border Force between April and August 2013 and who were (a) met by Border Force personnel in accordance with the compliance obligations summarised in the National Audit Office publication, The Border Force: Securing the Border, published in August 2013 and (b) were not met by Border Force personnel.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179579","179579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27167","2013-12-03","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK Border Force personnel were assigned to and given specific training for meeting passengers arriving into the UK assessed as high-risk on scheduled flights in 2012-13.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179580","179580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27168","2013-12-03","Home Office","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer from the Secretary of State for Transport of 12 November 2013, Official Report, column 572W, on aviation, why her Department has no plans to match arrivals data from general aviation entries into the UK with the National Air Traffic System.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179581","179581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27169","2013-12-02","Department for International Development","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department plans to allocate to the International Planned Parenthood Federation for (a) abortion, (b) family planning and (c) other reproductive health services in the next 12 months; what assessment she has made of the value for money gained from previous such expenditure since June 2010; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179574","179574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27170","2013-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent staff were employed by the National Tactical Response Group (NTRG) in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13; and how many staff will have been employed by the NTRG in 2013-14.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179582","179582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27171","2013-12-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on what occasions providers of prison education services in England and Wales have not met their contracted performance targets in each of the last five years; and what financial penalties were incurred in each such case.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179583","179583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/27172","2013-12-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2013, Official Report, columns 663-4W, when the names of companies receiving compensation will be published.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179584","179584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26708","2013-11-29","Home Office","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179170","179170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26712","2013-11-29","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that local authorities are aware of their legal duties on choice of accommodation and charging for residential accommodation; if he will issue guidance to local authorities highlighting their legal obligations and setting a usual cost for purchasing care that has due regard to the actual cost of providing care locally; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179157","179157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26713","2013-11-29","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue updated guidance on choice of accommodation and charging for residential accommodation in advance of any change in the number of adults in residential care who will pay a top-up once the capped costs reforms take effect from April 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179158","179158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26714","2013-11-29","Department for Education","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many places available for the training of teachers on the School Direct system are unfilled.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179176","179176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26715","2013-11-29","Department for Education","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many places are available for training teachers on the School Direct system.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179177","179177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26716","2013-11-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding his Department provides to conservation projects that aim to prevent a further decline in the (a) Asian elephant population, (b) African elephant population, (c) Asian rhinoceros population and (d) African rhinoceros population.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179178","179178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26717","2013-11-29","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients aged under 18 were admitted to hospital with a primary diagnosis of malnutrition in (a) England and (b) each London borough in 2011-12.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179179","179179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26718","2013-11-29","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many health services in each London borough have achieved 'You're Welcome' accreditation.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179180","179180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26719","2013-11-29","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of adults on the Care Programme Approach who were receiving secondary mental health services were in employment in (a) England (b) each mental health trust, (c) each parimary care trust, (d) each clinical commissioning group and (e) each local authority area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179181","179181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26720","2013-11-29","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of adults receiving secondary mental health services were in employment in (a) England, (b) each mental health trust, (c) each primary care trust, (d) each clinical commissioning group and (e) each local authority area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179182","179182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26721","2013-11-29","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on (a) locums, (b) agency nurses and (c) other temporary workers in the NHS (i) in England, (ii) in each hospital trust, (iii) by each community health service and (iv) in each mental health trust in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179183","179183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26722","2013-11-29","Department for Education","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what meetings he has planned with representatives of teaching trades unions relating to their grievances following his recent correspondence with them.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179184","179184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26723","2013-11-29","Department for Education","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish all recent correspondence with teaching trades unions and the NUT and NASUWT.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179185","179185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26724","2013-11-29","Department for Education","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will meet the NUT and NASUWT as part of an attempted dispute resolution.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179186","179186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26725","2013-11-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the effect of the decision by RWE not to proceed with the Atlantic Array offshore wind project on (a) UK industrial capability in the offshore wind industry, (b) the supply chain within the industry and (c) the UK's competitiveness in the offshore wind industry.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179187","179187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26726","2013-11-29","Department for Education","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of trainee teachers in (a) the School Direct programme and (b) tertiary institutions are disabled.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179188","179188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26727","2013-11-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to determine whether the Atlantic Array offshore wind project could go ahead with another company; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179189","179189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26728","2013-11-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179159","179159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26729","2013-11-29","Department for Education","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of trainee teachers who are in (a) the School Direct programme and (b) tertiary institutions are from a Black and minority ethnic community.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179190","179190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26730","2013-11-29","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the specific hurdles are that were described by the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority in its statement on 19 September 2013 regarding the recent science paper Mitochondrial replacement, evolution, and the clinic; and what assessment he has made of the validity of the conclusion in that paper to monitor fertility and health outcomes through to sexual maturity among the macaques already born after maternal spindle transfer.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179191","179191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26731","2013-11-29","Attorney General","2013-11-27","To ask the Attorney General, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in the Law Officers' Departments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179160","179160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26732","2013-11-29","Cabinet Office","2013-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179161","179161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26733","2013-11-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179162","179162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26734","2013-11-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179163","179163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26735","2013-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179164","179164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26736","2013-11-29","Department for Education","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179165","179165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26737","2013-11-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179166","179166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26738","2013-11-29","Department for Education","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much local authorities have paid as a result of legal fees incurred by parents appealing decisions made regarding special educational needs children in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179192","179192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26739","2013-11-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179167","179167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26740","2013-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179168","179168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26741","2013-11-29","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179169","179169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26742","2013-11-29","Department for International Development","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179171","179171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26743","2013-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179172","179172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26744","2013-11-29","Department for Transport","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179173","179173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26745","2013-11-29","HM Treasury","2013-11-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179174","179174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26746","2013-11-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are employed within centralised IT departments or teams in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179175","179175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26747","2013-11-29","Department for Education","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2013, Official Report, column 406W, on children in care: missing persons, how many children went missing from care in 2011-12; and how many such children were missing for over one month in each London borough.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179193","179193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26748","2013-11-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will revise the eligibility for higher winter fuel payments to allow people turning 80 after 22 September 2014 to receive a higher entitlement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179204","179204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26749","2013-11-29","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2013, Official Report, column 711W, on Family Nurse Partnership Programme, how many first-time mothers under the age of (a) 16, (b) 18 and (c) 20 there were in each London borough in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179194","179194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26750","2013-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of eligible (a) men and (b) women were released on home detention curfew in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179205","179205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26751","2013-11-29","Cabinet Office","2013-11-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people employed by private and voluntary sector providers of local government services in the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179195","179195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26752","2013-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) female and (b) male prisoners per 100 of the prison population were disciplined following adjudications in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179206","179206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26753","2013-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) female and (b) male prisoners per 100 of the prison population were disciplined following adjudications for violent incidents in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179207","179207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26754","2013-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the undertaking given in the National Security Through Technology White Paper Cm 8278, paragraph 117, what steps he has taken to pursue arrangements that give his Department's supplier base greater insight into the threats and problems faced by the armed services.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179196","179196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26755","2013-11-29","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to raise the issue of HIV prevention with his European counterparts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179208","179208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26756","2013-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the undertaking given in the National Security Through Technology White Paper Cm 8278, paragraph 116, whether he now publishes annually (a) his defence and security priority themes and (b) the supporting strategies for defence and security science and technology.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179197","179197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26757","2013-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that the UK has international support before formally requesting that the UN Human Rights Council sets up an international inquiry into allegations of war crimes during Sri Lanka's civil war; what assessment he has made of whether it will be necessary for the UK to raise the issue at UN level; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179209","179209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26758","2013-11-29","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on the potential negative health effects of homophobic bullying in schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179210","179210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26759","2013-11-29","HM Treasury","2013-11-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what revenue the Crown Estate receives for each (a) sea bed-fixed wind turbine and (b) floating wind turbine.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179211","179211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26760","2013-11-29","Department for Education","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what involvement his Department has in the troubled families programme.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179198","179198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26761","2013-11-29","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the report by the Care Quality Commission, The State of Health Care and Adult Social Care in England, on the number of people relying on a top-up to pay for a residential care home places; and how many local authorities build in regular reviews to check whether third parties are able and willing to pay such top-ups for these residents.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179212","179212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26762","2013-11-29","Department for Education","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many special needs schools for (a) two to nine year olds, (b) nine to 16 year olds and (c) over 16 year olds were in operation in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179199","179199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26763","2013-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions she has had with the US as part of the proposed Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement on the blockade of Cuba and existing sanctions on the EU businesses trading with that country.","Biography information for Mr Frank Doran","Mr Frank Doran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179213","179213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26764","2013-11-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions he has had with RWE on its decision not to proceed with the Atlantic Array offshore wind project; and whether he has received reports that the announcement by the Prime Minister to review green levies played a part in the decision by the company not to proceed.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179200","179200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26765","2013-11-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department plans to take to exploit available UK coal reserves.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179268","179268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26766","2013-11-29","HM Treasury","2013-11-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the potential reduction in the cost to his Department's tax-free childcare scheme from restricting eligibility for that scheme to parents earning less than (a) £100,000, (b) £90,000, (c) £80,000, (d) £75,000, (e) £70,000, (f) £65,000 and (g) £60,000 per year.","Biography information for Simon Wright","Simon Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179269","179269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26767","2013-11-29","HM Treasury","2013-11-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the potential reduction in the cost of his Department's proposed tax-free childcare scheme from restricting that scheme to providing support for up to two children.","Biography information for Simon Wright","Simon Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179270","179270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26768","2013-12-02","Department for Transport","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many properties in the entire safeguarded area for phase one of High Speed 2 are not to be demolished.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179222","179222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26769","2013-12-02","Department for Transport","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much Deloitte LLP was paid for producing the HS2 Property bond option report; and whether this report was reviewed by either an external independent panel or his Department.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179223","179223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26770","2013-12-02","Department for Transport","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when Deloitte LLP and Robert Colley were appointed to the new HS2 Ltd Economic Advisory Panel; and whether Deloitte had been commissioned to undertake any work for (a) HS2 Ltd and (b) his Department before this date.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179224","179224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26771","2013-12-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) nationality and (b) gender was of each suspected victim of trafficking referred to the Trafficking Victim Support Scheme operated by the Salvation Army in October 2013; in which (i) region, (ii) country and (iii) parliamentary constituency each of the suspected victims was found; and which agency referred each person to the Scheme.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179233","179233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26772","2013-12-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make it easier for domestic energy consumers to switch supplier.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179234","179234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26773","2013-11-29","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the estimate in the Care of Elderly People UK Market Survey by Laing and Buisson, published in January 2013, that the average amount paid by local authorities for residential care in 2012 was around £50 to £140 per week below a fair market price; if he will issue revised guidance to local authorities to ensure they have regard to the actual cost of providing care locally in care homes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179271","179271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26774","2013-12-02","Department for Education","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will meet the hon. Member for Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland and representatives of Handale Primary School to discuss the Priority School Building Programme.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179235","179235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26775","2013-11-29","HM Treasury","2013-11-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the economic benefits to the North West of England of Scotland remaining part of the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179272","179272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26776","2013-11-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the portability of Green Deal assessments.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179244","179244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26777","2013-11-29","Prime Minister","2013-11-27","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with his Spanish counterpart on the situation on the Spanish-Gibraltarian border.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179245","179245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26778","2013-12-02","Home Office","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the report by the Independent Chief Inspector of Borders and Immigration, An Inspection of Border Force Freight Operations, published in November 2013, what steps she plans to take to ensure that the lines of communication between her Department and HM Revenue and Customs are strengthened in order to prevent those smuggling goods into the UK from avoiding prosecution.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179236","179236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26779","2013-12-02","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many instances of eye injury inflicted by laser pens have been recorded in the last five years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179237","179237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26780","2013-12-02","Department for Transport","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what involvement Robert Colley had in Deloitte LLP's report on a property bond option for High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179225","179225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26781","2013-12-02","Department for Transport","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether a tendering process was undertaken to determine who would produce the report into a property bond option for High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179226","179226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26782","2013-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to his Department of the Export Support Team was in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and whether these costs have been reimbursed by the UK Trade & Investment Defence & Security Organisation.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179246","179246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26783","2013-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which export promotion teams including Ministry of Defence or military personnel have been established for (a) the Eurofighter Typhoon, (b) combat ships, (c) submarines and (d) complex weapons; and when each such team was set up.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179247","179247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26784","2013-12-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November 2013, Official Report, column 202W, on military aircraft, how many recorded laser-related events have resulted in accidents taking place.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179238","179238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26785","2013-11-29","Home Office","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to prevent persecution of others on the basis of their hair colour.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179248","179248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26786","2013-12-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been prosecuted for offences involving use of a laser pen in the last five years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179239","179239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26787","2013-12-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2013, Official Report, columns 82-3W, on disadvantaged families and with reference to the statement in the Answer that his Department does not hold the information requested relating to employment and incidence of anti-social behaviour (ASB), through what mechanisms his Department monitors (a) the effectivness of the programme against its stated criteria including employment and ASB and (b) its cost-effectiveness in terms of use of public funds; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179227","179227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26788","2013-12-02","HM Treasury","2013-11-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will consider replacing the separate primary and secondary National Insurance thresholds with a single threshold; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179241","179241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26789","2013-12-02","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the per capita spend on mental health services in West Sussex has been in each of the last five years; and how this spend compares to the national average in that period.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179228","179228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26790","2013-12-02","HM Treasury","2013-11-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of paying tax credits to citizens of other EU member states who are employed in the UK in the most recent year for which data are available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179242","179242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26791","2013-12-02","Department of Health","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the per capita breakdown of spending on mental health services in each local authority area has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179229","179229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26792","2013-12-02","HM Treasury","2013-11-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to bring forward changes to the eligibility criteria for citizens of other EU countries employed in the UK who apply for tax credits.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179243","179243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26793","2013-12-02","Home Office","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance she has issued on the repeat issuing of police information notices to the same person on the basis of similar allegations.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179230","179230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26794","2013-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what analysis his Department has undertaken of a link between artificial insemination of cattle and the spread of bovine tuberculosis; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179240","179240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26795","2013-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the under-occupancy penalty on non-resident fathers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179231","179231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26796","2013-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has (a) made and (b) received on the findings on abortion and human rights in the report of the Special Rapporteur on torture and other cruel, inhuman or degrading treatment or punishment, published on 1 February 2013.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179250","179250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26797","2013-12-02","Northern Ireland Office","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she is having with (a) the Northern Ireland Executive and (b) her Irish counterpart on the effect of changes in the cost of energy on older people in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179249","179249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26798","2013-11-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2013, Official Report, column 83W, where details of meetings that may have been held between officials in his Department and representatives of Cleveland Fire Authority have been published.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179251","179251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26799","2013-12-03","Department for Education","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding his Department plans to allocate to under three provision in school buildings being built as part of the Priority School Building Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179266","179266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/26800","2013-11-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what performance measures his Department has put in place for Jobcentre Plus offices.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179252","179252"
