"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385951","2015-07-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans she has to address the effects of the Renewable Heat Incentive on the ground source industry; and what consultation she plans to undertake with that industry on that incentive.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4483","4483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385952","2015-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the report, Give peace a chance, by the Campaign to Protect Rural England, published in May 2015, if he will make it his policy to (a) agree a definition of and (b) produce detailed planning guidance on tranquility.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4430","4430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385953","2015-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which places in London have air pollution levels that exceeded the EU limit on (a) NO2, (b) Ozone, (c) PM10 particles and (d) PM 2.5 particles in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4471","4471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385954","2015-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what contingent financial support is being provided for project risks associated with the Thames Tideway Tunnel infrastructure project; and what limit has been set on such support.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4465","4465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385955","2015-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether state aid approval from the EU Commission has been granted for the financial support package for the Thames Tideway Tunnel infrastructure project.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4462","4462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385956","2015-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, under what circumstances the Government would invest equity in the Thames Tideway Tunnel infrastructure project.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4463","4463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385957","2015-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what commitment she has made to provide loans should the Thames Tideway Tunnel infrastructure project be unable to access debt capital markets.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4461","4461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385958","2015-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on government financial support to enable the Thames Tideway Tunnel infrastructure project to attract private sector financing.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4459","4459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385959","2015-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to his contribution of 9 June 2015, Official Report, column 1056, what progress he has made on raising the question of import duties imposed on cane sugar with his EU counterparts.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4468","4468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385960","2015-07-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent progress has been made on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4484","4484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385961","2015-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the government of Pakistan on its attempt to close the offices of Save the Children in Islamabad.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4482","4482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385962","2015-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether an environmental impact assessment has been undertaken of the proposed award of licences for industrial fishing in British waters off Ascension Island.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4408","4408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385963","2015-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how fishing in British waters off Ascension Island will be policed; and what steps his Department is taking to prevent over-fishing or illegal bycatch landings in those waters.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4409","4409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385964","2015-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether surveys of fish populations have been undertaken in British waters off Ascension Island to ascertain the effects of industrial fishing.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4410","4410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385965","2015-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to all parties involved in the conflict in South Sudan on stopping the forced recruitment of children; and what steps he is taking to support UNMISS in taking preventative action to stop such forced recruitment.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4434","4434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385966","2015-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of (a) the likely numbers of British citizens resident elsewhere in the EU who would return to live in the UK in the event of a British exit from the EU and (b) the potential effect of such returnees on public services.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4435","4435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385967","2015-06-30","Department of Health","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has made to the Health and Care Professions Council on its decision to increase the mandatory registration fee for care workers.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4437","4437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385968","2015-06-30","Department of Health","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to increase mental health funding in real terms in the next spending review period.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4432","4432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385969","2015-06-30","Department of Health","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Health and Care Professions Council's decision to increase the mandatory registration fee for care workers on recruitment and retention of highly motivated staff in that profession.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4438","4438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385970","2015-06-30","Department of Health","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on how much each professional membership body in the health and social care sector has increased its mandatory registration fee by in the last year.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4439","4439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385971","2015-07-01","Department of Health","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in St Helens North constituency are identified as suffering from long-term illnesses; and what the comparable average figure is in the (a) North West and (b) UK.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4416","4416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385972","2015-07-01","Department of Health","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has for regional or national multi-disciplinary care teams to incorporate aspects of Huntington's disease care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4481","4481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385973","2015-07-01","Department of Health","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential cost and benefits of advanced genetic testing techniques for the clinical assessment and treatment of ovarian cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4475","4475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385974","2015-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the pardon granted to Alan Turing for his conviction under the Criminal Law Amendment Act 1885, what his policy is on granting pardons posthumously to people convicted under (a) the Witchcraft Acts 1563 and 1603, (b) the Blasphemy Act 1604 and (c) other legislation that has been repealed.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4469","4469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385975","2015-06-30","Home Office","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will (a) publish a new drug strategy and (b) consult drug treatment providers in the preparation of such a strategy; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4406","4406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385976","2015-07-01","Home Office","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Office for National Statistics' latest annual population statistics to June 2014, what steps she is taking to ensure that annual net migration is brought back down to the tens of thousands.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4443","4443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385977","2015-07-01","House of Commons Commission","2015-06-26","To ask the hon. Member for Mole Valley representing the House of Commons Commission, whether all contractors supplying a service to the House have now been signed up as living wage employers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4404","4404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385978","2015-06-30","Department for International Development","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to (a) reduce the size of and (b) increase the number of independent members on the Board of the Disasters Emergencies Committee.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4436","4436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385979","2015-06-30","Department for International Development","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in East Sudan.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4433","4433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385980","2015-06-30","Department for International Development","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of sanctions on people considered to be impeding the peace process in South Sudan.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4478","4478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385981","2015-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the business case for the privatisation of the collection and enforcement of fines compensation and other charges imposed by the criminal courts will be published.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4457","4457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385982","2015-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what payment methods will be available for people to pay fines, compensation and other charges imposed by the criminal courts under the contract for that service with a private provider.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4456","4456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385983","2015-07-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the policy is of HM Courts and Tribunals Service on sending reminders by (a) text message and (b) email to defendants reminding them of the time and date of (i) court hearings and (ii) bail conditions.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4420","4420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385984","2015-07-01","Prime Minister","2015-06-26","To ask the Prime Minister, how many times he has attended meetings of the British-Irish Council since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4417","4417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385985","2015-06-30","Prime Minister","2015-06-26","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will publish a list of all of his appointed (a) political, (b) trade and (c) other envoys; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4411","4411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385986","2015-07-01","Prime Minister","2015-06-26","To ask the Prime Minister, what meetings the Government's Anti-Corruption Champion has had with business organisations to discuss the operation of the Bribery Act 2010 and Government guidance on that Act since he took up his post.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4472","4472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385987","2015-07-01","Prime Minister","2015-06-26","To ask the Prime Minister, when (a) his Department and (b) the Cabinet Office has held meetings with business organisations to discuss the operation of the Bribery Act 2010 and that Government guidance on the Act since January 2015.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4473","4473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385988","2015-07-01","Department for Transport","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on assessing the case for electrifying the rail line from Bristol to Derby.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4466","4466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385989","2015-07-02","Department for Transport","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve local cycle infrastructure in cities and towns in Tyne and Wear.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4477","4477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385990","2015-07-01","Department for Transport","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2015 to Question 3530, by what date he expects Pacer trains to be withdrawn from service by those franchises managed by his Department.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4442","4442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385991","2015-07-02","Department for Transport","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to prevent bus companies reducing bus routes and services in the North East.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4476","4476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385992","2015-06-30","Department for Transport","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the electrification of the Valley Lines in Wales to be completed.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4431","4431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385993","2015-07-01","Department for Transport","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his oral statement of 25 June 2015, Official Report, column 1067-8, on Network Rail, what effect changes to Network Rail's programme will have on upgrading of stock on and electrification of the lines between (a) Liverpool and Manchester and (b) Liverpool and Wigan.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4423","4423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385994","2015-07-01","Department for Transport","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his oral statement of 25 June 2015, Official Report, column 1067-8, on Network Rail, what his policy is on electrification of the Leeds-Harrogate-York line.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4425","4425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385995","2015-07-01","Department for Transport","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of June 25 2015 to Question 3539, which external organisations have held meetings and on which dates with the Rail Infrastructure Futures unit since that unit's creation.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4427","4427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385996","2015-07-01","Department for Transport","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of June 25 2015 to Question 3449, what the total value was of the contracts entered into by Network Rail in connection with (a) Midland Main Line and (b) TransPennine electrification.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4428","4428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385997","2015-07-01","Department for Transport","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his oral statement of 25 June 2015, Official Report, column 1067-8, on Network Rail, which of the Midland Main Line speed improvement works referenced in that statement are additional to projects already committed under Control Period 5.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4429","4429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385998","2015-07-02","Women and Equalities","2015-06-26","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, which women's (a) rugby, (b) cricket and (c) football matches she has attended in an official capacity since taking office.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4418","4418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385999","2015-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with a learning disability are claiming employment and support allowance and are in the (a) work related activity and (b) support group.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4414","4414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386000","2015-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce the time taken for (a) disability living allowance and (b) personal independence payment assessments for people with a learning disability.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4415","4415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386001","2015-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with a learning disability are currently claiming jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4413","4413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386002","2015-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications of the High Court ruling of June 2015 relating to delays in payment of Personal Independence Payment (PIP) for his plans for implementing PIP.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4426","4426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386003","2015-07-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many privately rented households in the London Borough of Lewisham were in receipt of housing benefit in (a) 2010-11 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4444","4444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386004","2015-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason the Access to Work budget was underspent in 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4407","4407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386005","2015-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total value of payment of housing benefit was in (a) the UK, (b) West Midlands and (c) Coventry in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4452","4452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386006","2015-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of the total value of payment of housing benefit was for properties in London in the most recent period for what figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4453","4453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386007","2015-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many people were eligible to receive and (b) how many and what proportion of people were in receipt of carer's allowance in each local authority area on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4448","4448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386008","2015-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the forecast total value of housing benefit payments that will be made in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4451","4451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386009","2015-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many housing benefit claimants there were in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2011-12 and (e) 2010-11 in the London Borough of Lewisham.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4447","4447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386010","2015-07-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that his Department's website and digital services are accessible to people with sensory losses.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4485","4485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385741","2015-06-30","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many contested employment tribunal cases there were in England and Wales in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4234","4234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385742","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 14 May 2015 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms T Ali.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4227","4227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385743","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what target he has for the number of apprenticeship places to be taken by black and ethnic minority applicants; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4243","4243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385744","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of apprenticeship applications is made by black and ethnic minority applicants.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4244","4244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385745","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many adults he expects to be participating in non-apprenticeship vocational training by 2020.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4267","4267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385746","2015-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices have entered the nuclear sector in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4289","4289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385747","2015-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to address skills shortages in the nuclear sector.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4290","4290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385748","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has for private ownership of the British Business Bank; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4294","4294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385749","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his statement on 25 June 2015, HCWS54, whether the sale of the bank into private ownership will be undertaken using priority investors.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4310","4310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385750","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his statement on 25 June 2015, HCWS54 on the Green Investment Bank, whether the bank when privately-owned will be permitted to invest in nuclear technology.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4320","4320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385751","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his statement on 25 June 2015, HCWS54 on the Green Investment Bank, what control the Government will retain over the (i) appointment of the Chair of the Bank and (ii) strategic direction of the bank's activities following its move into private ownership.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4321","4321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385752","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his statement on 25 June 2015, HCWS54 on the Green Investment Bank, what the intended timescale is for moving the bank into private ownership.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4322","4322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385753","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his statement on 25 June 2015, HCWS54 on the Green Investment Bank, what percentage stake in the bank he will seek to maintain following a move into private ownership.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4323","4323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385754","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his statement on 25 June 2015, HCWS54 on the Green Investment Bank, whether existing staff and directors at the bank will be (a) gifted and (b) permitted to purchase shares in that Bank.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4324","4324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385755","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his statement on 25 June 2015, HCWS54 on the Green Investment Bank, whether shares in the bank will be offered directly to the public.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4325","4325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385756","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to UK Export Finance's 2014-15 Annual Report, what the defence goods for Saudi Arabia are for which Kirintec Ltd has been given £190,480 a bond support facility.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4318","4318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385757","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his statement on 25 June 2015, HCWS54 on the Green Investment Bank, what discussions he plans to have with (a) business organisations, (b) green investors and (c) environmental groups before making a final decision to move that Bank into private ownership.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4319","4319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385758","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices who started their apprenticeships since 2010 were already employed staff converted to apprenticeship status; and what the (a) age, (b) gender and (c) constituency was of each such person.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4341","4341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385759","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on devolving power on apprenticeship policy to local authorities.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4357","4357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385760","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the number of apprentices not paid the minimum wage since 2010; and what the (a) age, (b) gender and (c) parliamentary constituency was of each such apprentice.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4371","4371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385761","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to increase take-up of apprenticeships in engineering, construction and manufacturing.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4372","4372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385762","2015-06-30","Leader of the House","2015-06-25","To ask the Leader of the House, how many government bills introduced in each of the last five years have been (a) England, (b) England and Wales, (c) Great Britain, (d) Wales, (e) Scotland and (f) Northern Ireland only in the scope of their provisions.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4228","4228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385763","2015-06-30","Leader of the House","2015-06-25","To ask the Leader of the House, which government bills introduced in each of the last five years the provisions of which have not extended to Scotland.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4229","4229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385764","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the positive economic benefits of lower fuel prices caused by the fuel duty freeze.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4259","4259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385765","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the national debt, from which individuals or organisations has the money been borrowed; and to whom or to which organisations is the debt owed.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4358","4358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385766","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the gross value of sterling issued through the Government's quantitative easing initiation is included in calculations of the national debt.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4359","4359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385767","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what basis the national debt is calculated.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4360","4360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385768","2015-06-30","HM Treasury","2015-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will amend the VAT status of sixth form colleges so that they are treated the same as academies, free schools, university technical colleges and schools.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4349","4349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385769","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the potential implications for the UK economy are of Greece leaving the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4326","4326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385770","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans that the child element of child tax credit and the child element of universal credit will remain the same while universal credit is rolled out.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4306","4306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385771","2015-06-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much local authorities received in (a) England, (b) Lancashire and (c) Pendle constituency under the New Homes Bonus in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4317","4317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385772","2015-06-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether as part of a city region devolution existing local authority boundaries can be varied where a case is made for doing so.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4256","4256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385773","2015-06-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Local Government Boundary Commission can initiate a boundary review of a local authority in response to public representations without direct instruction from the Secretary of State or a request from the local authority in question.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4257","4257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385774","2015-06-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on the structure of the relationship between metro mayors and local authorities.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4225","4225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385775","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 14 May 2015 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms P Hamilton.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4226","4226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385776","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to improve the provision of access services for on-demand content.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4223","4223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385777","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to improve access to digital services for people with sensory loss.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4224","4224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385778","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to ensure roll-out of superfast broadband to (a) Seagrave and (b) Thrussington in Charnwood.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4254","4254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385779","2015-06-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when his Department will be publishing a response to its consultation on Reforming the Electronic Communications Code launched on 26 February 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4384","4384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385780","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will review the effectiveness of existing legislation on subtitles and audio description for on-demand television.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4378","4378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385781","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with television representatives on the setting of targets on the provision of subtitles for on-demand television services.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4379","4379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385782","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he plans to take to reduce the digital exclusion of people with sensory loss.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4377","4377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385783","2015-07-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the effect to a local economy of hosting the Tour of Britain.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4396","4396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385784","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the design of the Queen Elizabeth Class carrier decks has had to be adjusted to accommodate the heat produced by the F-35B lift fans.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4370","4370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385785","2015-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 June 2015 to Question 2717, in which location each of the nine military working dogs euthanized for aged - welfare reasons in September 2014 last worked.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4383","4383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385786","2015-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many pigs have been shot by his Department in order to replicate battlefield injuries in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4348","4348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385787","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the approximate land value is of each golf course owned by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4337","4337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385788","2015-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is contained within the category of receipts - personnel, as listed as a form of income in his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14 document; and how much was raised by each component of that category.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4352","4352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385789","2015-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is meant by the term receipts - personnel as listed as a form of income in his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4353","4353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385790","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the location is of each golf course owned by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4315","4315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385791","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recruits to the (a) army, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Royal Air Force in each year since 2010 originate from each Commonwealth country.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4314","4314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385792","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2015 to Question 2466, on armed forces: firearms how many of those firearms have been recovered.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4296","4296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385793","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2015 to Question 2466, on armed forces: firearms how many of those weapons were (a) handguns, (b) rifles and (c) automatic weapons.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4297","4297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385794","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he shared his review into bullying, discrimination and harassment in the Army with the Service Complaints Commissioner; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4252","4252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385795","2015-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 June 2015 to Question 2717, in which locations each of the dogs euthanised on the grounds of aged-welfare in September 2014 were euthanised.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4282","4282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385796","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the 2014 review into bullying, discrimination and harassment in the Army; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4250","4250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385797","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library the results of the sexual harassment survey by the Army between March and April 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4249","4249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385798","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) handguns, (b) rifles and (c) automatic weapons have been (i) lost and (ii) stolen in operations overseas in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4274","4274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385799","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Joint Personnel Administration IT system is able to discriminate between informally resolved and withdrawn service complaints; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4245","4245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385800","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff were employed in the office of the Service Complaints Commissioner in each year since 2008; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4246","4246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385801","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many legacy complaints were handled by the Service Complaints Commissioner in each year from 2010 to 2014; how many of those complaints are outstanding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4248","4248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385802","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will ask Ofsted to inspect local authority specialist education services for children with sensory impairments.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4265","4265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385803","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the cost to Ofsted of inspecting local area provision for children with special educational needs and disabilities in the last three years.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4263","4263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385804","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the pupil premium funding of the Pupil Premium was for secondary local authority schools in Sunderland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4264","4264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385805","2015-06-30","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish the next progress report on the Government's Tackling child sexual exploitation action plan, published in November 2011; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4233","4233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385806","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much pupil premium funding has been allocated to primary local authority schools in Sunderland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4266","4266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385807","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the effectiveness of Teachers of the Deaf and the quality of support they provide to deaf children and their families.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4268","4268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385808","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary and secondary students in (a) Sunderland and (b) England have been funded by the pupil premium in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4258","4258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385809","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy in on providing support for childcare costs incurred from providers not registered with Ofsted.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4273","4273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385810","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary schools have gone from an inadequate to a good Ofsted rating in four years since 2005; and what steps her Department takes to recognise the achievements of headteachers, teachers and governors.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4305","4305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385811","2015-06-30","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff who have been dismissed from her Department in the last three years were within 24 months of retirement.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4354","4354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385812","2015-06-30","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff who have been dismissed from her Department in the last three years were trade union representatives.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4355","4355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385813","2015-06-30","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff in her Department have been dismissed in the last three years; how many such staff were (a) disabled, (b) black and minority ethnic, (c) over 50 years old, (d) female and (e) male.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4356","4356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385814","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that (a) dyslexia and (b) other learning disabilities are tested for at an early age, and that the relevant support is given to make sure the child does not fall academically behind their peers.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4332","4332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385815","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will bring forward legislative proposals preventing people aged under 18 years old from being categorised as intentionally homeless.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4333","4333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385816","2015-06-30","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the VAT costs incurred by sixth form colleges in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4388","4388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385817","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking in schools to tackle childhood obesity.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4365","4365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385818","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2015 to Question 333, what steps (a) her Department and (b) Ofsted plans to take to monitor the effect on children of there being no educational psychologists employed by the local authority in whose area their school is located.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4347","4347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385819","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she plans to take to ensure that technology used for nuclear power meets rigorous safety, security and environmental standards.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4366","4366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385820","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the Competition and Markets Authority updated issue statement, Energy market investigation, published on 18 February 2015.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4367","4367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385821","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the findings of the report, Analysis of Generation Profitability by the Competition and Markets Authority, published on 25 February 2015.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4368","4368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385822","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to her contribution of 22 June 2015, Official Report, column 618, on onshore wind subsidies, when details of the remote island Contract for Difference strike price will be published.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4373","4373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385823","2015-07-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average annual power output is for solar panels installed in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4394","4394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385824","2015-07-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average annual power output is of wind turbines installed in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4395","4395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385825","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information her Department holds on the highest level of EBITDA on energy generation that has occurred in the last three years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4335","4335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385826","2015-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether it is her policy that high hazard areas of work at the Sellafield site remain a priority.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4293","4293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385827","2015-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how long it will take to complete decommissioning of Magnox sites on current annual expenditure.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4291","4291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385828","2015-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will raise with the Chancellor of the Exchequer the provision of further research and development tax relief to companies developing innovative technologies to help accelerate the process of decommissioning nuclear sites.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4292","4292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385829","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to support employment in the oil and gas sector in Aberdeen.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4313","4313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385830","2015-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential effects of withdrawal of subsidies to onshore wind projects on investor confidence in the offshore wind sector.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4283","4283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385831","2015-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the effect of changes to planning permission for onshore wind projects on investor confidence in the offshore wind sector.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4284","4284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385832","2015-06-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what arrangements are in place to determine long-term planning for the UK's energy mix; and what organisation is responsible for ensuring security of supply.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4285","4285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385833","2015-07-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many seismologists and geologists are employed by her Department; what advice her Department sought from seismologists and geologists on fracking in Lancashire and East Sussex; what the cost of this advice was; and if she will publish the advice she received from external services.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4288","4288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385834","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many advertisements that failed to meet the minimum standards for online pet advertising were removed from pet-related internet sites in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4270","4270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385835","2015-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to maintain the ban on the use of neonicotinoid pesticides.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4309","4309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385836","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on beak trimming of laying hens; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4338","4338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385837","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what salmon netting or trapping stations are operational around the English coast; where they are; and how many salmon were taken by each in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4304","4304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385838","2015-07-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to protect pubs in rural areas.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4403","4403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385839","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how her Department plans to reduce the disposal level of edible food in the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4336","4336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385840","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions his Department has had with manufacturers of anti-freeze on the addition of bittering agents to reduce ingestion by animals.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4362","4362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385841","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the government of the Republic of Sudan on the arrest and detention of Rev. Yat Michael and Rev. Peter Yen Reith of the South Sudan Presbyterian Evangelical Church.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4374","4374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385842","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the government of Egypt on the death sentence passed on the former President Mohammad Morsi.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4375","4375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385843","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what sanctions his Department has considered imposing on Egypt in response to the death sentence passed on Mohammad Morsi.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4376","4376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385844","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to prevent the use of chlorine bombs in Syria.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4311","4311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385845","2015-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had in the G7 and the EU on steps to reduce threats to religious freedom in Africa and the Middle East.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4279","4279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385846","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what guidance he gives to banks on the legality of conducting business with illegal settlements in the West Bank.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4275","4275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385847","2015-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what criteria the Government will use to determine the right time for the UK to recognise Palestine as a state; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4278","4278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385848","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage the Israeli government to abandon plans for a new settler city in Gvaot.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4276","4276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385849","2015-06-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations Ministers in his Department have made to their counterparts in Ethiopia on the detention of Andargachew Tsege.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4281","4281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385850","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients with a postal address in Wales have used hospital services in (a) Countess of Chester, (b) Arrowe Park, Wirral, (c) Clatterbridge, Wirral, (d) The Christie, Manchester, (e) Agnes Hunt, Gobowen and (f) Liverpool Children's Hospital in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4251","4251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385851","2015-07-01","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses were recruited by each NHS Trust in Lancashire in 2014; and how many of those nurses trained (a) at the University of Central Lancashire, (b) at Edge Hill University, (c) at Bolton University, (d) at other universities, (e) in Italy, (f) in Spain, (g) in other EU countries and (h) in non-EU countries.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4286","4286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385852","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the number of intensive care unit beds in the UK on the number of transplants that per capita the NHS can provide.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4312","4312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385853","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department evaluates the effectiveness of statins used in the NHS.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4327","4327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385854","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many intensive care unit beds there are per capita in the UK.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4316","4316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385855","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will require Birmingham Children's Hospital and Birmingham Heartlands Hospital Trusts to fund jointly a paediatric neuromuscular consultant.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4334","4334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385856","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to maintain current levels of financial support for the assistance of Alzheimers patients.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4328","4328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385857","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase awareness of organ donation.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4329","4329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385858","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people in England and Wales are waiting for a week or more for an appointment with a GP; and what steps he is taking to decrease the length of such waits.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4330","4330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385859","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the access of cervical cancer screenings to women under the age of 25.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4331","4331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385860","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of the proposed devolution of health care functions to Metro Mayors and Combined Authorities.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4343","4343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385861","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the criteria are by which NHS area teams assess Individual Funding Request (IFR) applications; whether there is a maximum threshold for the price of a medicine for which an IFR can be submitted; and whether different criteria are applied according to price.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4345","4345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385862","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England will issue a commissioning position on the use of Lomitapide for the treatment of Homozygous Familial Hypercholesterolemia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4346","4346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385863","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what date NHS England plans to publish decisions made by its Specialised Commissioning Committee on the draft clinical commissioning policies for (a) Duodopa for advanced Parkinson's disease and (b) other specialised services that are currently under consideration.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4399","4399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385864","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of NHS dentists.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4363","4363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385865","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress NHS England has made in its review of the draft clinical commissioning policy for Duodopa; and how the views of clinicians and those affected by Parkinson's disease have been taken into account during that review.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4398","4398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385866","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will review the funding she committed in September 2014 to strengthening border security measures at Calais to (a) bring forward planned expenditure and (b) increase the funding available.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4380","4380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385867","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to speed up the process of removing Muslim extremists living in the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4364","4364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385868","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase the number of Syrian refugees entering the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4402","4402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385869","2015-06-30","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which local authorities have agreed to take refugees under the resettlement programme for the most vulnerable Syrian refugees programme; and how many such refugees will be taken by each such authority.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4387","4387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385870","2015-06-30","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will allocate more resources to speed up the processing of applications for UK passports for British children born (a) overseas and (b) in areas of conflict.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4386","4386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385871","2015-07-01","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications from Eritrean nationals were decided in (a) April and (b) May 2015; and what decision was taken in each such case.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4392","4392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385872","2015-07-01","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will review and update her Department's country guidance on Eritrea relating to illegal exit and national service to take better account of the UN Commission of Inquiry on Human Rights in Eritrea.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4393","4393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385873","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations she has received from higher education institutions on the proposed reduction of English Language test centres.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4344","4344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385874","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department provides to employers sponsoring workers on Tier 2 visas on potential changes to their employees' immigration status as a result of 2011 immigration rules changes requiring workers who have been in the UK more than five years to earn more than £35,000 gross per annum; and what steps she is taking to help employers support such employees.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4295","4295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385875","2015-06-30","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional security arrangements have been made to ensure the safety of His Holiness the Dalai Lama during his visits to the UK this year.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4230","4230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385876","2015-06-30","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the risk posed to the Dalai Lama by Shugden followers and other organisations based in the UK who have signalled their intention to disrupt his overseas public engagements.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4231","4231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385877","2015-06-30","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what instructions have been issued to government departments regarding the retention of documents pertinent to the Goddard Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4232","4232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385878","2015-06-30","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress the Goddard Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse has made in its work; how many meetings it has had; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4235","4235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385879","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) budget is, (b) full-time equivalent staff is and (c) objectives are for 2015-16 of the taskforce on migration issues in the Mediterranean.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4261","4261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385880","2015-07-01","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what meetings her Department has had or plans to have with (a) representatives of church groups, (b) the Muslim Council of Britain, (c) the Board of Deputies, (d) the Christian Institute and (e) other faith groups on extremism disruption orders.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4287","4287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385881","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the French policing response at Calais; and whether she plans to meet the French interior minister and local police to discuss the security situation at that port.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4271","4271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385882","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of acts of criminal damage or violence undertaken in the pas de Calais region against vehicles owned by UK companies or citizens since July 2014; and what representations he has made to French authorities on that matter.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4269","4269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385883","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she next plans to meet (a) ferry operators, (b) Eurostar and (c) Eurotunnel to discuss the situation in Calais.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4272","4272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385884","2015-06-30","Department for International Development","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent progress her Department has made on tackling ebola in West Africa; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4280","4280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385885","2015-07-01","Department for International Development","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department allocates annually for research into neglected tropical diseases.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4389","4389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385886","2015-07-01","Department for International Development","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department allocates each year to ensure that people in the developing world living with HIV who have also contracted tuberculosis have access to anti-tuberculosis drugs.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4390","4390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385887","2015-07-01","Department for International Development","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department allocates each year to ensure that individuals in the developing world living with HIV have access to HIV drugs.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4391","4391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385888","2015-06-29","Department for International Development","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to improve the humanitarian situation in Yemen.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4369","4369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385889","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 1334, what the cost was of the research on prisoners' clothing and their self-esteem; and for what reasons the study was not sufficiently large to meet the quality assurance process required by the National Offender Management Service for publication.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4307","4307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385890","2015-07-01","Scotland Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will visit Preston to commemorate the Battle of Preston in 1715.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4236","4236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385891","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what statistics his Department holds on road traffic accidents at the Thrussington to Seagrove Road crossover with the A46 in each year from 2005 to 2014.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4247","4247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385892","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to improve the A46-Seagrave to Thrussington road crossover junction.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4253","4253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385893","2015-06-30","Department for Transport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate how many people in the Dundee area benefit from the Regional Air Connectivity Fund.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4308","4308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385894","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will develop a uniform standard for ensuring disruptive and heavily intoxicated airline passengers are not permitted to fly on subsequent occasions.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4298","4298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385895","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of Network Rail's ability to deliver major projects to time and budget; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4299","4299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385896","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Control Period 5 renewal and refurbishment plan for the Sussex area of the South East Route.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4300","4300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385897","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the planned expenditure in the Sussex area of the South East Route is for each year of Control Period 5.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4301","4301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385898","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase route capacity in the Sussex area of the South East Route; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4302","4302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385899","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the level of punctuality for passenger rail services in the Sussex area of the South East Route operated by (a) Southern Railways, (b) First Capital Connect, (c) London Overground and (d) First Great Western was in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4303","4303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385900","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish his Department's assessment of the evidence received in favour of the expansion of either Heathrow or Gatwick airport and the effect on job creation in the North.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4340","4340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385901","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the importance of hub connectivity for airports and businesses in the North of England; and what steps his Department is taking to encourage growth in (a) the UK domestic network and (b) from London airports to the North of England.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4339","4339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385902","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the amount of Regional Air Connectivity funding that will be made available in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4400","4400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385903","2015-06-30","Department for Transport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs that are supported in (a) Dundee and (b) the UK by regional air connectivity funding.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4381","4381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385904","2015-07-01","Department for Transport","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to issue a green paper on young drivers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4397","4397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385905","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what benchmark analysis of average household earnings his Department used to determine that £23,000 should be the new level at which the household benefit cap is set.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4255","4255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385906","2015-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will create a cancer care and support allowance for those who have been diagnosed with cancer and are either undergoing or awaiting treatments.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4277","4277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385907","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with a learning disability are currently claiming jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4240","4240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385908","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to tackle delays in carrying out work capability assessments for people with a learning disability.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4241","4241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385909","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his most recent estimate is of the number of people who will be claiming universal credit when it is fully rolled out.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4242","4242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385910","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department plans to publish as a result of the consultation on its draft complaints procedure; and (a) when and (b) where his Department plans to publish that information.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4260","4260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385911","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to implement the new complaints procedure in response to its consultation on the draft complaints procedure.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4262","4262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385912","2015-07-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to ensure that deaf young people aged 16 to 19 are treated appropriately during assessments for personal independence payments.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4237","4237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385913","2015-07-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress he has made in ensuring that the claim process for personal independence payments is accessible to (a) deaf people who do not use a telephone and (b) other deaf people.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4238","4238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385914","2015-07-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects that deaf people will be able to begin a claim for personal independence payments (a) by email and (b) online.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4239","4239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385915","2015-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Child Support Agency cases reviewed as part of the ongoing closure programme have been closed by his Department to date.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4382","4382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385916","2015-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications to the 2012 statutory child maintenance scheme made since January 2015 have been from parents whose previous Child Support Agency (CSA) case was shut down as part of the phased CSA case closure programme.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4385","4385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385917","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Prime Minister's Oral Answer of 24 June 2015, Official Report, columns 885-86 and to the Answer of 22 June 2015 to Question 2955, (a) for what reason his Department changed its policy on publishing statistics on the deaths of disability claimants, (b) when those statistics will be published, (c) how much those statistics will cost to produce, (d) for what reason those statistics could previously only be provided at disproportionate cost, (e) when his Department began collecting those statistics and (f) for what reason it began collecting those statistics.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4401","4401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385918","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of devolving the Work Programme to Metro Mayors and Combined Authorities.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4342","4342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385919","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the effect of changing the household benefit cap on the ability of victims of domestic violence to find affordable accommodation after leaving a refuge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4361","4361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385920","2015-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of removing tax credits on child poverty in Hove.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4350","4350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385921","2015-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of removing tax credits on in-work poverty in Hove.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4351","4351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385930","2015-07-01","HM Treasury","2015-06-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what cross-departmental work on productivity his Department is co-ordinating.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900666","900666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386826","2015-07-01","Cabinet Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure that people without access to technology are not adversely affected by the increased use of IT to deliver public services.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900667","900667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386827","2015-07-01","Cabinet Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to help reduce bureaucracy relating to public procurement for small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900668","900668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386828","2015-07-01","Cabinet Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to broaden the diversity of people considered for public appointments.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900663","900663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386829","2015-07-01","Cabinet Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to assess the handling of personal data by government departments.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900669","900669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386830","2015-07-01","Cabinet Office","2015-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of teenagers who will participate in the National Citizen Service this year.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900665","900665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385337","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on (a) productivity and (b) competitiveness in the UK of (i) skill deficits in young working-age women and (ii) difficulties working mothers have in securing affordable childcare provision to maintain their work.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4000","4000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385338","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish an evaluation of changes in UK natural capital since May 2010 when he publishes his Emergency Budget in July 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4002","4002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385339","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what rules apply to media interviews with (a) service personnel dealing with nuclear weapons and (b) other serving military personnel.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4001","4001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385340","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the compatibility of proposals  for a geological facility for radioactive waste up to 20 kilometres from land with the UK's obligations under the Convention for the Protection of the Marine Environment of the North-East Atlantic.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4105","4105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385341","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with (a) the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority and (b) Radioactive Waste Management Ltd on ensuring that the decision-making process for deciding on a geological disposal facility for radioactive waste is open and transparent.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4101","4101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385342","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of providing compensation to communities sited along railway lines and roads used to carry radioactive waste from existing nuclear facilities to final disposal in a national geological disposal facility.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4102","4102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385343","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in the (a) Welsh Assembly Government and (b) Northern Ireland Executive on participation of the devolved administrations in preparations for receipt of communications from communities putting themselves forward as prospective hosts for a geological disposal facility for radioactive waste activities in England, Wales and Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4103","4103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385344","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what resources her Department allocated to the work of the Independent Review Panel organised by the Geological Society to oversee draft guidance for the National Geological Screening being undertaken by Radioactive Waste Management Ltd; and what payment has been made to each panel member in respect of (a) per diem costs, (b) compensation for work time lost due to participation and (c) travel and subsistence costs to date.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4104","4104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385345","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to control immigration.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4106","4106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385346","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to prioritise research on dementia during this Parliament.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3985","3985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385347","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has for the funding of the UK stem cell donor register and cord blood programme over the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3986","3986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385348","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will launch a consultation on the proposal to ban seals being killed off the coast of the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3984","3984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385349","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for cross-border loss of revenue in Northern Ireland of changes in the level of fuel duty in his preparations for the Budget in July 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3983","3983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385350","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that the work of Innovate UK in supporting business-led innovation benefits all areas of the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3987","3987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385351","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to tackle the overuse of antibiotics in farms; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4183","4183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385352","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to implement the recommendation of the Fifth Report of the Education Select Committee, Life lessons: PHSE and SRE in schools, published on 17 February 2015, on the teaching of personal, social, health and economic education in all primary and secondary schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4146","4146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385353","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to address the effect of the overuse of antibiotics in farms animals.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4177","4177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385354","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average daily out-of-cell time was for prisoners in each prison in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4056","4056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385355","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many out-of-cell hours offenders are provided with at each prison establishment that operates planned restricted regimes.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4057","4057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385356","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how long each prison governor at each prison has been in post.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4058","4058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385357","2015-06-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support high streets.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4219","4219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385358","2015-06-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to protect the green belt; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4220","4220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385359","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who is notified of funding decisions by NHS England's Clinical Priorities Advisory Group before those decisions are published.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4178","4178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385360","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of defendants at (a) magistrates' courts and (b) Crown Courts changed their plea before trial in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4015","4015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385361","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost to the public purse is of preparing a (a) full pre-sentence report and (b) fast delivery report in magistrates' courts, including the time spent by probation staff in court whilst the report is being delivered and considered.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4020","4020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385362","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of the production of pre-sentence reports for courts in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4021","4021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385363","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, (a) how many additional days were added to prisoners' sentences and (b) in what proportion of adjudications days were added in (i) 2000, (ii) 2010 and (iii) the latest year for which information is held; and for what reasons the days were so added in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4016","4016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385364","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of life-sentenced prisoners were (a) recommended or (b) not recommended for transfer to an open prison by their respective parole board in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4022","4022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385365","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders on licence in West Yorkshire have travelled abroad unsupervised in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4019","4019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385366","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the monetary value was of fines (a) imposed, (b) collected, (c) legally cancelled, (d) administratively cancelled and (e) outstanding in (i) England and Wales and (ii) West Yorkshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4023","4023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385367","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offences of a violent nature were committed by women who were (a) under a community order or suspended sentence order and (b) on licence for a previous non-violent offence in the last year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4017","4017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385368","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the rate of utilisation was of each magistrates' court in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4018","4018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385369","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) murders, (b) burglaries, (c) rapes and (d) sex offences against children were committed in the latest year for which information is available; and how many and what proportion of those offences were committed by individuals who were on bail at the time.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4024","4024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385370","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) offences were committed by offenders on bail and (b) offenders committed offences whilst on bail in the latest year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4025","4025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385371","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) offences in West Yorkshire were committed by offenders on bail and (b) offenders in West Yorkshire committed offences whilst on bail during the most recent year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4115","4115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385372","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people who have served an indeterminate sentence for public protection have re-offended after release; and (a) how many and (b) which offences have been committed by such re-offenders in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4116","4116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385373","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the offences and length of time served in prison are of each of the 20 longest serving female prisoners.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4117","4117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385374","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in respect of which prisons he has received recent reports on the religious radicalisation of prisoners.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4113","4113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385375","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) males and (b) females received each sentencing outcome for each type of offence in each police force area in the most recent year for which information is available; and what the average custodial sentence length was for each gender for each offence type in each police force area.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4114","4114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385376","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of a sentence handed down was for each offence in (a) Crown and (b) magistrates' courts for (i) females and (ii) males in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4184","4184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385377","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders had (a) between 15 and 49, (b) between 50 and 99 and (c) 100 or more convictions in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4026","4026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385378","2015-06-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has any discretion in the imposition of the EU-level ban on the use of neonicotinoid pesticides in the UK; what assessment the Department has made of the impact of any use of such pesticides on the UK's bee population since the publication of An assessment of key evidence about neonicotinoids and bees, DEFRA, published in March 2013; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3942","3942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385379","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the government of Ethiopia on the continued detention without trial and possible torture of the British citizen Andargachew Tsege; and what steps the Government plans to take to ensure Mr Tsege's return home.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4006","4006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385380","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to tackle the plutonium stockpile.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4222","4222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385381","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of how long it will take to complete the decommissioning of Sellafield if annual expenditure on that process remains at its current level.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4148","4148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385382","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when her Department plans to make a decision on the reuse of plutonium.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4149","4149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385383","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress has been made on the decision on handling the UK's plutonium stockpile.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4150","4150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385384","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has to ensure that the Royal Mail's universal service obligation continues to be met.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4182","4182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385385","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of Royal Mail's effectiveness in meeting the universal service obligation in Aberdeenshire.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4176","4176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385386","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to include aortic stenosis in future cardiovascular strategies.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3997","3997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385387","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to task NICE with publication of guidelines for heart valve disease.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3998","3998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385388","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to ensure earlier referral of heart valve patients from secondary to tertiary care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3999","3999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385389","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on the continuation, cessation or expansion of the Regional Air Connectivity Fund.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4047","4047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385390","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate the number of jobs (a) created and (b) supported by the Regional Air Connectivity Fund.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4048","4048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385391","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which UK companies' employees gain more in tax credits than they pay in tax and national insurance contributions.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4207","4207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385392","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking in the case of Andargachew Tsege held in Ethiopia.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4041","4041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385393","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to recruit young people with the requisite skills to become NHS doctors and nurses.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4221","4221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385394","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons UK-resident EU citizens will not be allowed to vote in the EU referendum; and how many such people will be affected by that decision.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3952","3952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385395","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2015 to Question 334, what plans her Department has to issue new guidance to local authorities on timeframes for visits to privately fostered children.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3949","3949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385396","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2015 to Question 356, what the (a) purpose and (b) cost was of each contract let to Mott MacDonald since 2012.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3950","3950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385397","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2015 to Question 333, what guidance her Department issues to local authorities on the employment of educational psychologists.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3948","3948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385398","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions his Department has had with (a) NATO, (b) the OECD and (c) the UN on the definition of (i) defence expenditure and (ii) official development expenditure; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3970","3970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385399","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assumptions are being made about the receipts from any sale of Hyde Park Barracks in consideration of the Ministry of Defence's spending review 2015 settlement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3971","3971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385400","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether VAT is payable by the Ministry of Defence on the construction of new barracks.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3959","3959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385401","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the receipts from any sale of Hyde Park Barracks will be retained by the Ministry of Defence.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3960","3960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385402","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the value to the tourist economy of military, ceremonial and pageantry activities in London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3965","3965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385403","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with English Heritage on the possible listing of Hyde Park Barracks; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3964","3964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385404","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions his Department has had with (a) NATO, (b) the OECD and (c) the UN on the definition of (i) defence expenditure and (ii) official development expenditure; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3963","3963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385405","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his plans are for the future of Hyde Park Barracks; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3962","3962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385406","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what changes he intends to make to military law as a result of the decision to ratify the Hague Convention for the Protection of Cultural Property in the Event of Armed Conflict; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3958","3958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385407","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the lease from the Royal Parks for the Hyde Park Barracks site.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3969","3969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385408","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to relocate the Household Cavalry Mounted Regiment to Regent's Park Barracks; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3961","3961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385409","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the value of (a) Hyde Park Barracks and (b) Regent's Park Barracks.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3972","3972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385410","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the size of site needed to accommodate the Household Cavalry Mounted Regiment elsewhere in London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3967","3967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385411","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department paid in stamp duty in each financial year between 2000-01 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3968","3968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385412","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Project Rose outline business case.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3966","3966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385413","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was paid in bonuses to Network Rail executives in each financial year between 2010-11 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3957","3957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385414","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many employees of Network Rail earned more than £142,000 in each financial year between 2010-11 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3955","3955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385415","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve safety and reduce risk to passengers and the public in the Sussex area of the South East Route; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3956","3956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385416","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve asset resilience in the Sussex area of the South East Route; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3973","3973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385417","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding has been allocated to line resilience projects in the Sussex area of the South East Route for each year of Control Period 5.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3974","3974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385418","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will develop a single and clear set of guidelines for micro-businesses who will be required to automatically enrol their employees with a pension scheme for the first time to ensure that they can access the information they require cost-effectively.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3931","3931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385419","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department plans to offer micro-businesses in adapting to new automatic enrolment pension provisions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3932","3932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385420","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received on the potential risk of pensions auto-enrolment packages and products being mis-sold to micro-businesses.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3933","3933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385421","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much of the transport capital infrastructure spending announced in each Budget Statement in each year since 2011 was allocated to each (a) region and (b) constituency of the UK.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4040","4040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385422","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much of the Challenge Fund has been allocated in each region since that fund was announced.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4033","4033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385423","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department has spent on investment on science in Yorkshire in each of the last five years; and what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of that investment in boosting the economy in Yorkshire.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4151","4151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385424","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the relationship between ring-fencing his Department's science budget and the UK's science research capability.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4152","4152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385425","2015-06-29","Attorney General","2015-06-24","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussions he has had with the Director of Public Prosecutions about the performance of the Crown Prosecution Service in prosecuting child sexual abuse cases.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4111","4111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385426","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps are being taken to support self-employed workers in (a) Northamptonshire and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4059","4059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385427","2015-06-29","Cabinet Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) gender of the deceased person, (b) international classification of disease code for the underlying cause of death, (c) time taken to register the death, (d) year of death and (e) year the death was registered was for each death registered in Kettering constituency at least 366 days after the date of death in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013 and (v) 2014; and whether for each such death the deceased person was aged (A) under five, (B) five to 15, (C) 15 to 24, (D) 25 to 34, (E) 35 to 44, (F) 45 to 54, (G) 55 to 64 or (H) over 65 years when they died.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4196","4196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385428","2015-06-29","Cabinet Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths were registered in Kettering constituency at least 366 days after the date of death in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4197","4197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385429","2015-06-29","Cabinet Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths were registered in Kettering constituency at least 183 days after the date of death in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4198","4198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385430","2015-06-29","Cabinet Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths were registered in Kettering constituency in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4199","4199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385431","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the future of the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4086","4086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385432","2015-06-29","Scotland Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the timescale for the rollout of universal credit in Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4180","4180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385433","2015-06-29","Scotland Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the commissioning of analysis on the effect of welfare changes since 2010 on poverty levels in Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4181","4181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385434","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons he has not implemented the recommendation of Sir Robert Francis that the development of safe staffing guidance should be undertaken by NICE rather than NHS England.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3990","3990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385435","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of implementation of safe staffing guidance in the NHS.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3989","3989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385436","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the awarding of costs against claimants on the ability and willingness of people to bring claims for disability discrimination; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3937","3937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385437","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions the Prime Minister has had with his foreign counterparts on reducing greenhouse gas emissions in advance of the 2015 UN Climate Conference in Paris.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4137","4137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385438","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 23 June 2015 to Question 3244, what capabilities and specifications have been decided on for the next generation of RAF maritime reconnaissance aircraft; and which specific defence industrial organisations have made representations to his Department on the supply of aircraft or equipment to fulfil that role.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4190","4190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385439","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will hold meetings with his counterparts in Northern Ireland and Wales to discuss the introduction of BRCA testing for ovarian cancer in those areas.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4166","4166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385440","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects to meet the UK's commitments on the number of the most vulnerable Syrian refugees to be relocated to the UK.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4039","4039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385441","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what target she has for the number of the most vulnerable Syrian refugees to be relocated to the UK in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4038","4038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385442","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which local authorities have expressed an interest in taking refugees under the resettlement programme for the most vulnerable Syrian refugees; and how  many such refugees each local authority has agreed to host.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4037","4037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385443","2015-06-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his statement of 22 June 2015, Official Report, columns 617-9, whether local people will have the final say on planning applications for solar farms.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4206","4206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385444","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the additional tax revenue from savers choosing not to annuitise their retirement savings following the pensions flexibilities introduced on 6 April 2015 in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017, (d) 2018 and (e) 2019.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4211","4211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385445","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the additional tax revenue from savers choosing not to annuitise their retirement savings following the pensions flexibilities introduced on 6 April 2015 in (a) April 2015, (b) May 2015 and (c) June 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4212","4212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385446","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the availability and affordability of professional advice for those wishing to draw down their retirement income.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4209","4209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385447","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to (a) review the effectiveness of the Pension Wise service and (b) publish that review.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4210","4210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385448","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he has made on putting a Union flag on all new and renewed driving licences.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4155","4155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385449","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 June 2015 to Question 126 and the Answer of 24 June 2015 to Question 2877, if he will place in the Library the (a) correspondence and (b) minutes of meetings between 2010 and 2015 between his Department and Public Health England Advisory Committee on malaria prevention in relation to the use of Lariam or Mefloquine and reports of (i) hallucinations, (ii) psychosis and (iii) suicidal thoughts in personnel prescribed those medications.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4194","4194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385450","2015-06-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 June 2015 to Question 126 and the Answer of 24 June 2015 to Question 2877, when he became aware that he had no correspondence between Public Health England and his Department on hallucinations, psychosis or suicidal thoughts in personnel prescribed Mefloquine or Lariam; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4195","4195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385451","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many continence advisors were employed in the NHS in each year since 2005; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4127","4127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385452","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the annual cost of destroyed unused prescribed medication; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4128","4128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385453","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of attendances at A&E because of (a) urinary tract infections, (b) catheter-related infections and (c) stoma care issues in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4129","4129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385454","2015-06-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to increase the number of affordable rented homes.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4208","4208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385455","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 June 2015 to Question 2995, how his Department will support clinical commissioning groups to improve a transformation plan ruled inadequate.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4200","4200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385456","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 June 2015 to Question 2995, how his Department will support clinical commissioning groups to help them fulfil their transformation plans.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4201","4201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385457","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 June 2015 to Question 2995, what plans he has to allocate funding for children and young people's mental health service transformations to those clinical commissioning groups who do not produce a transformation plan.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4202","4202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385458","2015-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 26 March 2015 to Question 225021, what proportion of funds under the 2007-13 European Regional Development Fund which were committed after May 2010 have not yet been drawn down; and whether he expects the full amount to be drawn down before the September 2015 deadline.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4161","4161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385459","2015-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2015 to Question 2126, if he will list each of the beneficiaries under the Regional Growth Fund which did not draw down the full amount in each (a) region and (b) Regional Growth Fund bidding round.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4158","4158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385460","2015-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 22 June 2015 to Question 2810, what non-discretionary fees and payments were paid to each of those firms.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4159","4159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385461","2015-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2015 to Question 1837, when he plans to make a decision on whether the discretionary fee will be paid; what framework he has set for making that decision; and on what consideration it will be based.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4160","4160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385462","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential effects on wage levels in each sector of the economy of the removal of tax credits from EU migrants for their first four years' stay in the UK.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4121","4121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385463","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the number of EU nationals who would not have chosen to migrate to the UK if they had not been entitled to tax credits for the first four years of their stay.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4124","4124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385464","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of EU nationals claim working and child tax credits within a year of arrival in the UK; how many EU nationals resident in the UK have been in the UK for less than four years; and what proportion of those EU nationals claim child or working tax credits.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4118","4118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385465","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of whether the introduction of a mandatory four-year contributory period applied to both UK and EU nationals prior to eligibility for the tax credit element of universal credit would be permissible under EU law.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4119","4119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385466","2015-07-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether there are any barriers or regulations that prevent local authorities from requesting details of a person's tenure on council tax registration forms.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3946","3946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385467","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effects on the implementation of EU law in the UK of removing the words ever closer union from the preamble to the EU Treaties on Article 1 of the Treaty on European Union.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4003","4003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385468","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on how many European Court of Justice cases have cited the words Ever Closer Union from the preamble to the EU Treaties and Article 1 of the Treaty on European Union in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4004","4004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385469","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what effect the 1992 Edinburgh Agreement had on the application of EU treaties in the UK; and whether it is his Department's assumption that the European Court of Justice is obliged to follow the provisions of that Agreement.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4123","4123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385470","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times the procedure provided for in Council Decision 2009/857/EC on the implementation of Article 16(4) of the Treaty on European Union has been invoked in each of the years since that Decision entered force; what the concerns of the member states that invoked the procedure were in each such case; and how those concerns were met in the final decision taken in each such case.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4126","4126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385471","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of EU nationals is eligible for universal credit in those areas in which that benefit is being trialled.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4120","4120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385472","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what forms of local and central government support are available to an EU national working on the minimum wage other than tax credits.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4122","4122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385473","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to designate a marine protected area around Ascension Island.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3991","3991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385474","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to support the Indian government in protecting Asian elephants.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3992","3992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385475","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants there were in each year since 2010; and how many such claimants had Social Fund Loan payments deducted in each such year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4172","4172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385476","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants had Social Fund Loan repayments wrongly deducted from their benefits in each year since 2010; and how many of those deductions were due to (a) prior full loan repayment and (b) non-existence of the loan.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4173","4173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385477","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research her Department has commissioned on horizontal gene transmission between bacteria in the human gut which transfers antibiotic resistance from one organism to another regardless of its strain or of its human or animal origin.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4136","4136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385478","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect that withdrawal from the EU would have on British farming.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4214","4214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385479","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding her Department has allocated to delivery of the Government's 25-year plan to grow, buy and sell more British food.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4217","4217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385480","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her priorities are for reforming the Common Agricultural Policy; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4218","4218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385481","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding her Department plans to allocate to contributing to achieving the Government's target of three million more apprenticeships by expanding apprenticeships in the food, farming and agri-tech sector.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4215","4215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385482","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of how many apprentices work in the food, farming and agri-tech sector.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4216","4216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385483","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on the extend to which the presence of antibiotic resistant organisms in the human gut is the result of horizontal gene transmission from bacteria of farm animal origin, notwithstanding the strains of bacteria concerned.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4135","4135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385484","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether Ministers and officials in her Department have met the Responsible Use of Medicines in Agriculture Alliance.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4157","4157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385485","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what resources he plans to allocate to put in place a marine blue belt around the Overseas Territories to protect marine habitats in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4094","4094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385486","2015-06-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to launch his programme of pocket parks in towns and cities; and what budget he plans to allocate to that programme.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4093","4093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385487","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she expects to complete the network of Marine Conservation Zones.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4089","4089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385488","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to designate a marine blue belt around the Overseas Territories to protect marine habitats.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4095","4095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385489","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Single Inspection Taskforce will be established; and what Departmental resources she will allocate to it in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4090","4090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385490","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to designate the second tranche of Marine Conservation Zones.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4096","4096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385491","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to designate the third tranche of Marine Conservation Zones.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4097","4097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385492","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure that high animal welfare standards are incorporated into international trade agreements; and how her Department plans to measure such standards.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4091","4091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385493","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to (a) protect the Green Belt and (b) maintain national protections for Areas of Outstanding Natural Beauty, National Parks, Sites of Special Scientific Interest and other environmental designations.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4092","4092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385494","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish in full all monitoring data collected in each year of the badger culls in Gloucestershire and Somerset.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4187","4187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385495","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she plans to take to ensure that she receives independent scientific advice on safety, effectiveness and humaneness for each year of the badger cull pilots in Gloucestershire and Somerset.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4188","4188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385496","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she plans to take to ensure that monitoring data collected on the third year of the badger culls in Gloucestershire and Somerset is made available for independent scientific analysis; and what assessment she plans to make of that analysis as part of her decision on whether the culls should be extended to other areas.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4189","4189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385497","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential effect on the spread of antibiotic resistant strains of bacteria of increased use of antibiotics in farm animals; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4068","4068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385498","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on the proportion of antibiotic use in the UK which is accounted for by administration to animals on farms.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4066","4066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385499","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of the use of antibiotics in animals was accounted for by mass medication in the last six years.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4067","4067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385500","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will set a target to reduce farm antibiotic use.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4080","4080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385501","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department has taken to investigate the implications for human health of the appearance of antibiotic resistant strains of MRSA in pig meat.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4081","4081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385502","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take measures to reduce farm antibiotics use.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4082","4082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385503","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of traffic accidents in which the use of a satellite navigation system has been a contributing factor in the last five years.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3975","3975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385504","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Egyptian counterpart on holding elections in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4145","4145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385505","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for mental health patients in St Helens South and Whiston constituency.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4167","4167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385506","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has held with television broadcasters on improving services for people with sensory loss.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4036","4036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385507","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will publish guidelines to encourage improvements in access to digital services for people with sensory loss.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4034","4034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385508","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the quality of access to on demand television content for people with sensory loss.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4035","4035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385509","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the publication, Public Health England Marketing Strategy 2014 to 2017, what discussions he has had with Public Health England on its trial for improving screening uptake; and whether improving cervical screening uptake will form part of that trial.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4053","4053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385510","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the publication, Public Health England Marketing Strategy 2014 to 2017, what discussions he has had with Public Health England on whether its plan to develop marketing campaigns to drive earlier diagnosis based on the Be Clear on Cancer campaign model will include a focus on raising awareness of cervical screening across the UK.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4052","4052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385511","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Foreign Secretary on the potential effect on British companies of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3993","3993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385512","2015-06-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on the housing market of the expiration of permitted development rights in May 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4156","4156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385513","2015-06-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of properties that will not be completed upon the expiry of permitted development rights in May 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4078","4078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385514","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will announce a timetable for the Independent Review into the secondary ticketing market.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4125","4125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385515","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) households, (b) adults and (c) children have been affected by the benefit cap in each local authority area since the nationwide roll-out in Scotland.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4060","4060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385516","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish an impact assessment on the reduction of the benefit cap.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4061","4061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385517","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which bodies his Department consulted on the terms of reference for the review of the employment tribunal fees regime.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4085","4085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385518","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2015 to Question 3171, what steps his Department is taking to reduce accidents on the M56 between junctions 12 and 14.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3947","3947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385519","2015-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to support claimants of benefits find employment in Torbay.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4084","4084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385520","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2015 to Question 1960, what representations his Department has received from (a) other developed countries, (b) UN bodies, (c) EU institutions, (d) international health bodies and (e) international ethics bodies on the Human Fertilisation and Embryology (Mitochondrial Donation) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4186","4186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385521","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2015 to Question 216, whether it is his policy that services provided by the Family Planning Association constitute sufficient social, medical and practical support for women experiencing unplanned pregnancies in the UK; and what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of social, medical and practical support for women experiencing unplanned pregnancies in England and Wales.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4185","4185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385522","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2015 to Question 2148, whether it is his policy that a registered medical practitioner may form a good faith opinion for the purposes of section 1(1)(a) of the Abortion Act 1967 after having signed the statutory form HSA1.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4147","4147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385523","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to require every termination of pregnancy provider routinely to record a patient's NHS number.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4133","4133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385524","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost is to the NHS of an (a) medical and (b) surgical abortion when commissioned for delivery by the British Pregnancy Advisory Service.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4134","4134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385525","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of terminations of pregnancy commissioned for delivery in the private sector had NHS numbers missing from the patient's electronic record in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4132","4132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385526","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures are in place to prevent public funds paid to (a) the British Pregnancy Advisory Service, (b) Marie Stopes International, (c) the Family Planning Association and (d) Brook Charity from being used to support lobbying activities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4130","4130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385527","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is his policy not to record the NHS number for every termination of pregnancy contracted out by the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4131","4131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385528","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the status is of the Syrian refugee Raja Khouja and her husband Mahmoud Alhassan who are due to be deported to Saudi Arabia on 25 June 2015; and what her policy is on the deportation of individuals to countries which use the death penalty.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3988","3988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385529","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the capacity of the Independent Police Complaints Commission (IPCC) to hold the police to account pursuant to its obligations under Section 1.5 of the IPCC Home Office Framework Agreement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4010","4010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385530","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of whether the Independent Police Complaints Commission (IPCC) is capable of fulfilling the role set out for it in Section 1.7 of the IPCC Home Office Framework Agreement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4011","4011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385531","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of whether the Independent Police Complaints Commission has adequate resources to fulfil its statutory duty on investigating serious and sensitive cases.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4012","4012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385532","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate she has made of the number of serious and sensitive cases investigated by the Independent Police Complaints Commission in the last five years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4013","4013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385533","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to improve access to digital services for people with sensory loss.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3954","3954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385534","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to improve the provision of access services for on-demand content.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3953","3953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385535","2015-06-29","Women and Equalities","2015-06-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when and with whom she consulted on the details of regulations to be introduced under the Small Business, Enterprise and Employment Act 2015 for the purpose of requiring the publication of information showing whether there are differences in the pay of males and females.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4031","4031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385536","2015-06-29","Women and Equalities","2015-06-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to make regulations under section 78 of the Equality Act 2010 for the purpose of requiring the publication of information showing whether there are differences in the pay of males and females.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4029","4029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385537","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2015 to Question 1083, how much schools spent on recruiting teachers in (a) Sheffield and (b) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3936","3936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385538","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2015 to Question 1083, how much the Training and Development Agency spent on recruitment in each year from 2010 until it was disbanded in April 2012.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4144","4144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385539","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the number of renewable heat installations installed in (a) Sheffield and (b) the UK as a result of the Renewable Heat Incentive.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4028","4028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385540","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the number of renewable heat installations installed as a result of the (a) domestic and (b) non-domestic Renewable Heat Incentive since those schemes' inception.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4027","4027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385541","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the guidance given to jobcentre staff in pilot jobcentres on the Claimant Commitment and the responsibility of individuals to increase their earnings.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4030","4030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385542","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the claimant would be if income under (a) disability living allowance and (b) personal independence payments was subject to taxation.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4014","4014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385543","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has received from charities on the protection and welfare of pet dogs.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4174","4174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385544","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to protect the welfare of pet dogs.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4143","4143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385545","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England waited for more than a year for NHS treatment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3981","3981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385546","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to reduce childhood obesity in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3982","3982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385547","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS walk-in centres there were in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3940","3940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385548","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of appeals to the Tribunals Service from appellants in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England relating to (i) personal independence payments, (ii) employment and support allowance, (iii) income support, (vi) jobseeker's allowance and (v) tax credits were successful in (A) each quarter in 2014 and (B) the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4072","4072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385549","2015-06-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appellants in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England are waiting for the Tribunals Service to list their first-tier tribunal social security and child support appeal in respect of employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3941","3941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385550","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many illegal immigrants have been removed from Northern Ireland in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4110","4110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385551","2015-06-29","Northern Ireland Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, on how many occasions since its formation after the publication of the Hallett Report into the administrative scheme for On the Runs on 17 July 2014 has her Department's implementation team met; and who attended each such meeting.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4108","4108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385552","2015-06-29","Northern Ireland Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of appeals she has received from retired police officers on decisions by the Firearms Branch of the Police Service of Northern Ireland to withdraw their personal protection weapons were successful in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4109","4109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385553","2015-06-29","Northern Ireland Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent progress has been made on implementation of the recommendations of the Hallett Report into the administrative scheme for On the Runs published on 17 July 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4107","4107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385554","2015-06-29","Cabinet Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to link National Insurance numbering systems with voter registration to improve registration levels.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4204","4204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385555","2015-06-29","Cabinet Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent progress has been made on the next boundary review of parliamentary constituencies.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4065","4065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385556","2015-06-29","Women and Equalities","2015-06-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when the UK last nominated a member of the expert committee of the Convention on the Elimination of All Forms of Discrimination against Women; and for what reason she has not made a nomination in relation to forthcoming vacancies.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3995","3995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385557","2015-06-29","Department for Transport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on the electrification of the Midland Mainline; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4179","4179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385558","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Ethiopian counterpart on the detention of Andargachew Tsege.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4077","4077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385559","2015-06-29","Home Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many serving police officers there were in Torfaen constituency on (a) 6 May 2010 and (b) 7 May 2015.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4079","4079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385560","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to respond to the Work and Pensions Select Committee report, Benefit sanctions policy beyond the Oakley Review, HC 814, published on 24 March 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3938","3938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385561","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made in supporting local authorities to map and identify older residents at particular risk of loneliness.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4175","4175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385562","2015-06-29","Department for Education","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on inclusion of education policy and oversight in the Northern Powerhouse Initiative.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4032","4032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385563","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to tackle Hajj and Umrah tour and travel operators who break UK law and exploit people seeking to undertake a religious pilgrimage.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4203","4203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385564","2015-06-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to ensure that law enforcement and other agencies have the necessary expertise to deal with businesses who exploit people booking Hajj and Umrah tours.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4205","4205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385565","2015-07-01","Department for Transport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to respond to the Parliamentary Advisory Council for Transport Safety constituency data on road traffic accidents, published in March 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4168","4168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385566","2015-06-29","HM Treasury","2015-06-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will attend the Financing for Development Summit in July 2015 in Addis Ababa.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3939","3939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385567","2015-06-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will maintain the current restrictions on the use of neonicotinoid pesticides.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4153","4153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385568","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of the symptoms of ovarian cancer.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4154","4154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385569","2015-06-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2015 to Question 2685, if he will make it his policy to respond to Parliamentary Questions seeking benefits statistics which are held by his Department in Stat-Xplore by publishing extractions of the relevant data in those Answers.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3935","3935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385570","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the article written for the Huffington Post blog on 30 May 2015 by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Sport, Tourism and Heritage, if he will publish the letters she sent to her EU counterparts on FIFA.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4098","4098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385571","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to introduce a Major Events Bill in this Parliament.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4099","4099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385572","2015-06-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the terms of reference of the Earn or Learn implementation taskforce, how many of the two million new jobs and three million new apprenticeships he plans will be created in the cultural and creative sector.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4100","4100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385573","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of her plans to end the Renewable Obligation for onshore wind in 2016 on (a) the date by which onshore wind is expected to reach grid parity and (b) the ability of communities to generate their own power from onshore wind; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4062","4062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385574","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information her Department holds on the number of onshore windfarms (a) in planning and (b) in operation that are wholly or partly community-owned in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4063","4063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385575","2015-06-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to her Department's publication entitled Community Energy Strategy, published on 27 January 2014, what assessment she has made of the (a) financial and (b) non-financial benefits to local communities from (i) onshore wind, (ii) solar photovoltaic and (iii) other renewable generation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4064","4064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385576","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the planned visit of President Abdel Fatah ai-Sisi to the UK will take place; whether the Prime Minister plans to discuss the supply of military, security and police equipment to Egypt; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4073","4073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385577","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what independent evaluation his Department has commissioned on the effect of the Autism Awareness programme.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4049","4049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385578","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the funding for his Department's Autism Awareness programme has been spent; and what advertising programmes have been funded for that programme.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4050","4050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385579","2015-06-29","Department of Health","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the reach and scope of the Autism Awareness programme during the 2015-16 parliamentary session.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4051","4051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385580","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many of the recommendations of the report published in March 2012 and funded by his Department on Palestinian children in military custody have been carried out.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4142","4142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385581","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the efforts of his French counterpart to encourage new peace talks between Israel and Palestine.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4138","4138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385582","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on support he is giving to EU proposals to promote sea access to Gaza.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4042","4042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385583","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the demolition of the Arab-Israeli village of Um Al Huran.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4043","4043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385584","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Israeli counterparts on the prosecution of Israeli settlers for acts of violence against Palestinians.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4044","4044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385585","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether UK-supplied weaponry and components were used by Israel in its campaign against Gaza in 2014.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4045","4045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385586","2015-06-29","Department for International Development","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the humanitarian effect on Palestinians in the West Bank of restrictions on their movement.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4192","4192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385587","2015-06-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the humanitarian effect of the demolition of the villages of Umm Al Hiran and Atir in Israel.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4191","4191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385588","2015-06-29","Department for International Development","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the potential humanitarian effect of ending restrictions on exports out of Gaza; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4055","4055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385589","2015-06-29","Department for International Development","2015-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the potential humanitarian effect of ending restrictions on trade between Gaza and the West Bank.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 4054","4054"
